<text id="ST47">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:53:52</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-22</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0125</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Studies, academic research, design, advertising, TV, food, weekend activities, jobs, sport, advice about writing a research project</topics>
		<activity>Friends having pizza while chatting and proofreading a research project.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising,  requesting</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T07</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0125">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cardiff</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Welsh</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>wales</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>wales</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>wales</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Student / design freelancer</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Welsh -- Advanced; Finnish -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">so what did your tutor say?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0125">I'm just going to <trunc>fi</trunc> this is the last page</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="4" who="S0125"><unclear/> easier really</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">can I pop this on the floor just</u>
<u n="6" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah of course <pause dur="short"/> yep help yourself <pause dur="short"/> so my tutor sent me some feedback about um the draft</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh huh</u>
<u n="8" who="S0125">um and</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">oh is that what your <trunc>stat</trunc> status update was?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0125">errr</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">something about thanks for telling me with like twenty-four hours notice that <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="12" who="S0125" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0125">oh I don't know about that <pause dur="short"/> um yeah so my tutor sent me err feedback on the draft and it's really helpful actually <pause dur="short"/> because I sent it to the one who is not my course director and she is normally quite um restrictive with her comments <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't seem to like to help um people um out that much <pause dur="short"/> but this guy this tutor has given me some really constructive um feedback</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018"></u>
<u n="16" who="S0125">um which has enabled me to um make my final changes to the document and <trunc>o</trunc> go over the word count unfortunately quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> but um quite significantly <pause dur="short"/> but um hopefully with your help I can get it down</u>
<u n="17" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0125">um</u>
<u n="20" who="S0018" trans="overlap">what kind of feedback did he give you was it</u>
<u n="21" who="S0125">errm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0018">what to add or what to take out or</u>
<u n="23" who="S0125" trans="overlap">he he suggests I actually change the title of the document <pause dur="short"/> which  I don't  I don't agree with <pause dur="short"/> but anyway that's fine</u>
<u n="24" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="25" who="S0125">he asks me to define whether there's a formal strategy document for a particular question that I'm trying to answer <pause dur="short"/> erm and he my question to him was I'm concerned that it's not critical enough</u>
<u n="26" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0125">in terms of a review <pause dur="short"/> erm but erm he says that his observation is yes you can make it more critical by linking the ideas that I have together <pause dur="short"/> erm and being err creating a stronger argument either by linking them through the report or raising clear questions at the end</u>
<u n="28" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> do they impose the the title on you?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0125">no no it's my title</u>
<u n="30" who="S0018">oh right and what have you chosen?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0125">um the title of the report is um How do design and cultural values within Nordic design led businesses influence digital and visual communications?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="33" who="S0125">um so I'm looking at a few different things there but I'm looking at communications how they are influenced by design and cultural values</u>
<u n="34" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0125">within a business which happens to be in the Nordic region which happens to be design led</u>
<u n="36" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0125">um and er using the case study of my time spent working at the placement in the in <unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh okay so it's not just a report on what you learnt and stuff <pause dur="short"/> it's actually putting it into</u>
<u n="39" who="S0125"><trunc>Its</trunc></u>
<u n="40" who="S0018">an academic <trunc>cont</trunc> well a</u>
<u n="41" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0018">practical context</u>
<u n="43" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah it's about um</u>
<u n="44" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><unclear/> critically analysing it</u>
<u n="45" who="S0125" trans="overlap">it's I've I've proposed the piece of work myself so  it's not  it's not in answer to a explicit brief <pause dur="short"/> it's um it's of my own investigation and proposal <pause dur="short"/> so that's what I'm trying to answer</u>
<u n="46" who="S0018">and what did he suggest that you should change the title to?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0125">he suggested um how does <unclear/> the case study  this this  this business <pause dur="short"/> how does <unclear/> erm open brackets a design led Nordic business close brackets use cultural and design values to direct the communications strategy <pause dur="short"/> which I think I don't like because it's moving away slightly from from my original</u>
<u n="48" who="S0018">it is cos yours</u>
<u n="49" who="S0125">proposal</u>
<u n="50" who="S0018">yours isn't just about the design strategy it's about the digital and visual communications</u>
<u n="51" who="S0125">yes yes</u>
<u n="52" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0125">so  I'm not  I'm not obliged to change it that's fine</u>
<u n="54" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0125">and I can ignore it if I choose to <pause dur="short"/> but I think I'm fine with it <pause dur="short"/> I'm not going to start changing the title of a document at the last minute just because I've got one piece of advice telling me to</u>
<u n="56" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0125">when in the whole process of this project which is about six weeks now so far nobody has asked me to change the title and this tutor has seen this document this proposal all the way through the <trunc>pro</trunc> project <pause dur="short"/> so why at the last minute tell me to change it I'm not quite sure</u>
<u n="58" who="S0018">did did he say that it that the title best that this title best suited the content? Because if you changed the title you would imagine that you'd have to rejuggle the content <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0125" trans="overlap">his his first observation is the title needs to be reviewed to make it more concise without really changing the meaning or scope of the research</u>
<u n="60" who="S0018">oh okay so it's not semantics</u>
<u n="61" who="S0125" trans="overlap">conciseness</u>
<u n="62" who="S0018">it's just making the title shorter but the title that he's suggested is actually changing the focus isn't it?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0125">to me it felt like that <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> so that's why I'm ignoring it</u>
<u n="64" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="65" who="S0125">yep</u>
<u n="66" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> good idea</u>
<u n="67" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0018">is there do you want to try and make the title a bit more concise?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0125">no I'm fine with it <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>d</trunc> I'm not bothered <pause dur="short"/> what I'm more bothered about is the conciseness  to the  to the content</u>
<u n="70" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="71" who="S0125">I think that's the more critical</u>
<u n="72" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0125">nature <pause dur="short"/> because it's a a three thousand word report it has to be really concise</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yes that's sometimes the most difficult thing isn't it</u>
<u n="75" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0018">keeping within the word limit <pause dur="short"/> okay so what when I proofread it what kind of things do you want me to focus on</u>
<u n="77" who="S0125" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018">in particular</u>
<u n="79" who="S0125">erm like I said before um any instances of repetition <pause dur="short"/> um any um obvious um confusing arguments <pause dur="short"/> erm er anywhere you see that it's not concise <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah  have you got  have you got somewhere I can</u>
<u n="81" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah of course</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018">can write down</u>
<u n="83" who="S0125">here you go <pause dur="short"/> hold on</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">ooh you've got post its <pause dur="short"/> oh look at <trunc>th</trunc> Ooh look at these post its</u>
<u n="85" who="S0125" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">that's amazing</u>
<u n="87" who="S0125" trans="overlap">that's my selection</u>
<u n="88" who="S0018">where did you get that from?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0125">W H Smith's</u>
<u n="90" who="S0018">beautiful <pause dur="short"/> ooh I like it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Okay so sorry repeat conciseness</u>
<u n="91" who="S0125" trans="overlap">conciseness any repetition</u>
<u n="92" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="93" who="S0125">um and erm confusing argument</u>
<u n="94" who="S0018" trans="overlap">confusing argument</u>
<u n="95" who="S0125">this is actually <trunc>th</trunc> the diary that I kept when I was there</u>
<u n="96" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="97" who="S0125"><unclear/> reflective diary didn't go that well</u>
<u n="98" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0125">because normally on my reflective diaries I try to leave one page for the day's observation and leave the next page free for returning to that observation <pause dur="short"/> but as you can see on that one it's blank</u>
<u n="100" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0125">so I haven't really reflected on that day</u>
<u n="102" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0125">erm yes <pause dur="short"/> but anyway <trunc>i</trunc> it was a useful tool none the less</u>
<u n="104" who="S0018">is that what your case studies based on notes <pause dur="short"/> observation notes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0125" trans="overlap">erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> the methodology is um er a mixture of traditional case study done through erm a couple of interviews erm er observation <pause dur="short"/> erm it's all qualitative <pause dur="short"/> erm and er then I've added into the mix a little bit of more erm which <trunc>I</trunc> I've used the word holistic</u>
<u n="106" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0125">to describe um my approach <pause dur="short"/> because I wanted to do it ethnographically <pause dur="short"/> however the timescale was too short to do it <pause dur="short"/> it was a four week</u>
<u n="108" who="S0125">what would that mean then?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">ethnographic erm is generally widely erm understood as being when a researcher goes into a community or group of people and becomes a native to that group</u>
<u n="110" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0125">erm and</u>
<u n="112" who="S0018" trans="overlap">but you wanted to do <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="113" who="S0125">and  behaves as  behaves as one of them lives with them eats with them works with them <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> but erm er and I wanted  to do that  to do that visually by um taking photographic and video evidence of er erm of of my time in that group <pause dur="short"/> but um I did do this <pause dur="short"/> I did take photographic evidence and I've used quite a bit of it in the report</u>
<u n="114" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0125">it's quite a visual report but um er I don't know erm <trunc>the</trunc> there was some conflict and er it was slightly contentious um argument in er with my um not argument discussion with my um course tutor about using that particular <trunc>meth</trunc> methodology <pause dur="short"/> so I've changed it to case study through um observation</u>
<u n="116" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0125">interview and <trunc>particip</trunc> participatory um observation</u>
<u n="118" who="S0018" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="119" who="S0125">because um I was one of them <pause dur="short"/> I was working for them <pause dur="short"/> rather than a pure um silent observer</u>
<u n="120" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="121" who="S0125">erm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0018">cool <pause dur="short"/> okay so erm well shall I get down to reading it and then we'll have a brainstorm session</u>
<u n="123" who="S0125" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> If you like <pause dur="short"/> shall I give you a highlighter pen? Would that help?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018">yep probably</u>
<u n="125" who="S0125">erm <pause dur="short"/> it hasn't printed out the um er annotations  to the  to the images <pause dur="short"/> but that's fine cos I'll go through that and sort that</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="127" who="S0125">erm there you go</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="129" who="S0125">um what else? <unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You're welcome <pause dur="short"/> what you gonna do when <trunc>y</trunc> while I'm doing this?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0125">erm just going to work that bit out</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll put my head down and start reading then <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="133" who="S0125">so what did you think about reading that work?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">yeah I thought what what do you mean if it was easy to read or if it answers the question or</u>
<u n="135" who="S0125" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> I mean no um what what did you actually think of the subject <unclear/> things like that</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">really interesting</u>
<u n="137" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah I thought it was <pause dur="short"/> cos it kind of it does it it goes into stuff that you don't really think about  when you  when you think about a <trunc>comp</trunc> when you haven't studied stuff like this and you see a company and how they're communicating to the audience</u>
<u n="139" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">you're the audience but you don't really realise that there is a strategy behind the communication</u>
<u n="141" who="S0125">yeah I think sometimes it's um intrinsic</u>
<u n="142" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0125">or um er sometimes recognised but <trunc>bas</trunc> I think um er what's interesting for me is the comparisons you can draw between this which is talking about communication strategies and um strategies in design management <pause dur="short"/> because um when people talk about design in erm they <trunc>of</trunc> um famous designers like um oh who's the guy that um er German designer that's really famous for designing really simple things? Braun? You know the manufacturer</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0125">braun Braun <pause dur="short"/> um talks about how design should be um effortless you don't even notice it's there</u>
<u n="146" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0125">and um so when you realise that there's a strategy behind something for me it's like the um comparison that I'm drawing is the same as when a designer talks about a <trunc>beau</trunc> a really well functioning um exquisite piece of design that you don't even realise it's been designed and it's designed to function in a certain way <pause dur="short"/> it's the same thing</u>
<u n="148" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm yeah it's just there <pause dur="short"/> it works <pause dur="short"/> you just don't realise that it's had a lot of thinking put into it <pause dur="short"/> in a way it's like Mad Men <pause dur="short"/> you know when you see behind the scenes of what goes into an advertising campaign</u>
<u n="149" who="S0125" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0018">it's like you know they <trunc>d</trunc> they think about every single little visual bit of communication</u>
<u n="151" who="S0125" trans="overlap">have you read any of the blog that's on The Guardian website about Mad Men?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">er no</u>
<u n="153" who="S0125">you should read it because if you're a fan of it it every episode gets um um dissected</u>
<u n="154" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0125">through the blog and erm you can read about the nuances and the references that you probably didn't realise why they were there</u>
<u n="156" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="157" who="S0125">um that signify things to do with um a political um occasion or a historical event</u>
<u n="158" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0125">like I thin kin the last episode he <trunc>talk</trunc> he talked about a murder or a murderer in Texas that's where um a famous murderer and he like corrected the pronunciation or <trunc>th</trunc> the um one character er <trunc>D</trunc> Don Draper corrected who's the kind of weasly um character</u>
<u n="160" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh yeah um</u>
<u n="161" who="S0125">the really annoying one</u>
<u n="162" who="S0018" trans="overlap">Pete Campbell</u>
<u n="163" who="S0125">Pete Campbell <pause dur="short"/> he corrected him because he used the wrong umm name to describe this murderer and so it puts it into the context of the history that's happening at the time</u>
<u n="164" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0125">and that's why you know it sort of adds <pause dur="short"/> but the blog articles are really interesting to read because he explains more about the script</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0125">the scriptwriting and the the production the production values and things like that <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018">yeah that's really interesting</u>
<u n="169" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018">no I got into did you watch Lost?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0125">no only the first series really</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018" trans="overlap">really <pause dur="short"/> no I got really into Lost and I spent more time after watching it checking out the different theories of each different episode and um online</u>
<u n="173" who="S0125" trans="overlap">oh did you?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0125">so people used to write on forums</u>
<u n="176" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0125">or comment on blogs and things about it?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it was all dissecting cos there was a lot of cross referencing <pause dur="short"/> I really liked it because it didn't explicitly make everything very obvious</u>
<u n="179" who="S0125" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018">it it relied</u>
<u n="181" who="S0125" trans="overlap">no which is a criticism of American um drama or any kind of TV that comes out of America that it's dumbed down</u>
<u n="182" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> but it yeah I liked the fact that it assumed that its viewer was intelligent and kind of dangled little bits in front of you</u>
<u n="183" who="S0125" trans="overlap">titbits</u>
<u n="184" who="S0018">to see if you could make the connections</u>
<u n="185" who="S0125" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0018">and so it was it's like there was a lot of cross referencing because they were jumping backwards and forwards in time a lot as well</u>
<u n="187" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0018">you kind of clicked on relationships between <trunc>ce</trunc> different people</u>
<u n="189" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0018">that didn't really matter to the er you know the momentum of the plot <pause dur="short"/> but you think oh wow of course cos he knew her from when he met her mother on a plane</u>
<u n="191" who="S0125" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0018">going to blah blah blah and so they are oh he does know her <pause dur="short"/> it's not important to how the plot is</u>
<u n="193" who="S0125">no but</u>
<u n="194" who="S0018">being moved along but like yeah the total geek squad picking up on little things that</u>
<u n="195" who="S0125">but isn't it kind of like a common thread that draws all these um script writers together is their nerdiness sometimes isn't it</u>
<u n="196" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0125">they're often accused of being nerds</u>
<u n="198" who="S0018">probably</u>
<u n="199" who="S0125">and kind of obsessional about things and like <trunc>tha</trunc> that um film director Kevin Smith he's like this <pause dur="short"/> he he's a real sort of geek but produces some great films <pause dur="short"/> like like um Dogma</u>
<u n="200" who="S0018">uh huh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0125">and um oh Chasing Amy</u>
<u n="202" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0125">remember that film?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0125">kind of cult status films</u>
<u n="206" who="S0018">with Ben Affleck and</u>
<u n="207" who="S0125" trans="overlap">hmm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0018">yeah that kind of crowd</u>
<u n="209" who="S0125">yeah Matt Damon <pause dur="short"/> ooh pizza</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018" trans="overlap">pizza</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="211" who="S0018">so in your opinion would you say Mad Men is the most enjoyable American series of all time or what would be?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0125">no</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018">which what would you say is then?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0125">better? Sex and the City</u>
<u n="215" who="S0018">do you think so?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0125">longer running <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">but in terms of your enjoyment of it</u>
<u n="220" who="S0125">sex and the City <pause dur="short"/> more enjoyable</u>
<u n="221" who="S0018">that's really funny cos I find Sex and the City quite entertaining but I don't see it as being yes that's like Oscar Oscar quality <pause dur="short"/> whereas things like Mad Men and for me Lost were</u>
<u n="222" who="S0125">hmm well they did win lots of awards didn't they</u>
<u n="223" who="S0018">and Friends of course <pause dur="short"/> friends was brilliant</u>
<u n="224" who="S0125">hmm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0018" trans="overlap">although it's so dated now <pause dur="short"/> I was watching a couple of episodes</u>
<u n="226" who="S0125" trans="overlap">I <trunc>n</trunc> I mean I watched Friends but I was never like a Friends freak <pause dur="short"/> I didn't like really love it <pause dur="short"/> did you use to watch it a lot?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yep and then rewatch it <pause dur="short"/> when I lived in Barcelona we did a month of Friends DVDs <pause dur="short"/> we watched all of the ten series in about a month <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0125">oh my god</u>
<u n="229" who="S0018">in winter after work just getting through about six episodes a night</u>
<u n="230" who="S0125">is Spanish TV that bad?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yep Spanish TV you probably end up for having two hours of TV you end up watching one hour of adverts so it is</u>
<u n="232" who="S0125">horrendous</u>
<u n="233" who="S0018">did you watch um you being an expert in Nordic things did you watch The Killing</u>
<u n="234" who="S0125">mm yeah I loved that <pause dur="short"/> yeah did you watch it?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">yeah I rate it too</u>
<u n="236" who="S0125">I think it was great <pause dur="short"/> then the second series as well was great as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0125"><unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0018">I thought it was but the second series I didn't think was um I think sometimes they were just injecting twists and turns into the plot that didn't really need to be there</u>
<u n="240" who="S0125">hmm <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="241" who="S0018" trans="overlap">it felt maybe a bit contrived at times</u>
<u n="242" who="S0125">oh okay well I liked both</u>
<u n="243" who="S0018">but</u>
<u n="244" who="S0125" trans="overlap">I thought the acting was brilliant</u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">extremely entertaining <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0125">I was like waiting every Saturday <pause dur="short"/> oh there's a ne one started as well on BBC4 called The Bridge</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've heard of that <pause dur="short"/> is that more political though?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0125">no I think that's a thriller <pause dur="short"/> again</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">has it started already or</u>
<u n="250" who="S0125">it started last night</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">what channel?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0125">four <pause dur="short"/> bBC4</u>
<u n="253" who="S0018">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> and what about UK series? I don't think we do them as well do we</u>
<u n="254" who="S0125">hmm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0018">I think we do comedy and documentaries really well but</u>
<u n="256" who="S0125">yeah but</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">series</u>
<u n="258" who="S0125">like Silent Witness has like</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0125">been going for God knows how many years <pause dur="short"/> loads</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018">true</u>
<u n="262" who="S0125">it gets sold all over the World <pause dur="short"/> can watch it in Finland</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is each episode quite self contained?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018" trans="overlap">or is that does that have plot lines that run over?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0125">sort of <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> the characters are obviously the main characters remain the same but it's like it comes in two parts <pause dur="short"/> every week</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018" trans="overlap">hmm that's right <pause dur="short"/> that annoys me as well</u>
<u n="268" who="S0125">why?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Because I I prefer things to either be self contained in one episode or ongoing over a series</u>
<u n="270" who="S0125">why?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">I don't know  I don't know <pause dur="short"/> cos if <trunc>i</trunc> if it's going to be self contained it's just better to get it all over and done in one sitting</u>
<u n="272" who="S0125">are you impatient?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0125">I love Homeland though</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0125">incredible <pause dur="short"/> like everyone's going mad for it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm the guy who is the other you know the one that Brodie thought he killed</u>
<u n="278" who="S0125">mm yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0018">he's</u>
<u n="280" who="S0125">Morgan</u>
<u n="281" who="S0018">yeah he's from Birmingham</u>
<u n="282" who="S0125">oh right</u>
<u n="283" who="S0018">and he went to <anon type="place"/> which is where I did um some of my training</u>
<u n="284" who="S0125" trans="overlap">no way</u>
<u n="285" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he was doing a workshop a drama workshop with students from the school and er it was on Midlands Today</u>
<u n="286" who="S0125">mm mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0125">I think it was a good idea to get the pepperoni on this</u>
<u n="289" who="S0018">mm it's gorgeous isn't it</u>
<u n="290" who="S0125">yeah <pause dur="short"/> very nice <pause dur="short"/> I had a pizza at four o'clock in the morning <pause dur="short"/> no a curry at three o'clock this morning</u>
<u n="291" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">so what did you get up to last night</u>
<u n="295" who="S0125">we went to um we went to <anon type="place"/> and then we went into town <pause dur="short"/> into the island bar and <unclear/> had some cocktails had a bit of a dance</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">I don't know those places really <pause dur="short"/> oh is that the place</u>
<u n="297" who="S0125" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">is that the place we tried to get into on your birthday? Oh on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday <pause dur="short"/> after <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0125">no</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0125">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">it's not by the mailbox</u>
<u n="303" who="S0125">it's near there but it's on the <trunc>othe</trunc> it's by the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0125">do you know?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">erm I don't know where the <anon type="place"/> is but when we came out of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0125">the big road the like dual carriageway by the mailbox</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm underneath</u>
<u n="309" who="S0125">on the other side</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0125">A bit further down</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018">mm I think we tried to go there</u>
<u n="313" who="S0125">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">but it was packed full of er eighteen year olds</u>
<u n="315" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018">so we didn't go</u>
<u n="317" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> who else went?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0125">last night? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then a girl called Sophie who was my boss at Jigsaw</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0125">mm mm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018">did um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s Dad have her last night?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018">ah that's good <pause dur="short"/> that's nice <pause dur="short"/> how is Katie? What what's she up to? What's um the business how is the business going?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0125">alright I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">has her website gone live?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0125">no not yet <pause dur="short"/> she's um struggling to find time to work on it cos childcare</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> she has got a lot on her plate <pause dur="short"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> going to nursery two days a week or three?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0125">I think two</u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0018">yeah last time I saw her I think she said she was quite stressed because on the Thursdays and Fridays that she gets to work on the business you know she gets all these phone calls and text messages and at the same time she's <trunc>h</trunc> you know she's having <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> round to to pardon me to put up some shelves in her house</u>
<u n="333" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018">and she was trying to multitask everything that was going on in her life</u>
<u n="335" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018">she's she was like getting chest pains and stuff from it and getting so stressed</u>
<u n="337" who="S0125">hmm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0018">what's this sauce like is it oh <unclear/> garlicy</u>
<u n="339" who="S0125">it's quite nice</u>
<u n="340" who="S0018">it's alright <pause dur="short"/> it's not worth eating the crusts for though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0125">you don't eat crusts?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">mm if I'm super hungry yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">it depends on what the crusts or  what the  what the base of the pizza's like as well <pause dur="short"/> if it's morish yes if it's just a base then no</u>
<u n="345" who="S0125">mm this is a good combination of flavours though isn't it</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0125"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I think I'll get this done</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">what time's it got to be handed in?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0125">midday</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">well you can work on it tomorrow morning then as well</u>
<u n="351" who="S0125">I don't really like working in it in the mornings</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018" trans="overlap">hm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0125">cos no <unclear/> make me happy that it's done</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0125">but it depends how late it goes tonight I suppose</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">but then do you work better at night?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0125">I don't</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">really? When do you work better?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0125">in the mornings <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0018">well it would stand to reason maybe you did a couple more hours tonight have a good night's sleep and got up early and did it then</u>
<u n="361" who="S0125">yeah you're probably right <pause dur="short"/> I have to get it to the printers though as well</u>
<u n="362" who="S0018">how come?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0125">Cos it's got to be printed</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">can you not just print it out here?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0125">I could but I like to get them bound</u>
<u n="366" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0125">and these here these are all like my previous ones</u>
<u n="368" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh good</u>
<u n="369" who="S0125">I've been like keeping a copy of each</u>
<u n="370" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0125">everything I've handed in I've kept I've had a copy done so I'm building up like a bit of an archive of work really</u>
<u n="372" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0125">because <pause dur="short"/> because really you hand in this work you spend a great deal of your time studying but then what have you got to show for it? Cos actually the work is</u>
<u n="374" who="S0018" trans="overlap">knowledge</u>
<u n="375" who="S0125">yes but</u>
<u n="376" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0125">it's good to have these points of reference to go back to isn't it</u>
<u n="378" who="S0018">mm yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0125">erm and learn from</u>
<u n="380" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yep definitely</u>
<u n="381" who="S0125">or reflect upon maybe <pause dur="short"/> so when you get  the feedback back  the feedback back</u>
<u n="382" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0125">from your course tutor you can look over what they've said in relation to the piece of work with the actual piece of work in front of you and make more sense of it</u>
<u n="384" who="S0018">true <pause dur="short"/> where will you get it printed?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0125">in town <pause dur="short"/> mailboxes? It's um it's on Colmer Road</u>
<u n="386" who="S0018">is it expensive to <trunc>b</trunc> bind it and</u>
<u n="387" who="S0125">it can be <pause dur="short"/> it's normally about twenty pounds</u>
<u n="388" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0125">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0125">yeah but I I just I feel like it's worth it because this course it it means a lot to me</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and for the durability if you're going to keep on referring to it <pause dur="short"/> hm <pause dur="short"/> and do you think that once you finish the course and you're out there back again doing the business side of it that you will that there'll be a lot of things that you think oh yes I remember reading something about that what did it <pause dur="short"/> do you think it will be you'll come back and refer to things</u>
<u n="393" who="S0125">hmm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0018">things like that or</u>
<u n="395" who="S0125">I think so <pause dur="short"/> I think also it's about expanding my knowledge like you say and having more references to call upon when you want to try and justify</u>
<u n="396" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0125">a belief that you have in in a business context <pause dur="short"/> it's always a stronger argument if you can back it up with some evidence</u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0125">so this is all evidence gathering in a way</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">Will you do that to the client or  in your own  in your own interests</u>
<u n="401" who="S0125">in my own way of course it will be different because it won't be in an academic context and often it's about smaller pieces of information that you can get across clearly and concisely and easily</u>
<u n="402" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0125">that anybody can understand <pause dur="short"/> but if I have the academic understanding I can transpose it translate it</u>
<u n="404" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0125">into whichever context it needs to be in</u>
<u n="406" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0125">so I think that's good <pause dur="short"/> and it makes me feel cleverer</u>
<u n="408" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Cleverer <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0018">it gives you more perception more</u>
<u n="411" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0018">better grammar <pause dur="short"/> not <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0125">mm more clever</u>
<u n="414" who="S0018">yeah I found that after doing um the diploma</u>
<u n="415" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0018">in teaching that er I actually felt it kind of messed with my head after I just competed it and that when I was teaching I was just aware of all the different possible factors or effects and consequences involved in every single step of every single stage of a lesson <pause dur="short"/> that I found it quite overwhelming</u>
<u n="417" who="S0125">because you had <unclear/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0018" trans="overlap">because I'd studied it so in depth <pause dur="short"/> but then after a couple of months I just started actually feeling a lot more confident that oh no actually I don't have to think about every single little detail I just have to focus on certain areas and I felt a lot more confident</u>
<u n="419" who="S0125">that's good</u>
<u n="420" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0125">it's just choosing what information to use isn't it</u>
<u n="422" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0125">and what to discard <pause dur="short"/> like my report</u>
<u n="424" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh no but if you don't have to if it's not like of paramount importance</u>
<u n="425" who="S0125" trans="overlap"></u>
<u n="426" who="S0018">that you cut it down <pause dur="short"/> I mean how many words do you reckon you'll be able to get away with?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0125">it'd be nice to get to three thousand five hundred</u>
<u n="428" who="S0018">and what is it at now?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0125">hmm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0018">it was four thousand four hundred wasn't it?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0125">four thousand five hundred <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I still have to cut a thousand from it <pause dur="short"/> like yeah so it's that middle portion isn't it</u>
<u n="432" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0125">hm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0018">do you have any idea of any bits that you're just gonna cut out completely?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0125">hmm maybe once I've gone through what you've suggested in terms of like word order and conciseness potentially like this section on the um responsibility activities</u>
<u n="436" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0125">because that is that's a hundred and fifty almost <pause dur="short"/> so that's good</u>
<u n="438" who="S0018">I reckon maybe cut out two hundred words just by going through and er rewording things</u>
<u n="439" who="S0125">hm <pause dur="short"/> ss okay so that takes me to like three fifty <pause dur="short"/> and then I've got to find six fifty somewhere else</u>
<u n="440" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> blimey <pause dur="short"/> how much over was your last one? You said that they didn't penalise you for it</u>
<u n="441" who="S0125">well there's one six nine in that table as well so that's one seventy</u>
<u n="442" who="S0018">okay cool</u>
<u n="443" who="S0125">so that's now we're down to six fifty-five fifty-five three five five hundred and thirty</u>
<u n="444" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0125">sorry how much was it over the last one? I can check</u>
<u n="446" who="S0018">I heard your welsh accent come out then</u>
<u n="447" who="S0125" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm comes out excuse me it comes out when I go home to Wales</u>
<u n="448" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0018">and maybe in times of ridiculous stress</u>
<u n="451" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0018">and pressure</u>
<u n="453" who="S0125">yes maybe <pause dur="short"/> or when drunk</u>
<u n="454" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0125">three seven ninety and I think <unclear/> yeah it was a thousand over</u>
<u n="456" who="S0018">and yet it wasn't penalised?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0125">I don't believe so</u>
<u n="458" who="S0018">so why</u>
<u n="459" who="S0125">it scored eighty-nine percent</u>
<u n="460" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0018">so why do you want to cut this one down?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0125">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm panicking <pause dur="short"/> no no because they've explicitly said it needs to be concise</u>
<u n="464" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="465" who="S0125">hmm <pause dur="short"/> and the marker is different</u>
<u n="466" who="S0018">ah okay <pause dur="short"/> is the marker the same guy that gave you feedback on it?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0125">no</u>
<u n="468" who="S0018">hm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0125">have they moved into the nineties? On the radio <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm listening to all these songs it's like total blast from the past <pause dur="short"/> I haven't heard The Beautiful South in ages</u>
<u n="471" who="S0125">they were great</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018">I loved them <pause dur="short"/> and the House Martins <pause dur="short"/> I still listen to the House Martins</u>
<u n="473" who="S0125">do you? I don't think I've listened to them that much <pause dur="short"/> how old are you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0018">thirty-six <pause dur="short"/> and you?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0125">thirty-one <pause dur="short"/> so would you have bought their records?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0018">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was kind of like in when I was fifteen</u>
<u n="477" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018">sixteen <pause dur="short"/> the Beautiful South</u>
<u n="479" who="S0125">yeah but not the House Martins</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">the House Martins was earlier but my brother liked them so</u>
<u n="481" who="S0125" trans="overlap">oh okay you've got an older brother</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="483" who="S0125" trans="overlap">how old is your brother?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0018">three years older than me</u>
<u n="485" who="S0125">oh okay</u>
<u n="486" who="S0018">yeah he turned forty recently</u>
<u n="487" who="S0125">where does he live?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">Australia</u>
<u n="489" who="S0125">oh really</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0125" trans="overlap">where? Which city?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">Perth</u>
<u n="493" who="S0125">ah nice</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">with a barbeque Near the beach</u>
<u n="497" who="S0125">how long has he lived there?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018">ooh gosh I think he moved out there about five years ago</u>
<u n="499" who="S0125">and why did he go there?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018">oh just cos he he hated England <trunc>an</trunc></u>
<u n="501" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/> as easy as that</u>
<u n="502" who="S0018">yeah I I don't think he ever got himself into a situation in England that merited staying for</u>
<u n="503" who="S0125">oh right <pause dur="short"/> what does he do then?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0018">well he's in kind of marketing erm advertising <pause dur="short"/> er at the moment he's got a freelance contract with the one of the state governments to project manage some kind of informative marketing campaign</u>
<u n="505" who="S0125">oh right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> nice</u>
<u n="506" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> but er no when when I was living in Barcelona he he was working for a company that did all the publicity and packaging for pharmaceutical products for people like Beechams</u>
<u n="507" who="S0125">oh okay</u>
<u n="508" who="S0018">and so he came over to Madrid</u>
<u n="509" who="S0125">like branding and stuff like that</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm yep <pause dur="short"/> sO he came over to Madrid for a meeting and his translator let him down at the last moment</u>
<u n="511" who="S0125">oh no</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">so he phoned me up <pause dur="short"/> he said I need to fly you to Madrid to be my <trunc>transla</trunc> my interpreter <pause dur="short"/> so completely random situation in a meeting talking about the different pantones in the</u>
<u n="513" who="S0125">wow</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">and all that stuff</u>
<u n="515" who="S0125">sounds interesting</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">it was interesting yeah but my brother was so unprofessional he kept whispering stuff into my ear I was trying to focus on</u>
<u n="517" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh no</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> there was this one lady being a right bitch to him and er knowing that she didn't understand English he'd be saying things to me <pause dur="short"/> well tell her to go and herself then and obviously <vocal desc="laugh"/> well he <trunc>d</trunc> me translating that well he doesn't actually agree <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> as opposed to go jump off a cliff</u>
<u n="519" who="S0125">I love watching or um no I'm watching twenty twelve at the moment have you been watching that? It's like a <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="521" who="S0125">it's a spoof comedy um story about twenty twelve Olympics</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="523" who="S0125">and <trunc>i</trunc> it's got um Hugh Bonneville in it</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">oh I think I've heard of it yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah and</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018" trans="overlap">can I have another piece</u>
<u n="527" who="S0125">of course <pause dur="short"/> and <vocal desc="laugh"/> and um they've got these because it's like set in an office it's like this this office team of delivery office for the Olympics <pause dur="short"/> they've got people from like that are responsible for sustainability</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0125">and legacy and deliverance <pause dur="short"/> head of deliverance is Hugh Bonneville's er</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0125">title and um they they often show them like <trunc>sa</trunc> sat round a table in a meeting and they'll be like yes shall we just leave that there shall we just leave that on the table <pause dur="short"/> It's like this sort of saying within business now like can we just park that?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0125" trans="overlap">I've been I went to a um I went to a networking event in Helsinki and um  it was  it was kind of an international business <pause dur="short"/> the speaker was Finnish but speaking in English <pause dur="short"/> an American English accent <pause dur="short"/> she's like Okay we'll just park that there <pause dur="short"/> Basically I don't want to talk about that anymore I would rather talk about this <pause dur="short"/> let's park that <pause dur="short"/> I'm like I just think that's so awful <pause dur="short"/> can't you just acknowledge that or it's just a quick way of dealing with something you don't want to talk about</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0125">or like yes I think we'll just leave that on the table <pause dur="short"/> and then in this back to this twenty twelve they they constantly say absolutely absolutely yeah yeah cool absolutely absolutely <pause dur="short"/> And there's this character that Jessica Stevenson the <trunc>cha</trunc> the the um actress plays and from a PR company and she is horrendous <pause dur="short"/> she's just like cool yeah yeah okay right yeah errm what are we gonna what like have you got any ideas about that um er no okay and it's just you know when somebody's like speaking from the back of their throat and they're not like annunciating that much but they they've got this like posh like <unclear/> stilted accent like yeah okay great yeah <pause dur="short"/> And it's aagh so irritating but so amusing as well because it's based on reality</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0125">people exist like that</u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> and like The Office</u>
<u n="539" who="S0125">hmm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">Good parody on reality</u>
<u n="541" who="S0125">mm <pause dur="short"/> and how people don't let you finish your sentences in an office environment sometimes</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="543" who="S0125">and they try and like interrupt you and you just</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0125">or they don't listen to what you're saying</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">or use management speak <pause dur="short"/> yeah so let's all take this on board</u>
<u n="547" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0125">that's funny</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">so what is it is it is the build up to the Olympics</u>
<u n="551" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">or while they're actually happening?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0125">no it's the build up</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="555" who="S0125">and he's always being called upstairs to go and see Sebastian Coe</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="557" who="S0125">or Boris Johnson hasn't been told about something or so <trunc>ba</trunc> it's kin of like these <trunc>re</trunc> it's almost mm please <pause dur="short"/> realistic um references to people and things going on in like you can imagine it really happening like that</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">well it must be happening somewhere no?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">there's probably some kind of coordination office</u>
<u n="561" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">High up <pause dur="short"/> crikey <pause dur="short"/> are you going to watch any of the sporting events</u>
<u n="563" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018">in London?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0125">I hadn't really thought about it <pause dur="short"/> it sounds like it might be horrendous travel</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018">well there are posters up umm everywhere around Birmingham saying be careful the traffic might be</u>
<u n="567" who="S0125">what?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0018">certain motorways might be</u>
<u n="569" who="S0125" trans="overlap">in Birmingham?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0018">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it's cos they have events all around the country</u>
<u n="571" who="S0125" trans="overlap">oh I know they're playing football in Coventry</u>
<u n="572" who="S0018">oh are they?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0125">and in Birmingham</u>
<u n="574" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0125">the Aston Villa ground isn't it?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0018">I don't know</u>
<u n="577" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Have you had your fill?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0018">these pizzas are so filling</u>
<u n="579" who="S0125">they're terrible aren't they</u>
<u n="580" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0125">terribly good <pause dur="short"/> I'll get some tissues</u>
<u n="582" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0125"><unclear/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0018">very tasty <pause dur="short"/> do you want me to open the door for you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0125"><unclear/> tissues in that box</u>
<u n="586" who="S0018">I think <unclear/> is going to watch the boxing</u>
<u n="587" who="S0125">oh really <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0018">I've got a feeling that a friend of mine is playing as well she's got like some gig in some Olympic village or something <pause dur="short"/> but I think it's going to be particularly crazy <pause dur="short"/> how long does the whole shabang last for?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0125">um two weeks three weeks <unclear/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0018">I really have no idea</u>
<u n="591" who="S0125">might be a month <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="592" who="S0018">well they've said like even internet connections might be</u>
<u n="593" who="S0125">internet</u>
<u n="594" who="S0018">interrupted <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> because they've only got like</u>
<u n="595" who="S0125">bandwidth</u>
<u n="596" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's finite <trunc>isn</trunc></u>
<u n="597" who="S0125">aS long as I can watch Eastenders on iPlayer I don't care</u>
<u n="598" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0125">if something goes wrong with that then I will get upset</u>
<u n="600" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh it's gonna get crazy</u>
<u n="601" who="S0125">you think?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0018">oh god it's already started <pause dur="short"/> have you not noticed like all the adverts have started <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="603" who="S0125">oh yeah but</u>
<u n="604" who="S0018">everything's about Britain and Union Jacks everywhere its</u>
<u n="605" who="S0125">do you want to split this?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0018">no thanks I can't manage anymore</u>
<u n="607" who="S0125">neither can I really</u>
<u n="608" who="S0018">save it for you er late night</u>
<u n="609" who="S0125" trans="overlap">midnight snack</u>
<u n="610" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0125">put it in that little box</u>
<u n="612" who="S0018" trans="overlap">cold pizza is just as nice as hot pizza</u>
<u n="613" who="S0125" trans="overlap">oh god yeah I mean I just kind of painful face</u>
<u n="614" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0125">at the thought of being up at midnight working on this thing</u>
<u n="616" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="617" who="S0125">nine o'clock pizza <pause dur="short"/> what is the time?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0018">er half six</u>
<u n="619" who="S0125">oh is that all <pause dur="short"/> good <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was gonna be a lot later <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I opened that one</u>
<u n="620" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="621" who="S0125">I'm gonna save it</u>
<u n="622" who="S0018">how much was it in total?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0125">Don't worry about it</u>
<u n="624" who="S0018">are you sure?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0125">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0018">that's very kind of you <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't expecting it</u>
<u n="627" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You weren't expecting it <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice surprise</u>
<u n="628" who="S0018">okay so the parts I <pause dur="short"/> oh gosh is this alright on putting on the table? Have you got a spare coaster?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0125">just<unclear/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0125">thanks</u>
<u n="632" who="S0018">sorry</u>
<u n="633" who="S0125">that's alright</u>
<u n="634" who="S0018">oh <trunc>y</trunc> I've put my cup of tea down on the advert for Ben and Jerry's ice cream</u>
<u n="635" who="S0125"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0018">once you start eating junk food it's very difficult to stop <pause dur="short"/> okay so  I thought  I thought the introduction was all pertinent <pause dur="short"/> maybe you could cut cut it down a little bit just by simplifying your sentences</u>
<u n="637" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> then in part one <pause dur="short"/> errm I can't remember whether there was um yeah there was maybe parts about I don't know that this two sentence paragraph here I thought maybe was</u>
<u n="639" who="S0125"></u>
<u n="640" who="S0018">no I thought maybe this information was already kind of included cos it's saying</u>
<u n="641" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yes I know</u>
<u n="642" who="S0018">it's working across different expertise areas but is that part of the small interdisciplinary team <pause dur="short"/> is that meaning the same thing</u>
<u n="643" who="S0125">possibly</u>
<u n="644" who="S0018">does it need to be</u>
<u n="645" who="S0125">I'll check</u>
<u n="646" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> erm then</u>
<u n="647" who="S0125">relevance <pause dur="short"/> er you suggested moving that</u>
<u n="648" who="S0018">yeah to the previous page cos that's where it was giving an example of <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> oh it depends whether you want to mix the lit review with the primary findings</u>
<u n="649" who="S0125">okay</u>
<u n="650" who="S0018">but I just thought it seemed a bit weird there because you didn't really talk about the structure here whereas you did here</u>
<u n="651" who="S0125">okay</u>
<u n="652" who="S0018">do you see what I mean</u>
<u n="653" who="S0125">yep</u>
<u n="654" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> oh and when I put develop this I just when you put here that the email newsletter is an illustration of this <pause dur="short"/> maybe it needs another part of the sentence to qualify why <pause dur="short"/> so just develop that</u>
<u n="655" who="S0125" trans="overlap">there's data in here that's missing that you haven't seen that explains it</u>
<u n="656" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="657" who="S0125">so I think that wil be okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll check</u>
<u n="658" who="S0018">okay cool <pause dur="short"/> and then <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> was there yeah cos that that that part refers to back to stuff that you've put in the lit review before</u>
<u n="659" who="S0125">but it's about</u>
<u n="660" who="S0018">and the branding that you've discussed before</u>
<u n="661" who="S0125">okay I can get rid of <pause dur="short"/> where's the pen?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0018">it depends if <pause dur="short"/> it's difficult for me to know what's superfluous cos I don't actually understand it</u>
<u n="663" who="S0125" trans="overlap">I think that might be there <pause dur="short"/> this is the actual data information about the company so that's fine <pause dur="short"/> that explains what they're doing <pause dur="short"/> how they're doing it in terms of visual communications <pause dur="short"/> erm okay <pause dur="short"/> err <pause dur="short"/> what was that <trunc>you</trunc></u>
<u n="664" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="665" who="S0125">you suggested putting that down</u>
<u n="666" who="S0018">just putting those two sentences down with that one because</u>
<u n="667" who="S0125" trans="overlap">oh okay fine</u>
<u n="668" who="S0018">it it wasn't logical to the reader how to</u>
<u n="669" who="S0125" trans="overlap">reads better <pause dur="short"/> yep alright</u>
<u n="670" who="S0018">where it followed on from <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah the references <pause dur="short"/> um I tend to either put a reference at the end of the sentence in brackets as opposed to</u>
<u n="671" who="S0125">yeah it should be there then shouldn't it</u>
<u n="672" who="S0018">Cos it</u>
<u n="673" who="S0125"><unclear/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0018">can be quite clunky and it adds extra words to your word count as well</u>
<u n="675" who="S0125">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0018">so or you could say um it is argued that at the beginning of the sentence and then in in <trunc>pa</trunc> er brackets at the end put who it was who stated it and the year <pause dur="short"/> um also you don't need a full stop <pause dur="short"/> this is being really pernickety but you don't need a full stop at the end of the sentence before you open the brackets to put the reference</u>
<u n="677" who="S0125">sure</u>
<u n="678" who="S0018">so I've um scribbled that out on quite a few occasions <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I didn't <pause dur="short"/> that was more research <pause dur="short"/> that part was</u>
<u n="679" who="S0125">that's to do with my methodology</u>
<u n="680" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0125">it's a challenge <pause dur="short"/> um I'll look at whether I can</u>
<u n="682" who="S0018">maybe cos you've done quite a lot of criticising your design method and suggesting</u>
<u n="683" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0018">findings <pause dur="short"/> maybe that would be a bit you could target to take out <pause dur="short"/> oh these were just a few of the sentences that I thought that by fronting</u>
<u n="685" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0018">the most important bit of the sentence it would be clearer <pause dur="short"/> and it would also um take your word count down <pause dur="short"/> um yeah and I've just um made some of your sentences shorter</u>
<u n="687" who="S0125">yep fine</u>
<u n="688" who="S0018">by splitting them up <pause dur="short"/> although that's not going to help you with the word count but <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing else in there thought you could take out</u>
<u n="689" who="S0125">okay fine</u>
<u n="690" who="S0018">or there</u>
<u n="691" who="S0125">I might need to um tidy this bit up <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> okay fine</u>
<u n="692" who="S0018">oh and check that thing that if you um <pause dur="short"/> if it's not actually quoted as a direct reference as a direct quote with speech marks you don't need to put the</u>
<u n="693" who="S0125">okay</u>
<u n="694" who="S0018">the page number <pause dur="short"/> however if it is if it's in <trunc>quo</trunc> if you've paraphrased it I don't think you need the page that it's come from</u>
<u n="695" who="S0125">okay</u>
<u n="696" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/>  Um um um um  um <pause dur="short"/> yeah and that was just the thing about if it's not a published source you don't need to reference it</u>
<u n="697" who="S0125" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="698" who="S0018">and just the translated from Finnish as well just stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> it's just adding extra words</u>
<u n="699" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0018">Don't know if it's necessary <pause dur="short"/> er I think I'm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0125">this bit I need to move cos that's kind of like a primary piece of evidence</u>
<u n="702" who="S0018">ah so you put it after the</u>
<u n="703" who="S0125">yeah and also I'm already <trunc>s</trunc> I'm going to say about the approach <pause dur="short"/> I can get rid of that sentence</u>
<u n="704" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="705" who="S0125">right fine</u>
<u n="706" who="S0018">okey dokey <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah  that was a that was a paragraph we talked about though wasn't it</u>
<u n="707" who="S0125">yep</u>
<u n="708" who="S0018">um yeah how come you've got a title here at the <trunc>bot</trunc> top of this</u>
<u n="709" who="S0125">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it's fine don't worry</u>
<u n="710" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0125">it's fine <pause dur="short"/> get rid of that</u>
<u n="712" who="S0018">and then</u>
<u n="713" who="S0125">I was thinkng this bit might be a bit big and maybe I can just reduce it</u>
<u n="714" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="715" who="S0125">either by putting more of this into the</u>
<u n="716" who="S0018">un-huh</u>
<u n="717" who="S0125">or um <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay fine</u>
<u n="718" who="S0018">or just cutting it out if it's not</u>
<u n="719" who="S0125">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it demonstrates how that previous point has been applied but I'll just okay</u>
<u n="720" who="S0018">is it part of the ongoing text or is it a caption?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0125">that's a caption <pause dur="short"/> quite a big caption though</u>
<u n="722" who="S0018">that bit's ongoing text?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0125">yep</u>
<u n="724" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah with the research methodology there was <pause dur="short"/> how long was that supposed to be cos I think it falls more or less</u>
<u n="725" who="S0125">four hundred</u>
<u n="726" who="S0018">more or less falls into the word limit</u>
<u n="727" who="S0125">yep</u>
<u n="728" who="S0018">so I don't think there's a problem with that cutting that bit down <pause dur="short"/> oh the conclusion <pause dur="short"/> I just thought it was maybe a little structured in a bit of a willy nilly</u>
<u n="729" who="S0125">yep</u>
<u n="730" who="S0018">manner <pause dur="short"/> cos it um I think you need to summarise the key points <pause dur="short"/> so what was your question? The question was How do Design and Cultural Values Influence Communications? So actually say it the first sentence through the study I have ascertained that um communications are influenced to a certain extent by design and cultural values such as blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> just summarise it</u>
<u n="731" who="S0125">yep</u>
<u n="732" who="S0018">and just make it really explicit <pause dur="short"/> cos then you've you've gone <trunc>un</trunc> basically you're saying a lot about how what you do in he future</u>
<u n="733" who="S0125">mm</u>
<u n="734" who="S0018">whereas I think it the booklet it said summarise your main your key points first</u>
<u n="735" who="S0125">yeah okay</u>
<u n="736" who="S0018">um</u>
<u n="737" who="S0125"><unclear/> shorter sentences</u>
<u n="738" who="S0018">I didn't really understand that</u>
<u n="739" who="S0125">that's because that's a piece I've <trunc>jus</trunc> I've just added and hadn't really looked at</u>
<u n="740" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="741" who="S0125">that's it okay</u>
<u n="742" who="S0018">oh and that was that last paragraph that we thought maybe</u>
<u n="743" who="S0125" trans="overlap">yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="744" who="S0018">wasn't necessary</u>
<u n="745" who="S0125">okay <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="746" who="S0018">but kudos to you <pause dur="short"/> it's an amazing piece of work woman</u>
<u n="747" who="S0125">really I don't know yet</u>
<u n="748" who="S0018"><unclear/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0125">yes</u>
<u n="750" who="S0018"><unclear/> What you gonna do on it? You gonna read it through again and edit it?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0125" trans="overlap">I'm just going to start editing it now</u>
<u n="752" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="753" who="S0125">yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0018">right I'll go downstairs for a bit</u>
<u n="755" who="S0125">alright</u>
<u n="756" who="S0018">I'll come back up <pause dur="short"/> if there's anything like if you want to give me any of the pages and say can you keep all the meaning but cut fifty words out of that paragraph I could probably <trunc>re</trunc> I could probably juggle the sentences the words and sentences</u>
<u n="757" who="S0125" trans="overlap">well let me get  let me get through it based on what you've done here and then I'll see what I'm down to and then see how we go from there</u>
<u n="758" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> coolio coolio</u>
<u n="759" who="S0125">okay</u>
<u n="760" who="S0018">nice one</u>
</body>
</text>
