<text id="ST62">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:07</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0181 S0182</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers’ home office,  Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Photography, Japan, badgers</topics>
		<activity>Couple talking about old photos</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, anecdote telling, telling jokes </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T05</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0181">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Chelmsford, Essex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0182">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Japanese -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0181">so are most of the things you have from like two thousand five or when?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0182">no <pause dur="short"/> they're from all over <pause dur="short"/> all years</u>
<u n="3" who="S0181">like like when's all years begin?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0182">well from two thousand and five right up to I guess December of last year</u>
<u n="5" who="S0181">oh right</u>
<u n="6" who="S0182">and I have a bunch of ones that for some reason I've named L J ran one to two three four and onwards</u>
<u n="7" who="S0181">presumably L J would stand for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0182">yeah and ran I don't know what ran means</u>
<u n="9" who="S0181">you wanted to post them to the internet and they were something to do with running</u>
<u n="10" who="S0182">no <pause dur="short"/> random <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0181">random pictures are therefore called ran</u>
<u n="12" who="S0182" trans="overlap">I've just figured out how my mind works yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0181">logical</u>
<u n="14" who="S0182">yes</u>
<u n="15" who="S0181"><unclear/> similar thing I don't have anything earlier than two thousand and five <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit odd like that</u>
<u n="16" who="S0182">that's when our life started <pause dur="short"/> I guess <pause dur="short"/> actually I think it's pretty much</u>
<u n="17" who="S0181">I think it's when like we had digital cameras <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0182">no yeah it's when I I started getting my camera</u>
<u n="19" who="S0181">ah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0182">and I've got a lots lots of ones from <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> usually of food <pause dur="short"/> I've got one of a pestle and mortar with ground up sesame seeds in it</u>
<u n="21" who="S0181">do you pestle or pestle?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0182">pestle <pause dur="short"/> I said well I say pestle but you spell it pestle</u>
<u n="23" who="S0181">I also pronounce it pestle</u>
<u n="24" who="S0182">do you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0181">yes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0182">uh have I been saying it wrong all this time then</u>
<u n="27" who="S0181">I have no idea <pause dur="short"/> we should consult an authority <pause dur="short"/> such as Baba Yaga</u>
<u n="28" who="S0182">well I was thinking more like my mum but I got it from her so</u>
<u n="29" who="S0181">I'll refrain from the obvious joke about resemblances between your mum and Baba Yaga <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0182"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You can't say that</u>
<u n="31" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/> She'd think it was hilarious</u>
<u n="32" who="S0182">maybe</u>
<u n="33" who="S0181">but no seriously you know <pause dur="short"/> pestle <pause dur="short"/> baba Yaga <pause dur="short"/> obvious <pause dur="short"/> no? No</u>
<u n="34" who="S0182">no</u>
<u n="35" who="S0181">oh</u>
<u n="36" who="S0182">and I have a picture of some um not green tea I think it's I'm not quite sure what it is but you drink it on uh graduation day</u>
<u n="37" who="S0181">not like special green tea matcha?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0182">no I think it's it might be kombu</u>
<u n="39" who="S0181">I don't know what kombu is <pause dur="short"/> a special kind of green tea?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0182" trans="overlap">sea <pause dur="short"/> seaweed <pause dur="short"/> I think it's got seaweed in it</u>
<u n="41" who="S0181">Green tea with seaweed in it</u>
<u n="42" who="S0182">something like that</u>
<u n="43" who="S0181">so it's  a sort of</u>
<u n="44" who="S0182">like kombucha</u>
<u n="45" who="S0181">a sort of hazing of recently graduated students then</u>
<u n="46" who="S0182">no no no that's that's given to the teachers</u>
<u n="47" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0182">so I've got a picture of um a a some I think kombucha with uh  petals floating in it and the the guide to the graduation is just inside the frame so you can see that it says <trunc>ge</trunc> graduation in Japanese but you can't see what school it is or anything <pause dur="short"/> just sort of like stock photography style</u>
<u n="49" who="S0181">perfect <pause dur="short"/> there we go</u>
<u n="50" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0181">you can post it to a stock site <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="52" who="S0182" trans="overlap">uh oh yeah <trunc>w</trunc> no no I don't think I can cos the the um resolution is terrible cos it was a digital <trunc>phot</trunc> uh <trunc>s</trunc> well it's from my iPhone</u>
<u n="53" who="S0181">okay right <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's not gonna cut it then</u>
<u n="54" who="S0182" trans="overlap">so it's not yeah but it was kind of what I was going for for a a blog</u>
<u n="55" who="S0181">even if it's awesome it's not gonna cut it <pause dur="short"/> it's quite weird but like micro stock sites</u>
<u n="56" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0181">um because they can't afford to employ like professionals to evaluate the pictures</u>
<u n="58" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0181">and to price them etcetera basically go entirely off technical specifications when they're deciding what to accept</u>
<u n="60" who="S0182">really</u>
<u n="61" who="S0181">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so while like a a a brilliant photograph taken on an iPhone could actually make it onto like a top premium like Getty editorial section sell for hundreds of dollars</u>
<u n="62" who="S0182">mm mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0181">it wouldn't get onto a micro stock site <pause dur="short"/> conversely an absolutely dreadful photograph of technical high quality would probably pass for micro stock</u>
<u n="64" who="S0182">I see that a lot of <trunc>t</trunc> times on um photo communities <pause dur="short"/> there are people out there with absolutely fantastic cameras taking pictures of cups of coffee</u>
<u n="65" who="S0181">keeping to the theme of micro stock most of the sites have list of things they don't want to see and it's usually like stuff that is lying around your apartment</u>
<u n="66" who="S0182">but people do that <pause dur="short"/> someone I think they they</u>
<u n="67" who="S0181">well</u>
<u n="68" who="S0182">they took a picture of their neighbour's garden cos they liked their pumpkins or something</u>
<u n="69" who="S0181">on the plus side that totally doesn't sell <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> cos that's the other thing is like the micro stock sites admit they have this sort of slight issue that like garbage can get in if it's technically okay</u>
<u n="70" who="S0182">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0181">but it's not gonna sell so it's sort of self correcting right</u>
<u n="72" who="S0182"><unclear/> and another thing with <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0181">brilliant demonstration of the market system or something</u>
<u n="74" who="S0182">is that if you do a <trunc>pic</trunc> if you take a picture of a beautiful sunset then people just start voting for that <pause dur="short"/> I I don't get it</u>
<u n="75" who="S0181">could probably learn something about the marketing of photography</u>
<u n="76" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0181">except who wants a stock photograph of a sunset <pause dur="short"/> nobody</u>
<u n="78" who="S0182">no <pause dur="short"/> well it's not about stock photography but a lot of the ones that get that are ranked highly they're um they're pictures of nature and sunsets <pause dur="short"/> done in such a way they tell you nothing about the country they're in or anything except that it had a that there was a beautiful sunset that day</u>
<u n="79" who="S0181">is this in the context of like pure photo context or are you talking like Day on Earth or what?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0182">stuff like that like the photo files community</u>
<u n="81" who="S0181" trans="overlap"><trunc>S</trunc> Sometimes tells you nothing about the country is acceptable isn't it?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0182">mm it's okay</u>
<u n="83" who="S0181" trans="overlap">depends what you're interested in <pause dur="short"/> wow that is a strange strange statue</u>
<u n="84" who="S0182">what are you looking at?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0181">A photo of a strange strange statue <pause dur="short"/> um Yokohama</u>
<u n="86" who="S0182">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> which statue?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0181">the one of the cat standing on the pile of houses</u>
<u n="88" who="S0182">have I seen it? I must have seen it</u>
<u n="89" who="S0181">I think you were there <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it looks like like the first time we went to Yokohama <pause dur="short"/> I've got photos of graffiti and things</u>
<u n="90" who="S0182">okay I'm gonna google that and I'm gonna look for cat standing on houses photograph</u>
<u n="91" who="S0181">that's art man</u>
<u n="92" who="S0182">cat houses <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna add in Yokohama</u>
<u n="93" who="S0181">you'll get hundreds of photos of actual cats <pause dur="short"/> which are actually what I would expect to win all these photo contexts we were discussing</u>
<u n="94" who="S0182">yes some people just vote for the cats</u>
<u n="95" who="S0181">well who wouldn't</u>
<u n="96" who="S0182">cats houses Yokohama statue <pause dur="short"/> my first hit is pets in Japan <pause dur="short"/> nursing care for pets <pause dur="short"/> cat cafes and dot dot dot</u>
<u n="97" who="S0181">okay do you remember those shots from York you were talking about</u>
<u n="98" who="S0182">yuh-huh</u>
<u n="99" who="S0181">and wondering what they were <pause dur="short"/> I can actually tell you they were taken on the twenty-seventh of January</u>
<u n="100" who="S0182">oh I know that</u>
<u n="101" who="S0181">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I can actually tell you where it was <pause dur="short"/> um you know okay this is really imprecise but you know that gate that we always seem to end up using when we go to York probably because we always stay in like a B and B just outside it</u>
<u n="102" who="S0182">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0181">it's the one up the north west westest  near the  near the <anon type="place"/> to the west of the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0182">okay</u>
<u n="105" who="S0181">north of the train station <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0182">okay</u>
<u n="107" who="S0181">anyway so just south of there</u>
<u n="108" who="S0182">mm mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0181">just across the road outside the walls there's a sort of ruins of an abbey and there's a sort of museum castle and a park full of squirrels</u>
<u n="110" who="S0182">mm mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0181">and that was where that all is</u>
<u n="112" who="S0182">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we did take a lot of pictures of squirrels <pause dur="short"/> almost as if we knew we weren't gonna see them any more for about five years</u>
<u n="113" who="S0181">and then we did</u>
<u n="114" who="S0182">we did</u>
<u n="115" who="S0181"><pause dur="long"/> You know I just made fun of people for taking pictures of cats and I found like an entire folder that's basically just the cat dressed as Santa <pause dur="short"/> so yes</u>
<u n="116" who="S0182">he didn't seem to mind <pause dur="short"/> but it but it's it's our cat</u>
<u n="117" who="S0181" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it kept him warm so</u>
<u n="118" who="S0182">it's like cats are a lot like kids <pause dur="short"/> no-one wants to see anybody else's</u>
<u n="119" who="S0181">it's our cat and we never posted it on the internet as</u>
<u n="120" who="S0182">yeah yeah that's the main thing</u>
<u n="121" who="S0181">look the cat is dressed as Santa</u>
<u n="122" who="S0182">but he was very happy with it <unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0181">well he was warm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0182">yes <pause dur="short"/> but I think he genuinely liked being Santa <pause dur="long"/> Hm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0181">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I hate?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0182">no</u>
<u n="127" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm gonna tell you</u>
<u n="128" who="S0182">I guessed that</u>
<u n="129" who="S0181">photographs taken at firework displays</u>
<u n="130" who="S0182">oh I do that</u>
<u n="131" who="S0181">I always find I end up with about four hundred and it can quickly trim it down to about one hundred but you really only want to keep about five and it's making the final cut right it's like which of these almost identical photographs is better</u>
<u n="132" who="S0182">no no no if basically if if it isn't blurred it gets kept <pause dur="short"/> that reduces it to about five</u>
<u n="133" who="S0181">oh really</u>
<u n="134" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0181">I guess I'm better at taking photographs of fireworks than you which</u>
<u n="136" who="S0182">you may well be</u>
<u n="137" who="S0181">surprises me greatly <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="138" who="S0182">it's a matter of just holding the camera <trunc>st</trunc> still but if you use an iPhone then basically adjusts it basically assumes that you're just taking things randomly and takes it well but if you're taking a digital <unclear/>  with a  with a professional camera</u>
<u n="139" who="S0181" trans="overlap">no I I think digital camera shots that can come out not blurred <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's just cos I take so many</u>
<u n="140" who="S0182">okay</u>
<u n="141" who="S0181">I think I just take way many more than you at firework displays</u>
<u n="142" who="S0182">could be</u>
<u n="143" who="S0181">that's another thing that you can't sell anyway <pause dur="short"/> firework photos</u>
<u n="144" who="S0182">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> depends <trunc>ho</trunc> what you're taking it of <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0181">there was someone launching fireworks last night actually did you?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0182">I didn't what time?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0181">oh I dunno <pause dur="short"/> nine PM or something <pause dur="short"/> that was a complete guess</u>
<u n="148" who="S0182"><trunc>Ni</trunc> what was I? I was watching the Mentalist wasn't I</u>
<u n="149" who="S0181">no okay it must have been earlier than nine PM then</u>
<u n="150" who="S0182">okay <pause dur="short"/> then I was watching that I wasn't watching <pause dur="short"/> I was in the room with Mum and Dad watching that show about trucks</u>
<u n="151" who="S0181">that sounds painful</u>
<u n="152" who="S0182">it is kind of hypnotic they were making I think it was Harry Hill that was making fun of kind of it the other day <pause dur="short"/> cos they try and inject a lot of drama into a guy who might not make his deliveries on time</u>
<u n="153" who="S0181">what show about trucks was this like world's most extreme</u>
<u n="154" who="S0182">Eddie</u>
<u n="155" who="S0181">tough demon truckers of doom</u>
<u n="156" who="S0182">it was the Eddie something or other trucking thing</u>
<u n="157" who="S0181">A different trucking thing</u>
<u n="158" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0181">oh the um after the famous company</u>
<u n="160" who="S0182">yes</u>
<u n="161" who="S0181">Eddie Stobart</u>
<u n="162" who="S0182">that's it</u>
<u n="163" who="S0181">which is a as I said</u>
<u n="164" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0181">famous company in the UK so locally famous company</u>
<u n="166" who="S0182">why I was look basically I find it very fascinating when they talk about um how famous or how many genuine fans they have</u>
<u n="167" who="S0181">yeah it's like</u>
<u n="168" who="S0182">that is  that is fascinating</u>
<u n="169" who="S0181">can you think of any hobby more more like ridiculous than train spotting</u>
<u n="170" who="S0182">um</u>
<u n="171" who="S0181">truck spotting</u>
<u n="172" who="S0182">I probably have a few of those hobbies myself</u>
<u n="173" who="S0181">well yeah probably the same here but who was that comedian though was that on the radio or was it on TV the other day? I can't remember</u>
<u n="174" who="S0182">well describe the comedian and I will</u>
<u n="175" who="S0181">oh no the the joke was like all these train spotters <pause dur="short"/> I can't think of any more pathetic hobby <pause dur="short"/> I counted a hundred and forty-seven of them this morning <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0182">I I don't think I heard that or saw it or whatever it was on</u>
<u n="177" who="S0181">was probably on the radio then</u>
<u n="178" who="S0182">oh okay</u>
<u n="179" who="S0181"><pause dur="long"/> Might have been on Newscheck</u>
<u n="180" who="S0182">oh could've been</u>
<u n="181" who="S0181"><pause dur="long"/> Or it might have been that um the the programme about Glasgow</u>
<u n="182" who="S0182">yeah I can see why they'd need a few comedians on that</u>
<u n="183" who="S0181">no don't you remember there was a comedian presenting a programme about Glasgow</u>
<u n="184" who="S0182">oh <pause dur="short"/> it it wasn't really about Glasgow it was I thought it was about issues in Glasgow that turn up in his set</u>
<u n="185" who="S0181">no it was about Glasgow <pause dur="short"/> just Glasgow as a giant bag of issues and being from Glasgow it produces much of his material</u>
<u n="186" who="S0182">I thought it was more about his material</u>
<u n="187" who="S0181" trans="overlap">because let's face it if you're <trunc>do</trunc> if you're from Glasgow and you're doing dark comedy you're never gonna want for content <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0182">um <pause dur="short"/> glasgow isn't that bad</u>
<u n="189" who="S0181">you've been there <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You remember Eve's story about the time the post office blew up</u>
<u n="190" who="S0182">uh vaguely</u>
<u n="191" who="S0181">that's Glasgow <pause dur="short"/> central Glasgow is really really nice</u>
<u n="192" who="S0182">mm mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0181">but that is a tiny percentage of the whole city <pause dur="long"/> You know that Glasgow is the murder capital of Europe right</u>
<u n="194" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0181">yeah not not some like economically devastated ex part of like a Balkan war zone or something like that <pause dur="short"/> it's Glasgow</u>
<u n="196" who="S0182">okay</u>
<u n="197" who="S0181">yeah <pause dur="long"/> Which is you know a fact <pause dur="short"/> so people make all these features about how Glasgow is a great city of culture and it's cruel to perpetuate this stereotype about Glasgow and then you go there and there's this wasteland of industrial places and hey murder capital of Europe</u>
<u n="198" who="S0182">well</u>
<u n="199" who="S0181">on a related note I don't think I have any photos of Glasgow which is interesting given the amount of times I have been there</u>
<u n="200" who="S0182">I've only been there once</u>
<u n="201" who="S0181">might might be a further commentary on it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0182">I have a picture of <trunc>i</trunc> of Ikebukuro here <pause dur="short"/> and it's just a picture of a guy in a Mojo Jojo outfit</u>
<u n="203" who="S0181">that is very right and proper <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0182">interesting that you have nothing</u>
<u n="205" who="S0181" trans="overlap">mojo Jojo <pause dur="short"/> you were just waiting for me to say that weren't you?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0182">no no I wasn't</u>
<u n="207" who="S0181">um</u>
<u n="208" who="S0182">I'm just I think he's advertising cars</u>
<u n="209" who="S0181">and why not</u>
<u n="210" who="S0182">indeed <pause dur="long"/> Hm <pause dur="short"/> a lot of my iPhone pictures have uh GPS coordinates embedded in them</u>
<u n="211" who="S0181" trans="overlap">it would be really  it would be really geeky to ask which kind of Mojo Jojo he was <pause dur="short"/> like which version of the series <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0182">okay what do you mean?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0181">well I mean is</u>
<u n="214" who="S0182">how would I tell?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0181">oh I don't <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to compare the character designs from the different incarnations of the series</u>
<u n="216" who="S0182">I really don't care enough to do that</u>
<u n="217" who="S0181">no it's not really worth the effort is it</u>
<u n="218" who="S0182">I've got some of Odaiba at night and I think it might have been after the Dragonforce concert or whatever it was called</u>
<u n="219" who="S0181">that was the Dragonforce <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0182">there's um trees <pause dur="short"/> I think it's sakura or maybe ume</u>
<u n="221" who="S0181">what is ume again in English?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0182">plum <pause dur="short"/> I think well it's it's not</u>
<u n="223" who="S0181">plum <pause dur="short"/> oh right like in as in umeboshi</u>
<u n="224" who="S0182">it's not  plum but it it's close enough</u>
<u n="225" who="S0181">if forced to translate it you could write Japanese plum or something</u>
<u n="226" who="S0182">mm <pause dur="short"/> or apricot <pause dur="short"/> japanese apricots <pause dur="short"/> sometimes translated as</u>
<u n="227" who="S0181">they are actually more like apricots aren't they</u>
<u n="228" who="S0182" trans="overlap">they are more like apricots yeah <pause dur="short"/> green apricots</u>
<u n="229" who="S0181">marvellous</u>
<u n="230" who="S0182">they're nothing like plums</u>
<u n="231" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0182">it's just one day someone said well plum <pause dur="short"/> and I guess they went <trunc>pf</trunc> whatever</u>
<u n="233" who="S0181">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so translating between Japanese and English is often done very badly</u>
<u n="234" who="S0182">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0181"><pause dur="long"/> Like that translation of badger thing I keep talking about</u>
<u n="236" who="S0182">uh-huh</u>
<u n="237" who="S0181">that's something else I don't have I have no photos of badgers</u>
<u n="238" who="S0182">I have never even seen a badger so</u>
<u n="239" who="S0181">really</u>
<u n="240" who="S0182">yeah never</u>
<u n="241" who="S0181">wow <pause dur="short"/> that's fascinating</u>
<u n="242" who="S0182">what do you mean that's fascinating? Why is it fascinating?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0181">well it's just kind of weird to like live in rural England and never see a badger</u>
<u n="244" who="S0182">I haven't actually lived in rural England for any length of time</u>
<u n="245" who="S0181">I suppose suppose not actually <pause dur="short"/> you don't really get urban badgers in London do you?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0182">you don't <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> so there you go <pause dur="short"/> you could try and fix that for me if you want</u>
<u n="247" who="S0181">mm <pause dur="short"/> I actually don't know how to pronounce um the scientific name of badgers which is meles or maybe meles or meles</u>
<u n="248" who="S0182">melay?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0181">M E L E S meles</u>
<u n="250" who="S0182">okay <pause dur="short"/> I don't have much to say about that unfortunately <pause dur="short"/> and now I've found</u>
<u n="251" who="S0181" trans="overlap">well it makes it difficult for me to try and explain the whole different types of badger problem if I can't even pronounce the word I want to use</u>
<u n="252" who="S0182">right <pause dur="short"/> wow I've got a picture of another special kit kat <pause dur="short"/> it's actually espresso  <trunc>Ex</trunc> uh espresso coffee <pause dur="short"/> and it's with another drink it's um Sekai No Kitchen Kara and it's caramel au lait</u>
<u n="253" who="S0181">okay</u>
<u n="254" who="S0182">it was really good <pause dur="short"/> it tasted like butter <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0181">fair enough</u>
<u n="256" who="S0182">no but that sounds when I said that to someone they thought that sounded really nasty but</u>
<u n="257" who="S0181">it certainly doesn't make it sound good</u>
<u n="258" who="S0182">but it you if you look at the back the calories is not</u>
<u n="259" who="S0181">is not</u>
<u n="260" who="S0182">not too high</u>
<u n="261" who="S0181">fair enough</u>
<u n="262" who="S0182">it's a it's less than uh a regular regular coffee even</u>
<u n="263" who="S0181">got it</u>
<u n="264" who="S0182">because probably because it's just all flavouring <pause dur="short"/> flavouring and milk <pause dur="short"/> but it was really good</u>
<u n="265" who="S0181"><pause dur="long"/> Here we go <pause dur="short"/> badgers <pause dur="short"/> here we go <pause dur="short"/> so when you say badger to a British person right</u>
<u n="266" who="S0182">uh-huh</u>
<u n="267" who="S0181">they think of the the the kind with the black and white stripy face</u>
<u n="268" who="S0182">yuh-huh</u>
<u n="269" who="S0181">which is meles meles <pause dur="short"/> okay got that?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0182">okay <pause dur="short"/> that sounds like a good name for an indie band</u>
<u n="271" who="S0181">it is <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> when most people in Japan are told to imagine like a foreign badger a non Japanese badger yeah they think of a different kind of plain brown one which is meles leucurus which is the kind you get in China and Russia <pause dur="short"/> I'm guessing that somewhere down the line some compiler of like school science textbooks wasn't very precise in their badger types</u>
<u n="272" who="S0182">that's terrible</u>
<u n="273" who="S0181">it's very terrible <pause dur="short"/> and you do get badgers in Japan which are meles anakuma</u>
<u n="274" who="S0182">anakuma</u>
<u n="275" who="S0181">anakuma</u>
<u n="276" who="S0182">oh <trunc>ha</trunc> ana would  be in  be in hole kuma <trunc>re</trunc> means bear <pause dur="short"/> hole bear</u>
<u n="277" who="S0181">hole bear <pause dur="short"/> which is quite interesting because the Japanese ones actually have like they look like they have the body of the Asian one and the sort of like European style black and white face so</u>
<u n="278" who="S0182">right</u>
<u n="279" who="S0181">the Japanese badgers actually look really similar</u>
<u n="280" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0181">to like a British badger</u>
<u n="282" who="S0182">right</u>
<u n="283" who="S0181">but the existence of British type badgers is not known to people in Japan</u>
<u n="284" who="S0182">right</u>
<u n="285" who="S0181">and it's one of those things that's really hard to explain to people because then they start punching it into their dictionary and the dictionary is giving them the wrong answer</u>
<u n="286" who="S0182">yes</u>
<u n="287" who="S0181">because it's calling up the like generic Asian one <pause dur="short"/> you get the idea</u>
<u n="288" who="S0182">I get the idea <pause dur="short"/> now  and <unclear/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0181" trans="overlap">and there are no badgers in Hokkaido</u>
<u n="290" who="S0182">that must be a very sad place</u>
<u n="291" who="S0181">yes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh I'm sorry I have to be precise here</u>
<u n="292" who="S0182">yes</u>
<u n="293" who="S0181">the one that you get in the UK is meles meles meles</u>
<u n="294" who="S0182">now that is an awesome name for an indie band</u>
<u n="295" who="S0181">yes <pause dur="short"/> you also get some other ones for example in Crete you get meles meles <trunc>ac</trunc> arcalus</u>
<u n="296" who="S0182">mm mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0181">and in like Afghanistan and you know around in the Middle East you get meles meles canescens <pause dur="short"/> these all look kind of like stripy face types <pause dur="short"/> there's the Iberian badger meles meles marianensis <pause dur="short"/> the Norwegian badger meles meles milleri which only exists in south west Norway</u>
<u n="298" who="S0182">okay</u>
<u n="299" who="S0181">there's the Rhodian badger <pause dur="short"/> yeah so there are a lot of varieties on the European stripy face type <pause dur="short"/> I'm amazed you've never seen one</u>
<u n="300" who="S0182">why?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0181">you you should go out and take nature photographs <pause dur="short"/> they're</u>
<u n="302" who="S0182">you can't</u>
<u n="303" who="S0181">they're great for selling to stock sites <pause dur="short"/> you get to lie in a ditch for four hours and then you see a badger <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> What a fun way to spend an evening</u>
<u n="304" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0181">you know I was trying to sort out my photos and I've just spent the entire time talking about badgers</u>
<u n="306" who="S0182">and I'm I'm actually getting on quite well I'm <trunc>setti</trunc> I'm sorting them by date</u>
<u n="307" who="S0181">I'm way behind where I want to be <pause dur="short"/> I'm sorting by like sort of date and location</u>
<u n="308" who="S0182">right</u>
<u n="309" who="S0181">do you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0181">so if there were sort of two distinct activities on one day they'll become two different folders</u>
<u n="312" who="S0182">yes <pause dur="short"/> same here</u>
<u n="313" who="S0181">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I'd also like to note that the honey badger is not a meles at all it's a different subspecies</u>
<u n="314" who="S0182">well honey badger don't give a shit</u>
<u n="315" who="S0181" trans="overlap"><trunc>Mellivor</trunc> suppose that was inevitable wasn't it that joke</u>
<u n="316" who="S0182">yes</u>
<u n="317" who="S0181">and the American badger is a completely different subspecies <pause dur="short"/> but it looks vaguely similar to the European badger <pause dur="short"/> presumably some settlers were short on names for things <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0182">yeah just wander round calling everything a badger <pause dur="short"/> that's a badger <pause dur="short"/> that's a badger <pause dur="short"/> that tree is a badger</u>
<u n="319" who="S0181">hey there are like four cities called Aberdeen in America <pause dur="short"/> You know</u>
<u n="320" who="S0182">mm mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0181">and what's with Perth? There are Perths in the USA and I don't uh</u>
<u n="322" who="S0182" trans="overlap">that's what I've asked myself all this time <pause dur="short"/> what is with Perth?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0181" trans="overlap">what is with Perth? Right there are Perths in the US and Canada <pause dur="short"/> there's obviously the famous one in Australia and they're all named after well Perth <pause dur="short"/> now why?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0182">not really worth it is it</u>
<u n="325" who="S0181">maybe hey <trunc>m</trunc> maybe that solves the mystery <pause dur="short"/> maybe Perth used to be a much bigger place and then everyone left to go and live in Australia and the US and that's why it's become the sort of through through route that it is now</u>
<u n="326" who="S0182">maybe they turned up there and just went this is just as shitty as it was back home <pause dur="short"/> I think I'll call it Perth <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0181">no I reckon Perth might have been <pause dur="short"/> in fact Perth is quite nice it's just there's nothing there <pause dur="short"/> it's it's a place that you go through on the way to somewhere else</u>
<u n="328" who="S0182" trans="overlap">which is just like America when they first arrived</u>
<u n="329" who="S0181">without stopping <pause dur="short"/> you stop when you go and colonise America right</u>
<u n="330" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0181">but in Perth you just drive through without stopping <pause dur="short"/> that's what that's all there is <pause dur="short"/> it is a mystery</u>
<u n="332" who="S0182"><trunc>I</trunc></u>
<u n="333" who="S0181">maybe in the distant past when people had to travel more slowly they all stopped in Perth <pause dur="short"/> it's my new theory</u>
<u n="334" who="S0182">and I have a picture of Mushi-shi which was a movie that was out on the twenty-fourth of March <pause dur="short"/> dunno what year <pause dur="short"/> it's from the director of well the director had something to do with Akira and Steam Boy</u>
<u n="335" who="S0181">okay</u>
<u n="336" who="S0182">and it starred Odagiri Jocirc <pause dur="short"/> I never saw it <pause dur="short"/> I'd still like to though <pause dur="short"/> and do you know what the kanji for mushi is?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0181">no</u>
<u n="338" who="S0182">well you know what the kanji for regular mushi is?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0181">yes</u>
<u n="340" who="S0182">well it's just three of them <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0181">oh</u>
<u n="342" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0181">particularly large and impressive insect then</u>
<u n="344" who="S0182">I guess <pause dur="short"/> well I think it's spirit in this case</u>
<u n="345" who="S0181">I wish you could do that in English <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0182">like <trunc>y</trunc> you'd have like the word for cat and then you'd repeat it three times cat cat cat and that would mean a tiger</u>
<u n="347" who="S0181">exactly <pause dur="short"/> how convenient would that <trunc>no</trunc> would that not be convenient?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0182"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It would yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0181">I also don't seem to have any photographs of tigers here which is a shame cos I know I have some photographs of tigers somewhere</u>
<u n="350" who="S0182">you were very excited <pause dur="short"/> I saw in the Natural History Museum I saw well it was a stuffed tiger but it was actually a hybrid tiger of two different types of tiger and its paws were so big <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0181">what do you call it when you hybridise tigers cos you know if you cross breed like a lion and a tiger it's called a liger</u>
<u n="352" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0181">very bit of obvious portmanteau assembly there</u>
<u n="354" who="S0182">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0181">but if you cross breed a tiger and a tiger we're gonna call it a <trunc>t</trunc> a tiger</u>
<u n="356" who="S0182">tiger</u>
<u n="357" who="S0181">oh <pause dur="short"/> curses</u>
<u n="358" who="S0182">but anyway <pause dur="short"/> that is what I saw</u>
<u n="359" who="S0181">so apparently if you cross breed a tiger and a different kind of tiger you get a tiger with massive paws</u>
<u n="360" who="S0182">well I don't know it might just have been <vocal desc="laugh"/> what a tiger looks like</u>
<u n="361" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You're not experienced with tigers</u>
<u n="362" who="S0182">well I can't remember the last time I went to the zoo cos I thought about going to Ueno but Ueno is a sad place</u>
<u n="363" who="S0181">mm mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0182">all the animals look unhappy</u>
<u n="365" who="S0181" trans="overlap">so I met this cross bred tiger</u>
<u n="366" who="S0182">right</u>
<u n="367" who="S0181">and I said to him what's it like being a cross bred tiger and he said well I have huge paws <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0182">I hate you</u>
<u n="369" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's funny man</u>
<u n="370" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0181">that is a classic of comedy</u>
<u n="372" who="S0182"><pause dur="long"/> Got one of Tanabata here</u>
<u n="373" who="S0181">which Tanabata?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0182">well Tanabata Tanabata in July</u>
<u n="375" who="S0181">like like no particular year just a random</u>
<u n="376" who="S0182">oh two thousand and six Tanabata</u>
<u n="377" who="S0181"><trunc>r</trunc> random random festival <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0182">just of all the wishes hanging on the trees <pause dur="long"/> And actually now I can actually read one of them it says I wish to win the lottery</u>
<u n="379" who="S0181">what a heart warming wish</u>
<u n="380" who="S0182">I wish to win the lottery</u>
<u n="381" who="S0181">I think you have to buy a ticket first</u>
<u n="382" who="S0182">well actually Mum buys a ticket every week</u>
<u n="383" who="S0181">yeah but doesn't mean she'd give us anything if she won</u>
<u n="384" who="S0182">well it depends</u>
<u n="385" who="S0181" trans="overlap">did you help her pick numbers this time?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0182">I did actually</u>
<u n="387" who="S0181">you've gotta do that</u>
<u n="388" who="S0182">I usually try not to pick them rhythmically so I I don't like go this then this then this and a certain number in each column because I tend to bunch them up together cos the balls tend to fall that way <pause dur="short"/> which means I am actually thinking about the potential possibility of maybe winning</u>
<u n="389" who="S0181"><trunc>Y</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc> you understand that none of that is true if you see what I mean</u>
<u n="390" who="S0182">well</u>
<u n="391" who="S0181">like <trunc>l</trunc> analysing historical data for numbers etcetera for the lottery doesn't actually do anything</u>
<u n="392" who="S0182">yeah but they do bunch up <pause dur="short"/> they don't  they don't  fall like one in the zero column one in the ones twenties thirties forties</u>
<u n="393" who="S0181">it it appears that way <pause dur="short"/> but the net distribution is random</u>
<u n="394" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0181">random</u>
<u n="396" who="S0182">I know that</u>
<u n="397" who="S0181">oh I just found a whole series of photographs I took of a cat sitting on top of the offering box at a temple in Kyoto</u>
<u n="398" who="S0182">that sounds like you</u>
<u n="399" who="S0181">they're great pictures <pause dur="short"/> something you never see in the UK is it <pause dur="short"/> you never go into a church and there's a cat sitting on the altar <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0182">that is very true</u>
<u n="401" who="S0181"><pause dur="long"/> Hey now there's an idea</u>
<u n="402" who="S0182">oh no you're not gonna do that again</u>
<u n="403" who="S0181">we have a cat</u>
<u n="404" who="S0182">priests don't like cats as much as you do</u>
<u n="405" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> we're talking about stock photos and everyone takes the same old things right</u>
<u n="406" who="S0182">uh-huh</u>
<u n="407" who="S0181">I bet none of the sites have a cat standing on a church altar</u>
<u n="408" who="S0182">you are actually doing exactly what I thought you were doing</u>
<u n="409" who="S0181"><unclear/> it's just a great idea I mean I'm sure lots of people could use that to illustrate their you know it could be allegorical in some way <pause dur="short"/> or just cute</u>
<u n="410" who="S0182">it could advertise church bingo nights</u>
<u n="411" who="S0181">do churches really have bingo nights I mean really</u>
<u n="412" who="S0182" trans="overlap">in <trunc>y</trunc> just ask Mum</u>
<u n="413" who="S0181">does she go to church bingo nights?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0182">she goes to pretty much anything the church does</u>
<u n="415" who="S0181">do I have to start being nice about bingo now?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0182">um actually I don't think she really likes bingo <pause dur="short"/> I think she'd see it as a sign as of getting old</u>
<u n="417" who="S0181">well it is <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> She's she would be <trunc>q</trunc></u>
<u n="418" who="S0182">well not any more</u>
<u n="419" who="S0181">she would be quite correct in that assessment <pause dur="short"/> what do you mean not any more?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0182">well <pause dur="short"/> it seems to be a young person's sport now</u>
<u n="421" who="S0181">if you're drunk</u>
<u n="422" who="S0182">well basically going out having a drink and maybe you get a chance to win some money I mean I <trunc>ca</trunc> I can't really fault that <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather play poker though</u>
<u n="423" who="S0181">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um well that's the whole thing I I guess it's just like <trunc>y</trunc> you can get the same thing by playing poker of course if you're sitting there and drinking you're totally losing while you're playing poker but you you can still have fun</u>
<u n="424" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0181">and drink and have a chance to win some money although a a lower chance because you're drinking and someone there isn't but I guess the main difference there is poker is a bit classier than bingo right <pause dur="short"/> you you expect people to have a higher standard of dress in a casino</u>
<u n="426" who="S0182" trans="overlap">but you have a greater chance of losing money <pause dur="short"/> I mean once you've paid your money for bingo you can't lose any more it's like a fixed rate</u>
<u n="427" who="S0181" trans="overlap">it's just bingo halls are just so grim</u>
<u n="428" who="S0182">do you know that for a fact?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0181">Don't you remember the one we walked past in <anon type="place"/> with the photo outside of the you know the <trunc>ad</trunc> the the supposedly advertising poster</u>
<u n="430" who="S0182">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> I've always found that pictures of</u>
<u n="431" who="S0181"><trunc>W</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> it was really like it's like are you an aging working class woman</u>
<u n="432" who="S0182">pictures of  people on their nights out look crap</u>
<u n="433" who="S0181">but but those ones</u>
<u n="434" who="S0182" trans="overlap">they only mean anything to people who were there at the time</u>
<u n="435" who="S0181">they they they were supposed to be marketing their place and they've got these photographs of these people and it's like are you an aging working class woman? Drown your sorrows with bingo <pause dur="short"/> they they just could've just chosen</u>
<u n="436" who="S0182">okay</u>
<u n="437" who="S0181">much better models you know</u>
<u n="438" who="S0182">well I think they were actually taking picture of</u>
<u n="439" who="S0181">for example</u>
<u n="440" who="S0182">of people having fun saying you could have fun too like this or you could still get a picture</u>
<u n="441" who="S0181" trans="overlap">do you have a terrible fake tan? It's like you can make a case for photographing natural people and you can make a <trunc>f</trunc> case for photographing you know professional models and you can make a case for like heavily heavily photoshoping your image to make people look better but why would you take a picture of someone who's painted themselves orange?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0182">clearly you've never seen Charlie and the Chocolate Factory</u>
<u n="443" who="S0181">well yes exactly <pause dur="long"/> Maybe I'm just cynical <pause dur="short"/> I have all</u>
<u n="444" who="S0182">with everything</u>
<u n="445" who="S0181">these beach photos here but all the beach photos I've ever taken seem to be rain</u>
<u n="446" who="S0182">I've got some really nice pictures of the um of the</u>
<u n="447" who="S0181">it's just always raining in beach photos</u>
<u n="448" who="S0182">sunset reflecting in the kind of wash in in the sea</u>
<u n="449" who="S0181">yeah <pause dur="short"/> actually I'm exaggerating for comic effect <pause dur="short"/> it's snowing in several of my beach photos <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0182">mm <pause dur="short"/> it was snowing very hard in um <anon type="place"/> one day and actually I decided to take a walk when  I came  I came across a surfer coming back from the beach <pause dur="short"/> he looked pretty cold <pause dur="short"/> all wet suit and everything</u>
<u n="451" who="S0181">one would presume he was pretty cold</u>
<u n="452" who="S0182">and here I have taken a picture of pudding in a can <pause dur="short"/> it's called pud in shape</u>
<u n="453" who="S0181">what is it? Is it actually like creme caramel or is it some other flavour?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0182" trans="overlap">yeah it's <trunc>cre</trunc> creme <trunc>camera</trunc> caramel in a can you shake it up and I guess there's some kind of a reaction and it the drink kind of goes hard a bit and it's kind of puddingy</u>
<u n="455" who="S0181">that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0182">I'm very impressed</u>
<u n="457" who="S0181">and they mean interesting in the sort of polite way of saying that is a terrible and hideous thing</u>
<u n="458" who="S0182"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh <pause dur="short"/> well obviously I drank it</u>
<u n="459" who="S0181">was it good?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0182">mm it's not bad</u>
<u n="461" who="S0181">I got pretty much put off all the whole sort of like you know jelly in can kind of drinks and all those</u>
<u n="462" who="S0182">mm mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0181">kind of things did I tell you that story?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0182">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="465" who="S0181">well I went to buy some Dr Pepper from this vending machine</u>
<u n="466" who="S0182" trans="overlap">oh you got the wrong one and you got <trunc>alo</trunc> aloe vera in it <unclear/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0181" trans="overlap">yeah the vending machine was misloaded and I got this aloe vera drink so I thought well I have it now <pause dur="short"/> what I didn't realise it was aloe vera with lumps of jelly inside it</u>
<u n="468" who="S0182">no it wasn't lumps of jelly it's it's lumps of aloe</u>
<u n="469" who="S0181">well that's worse</u>
<u n="470" who="S0182">is it?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0181">but because I wasn't expecting any such thing it was quite a shock <pause dur="long"/> I think it wasn't actual lumps of like the plant aloe</u>
<u n="472" who="S0182">I believe it is some some are edible some aren't <pause dur="short"/> since you asked</u>
<u n="473" who="S0181">I hope it was the edible kind</u>
<u n="474" who="S0182">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> although I think there was a slight scandal a few years back when people starting putting lumps of aloe in that weren't the edible type and were actually slightly poisonous</u>
<u n="475" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/> A slight scandal</u>
<u n="476" who="S0182">well you know there's a <trunc>s</trunc> food scandal every year or so</u>
<u n="477" who="S0181">that's true yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0182">think people were a little bit embarrassed that it wasn't from China this time <pause dur="short"/> oh I've got a picture of you in some kind of Izakaya I think <pause dur="short"/> oh on on the boat</u>
<u n="479" who="S0181">what the <trunc>n</trunc> nova work party</u>
<u n="480" who="S0182">yep that's the one <pause dur="short"/> wow I must've been really drunk cos it does not look good at all</u>
<u n="481" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I like how when you have a terrible photo of me you politely assume you're drunk and a bad photographer rather than I'm drunk and look terrible</u>
<u n="482" who="S0182">no no not that you look terrible <pause dur="short"/> the food you're cooking looks terrible</u>
<u n="483" who="S0181">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> well it was um was it okonomiyaki</u>
<u n="484" who="S0182">yes it was</u>
<u n="485" who="S0181">were you you cook it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0182">yeah it does I guess it does look terrible as a raw</u>
<u n="487" who="S0181">yep it does look terrible</u>
<u n="488" who="S0182"><pause dur="long"/> Mind you the dessert one I think wasn't it monjayaki <pause dur="short"/> there's a</u>
<u n="489" who="S0181">I can never remember the difference</u>
<u n="490" who="S0182">uh there was <pause dur="short"/> but the dessert monjayaki was really good <pause dur="short"/> although by the end I had actually drunk quite a lot so maybe it wasn't that good <pause dur="long"/> I've got a cooking class</u>
<u n="491" who="S0181">mm mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0182">these are from Autumn two thousand and seven by the way</u>
<u n="493" who="S0181">just everything so far</u>
<u n="494" who="S0182">well no just this this block of stuff <pause dur="short"/> although Tanamata was two thousand and six</u>
<u n="495" who="S0181">got it</u>
<u n="496" who="S0182"><pause dur="long"/> Gonna turn the light on</u>
<u n="497" who="S0181">Good idea</u>
<u n="498" who="S0182"><pause dur="long"/> Shall I close the curtains too or?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0181">um yeah go ahead <pause dur="short"/> actually no don't bother <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>n</trunc> no it's nowhere near dark outside</u>
<u n="500" who="S0182">but it's dark in here</u>
<u n="501" who="S0181">yeah but can still leave the curtains open</u>
<u n="502" who="S0182">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0181">light is healthy</u>
<u n="504" who="S0182">alright <pause dur="short"/> do you wanna make more coffee?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0181">um yes it's gonna take a while to sort through all of these and I've also somehow mis-sorted a whole bunch of them</u>
<u n="506" who="S0182">I'm gonna do about three folders a day which will probably take long enough</u>
<u n="507" who="S0181">it will take quite some time yes</u>
<u n="508" who="S0182">well I'm getting to P now</u>
<u n="509" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0182">no  as in  as in P in the alphabet P</u>
<u n="511" who="S0181"><trunc>Y</trunc> yeah I I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I got it I was just amused</u>
<u n="512" who="S0182">and P is full of <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0181"><vocal desc="laugh"/> A problem here my photo folders are full of pee</u>
<u n="514" who="S0182"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well no P P is <vocal desc="laugh"/> basically that has photographs photos photos two photos</u>
<u n="515" who="S0181" trans="overlap">oh you named your folders photo photos <trunc>pho</trunc></u>
<u n="516" who="S0182">yeah well you you did when you found all those folders all over the place</u>
<u n="517" who="S0181" trans="overlap">that's right when when I was compiling all of the stuff that you'd just sort of</u>
<u n="518" who="S0182">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0181">stashed  like a  like a photo squirrel</u>
<u n="520" who="S0182"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I'm searching through those now <pause dur="short"/> removing duplicates</u>
<u n="521" who="S0181">the photographer may be considered as similar to the squirrel in behaviour</u>
<u n="522" who="S0182">uh-huh</u>
<u n="523" who="S0181">in storing up stock imagery for the winter <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0182"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's true</u>
<u n="525" who="S0181"><pause dur="long"/> Yeah it will take me many more hours to sort through the rest of these so maybe some coffee would be good eh</u>
<u n="526" who="S0182">are you telling me to make it?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0181">no I'm just observing it would be a good idea</u>
<u n="528" who="S0182">okay well let me just finish off this folder and then I will go and make it then</u>
<u n="529" who="S0181">okay well I might come and help actually</u>
<u n="530" who="S0182">right</u>
<u n="531" who="S0181">or get some other stuff done</u>
</body>
</text>
