<text id="ST64">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:29</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0012 S0013</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>no info</topics>
		<activity>no info</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0012">
				<exactage>70</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessey, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mattishal, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0013">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow, Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Childminder (retired)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0012">I've had a good day while you've been <trunc>de</trunc> gallivanting out playing</u>
<u n="2" who="S0013">have you?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0012">yes I have I've mowed all the lawns is it all the lawns? yeah I've mowed the greenhouse the orchard the play area and</u>
<u n="4" who="S0013">the main lawn</u>
<u n="5" who="S0012">the main lawn which is about over half an acre of walking <pause dur="short"/> more than that</u>
<u n="6" who="S0013">yeah I suppose it is</u>
<u n="7" who="S0012">about an acre of walking</u>
<u n="8" who="S0013"><unclear/> something?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0012">yeah well we've got</u>
<u n="10" who="S0013">lawn</u>
<u n="11" who="S0012">yeah that's just lawn <pause dur="short"/> we had more when we did the front garden</u>
<u n="12" who="S0013">do you reckon so?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0012">that was all lawn</u>
<u n="14" who="S0013">it can't be quite half an acre can it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0012">well of course it is if you if you think we've got we've got about two and seven eighths isn't it? or nearly two hectares</u>
<u n="16" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah mm well I should think one is the field isn't it</u>
<u n="17" who="S0012">yeah there's a there's</u>
<u n="18" who="S0013">or three quarters of it</u>
<u n="19" who="S0012">yeah I don't really know how much it is but</u>
<u n="20" who="S0013">it's a lot that is a lot</u>
<u n="21" who="S0012">it <trunc>fe</trunc> it feels like three hundred miles but there you go oh</u>
<u n="22" who="S0013">here you are</u>
<u n="23" who="S0012">it keeps you fit</u>
<u n="24" who="S0013">oh lift your hand up arm? what have you done to your arm?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0012">oh I just slit it open</u>
<u n="26" who="S0013">no you haven't have you?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0012">yeah that that that was the bramble that went <vocal desc="misc"/> right across my arm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0013">gosh that looks</u>
<u n="29" who="S0012">it looks like a really good</u>
<u n="30" who="S0013">that's about six inches</u>
<u n="31" who="S0012">yeah no three three <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come on three inches</u>
<u n="32" who="S0013">it looks horrible</u>
<u n="33" who="S0012">I haven't got a six inch arm <pause dur="short"/> oh I I weren't really going to have a chocolate biscuit</u>
<u n="34" who="S0013">oh I'll put it away then</u>
<u n="35" who="S0012">no I'll eat it now you'll give it to me cos</u>
<u n="36" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0012">sugar diabetes is the is the thing that you've got to look out for at my age</u>
<u n="38" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="39" who="S0012">so they say oh <pause dur="short"/> well who put them on there?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0013">oh you really ought to come out and see the sheep you know <pause dur="short"/> all the way down <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0012">well I had too much to do you went gallivanting</u>
<u n="42" who="S0013">thirty-seven sheep there are in the village</u>
<u n="43" who="S0012">that's really brilliant</u>
<u n="44" who="S0013">it is isn't it</u>
<u n="45" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0013">and some of them are so good <pause dur="short"/> that includes the two real ones</u>
<u n="47" who="S0012">pardon?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0013">that includes the two real ones</u>
<u n="49" who="S0012">who who had the real ones?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0013"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0012">oh of course she would wouldn't she</u>
<u n="52" who="S0013">yeah penned up outside <pause dur="short"/> they've been ever so good</u>
<u n="53" who="S0012">well why didn't we go in for it?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0013">why what?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0012">why didn't we do a sheep?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0013">it's well were <unclear/> weren't we <pause dur="short"/> we got too busy with other things</u>
<u n="57" who="S0012">everything happens at once doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> that's a real problem</u>
<u n="58" who="S0013">some of them are very inventive</u>
<u n="59" who="S0012">well we could have done a sheep I could have stood out there dressed up as <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="60" who="S0013">some are just wooden heads you know</u>
<u n="61" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0013">and some are kind of well <pause dur="short"/> well there's so many different things there's even one just with a black bin liner which doesn't look very good <pause dur="short"/> but it's a black sheep</u>
<u n="63" who="S0012">but I could have actually stood out there looking sheepish</u>
<u n="64" who="S0013">no no that's not the idea <pause dur="short"/> mind you there's one down <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> road <pause dur="short"/> they've put a a boy's face on it which is not very nice</u>
<u n="65" who="S0012">yeah well he looks sheepish</u>
<u n="66" who="S0013">yeah he looks he's was hanging hanging over the fence <pause dur="short"/> I didn't like that one <pause dur="short"/> a bit creepy</u>
<u n="67" who="S0012">no it's fun it's not creepy</u>
<u n="68" who="S0013">yeah no that one was quite creepy</u>
<u n="69" who="S0012">was it?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0013">you'll know what I mean mm <pause dur="short"/> it's like you're being <trunc>hu</trunc> the boy was being hung <pause dur="short"/> cos it was like a a woolly jumper on as well</u>
<u n="71" who="S0012">that would have been a good one <pause dur="short"/> just hang a jumper outside there and a and a and a big high jump thing</u>
<u n="72" who="S0013">a big what?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0012">a high jump right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0012">and then a woolly jumper</u>
<u n="76" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0012">on a spring</u>
<u n="78" who="S0013">no head?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0012">no it's just a woolly jumper</u>
<u n="80" who="S0013">oh gosh</u>
<u n="81" who="S0012">god come on keep up keep up</u>
<u n="82" who="S0013">I don't know if they checked out these sheep before they went up <pause dur="short"/> they all have numbers and they all have letters and you have to collect up all the letters and rearrange it to make a saying</u>
<u n="83" who="S0012">a wolf in sheep's clothing?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0013">could be <pause dur="short"/> well that's a good idea isn't cos</u>
<u n="85" who="S0012">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="86" who="S0013">like someone was saying it it really gets you to see <anon type="place"/> because they're talking about all the different roads so many different roads and so widespread</u>
<u n="87" who="S0012">I know <anon type="place"/> is</u>
<u n="88" who="S0013">I mean to be right up here and right down er er down <anon type="place"/> way</u>
<u n="89" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0013">that's a lot isn't it</u>
<u n="91" who="S0012">yeah it is a lot and it's you know you have one thousand and well over one I don't know whether it's one thousand three hundred or one thousand five hundred dwellings <pause dur="short"/> and if if you put two people to each dwelling that's three thousand people in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0013">yeah it is quite big</u>
<u n="93" who="S0012">so I don't know whether I'm right or wrong but I think there's about one thousand one hundred <trunc>pe</trunc> er dwellings in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0012">that will still make three people two thousand two hundred doesn't it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0012">but they think there's three thousand people in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="99" who="S0012">well that's because <trunc>i</trunc> if you think of two and a half people or three and a half people to one household</u>
<u n="100" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0012">cos <anon type="place"/> school is about five hundred pupils in that</u>
<u n="102" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0012">isn't there</u>
<u n="104" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0012">it's quite a lot</u>
<u n="106" who="S0013">I saw erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s daughter</u>
<u n="107" who="S0012">did you? what was she up to?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0013">she was doing a stall but she was so busy I</u>
<u n="109" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="110" who="S0013">couldn't <pause dur="short"/> I think it was it fish for sheep or something like that <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what that one was they had all sorts there <pause dur="short"/> it was really good</u>
<u n="111" who="S0012">why didn't you ever go?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0013">well I've had a go at the cakes tombola</u>
<u n="113" who="S0012">why didn't you make me come with you?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0013">I tried <pause dur="short"/> everyone says why didn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0012">and what did you say?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0013">he didn't want to</u>
<u n="117" who="S0012">you didn't tell them that did you?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0012">you wicked woman I did want to</u>
<u n="120" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="121" who="S0012">I was too busy</u>
<u n="122" who="S0013">I they asked me what you're busy doing and I told them <pause dur="short"/> right I told them you were busy setting up a workshop</u>
<u n="123" who="S0012">oh you're <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> now I'm not going to be loved in <anon type="place"/> any more <pause dur="short"/> cos you couldn't lie</u>
<u n="124" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/> erm did I tell you about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="126" who="S0013">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is now doing a travel and tourism course at <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> college</u>
<u n="127" who="S0012">wow is she?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0013">but erm she did say she was getting a bit bored because they aren't that many lessons and I said I told her about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and how she skipped lots of lessons as well</u>
<u n="129" who="S0012">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0013">because there wasn't enough going on so I just told to watch out for that <pause dur="short"/> but she just thinks she wants to do more so she won't be hopefully and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is very keen on dramatics of course</u>
<u n="131" who="S0012">yeah well she always was</u>
<u n="132" who="S0013">and she's been asked to do plays and and do a lot of singing in it</u>
<u n="133" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0013">she said she's too nervous but she'll be alright</u>
<u n="135" who="S0012">no she she did lots of stuff with us didn't she when she was here</u>
<u n="136" who="S0013">she did didn't she</u>
<u n="137" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you could see where she was going in life but I thought <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was going the wildlife way</u>
<u n="138" who="S0013">yeah well I asked about that so she said she was she's still very keen on er <pause dur="short"/> on wildlife and that but they don't go out so much at the weekends now <pause dur="short"/> cos of petrol and stuff they're finding it difficult <pause dur="short"/> she's still on her own but kind of with <pause dur="short"/> do you remember the fireman at that fancy dress party?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0013">I <trunc>j</trunc> she said I only have to say do you know the fireman? and everyone seems to remember the fireman obviously</u>
<u n="141" who="S0012">yeah well cos he looked like erm him off</u>
<u n="142" who="S0013">a bit like Robson Green</u>
<u n="143" who="S0012">Robson Green didn't he he looked like him didn't he? <pause dur="short"/> and everyone fell in love with him immediately</u>
<u n="144" who="S0013" trans="overlap">and er he was very good looking anyway wasn't he</u>
<u n="145" who="S0012">well you fell in love with him</u>
<u n="146" who="S0013">well perhaps the universe perhaps the uniform again</u>
<u n="147" who="S0012">well it is the uniform isn't it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0013">but anyway she's she's she's known him for about fourteen years and they've seeing each other properly but he lives in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> he used to he came from Wales for that party</u>
<u n="149" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0013">right she that's how long she's know him so they've been keeping in touch since that</u>
<u n="151" who="S0012" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="152" who="S0013">but he lives in <anon type="place"/> so they see each other well at least once a month she said but the girls love him of course because they've always known him</u>
<u n="153" who="S0012">yeah and he's a lovely bloke</u>
<u n="154" who="S0013">he hasn't got any children <pause dur="short"/> always wanted children so <pause dur="short"/> it seems quite quite good</u>
<u n="155" who="S0012">well maybe he should get in touch with a younger <trunc>bir</trunc> person</u>
<u n="156" who="S0013">what?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0012">well she's too late to have children now isn't she <pause dur="short"/> more</u>
<u n="158" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="159" who="S0012">I'm talking about whether he want one of his own or not</u>
<u n="160" who="S0013">oh no I don't think so cos he's got the same age now and <pause dur="short"/> ah anyway they're seeing each other and they're very happy</u>
<u n="161" who="S0012">oh that's good</u>
<u n="162" who="S0013">even though it's only one a month <pause dur="short"/> roughly</u>
<u n="163" who="S0012">that's yeah well that's enough to see anyone</u>
<u n="164" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0013">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0012">yeah well what did they used to say? <pause dur="short"/> once a night always a night once a month enough</u>
<u n="168" who="S0013">right oh</u>
<u n="169" who="S0012">it's true isn't it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0013">or don't you believe that? I don't know if that was the right one the right word</u>
<u n="171" who="S0012">it's not the right one but I've I've put my my cape on my my</u>
<u n="172" who="S0013" trans="overlap">adapted it yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0012">slant on it</u>
<u n="174" who="S0013">yeah anyway she's seems very happy and that's oh it was really nice to have a chat because she erm I said oh hello she just said she caught me cos I'm just eating this <trunc>ca</trunc> great big cake</u>
<u n="175" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0013">I said I'm just taking a break I'm supposed to be doing the er promoting</u>
<u n="177" who="S0012" trans="overlap">taking a break eating a cake</u>
<u n="178" who="S0013">promoting the er <pause dur="short"/> enterprise place</u>
<u n="179" who="S0012">oh yeah she works there doesn't she</u>
<u n="180" who="S0013">yeah so she's in her she got a top thing</u>
<u n="181" who="S0012">oh right she works there</u>
<u n="182" who="S0013"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0012">oh wow</u>
<u n="186" who="S0013">so I actually I held her up for quite a long time and they don't have <trunc>pre</trunc> her colleague had to do it all by himself</u>
<u n="187" who="S0012">well that wasn't</u>
<u n="188" who="S0013">by herself <pause dur="short"/> and so yeah she said oh you caught me <pause dur="short"/> sit down <pause dur="short"/> so I sat down cos she happened to be at the table which was kind of nice</u>
<u n="189" who="S0012">well she would be eating a cake</u>
<u n="190" who="S0013">no I just happened to be next to her stall I don't know</u>
<u n="191" who="S0012">oh I see right yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0013">it wasn't wasn't the cakey bit if you see what I mean <pause dur="short"/> not where they were selling them</u>
<u n="193" who="S0012">oh right she'd already bought it</u>
<u n="194" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0012">and took it to her table</u>
<u n="196" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0012">ah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0013">so I had a nice long chat with her</u>
<u n="199" who="S0012">well she's a lovely lady</u>
<u n="200" who="S0013">she is nice isn't she</u>
<u n="201" who="S0012">yeah she is <pause dur="short"/> she's had a hard life</u>
<u n="202" who="S0013">yeah oh she and she told me about their dad as well <pause dur="short"/> she said he's coming over to see them at Christmas <pause dur="short"/> but er <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she cos because we're not connected now I think she feels like she can talk a bit more about that type of thing</u>
<u n="203" who="S0012">probably yeah yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0013">anyway because er you know <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a bit more reserved but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still thinks he's the most wonderful person in the world <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="205" who="S0012">well she would do because she's young now</u>
<u n="206" who="S0013">well she would do yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0013">but they they always they always get so excited when they find out he's coming over to see them and then then it all goes wrong and they're so disillusioned and it all goes wrong again <pause dur="short"/> and they sort of</u>
<u n="209" who="S0012">well that's because they expect too much probably</u>
<u n="210" who="S0013">probably is</u>
<u n="211" who="S0012">I mean <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>if you think of what these families that are separated have to do <pause dur="short"/> the bloke actually takes people takes their his children to cos never that's never the bloke that's that's erm got <unclear/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's sad isn't it not usually no</u>
<u n="213" who="S0012">with the children no</u>
<u n="214" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0012">so the bloke has to come along and he has to treat them doesn't he</u>
<u n="216" who="S0013">yes</u>
<u n="217" who="S0012">cos he only sees them probably once a week or</u>
<u n="218" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0012">if he's lucky so he treats them and then he becomes the <trunc>wo</trunc> most wonderful person in the world</u>
<u n="220" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0012">because the others <pause dur="short"/> they're just the mundane life you go to school you get up in the morning you have to you have to get dressed and you do all this that and the other and and you have the the ordinary bit of life <pause dur="short"/> whereas the dad comes along once or twice once a week or whenever and treats them to a circus or a a zoo or a show and he gets the best he gets he gets the points doesn't he</u>
<u n="222" who="S0013" trans="overlap">he does in general <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0012">he gets the points and you know they look forward to it</u>
<u n="224" who="S0013">and mum has to say <pause dur="short"/> clean up your room</u>
<u n="225" who="S0012" trans="overlap">and mum has to say come one clean up your room get on with your life</u>
<u n="226" who="S0013" trans="overlap">help help us with the washing up and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="227" who="S0012">yeah and they go oh dad isn't like that <pause dur="short"/> dad take us here dad take us there <pause dur="short"/> but the boot on the other foot would be <pause dur="short"/> mum taking them everywhere and dad doing the mundane jobs like er taking them to school and getting them dressed and doing all that business</u>
<u n="228" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0012">you know it's just it's just</u>
<u n="230" who="S0013">but in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s case because he's in <anon type="place"/> isn't he</u>
<u n="231" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0013">and they get so excited and then <pause dur="short"/> it's he's he doesn't do the nice things <pause dur="short"/> like they're expecting I suppose</u>
<u n="233" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="234" who="S0013">he's not the wonderful person that</u>
<u n="235" who="S0012">kids have got too much expectations anyway haven't they</u>
<u n="236" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0012">I mean you have only got to <trunc>b</trunc> think about Christmas <pause dur="short"/> and they have all these wonderful wonderful</u>
<u n="238" who="S0013">well it is like that with ordinary families isn't it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0012">well it is</u>
<u n="240" who="S0013">at Christmas you think oh it will be great to see so and so again and that and then they either turn up boring or</u>
<u n="241" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> well that's like when we <trunc>ha</trunc> when you have parties and stuff like that</u>
<u n="242" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0012">I mean I went to the class of fifty-nine <pause dur="short"/> nineteen fifty-nine <pause dur="short"/> right and I went to this this reunion I knew well I knew about three people and all the rest of them were old and I looked at them and thought</u>
<u n="244" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0012">did I ever know you? did I ever? I I can't remember you I <trunc>kno</trunc> I I remembered about three people because I've kept in contact with them since we left school</u>
<u n="246" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0012">you know</u>
<u n="248" who="S0013">otherwise it's a huge gap isn't it</u>
<u n="249" who="S0012">that's a massive gap you you think of <trunc>fif</trunc> nineteen fifty-nine to the year two thousand <pause dur="short"/> that's that's forty-one years</u>
<u n="250" who="S0013">and you're talking about from about fifteen</u>
<u n="251" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0013">from fifteen onwards well you change dramatically fifteen to thirty don't</u>
<u n="253" who="S0012">god you have yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0013">I mean fifteen to twenty even</u>
<u n="255" who="S0012">but there there there is one regret I have about that about not meeting my headmaster Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who was an absolute fantastic bloke and er <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to thank him for what he did for me</u>
<u n="256" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0012">but of course I never got round to it <pause dur="short"/> you don't think of that do you until until it's too late</u>
<u n="258" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no you don't</u>
<u n="259" who="S0012">it's like that's like telling your father you love him</u>
<u n="260" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0012">which no bloke ever does</u>
<u n="262" who="S0013">or or anyone <unclear/> anything anyone</u>
<u n="263" who="S0012">or yeah you know</u>
<u n="264" who="S0013">you don't you don't do it otherwise they think what's wrong?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you don't think <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0013">I don't know why they</u>
<u n="267" who="S0012">you can tell your mother you love her but your father is just a different thing isn't it <pause dur="short"/> my dad well</u>
<u n="268" who="S0013">oh I don't know not really but like if if you haven't done it most of your life</u>
<u n="269" who="S0012">well we didn't even send birthday cards Christmas cards or anything</u>
<u n="270" who="S0013">no we didn't did we</u>
<u n="271" who="S0012">no we didn't <pause dur="short"/> we just we just did Christmas we did we didn't do birthdays</u>
<u n="272" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0012">and <pause dur="short"/> really when when you when you get down to the nitty-gritty there's no need to do birthdays</u>
<u n="274" who="S0013">yes there is</u>
<u n="275" who="S0012">no well just cos yours is coming up on the <anon type="dateOfBirth"/> and and you have to remind me or somebody else does <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will ding ding it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday <pause dur="short"/> don't forget</u>
<u n="276" who="S0013">how many times did she? got in touch with you in the holiday</u>
<u n="277" who="S0012">oh she did <pause dur="short"/> don't forget well I did remember didn't I</u>
<u n="278" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="279" who="S0012">I did I made you a card</u>
<u n="280" who="S0013">on on a piece of scrap paper yes</u>
<u n="281" who="S0012">that's the only paper I had</u>
<u n="282" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0012">what do you want me to do? go out</u>
<u n="284" who="S0013">don't know</u>
<u n="285" who="S0012">go out to <anon type="place"/> and buy erm buy you a card and when we were fifty miles away from any</u>
<u n="286" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0012">anywhere at all?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0013">but you knew we were going <trunc>h</trunc> on holiday with my birthday time</u>
<u n="289" who="S0012">yeah but that your birthday came in the middle of the holiday</u>
<u n="290" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0012">and I made you a lovely card</u>
<u n="292" who="S0013">no excuse</u>
<u n="293" who="S0012">and I gave you a beautiful present</u>
<u n="294" who="S0013">sample bottles of shampoo and conditioner</u>
<u n="295" who="S0012">and you paid for them</u>
<u n="296" who="S0013">about fifteen mil <pause dur="short"/> and I paid for them</u>
<u n="297" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0013">yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0012">well you had to I didn't</u>
<u n="300" who="S0013">that's that that has to be the classic one</u>
<u n="301" who="S0012">this is the whole problem you see I don't have any money</u>
<u n="302" who="S0013">no that has to be the classic</u>
<u n="303" who="S0012">you don't allow me to have any money cos you think I lose it</u>
<u n="304" who="S0013">oh you've got a card</u>
<u n="305" who="S0012">so it how can you buy a <trunc>twe</trunc></u>
<u n="306" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0012">twelve and a half pence bottle of?</u>
<u n="308" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0013">no you can't</u>
<u n="310" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0012">right with a card <pause dur="short"/> huh?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0012">come on give me some due</u>
<u n="314" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0012">anyhow you got a birthday present I don't know what you're worried about</u>
<u n="316" who="S0013">I did okay I'm not I'm not not saying anything <unclear> thank you</unclear></u>
<u n="317" who="S0012">you might not get a birthday present now this year</u>
<u n="318" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="319" who="S0012">you probably won't</u>
<u n="320" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0012">cos you don't appreciate it</u>
<u n="322" who="S0013">I did appreciate <unclear/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0012">you didn't appreciate the goat collar you didn't appreciate the goat</u>
<u n="324" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0012">you didn't appreciate your rubber boots you didn't</u>
<u n="326" who="S0013">I did appreciate them</u>
<u n="327" who="S0012">you didn't appreciate the spade you didn't appreciate the fork</u>
<u n="328" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I've I've appreciated everything</u>
<u n="329" who="S0012">no you didn't</u>
<u n="330" who="S0013">I have</u>
<u n="331" who="S0012">you told everyone</u>
<u n="332" who="S0013">I have no er that <trunc>w</trunc> the the shampoo and conditioner was a bit</u>
<u n="333" who="S0012">no you told everyone you know what I got for birthday? <vocal desc="laugh"/> a pair of rubber boots</u>
<u n="334" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0012">don't you? come on</u>
<u n="336" who="S0013">no only occasionally</u>
<u n="337" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0012">only occasionally only occasionally to everybody we know</u>
<u n="339" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0012">come on</u>
<u n="341" who="S0013">but you <trunc>usua</trunc>usually bring it up so it's your fault <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0012">I don't bring it up</u>
<u n="343" who="S0013">yes you do</u>
<u n="344" who="S0012">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> brings it up</u>
<u n="345" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> brings it up every year</u>
<u n="347" who="S0013">yeah every time we see her just about isn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0012">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> brings it up</u>
<u n="349" who="S0013">good old <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0012">she's lovely</u>
<u n="351" who="S0013">oh I meant I kept meaning to write back and say thank you now it's too late</u>
<u n="352" who="S0012">thank you for what?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0013" trans="overlap">isn't it? thank you for having us at the during the summer</u>
<u n="354" who="S0012">mm well</u>
<u n="355" who="S0013">mm too late really</u>
<u n="356" who="S0012">no er that no it's</u>
<u n="357" who="S0013">to send it <unclear/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0012">you don't have to say thank you we said thank you when we were up there</u>
<u n="359" who="S0013">yeah I know</u>
<u n="360" who="S0012">what more do you want?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0013">it would've been nice nice to write something</u>
<u n="362" who="S0012">you're too you're too soft <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm going to have to harden you off</u>
<u n="363" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0012">I think I do it the right way you do it the the really er oh oh scary way</u>
<u n="365" who="S0013">oh I'll just have to write to everyone at Christmas</u>
<u n="366" who="S0012">why? <pause dur="short"/> my family never did</u>
<u n="367" who="S0013">you can just send Christmas cards you do to people you don't see from year to year</u>
<u n="368" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you just send yeah yeah you send <trunc>Christ</trunc> oh it's a load of rubbish isn't it come on <pause dur="short"/> you haven't seen anyone for forty-eight years and you send them a Christmas card?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0013">I suppose it is a bit dated now <pause dur="short"/> forty-eight years?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0012">well whatever <pause dur="short"/> I mean people have got my mum used to have a list right and we hadn't seen these people <pause dur="short"/> well I'd never met them but mum used to have a list and she spent I know stamps were only a tuppence ha'penny then probably a penny in old money <pause dur="short"/> and the card only cost <pause dur="short"/> five pence or one and six as they'd say one and six <pause dur="short"/> something like that <pause dur="short"/> she used to send about fifty cards</u>
<u n="371" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0012">right and she used to post them every year fifty cards which in today's money would have cost about twenty-five quid</u>
<u n="373" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0012">wouldn't it</u>
<u n="375" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0012">just for the post not for the cards the cards would now cost a pound so that's a pound for the cards which is fifty quid and twenty-five quid to post it is seventy-five quid</u>
<u n="377" who="S0013">yeah a lot of money</u>
<u n="378" who="S0012">you know but they used to send it they used to send cards to each other and never met never seen the people for donkey's yonks</u>
<u n="379" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0012">and yet she felt it her duty to send them cards</u>
<u n="381" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0012">and I used to have to go out well I posted all your cards didn't I</u>
<u n="383" who="S0013">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0012">oh no I didn't did I I left them in the front of the</u>
<u n="385" who="S0013">no you didn't <pause dur="short"/> no you had all the stamps on as well</u>
<u n="386" who="S0012">so how many friends did you lose?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0013">that was a waste <pause dur="short"/> huh?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0012">how many friends did you lose by not me posting the cards?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0013">a few <pause dur="short"/> I did</u>
<u n="390" who="S0012">well they weren't friends then were they? <pause dur="short"/> mm?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0013">you trust people to send to to do that sort of thing I never never trusted anyone since <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't even say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can you post the card on the way home? no I don't trust anyone I've got to do it</u>
<u n="392" who="S0012">yeah but I mean the you you <trunc>ha</trunc> we had about <trunc>twen</trunc> I had about twenty-five cards didn't I in in in my glove compartment in the car?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0012">so?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0013">well why didn't you post them?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0012">I forgot but did you get twenty-five cards back from them people?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0013">maybe I don't know</u>
<u n="398" who="S0012">no you didn't</u>
<u n="399" who="S0013">anyway</u>
<u n="400" who="S0012">you didn't <pause dur="short"/> so I saved you an enormous amount of money over the years by not by forgetting</u>
<u n="401" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0012">so you I think you owe me quite a lot of money actually</u>
<u n="403" who="S0013">well I like to keep sending cards but logically it doesn't it's not right <pause dur="short"/> but it's not the same sending by email is it</u>
<u n="404" who="S0012">email is is is just email is an excuse</u>
<u n="405" who="S0013" trans="overlap">not at Christmas <pause dur="short"/> it is isn't it it is an excuse</u>
<u n="406" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that's a that's an excuse</u>
<u n="407" who="S0013" trans="overlap">that's being stingy as well isn't it really</u>
<u n="408" who="S0012">that's horrible email I think and text</u>
<u n="409" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I think I think they need to write</u>
<u n="410" who="S0012">anyone who <trunc>lo</trunc> email and texts are just lazy idiots lazy I could I could call them</u>
<u n="411" who="S0013">no you don't</u>
<u n="412" who="S0012">something else with a but it's just a lazy idle thing</u>
<u n="413" who="S0013">it is really</u>
<u n="414" who="S0012">and well email is just a way of getting out of thinking about people</u>
<u n="415" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0012">oh I mean what what did we get one year? I got a round robin</u>
<u n="417" who="S0013">yes I don't like those</u>
<u n="418" who="S0012">and what about that?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0012">you know this is the round robin</u>
<u n="421" who="S0013" trans="overlap">this is what we've been doing all year</u>
<u n="422" who="S0012">this is my</u>
<u n="423" who="S0013">you do like to know what people are doing</u>
<u n="424" who="S0012">yeah but it sends to everybody who whose oh that was awful</u>
<u n="425" who="S0013">but it just seems so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0012">and I thought if you're going to you know you write out what you've been doing for the and and what your family have been doing for the past year and then you've got all these all the people in your address book and you just go click and it's not personal any more is it</u>
<u n="427" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="428" who="S0012">it's not personal at all you sent it to a hundred and thirty people who doesn't who don't really matter to you</u>
<u n="429" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0012">but you think oh right I'll just send them all</u>
<u n="431" who="S0013">like another person doesn't matter does it</u>
<u n="432" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="433" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0012">so I think email and text is an excuse</u>
<u n="435" who="S0013">yeah I think you've still got to send cards</u>
<u n="436" who="S0012">that's a big excuse email and texts</u>
<u n="437" who="S0013">it is</u>
<u n="438" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> an <trunc>excu</trunc> oh we just I'll just send a text <vocal desc="misc"/> done</u>
<u n="439" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0012">you don't have to think about anything do you <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to think about who you are sending it to or anything you just send</u>
<u n="441" who="S0013">not when it's multi people no</u>
<u n="442" who="S0012">these multi texts or happy birthday or happy Christmas or whatever well done to a hundred and thirty people that you think you know but you don't <pause dur="short"/> I haven't finished my tea</u>
<u n="443" who="S0013">we better get back haven't you?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0012">I haven't finished my tea</u>
<u n="445" who="S0013">oh gosh you haven't</u>
<u n="446" who="S0012">you keep yapping so much <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0013">I finished mine ages ago oh no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I haven't quite finished mine oh I give up on it</u>
<u n="448" who="S0012">you didn't really <trunc>ne</trunc> what are we eating tonight anyway?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0013">fish</u>
<u n="450" who="S0012">and?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0013">erm fish and sauce parsley sauce</u>
<u n="452" who="S0012">and a</u>
<u n="453" who="S0013">carrots erm some kale I'll go and pick some kale in a minute</u>
<u n="454" who="S0012">and I said I'd find some little tiny potatoes</u>
<u n="455" who="S0013">oh yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0012">to cook in their jackets</u>
<u n="457" who="S0013">that's good yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0013">boil in their jackets</u>
<u n="460" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0013">yep that will be alright</u>
<u n="462" who="S0012">I like popping in potatoes because they're like they're like pop in a a boil they go <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0013">oh you are disgusting</u>
<u n="464" who="S0012">what?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0013">you're disgusting</u>
<u n="466" who="S0012">I'm not you you get hold of the potato you can half it</u>
<u n="467" who="S0013">there was no need to say that though</u>
<u n="468" who="S0012">you get hold of the the the actual er skin and go <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="470" who="S0012">and it pops like a big pimple <pause dur="short"/> that's that's about sixty years ago since I</u>
<u n="471" who="S0013">no I don't think I'll have any potatoes <pause dur="short"/> I'll just have the carrots and kale with my fish</u>
<u n="472" who="S0012">well I'm going to have the popping pimples</u>
<u n="473" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0012">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stop spewing over the corner</u>
<u n="475" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="476" who="S0012">right I think you better get on with your work <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0013">yeah will do <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
