<text id="STBF">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:19:56</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0428 S0432</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Cambridge University Press Printing House</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Bonfire night, festivals, fireworks, Valencia</topics>
		<activity>Lunchtime chat</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, requesting, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0428">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Eastern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0432">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>White British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lincoln</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands/ East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Gamlingay, Cambridgeshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Chinese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0432">no <pause dur="short"/> technically <vocal desc="laugh"/> we were meant to be <pause dur="short"/> we were meant to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0428">actually I was listening to that recording yesterday it was like I think I might take the day off after Bonfire Night you were saying</u>
<u n="3" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I'd totally forgot about that I forgot to take the day off actually</u>
<u n="4" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah you were like <pause dur="short"/> you were like going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0432">yeah but it's that was meant we thought it was tonight <pause dur="short"/> but it was last night <vocal desc="laugh"/> so we totally missed it</u>
<u n="6" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's so funny</u>
<u n="7" who="S0432">yeah we got a text from er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother and he was like so you are coming down? and we were like yeah what time is it? and he was like well it's starting in like half an hour <vocal desc="laugh"/> and we thought it was tomorrow night so now we're not I</u>
<u n="8" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0432">mean apparently <anon type="place"/> fireworks are on Friday night so I don't know whether to go to those</u>
<u n="10" who="S0428" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> they are really good</u>
<u n="11" who="S0432">because apparently they are really good yeah and last year they <pause dur="short"/> apparently I need to Youtube but</u>
<u n="12" who="S0428">I was there</u>
<u n="13" who="S0432">were you? they did the Frozen ones</u>
<u n="14" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah last year <pause dur="short"/> they did what?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0432">they did to the tune of Frozen or something</u>
<u n="16" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0432">was it really good?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0428">it was good erm because obviously they <pause dur="short"/> they make them there that's the factory is in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I might go <pause dur="short"/> yeah that makes sense now my sister was saying that and I was ignoring her</u>
<u n="20" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0432">yeah I think she mentioned that</u>
<u n="22" who="S0428">yeah and erm <pause dur="short"/> so they kind of give them a free or really cheap because they are amazing but you kind of get stuck in a really long queue getting there cos like the traffic and everything <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I can imagine <pause dur="short"/> I might mention that to my sister actually</u>
<u n="24" who="S0428">and like erm it has not been <unclear>ninety-seven</unclear> but then Heart go and like do a big like MCing and</u>
<u n="25" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="26" who="S0428">yeah there's millions of people <pause dur="short"/> it used to be like this kind of really small event that <pause dur="short"/> they do it to music or like but like really small and now it is kind of like massive</u>
<u n="27" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I only really heard about it last year and I think that's just cos they did it to like the Frozen the Frozen song or something and obviously that was massive</u>
<u n="28" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think they've they've done really like it was they've like marketed it so well because it used to be just not like nothing just kind of</u>
<u n="29" who="S0432">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah just like a village or like a town</u>
<u n="30" who="S0428">yeah that people go from <pause dur="short"/> I think it was busy last year <pause dur="short"/> but not massively massively busy</u>
<u n="31" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how much tickets are actually to be <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but my sister has taken <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah she was like I need to get some ear defenders for babies</u>
<u n="32" who="S0428">oh so you got some <pause dur="short"/> is she going to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0432">yeah yeah and she was like oh I don't know whether to take a pram or get one of the like harness things whatever and I was like definitely take a harness</u>
<u n="34" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> carry ones probably <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos the ground it is all long grass so</u>
<u n="35" who="S0432">yeah and I was like it is even going to be like that or like boggy or something <pause dur="short"/> yeah and it is just erm I think it would be annoying anyway with the crowds of people even if the floor was fine</u>
<u n="36" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah and boggy yeah you need to wear wellies <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0432">yeah it just I was like definitely take <pause dur="short"/> it he is quite heavy so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might have to have him <vocal desc="laugh"/> or take it in turns because he would have <trunc>a</trunc> he will probably be asleep</u>
<u n="38" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but it is really worth going to see</u>
<u n="39" who="S0432">yeah I might go then because I wasn't going to bother <pause dur="short"/> but because we were going tonight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0428" trans="overlap">they've got <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> they've got the ones here on Thursday which are quite good</u>
<u n="41" who="S0432">oh yeah the erm I saw that the roads were gonna be closed</u>
<u n="42" who="S0428">but yeah it is so annoying when you have to like get stuck in a traffic jam just to see fireworks</u>
<u n="43" who="S0432">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah we erm <pause dur="short"/> there was erm Sunday night I think the ones in <anon type="place"/> were on they were due to start at six but there was problems and they had to get someone in from Luton to to take over or something so they didn't start until seven <pause dur="short"/> but we we've got like a single-storey extension out the back and we just sat on the roof of that and watched them and they lasted like fifteen minutes <pause dur="short"/> so everyone was obviously waiting there for an hour or more just to see fifteen minutes and they weren't even they tried to do it to music as well but it was just a bit creepy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh really <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> that <pause dur="short"/> it's like erm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0432">it was like Lord of the Rings music or something and I was like this is weird</u>
<u n="46" who="S0428">I don't know since seeing them in Valencia I am a little bit like <pause dur="short"/> did you ever the firework displays there?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not I can't remember what it was for</u>
<u n="48" who="S0428">were they at the beach?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0432">I wasn't on the <pause dur="short"/> they might of <pause dur="short"/> no I don't know where I was</u>
<u n="50" who="S0428">were you there September to February?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0432">maybe it was something for like <anon type="place"/> day or?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0428">yeah and they did them in the park</u>
<u n="55" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0428">and they are incredible</u>
<u n="57" who="S0432">yeah I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah it must have been those ones I can't remember when it was actually I just remember that <pause dur="short"/> but they were really good</u>
<u n="58" who="S0428" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah during Fallas they're every night like that and they do really big ones for the beach and they have like the <foreign lang="spa">mascleta</foreign></u>
<u n="59" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0428">and everything and so now when I see them here I'm like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0432">yeah it is a bit is that it? really?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0432">yeah they were really good</u>
<u n="64" who="S0428">when I was in Valencia last week erm <pause dur="short"/> I was in <anon type="place"/> my friend's cafe and my friend was picking me up to go to the country and <pause dur="short"/> like a track you know like <unclear/> like the <unclear/> down the track went off and I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm in a war zone <pause dur="short"/> it's just crazy it is just mental that that happens and people just don't even flinch even like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's two is just like</u>
<u n="65" who="S0432" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but oh I think it <pause dur="short"/> I saw some in the square as well <pause dur="short"/> in the day though they did the I can't <unclear>remember the</unclear></u>
<u n="66" who="S0428">oh the er the <foreign lang="spa">mascleta</foreign> in the day</u>
<u n="67" who="S0432">yeah it was that <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I was like it was just the erm they'd got like <unclear/> of it</u>
<u n="68" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> oh okay</u>
<u n="69" who="S0432">I can't remember like</u>
<u n="70" who="S0428">did they have the big cage up?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0432">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0428">yeah for the last fire?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no er <pause dur="short"/> because I wasn't there for fireworks they had something in <pause dur="short"/> they might <pause dur="short"/> that might be the same day I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I think it was actually because it was the day after I saw the ones at night and I was like what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> why are you doing it in the day? and it was just <pause dur="short"/> and there was like a massive crowd like <pause dur="short"/> I am like oh it was just really noisy and sounded like you were in a war zone or something</u>
<u n="74" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no it wasn't <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's really strange cos at the beginning I was like I don't get this but then the year after I was like I love it and now I really like it but I think it's so different like it is such a different concept than we'd have <pause dur="short"/> like just setting off fireworks in the day and you can't see them just for noise but erm I think cos I <trunc>wa</trunc> I was I spent like quite a lot of time working on that square so obviously like we just couldn't you couldn't have a lesson and like people couldn't get to lessons like</u>
<u n="75" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was just because there were parades and all sorts there I think it was <pause dur="short"/> yeah there was <foreign lang="spa">dia</foreign> that <unclear/> or something like that or something</u>
<u n="76" who="S0428">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah maybe</u>
<u n="77" who="S0432">I think that was November <pause dur="short"/> I I have November</u>
<u n="78" who="S0428">there's <foreign lang="spa">puente</foreign> in November</u>
<u n="79" who="S0432">yeah maybe it was that</u>
<u n="80" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0432">no it might have been before that I can't remember because the weather was really hot and I don't <pause dur="short"/> I remember November being quite rainy</u>
<u n="82" who="S0428">I think tenth of October is <foreign lang="spa">dia de la comunidad</foreign></u>
<u n="83" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0428">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="85" who="S0432">yeah it was at then because I know the parade was there for that</u>
<u n="86" who="S0428" trans="overlap">well there's like Spanish <trunc>a</trunc> yeah there's so many there's <unclear>appointee</unclear> the like round the tenth of October ish a I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I would have to look <pause dur="short"/> but it's crazy cos even in all the tiny villages as well they do them in the winter</u>
<u n="87" who="S0432">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> everyone like dresses up don't they?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0432">oh I want to go back why have we got back on to <anon type="place"/> again?</u>
<u n="90" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0428">that's all we talk about <pause dur="short"/> they have some really weird traditions though like when I was living in <anon type="place"/> they have this thing called the Festival of the Sardine</u>
<u n="92" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god</u>
<u n="93" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and it's <pause dur="short"/> yeah so it's around carnival it is just before Lent starts</u>
<u n="94" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0428">and it's kind of like like the sardines are crying because they are gonna be eaten because no one can eat meat <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it is like they <pause dur="short"/> they <trunc>pu</trunc> they make this really big model of a sardine and they like parade it through the streets and there's like all these cross dressed like god knows what on like stilts like and then they they parade it round and you follow it and you end up in like the main square by the Town Hall and everyone like circles it like crying <vocal desc="laugh"/> lamenting like saying these poems to it like</u>
<u n="96" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> really? <pause dur="short"/> just like one sardine <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah to this one massive sardine and then they burn it</u>
<u n="98" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="99" who="S0428">and I was like what? what is this? <vocal desc="laugh"/> this is just mental</u>
<u n="100" who="S0432">yeah so like for an outsider I suppose it's just a bit like woah what's going on?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and they just then they burnt it and people just were dancing around it like singing these traditional songs</u>
<u n="102" who="S0432">mm <pause dur="short"/> but then it must be like when leading it up to it it is a bit like oh I'm so excited for <pause dur="short"/> like for the actual Spanish people</u>
<u n="103" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think so</u>
<u n="104" who="S0432" trans="overlap">they must be get quite excited about the festivals and things like that</u>
<u n="105" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah my friend my friend who's got her the two year old has already decided when she is eight she is going to be like the <foreign lang="spa">fallera mayor infantil</foreign> and like she has got her own dress even though she's two</u>
<u n="106" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> really? <pause dur="short"/> oh they spend a fortune on those dresses don't they</u>
<u n="107" who="S0428">they're mental</u>
<u n="108" who="S0432">ridiculous I remember <pause dur="short"/> like seeing like people in shops getting like measured up for them <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> is it in March?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but they they like</u>
<u n="110" who="S0432" trans="overlap">so like I didn't think I would see any of it but obviously they prepare for ages don't they and just</u>
<u n="111" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> all year</u>
<u n="112" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0428">but it is all like</u>
<u n="114" who="S0432">they make the erm like</u>
<u n="115" who="S0428">statues</u>
<u n="116" who="S0432">statues that's it I was going to say models</u>
<u n="117" who="S0428" trans="overlap">well no what do they call like kind papier mâché like models yeah like <foreign lang="spa"><trunc>fa</trunc>falla</foreign> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0432">yeah like <pause dur="short"/> yeah they do them all year <pause dur="short"/> yeah they do them all year round though they work on it for a whole year and then just burn it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0428">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like I was cos I the last time I was there I was in a <foreign lang="spa">pallea</foreign> party on <anon type="place"/> and they are like yeah this falla cost like a hundred thousand euros and I was like that's so much money <pause dur="short"/> to just burn</u>
<u n="120" who="S0432" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> to just burn <pause dur="short"/> I'd <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't know I didn't see it</u>
<u n="121" who="S0428">it's mental <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>suc</trunc> in also like all the fireworks like that the <foreign lang="spa">mascleta</foreign> is every day from the first to the <trunc>ninet</trunc> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah first to the nineteenth of March every day they like are blowing up and then they have the massive fireworks displays from the fifteenth to the nineteenth so that's so many fireworks</u>
<u n="122" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah my friend was just like I can't sleep cos they go on quite late at night don't they? as well</u>
<u n="123" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0432">she was like she was I've had enough <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't cope like it is fun for the first few days <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then like the fireworks go off like in the streets as well so she was a bit scared like to go out</u>
<u n="125" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah like <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they are called erm they call them <foreign lang="spa">borrachos</foreign> and they are ones that like do this and they go through the crowd and like they are banned they're so dangerous</u>
<u n="126" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they are I <pause dur="short"/> when I heard about that I was like I'm actually quite glad I am not going to be there but</u>
<u n="127" who="S0428">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's kind of it it's fine but when it was like <anon type="place"/> I didn't like the atmosphere there it was just like all these these fireworks going off and</u>
<u n="128" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I always felt like I was a bit because it is like near the uni it is a bit kind of <pause dur="short"/> rowdy and a bit too much <vocal desc="laugh"/> like all uni students just trying to be cool</u>
<u n="129" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah like I loved like <anon type="place"/> I don't know if you remember it was like <pause dur="short"/> it was a <anon type="place"/> of <anon type="place"/> and it had loads of circles on the top and I loved just going there and like reading a book and then once I was like ah there's some nice like little tapas places around there <pause dur="short"/> and I went and at night it is like a massive <foreign lang="spa">botellon</foreign> it was really like <pause dur="short"/> I didn't I didn't like the atmosphere at all</u>
<u n="130" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I never to one of those but erm <pause dur="short"/> one of the girls I met out there she was on Erasmus as well she lived near there and she was always going to the like the <foreign lang="spa">botellon</foreign> and I was just like oh I think I might give it a miss</u>
<u n="131" who="S0428">yeah not sure I fancy that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0432">no <pause dur="short"/> there was always loads on like <anon type="place"/> it was like a uni thing and <pause dur="short"/> well it wasn't but a lot of uni students went <pause dur="short"/> and like down the beach</u>
<u n="133" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> the beach in the summer I went I think I went to one of the beach but not like <pause dur="short"/> not an organised one it was just for like me <vocal desc="laugh"/> and like a group of my friends</u>
<u n="134" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I went to one <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0428">yeah well I I love just going down to the beach so any opportunity to go down to the beach</u>
<u n="136" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah what was <pause dur="short"/> was it like the port that was a bit further down and there was like bar with like basically with like basically like <trunc>mattress</trunc> mattresses out the front weren't there</u>
<u n="137" who="S0428">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm I loved it yeah they and it was quite expensive</u>
<u n="138" who="S0432">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0428">and there's like <trunc>anoth</trunc> there's a bar that cos you can go on the port and there's loads of bars that kind of look out to sea but there's one that looks back to a second harbour cos it's kind of two ports and it's the one where they have the American sailing <unclear/> and it <pause dur="short"/> when you look it looks like you look back over it you can kind of see that although it feels like a mini skyline like nothing impressive but you think oh <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm it looks back over the <foreign lang="spa">tinglados</foreign> the big warehouse <foreign lang="spa">tinglados</foreign></u>
<u n="140" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="141" who="S0428">I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> erm so <pause dur="short"/> you look you look back and at night it is so pretentious but you like you can go <pause dur="short"/> we used to go and have like one cocktail it would be like four o'clock and the sun would be there and there would no one there</u>
<u n="142" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah I can imagine <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah we went er cos we went on like a bike ride <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then and just like chained them up and or put them back in the block and then just walked around that bit</u>
<u n="143" who="S0428">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is so nice</u>
<u n="144" who="S0432">mm just have one we where like mm maybe that's enough for one <pause dur="short"/> for the price of four</u>
<u n="145" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> after the <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> my friend is seven months pregnant and she gets on a <foreign lang="spa">Valenbici</foreign> every day</u>
<u n="146" who="S0432">oh does she?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0428">yeah I'm like be careful they're so heavy</u>
<u n="148" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they are I never used to <pause dur="short"/> well I liked cycling but just on them ones always a bit conscious of <pause dur="short"/> falling off because they are <vocal desc="laugh"/> they are so front heavy as well aren't they it is not like the whole bike is it's <pause dur="short"/> hard to</u>
<u n="149" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was really bad but I like erm I like it round there it is really funny because I was with my friend down there and erm obviously it is the formula One track I was like it's so easy to cycle here he was like it is a Formula One track and I was like oh wow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah they don't use that any more do they?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0428">erm they <pause dur="short"/> they got fined massively because they had signed a five year contract to do the Formula One there and then I think they had the year the last year I was there so you were there they didn't have it but I think they've got it back again now <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember</u>
<u n="152" who="S0432" trans="overlap">or do they now? <pause dur="long"/> yeah I think I I don't know where I heard it but I'm sure I heard that it is going to come back into use or something I don't really follow Formula One</u>
<u n="153" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <vocal desc="laugh"/> just care about <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I see pictures of the like Science and Arts area and I I loved it there</u>
<u n="155" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> it is amazing like when erm I was walking with my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like look it's amazing <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she was like oh</u>
<u n="156" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I went to like I remember I think it was in the first week I was there I went to like a fashion show that was at one of them I can't remember which building it was</u>
<u n="157" who="S0428">I did all the English for that</u>
<u n="158" who="S0432">did you?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it would have been that year yeah cos erm the people running it were from Abercrombie and Fitch</u>
<u n="160" who="S0432">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0428">and I used to teach them English and then I did like loads of the translations <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's really funny I didn't go</u>
<u n="162" who="S0432" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah my erm <pause dur="short"/> my erm <pause dur="short"/> belgian flatmate she was like oh yeah we have to because was into fashion and stuff and all her French friends and Belgian friends whatever were like yeah we've got to go so I went like in my best dress <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0432">and it was yeah it was alright it was just <pause dur="short"/> they came outside and I walked in there was like a platform in the water <pause dur="short"/> so they were like <vocal desc="misc"/> and there was like people singing and stuff it was quite good no it was alright and one of the <pause dur="short"/> they were wearing really high stilettos and one of the ladies fell and I think her foot slipped into the water and we were like oh no how embarrassing I hope there isn't</u>
<u n="165" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> the fear <pause dur="short"/> really? <pause dur="short"/> oh no don't that would be awful</u>
<u n="166" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0428">the first year I was there erm they drained one of the pools like the one between you know the building that is kind of that not the <pause dur="short"/> not the <trunc>helme</trunc> not the first one but the second one I think it's <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what's in there actually</u>
<u n="168" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0428"><unclear/> between that and like the club at the top like the garden bit</u>
<u n="170" who="S0432">yeah the oh what's that called? erm the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> yeah so that pool there they like drained it all and they had erm Arctic Monkeys free concert</u>
<u n="172" who="S0432">really</u>
<u n="173" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0432">oh wow</u>
<u n="175" who="S0428">and erm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0432">and I would have liked to have gone <unclear>to that</unclear></u>
<u n="177" who="S0428">I think the year before someone really like someone like that erm and they were just yeah they were like MTV parties but then they they had to be cut cos there was no funding for them</u>
<u n="178" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh that would have been good to</u>
<u n="179" who="S0428" trans="overlap">but I'm sure they are the kind of things that will start up again</u>
<u n="180" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0428">but it's just draining all that water for a concert that's mental</u>
<u n="182" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw they had like zorbing on one of them and people were having races or something I don't know I was like oh that looks like fun <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then I saw a car advert being filmed there</u>
<u n="183" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh really?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0432">yeah I can't remember oh I can't remember what car it was for now I was like I am going to have to watch the advert and I don't think I ever did</u>
<u n="185" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did you was the dinosaur there in the water? there was like a massive dinosaur there for ages and we were like what's that doing?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0432" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc> I don't remember that <pause dur="short"/> really? <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0428">cos I used to work like if you go up from the <anon type="place"/> pretty much that my school in my last year was there so I always used to go and sit and read</u>
<u n="188" who="S0432">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>toward</trunc> like inland or like towards the coast?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0428">erm inland towards <anon type="place"/> so like just before between like <anon type="place"/> and the river that kind of posh area</u>
<u n="190" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="191" who="S0428">oh <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I liked the eye</u>
<u n="193" who="S0428">that's gone</u>
<u n="194" who="S0432">what?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0428">the eye hang on</u>
<u n="196" who="S0432">as in the building that's half an eye and then when it is lit up at night it the eye <pause dur="short"/> yeah it like creates the the lights <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh sorry yeah <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> shadow so beautiful I thought you were talking because they put a Ferris wheel <pause dur="short"/> erm near the <anon type="place"/> but they've <pause dur="short"/> I think they've taken I think it is just a temporary one so that's why I thought you like the <anon type="place"/> in London</u>
<u n="198" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh did they? <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I like that</u>
<u n="199" who="S0428">I would like to go back for <unclear>Fallas</unclear> again because</u>
<u n="200" who="S0432">I want to go to <unclear>Fallas</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> but you have to book like really far in advance or like stay outside of <anon type="place"/> I think because it is really expensive isn't it?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if you want to go like one year erm let me know because all my friends leave and they don't rent their places out they don't particularly want like like people they don't know there but like I am sure they they are all like no we just they hate it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I can imagine like every year <unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0428">yeah but like all their flats are free so you can stay for free or like just a little bit</u>
<u n="204" who="S0432" trans="overlap">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I might yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0428">cos <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0432">I mean I'd probably be really scared and like not want to go out ever <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0428">the centre's fine it is <pause dur="short"/> it's fun but it is just mental but <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to go and be with my Spanish friends and they're <pause dur="short"/> in their <anon type="place"/> it's it's fun</u>
<u n="208" who="S0432">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I actually know anyone that's there now <pause dur="short"/> I know one erm <pause dur="short"/> girl she actually came over to <anon type="place"/> for Erasmus and she was there or she is from <pause dur="short"/> I think she was from Ecuador but she was living in <anon type="place"/> for quite a while so I could ask her if she <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if she is still I think she's in <anon type="place"/> still but I am sure she will like <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure she would go back for <unclear>Fallas</unclear></u>
<u n="209" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh really? <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="210" who="S0432">hello</u>
<u n="211" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">hello <pause dur="short"/> is this the <trunc>tou</trunc></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
