<text id="STEY">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:24:58</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0456 S0463</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s office, Joensuu, Finland. </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Aquaintences</relationships>
		<topics>politics, right-to-buy, renting buildings, Jeremy Corbyn, housing, Guardian articles, immigration, Labour Leadership election.</topics>
		<activity>Talking about politics</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Inquiring, Requesting, Anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0456">
				<exactage>44</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/ German</nat>
				<birthplace>Salzkotten</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>German</l1>
				<lingorig>English</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scouse</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Liverpool</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer (English Language and Literature)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0463">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scouse</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Liverpool</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>All my life</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Taxi Cab driver</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0463">perhaps right to buy wasn't such a good idea</u>
<u n="2" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0463">you know er you couldn't have had this conversation this wasn't part of the discourse</u>
<u n="4" who="S0456">no</u>
<u n="5" who="S0463">five years ago</u>
<u n="6" who="S0456">I think the the the clearest thing about right to buy is because people still need a right to buy I had that on the doorstep oh yeah because I hadn't decided because we've got our council well not council but housing association <unclear>asking</unclear> were you thinking about buying erm but obviously Alison Alison McGowen got in but</u>
<u n="7" who="S0463">the crime is about the crime is about the capital receipts you can you</u>
<u n="8" who="S0456" trans="overlap">that one and of course that here there there there wasn't a firm and secure way that people keep it rather than it gets bought and then it's just object of speculation</u>
<u n="9" who="S0463">oh no cos <unclear>we it's</unclear></u>
<u n="10" who="S0456" trans="overlap">cos most of the right to buy they're not with the buyers they're with big new landlords who</u>
<u n="11" who="S0463">but it was even worse <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at the start because at the start which people don't remember I do because it was my first job at <anon type="place"/> council was that the local councils themselves gave mortgages as well as banks and they were given a hundred percent mortgages and they were giving a hundred percent mortgages to sixty year old people and then repossessing their homes when they couldn't pay and and they were on commission to sell those properties</u>
<u n="12" who="S0456">so there there was a mini two thousand eight already yeah because that was what it was selling to those you know subprime</u>
<u n="13" who="S0463" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's right yeah absolutely yeah yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0456">yeah because I remember er one of my elderly neighbours was saying that</u>
<u n="15" who="S0463">and the kids were bugging them their parents as well into into doing it</u>
<u n="16" who="S0456">oh yeah because it's they know</u>
<u n="17" who="S0463">they'll inherit it</u>
<u n="18" who="S0456">it'll be theirs</u>
<u n="19" who="S0463">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0456">well that was Hope Place the play that I saw last summer not this summer in in the Everyman that was all about it they had this house in Hope Place and it was council and parents had died the one who looked after the mother I suppose the one unmarried spinster was living there but all the kids obviously inherited it when their mother died and they were dead keen you know that we'll get zillions for this get the estate agent and of course the whole history that was was really the story but yeah that was there</u>
<u n="21" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0456">because they <unclear/> and they bullied the older sister into it and er she she didn't like it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0463">yes I mean for example there was a where I worked we took stock transfer over loads of properties from <anon type="place"/> council and there was one big house that was housing a family of eight so clearly you know worth quite a lot of money and the amount of <unclear/> our chief exec went through to try and get them out so she could sell the place I stopped him and told him look what you're trying to do is illegal but that's it you know once you put these properties into the hands of a chief exec rather than an unaccounted <trunc>represent</trunc> er sorry an elected representative erm they're just thinking bottom line bottom line bottom line</u>
<u n="24" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah well it's just well just look at what's going on here that er <anon type="place"/> is is being cleared because the rents are cheaper in the new building it's like rents</u>
<u n="25" who="S0463">oh is that why?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0456">who's owning them yeah no it's have you heard of the internal market? does that sound familiar?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0463">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0456">that must be the one that it is because as far as I would think the whole area and every building on it belongs to the university so the rents who would charge them? it's the university</u>
<u n="29" who="S0463">who would be paying rent? why would the university be paying rent?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0456">no it it it's same in in Britain this is why you have you use max yeah in Britain by law universities have to make maximum use of the property portfolio that they have <pause dur="short"/> it's the law so much for them being free the best thing is Educa is the place that has two large erm lecture theatres and our student numbers haven't dropped so they have to rent back something the building that they have otherwise abandoned because our dean is now no longer there he's there I'm in Educa come next week</u>
<u n="31" who="S0463">oh really?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah because phonetics and phonology needs a large space erm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0463">oh you mean you're not moving your office you're just lecturing?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0456" trans="overlap">no no but yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0463">Educa's the the old wooden building isn't it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0456" trans="overlap">the old building the one that's</u>
<u n="37" who="S0463" trans="overlap">the <trunc>c</trunc> the school</u>
<u n="38" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0463">yeah how about the school kids are are they staying there or?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0456">it's not the school it is a university building so inside</u>
<u n="41" who="S0463">I know but they but they have don't they have the equivalent of a crèche though?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0456">yeah that will stay I think it's just the building itself</u>
<u n="43" who="S0463" trans="overlap">that will stay in there yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0456">so but it's it's it's extremely clever and they said well somebody pointed out that obviously the rents will go up because now there is a demand to be there <vocal desc="laugh"/> plus they have to now extra pay extra you know because they can dictate the rents if it would be like that if it would be the open market because Educa building has the kinds of rooms that the university needs <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's it's it's mental and it's just because of accounting</u>
<u n="45" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0456">just to create a market when there is no real market</u>
<u n="47" who="S0463">I was thinking you know if I was ever to have kind of access to power one of the one of the more mundane things I would do very quickly would be to sweep away the amount of counts and codes that you have in erm for example local authorities and housing associations</u>
<u n="48" who="S0456" trans="overlap">public yes</u>
<u n="49" who="S0463">the amount of work that goes into that</u>
<u n="50" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0463">you know unnecessary work most of the time</u>
<u n="52" who="S0456">and it being unnecessary means it has to be done because you have to have compliance</u>
<u n="53" who="S0463">oh yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0456">so you have to pay people and that comes out of your budget</u>
<u n="55" who="S0463">yeah and then you have to pay auditors to audit it erm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0456">mm so it's it's it's free for them because they cannot not work for you erm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0463">mm just it's it's a complete waste of time</u>
<u n="58" who="S0456">and as I said this is this is pushing money from left to right</u>
<u n="59" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0456"><unclear>might thin the old</unclear> large budget and you know there's there's no point</u>
<u n="61" who="S0463">I've done it professionally I know how it works you know I've worked in finance erm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0456">yeah if you if you would say that buildings are underused because you know partly that happened in biology their building is far too large there's just not enough people who want to do it erm and you cannot make more use out of it within the university you should see whether there is not a way of leasing out part of it as office space you know or whatever erm the thing is here you have to what who would be a taker?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0463" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0456">it's it's it's it's pointless</u>
<u n="65" who="S0463">I just think the whole thing sucks</u>
<u n="66" who="S0456">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0463">again it's just a waste these things nearly always end up costing more than they say it's not actually about the bottom line in that sense it's about disciplining university staff and public sector staff into the behaviours of the market</u>
<u n="68" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0463">it's NPA it's new public management all over</u>
<u n="70" who="S0456">did you see the I think it was in The Guardian last week er this guy votes that er a good friend of his always voted Labour and nothing but being a nurse and she said it's not so bad I can't stand it and I will go and take my expertise which is clearly not valued into the private sector</u>
<u n="71" who="S0463">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0456">and a lot of my colleagues think the same and yet the thing is that we accommodate ourselves so we're all Thatcherites now</u>
<u n="73" who="S0463">I know</u>
<u n="74" who="S0456">it's exactly what you said yeah it's the the thinking</u>
<u n="75" who="S0463" trans="overlap">yeah it's what right to buy was all about and the selling the shares</u>
<u n="76" who="S0456" trans="overlap">has has gone more than skin deep</u>
<u n="77" who="S0463">oh yeah it was a very successful project</u>
<u n="78" who="S0456">mm yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0463">right to buy was all about that and privatisation was about that creation creating a nation of shareholders so that everyone has everyone has erm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0456">an interest in capitalism</u>
<u n="81" who="S0463">yes but what was the expression I was looking for? something in the game everyone has some I can't remember the expression</u>
<u n="82" who="S0456" trans="overlap">a foothold?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0463">no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0456" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="85" who="S0463">but yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0456">well everybody has something to lose</u>
<u n="87" who="S0463">yes</u>
<u n="88" who="S0456">shares can go down as well as up</u>
<u n="89" who="S0463" trans="overlap">yes well they did but also no one has those shares any more remember?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0456">well apart from a couple of workers</u>
<u n="91" who="S0463">sorry?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0456">apart of a couple of workers who still have their VG shares</u>
<u n="93" who="S0463" trans="overlap">ah some yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0456" trans="overlap">but you know it's</u>
<u n="95" who="S0463">but they're you know most of the people sold them off instantly well you know this is exactly what happened in Russia</u>
<u n="96" who="S0456">yeah well not just Russia yeah was was it the Czech Republic that they had coupons?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0463">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0456" trans="overlap">this is this is one five millionth of however many Czech there are of the nation as well</u>
<u n="99" who="S0463">I I I think you know one of the great there was a very good piece by erm Owen</u>
<u n="100" who="S0456">mm James?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0463">yes er his honest appraisal of what he thought Corbyn could achieve and should try to achieve I don't know if you saw it?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0456">I think I only saw the headlines</u>
<u n="103" who="S0463">it was it was a good piece erm you know quite realistic</u>
<u n="104" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0463">erm and one of the things I thought was missing from it I know I've kind of commented on it was about framing now clearly</u>
<u n="106" who="S0456">framing?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0463">framing narratives</u>
<u n="108" who="S0456">oh yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0456">well which was the the thing that was so sadly missing in the last election</u>
<u n="111" who="S0463">yes and I think it was a very very powerful frame narrative</u>
<u n="112" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0463">they Labour use now particular left Labour which is framing the economic crises of two thousand and nine er <trunc>se</trunc> back to seventy-nine sorry and erm the James Meek narrative <pause dur="long"/> exactly</u>
<u n="114" who="S0456">here we go</u>
<u n="115" who="S0463">yes exactly</u>
<u n="116" who="S0456">see you've been primed by seeing the book in front of you</u>
<u n="117" who="S0463"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I <trunc>di</trunc> I didn't see it actually but yeah <trunc>a</trunc> <trunc>a</trunc> and the angle you were telling me <trunc>le</trunc>left patriotism and the angle would be that the right is unpatriotic</u>
<u n="118" who="S0456">which is true I mean</u>
<u n="119" who="S0463">well I know it is but no one</u>
<u n="120" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0463" trans="overlap">it's a classic Orwellian argument</u>
<u n="122" who="S0456" trans="overlap">and with the <unclear/> it's just Cameron keeps saying it's like</u>
<u n="123" who="S0463">yeah it's a classic Orwell argument you know the left has to reclaim patriotism but I don't think it has to reclaim it in this crappy blue Labour way it can actually reclaim from a much more self-assured and confident perspective which is to do with the fact that this nation once had things we have been stripped</u>
<u n="124" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm yeah well I think New Labour did that didn't they? the the whole thing of getting the Union Jack and ripping it out of the hands of BNF and BNP</u>
<u n="125" who="S0463">yeah they did that</u>
<u n="126" who="S0456">erm even though it was sort of a very muscular form of it it wasn't the nationalism and you could see that you know that it tried to push the</u>
<u n="127" who="S0463">they made it safe</u>
<u n="128" who="S0456">yeah the inclusively inclusive notion of it yeah if you're British doesn't matter whether you're white Asian background black gay erm you know the whole thing that even up to the May of ninety-seven was those things that were taboo or bad New Labour came in and shifted really really dramatically really really quickly</u>
<u n="129" who="S0463">well they went from there ain't no black in the Union Jack all the way to Cool Britannia</u>
<u n="130" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0463">didn't they? but erm and interestingly you probably know this but apparently the largest proportion of people who designate themselves British are immigrants</u>
<u n="132" who="S0456">are?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0463">immigrants</u>
<u n="134" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0463">erm because English people think of themselves as English erm Scottish as Scottish obviously but er</u>
<u n="136" who="S0456">yeah my neighbour I'm not British I'm English</u>
<u n="137" who="S0463">yeah exactly or I'm Scouse</u>
<u n="138" who="S0456">yeah no even more so yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0463"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but er it's it's people of erm particularly sort of erm Afro-Caribbean people or Asian British people who are saying that we're British so I think that is a a mark of the success of the project that you're talking about yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and people have taken it on and the people who came as refugees when they were still allowed to be called refugees</u>
<u n="141" who="S0463">good piece by John Harris</u>
<u n="142" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah John Harris erm it's interesting as well because I you know headline and like hang on he doesn't talk about them until the very last paragraph</u>
<u n="143" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0456">erm you know and it's true I mean I remember</u>
<u n="145" who="S0463">I remember Blunkett tying himself up in knots don't you?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0456">yeah oh yeah it was scary but I didn't remember Michael Howard's campaign and I thought I'm scared cos I'm not British enough</u>
<u n="147" who="S0463">to be honest with you erm er the partner of my friend in London <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she's she's very nervous now about erm the referendum</u>
<u n="148" who="S0456" trans="overlap">what the EU thing?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0456">yeah it's well did you see the the the Guardian does all these you know this is the Guardian and ding ding but erm yeah that crowd project so they put something out and then of course yes you can just collect photos or whatever but sometimes it is a survey et cetera and eventually there might be a piece of interest or not but erm when it was first voiced and I think that might have been directly after the election could have been still before that erm they asked for people erm people's responses whether people get second citizenship et cetera et cetera so people coming from outside or people who have a British passport and say well because of our <unclear>feelings</unclear> our lives within the EU we'll try and see a <trunc>ga</trunc> a non-British EU passport so we can carry on erm so far there has be no piece but they they clearly collected stories on that so</u>
<u n="151" who="S0463">have you any sense of how that vote will go?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0456">I mean it was there was never a question for such a long time it was a bit like I don't know but you know the it the majority wouldn't vote against that but because why would you have a referendum and it it's having a referendum is usually that politics has failed erm if it's not part of your constitution anyway</u>
<u n="153" who="S0463">they've got to mobilise the London vote haven't they? cos London is so disproportionately large</u>
<u n="154" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah plus of course</u>
<u n="155" who="S0463">and for the business people with an interest in being in Europe</u>
<u n="156" who="S0456">all all the EU citizens that live in London</u>
<u n="157" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0456">well will they have a vote though?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0463">probably not</u>
<u n="160" who="S0456">let's hope they're married to people with British passports then <vocal desc="laugh"/> you you have to go from reactionary types of things just to I mean it's ridiculous because I remember one of those things was er</u>
<u n="161" who="S0463">it doesn't feel real does it?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0456">yeah think EU I mean what would have happened er Liverpool was on the list of you know hanging out to dry and it was EU money <trunc>beca</trunc> and the EU insisted on giving it to Merseyside</u>
<u n="163" who="S0463" trans="overlap">they gave loads to Knowsley didn't they?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0456">not to London</u>
<u n="165" who="S0463">to Knowsley I remember they have loads cos Knowsley was the poorest borough in the country I think</u>
<u n="166" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0463">at the time</u>
<u n="168" who="S0456">yeah well and all the infrastructure projects you know Mersey railway just you know</u>
<u n="169" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0456">the Dutch came in and basically it was given to them I mean the only thing that wasn't er done up was the actual fleet of trains but you had brand new stations that the whole erm infrastructure around it all done with EU money</u>
<u n="171" who="S0463" trans="overlap">when was the <unclear/> built?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0456">Merseyrail</u>
<u n="173" who="S0463">in the seventies?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0456">no no no in in the eighties and nineties</u>
<u n="175" who="S0463">what's I'm I'm I'm lost</u>
<u n="176" who="S0456">well the things like Brunswick station erm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0463">right more things</u>
<u n="178" who="S0456">Birkenhead park Conway Conway whatever station em er in Birkenhead</u>
<u n="179" who="S0463">right</u>
<u n="180" who="S0456">erm all that was EU funding</u>
<u n="181" who="S0463">okay</u>
<u n="182" who="S0456">erm and doing the stations up apart from the main stations in Liverpool that are only done now</u>
<u n="183" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0456">erm and</u>
<u n="185" who="S0463">with a new big station aren't they?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0463">yeah it's it's yeah I guess I've never taken the train to the Wirral I've only ever driven so</u>
<u n="188" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah so yeah but yeah that's that's one of the many many instances of EU money that came into Merseyside</u>
<u n="189" who="S0463">yeah well I guess the the city of culture business was EU money wasn't it?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0456">yeah mm yeah yeah plus of course saying that because that just said oh no we want the money and then we distribute it and EU saying no because if you get the money they'll never see a penny of it</u>
<u n="191" who="S0463">no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0456">erm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0463">party before country</u>
<u n="194" who="S0456">mm ah shocking but yeah it just makes you angry but erm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0463"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0463">you need to back Jeremy mate</u>
<u n="197" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well the <unclear/> isn't all it's it's it's if if voting for a leader of the opposition would change things I'm sure other people would have done that</u>
<u n="198" who="S0463">hey?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0456">well if if having having the right leader of the opposition would have done the trick erm I'm sure other people would have tried that before</u>
<u n="200" who="S0463">like what?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0456">well getting a leader of the opposition that is just the perfect fit and that changes it all <pause dur="short"/> I'm not convinced but you know it's it's my party whoever will be the leader and that's that's that's not the difference I mean if it would be Liz Truss no not Liz Truss the Liz Truss that isn't Liz Truss Liz Kendall that might might be tricky but</u>
<u n="202" who="S0463">what does your instinct tell you?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0456">oh I can't</u>
<u n="204" who="S0463">rather than your intellect what does your instinct tell you?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0456">well who is going to win for a start no as does</u>
<u n="206" who="S0463">no not intellect</u>
<u n="207" who="S0456">yeah I know</u>
<u n="208" who="S0463">if you were talking simply about <unclear/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0456">my main well that tells me that none of the four is who I would have voted for or selected full stop</u>
<u n="210" who="S0463">why?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0456">well none seems to be of the right calibre and it was it was the whole procedure is too long and started too early and all it seemed to do is just giving the Tories yet another free run as they had in twenty ten erm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0456">and of course having having one that goes on for nearly a year is just ridiculous</u>
<u n="214" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0456">yeah it's it's clear you should have hustings and then vote but you know why would it take longer than an election campaign?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0463">are you unsympathetic towards Corbyn's policies?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0456">I don't know enough of his policies no I mean it's the I can't I can't put myself in the role because who I am? as I said I'm just a single member whoever becomes the leader or whoever I would want to become the leader that's neither here nor there whatever happens after whatever happens between September</u>
<u n="218" who="S0463">mm twelfth I think</u>
<u n="219" who="S0456">twelfth so next week and twenty-twenty or ideally before that but god know that's not going to happen within a fixed term parliaments unless they all die erm that is the important bit and of course what you would want to see is you know you have the contenders so they are obviously people who have a drive to do something you want them integrated erm cos they all will have something to offer erm and that's the thing yeah what what do I know about Corbyn very little from himself because everybody is telling you what Corbyn does or who he's met or his what his policies are</u>
<u n="220" who="S0463">I know I used to work with him</u>
<u n="221" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0463">I did</u>
<u n="223" who="S0456">well okay</u>
<u n="224" who="S0463">erm because I used to have to respond to him er in writing and at meetings when he was standing for <anon type="place"/> council</u>
<u n="225" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0463">erm and you know he was a pain in the arse and it but it a good way erm cos he</u>
<u n="227" who="S0456">he was insistent</u>
<u n="228" who="S0463">he was insistent and he was very erm good at representing his constituents doing his job</u>
<u n="229" who="S0456">mm yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0463">erm but he's I mean I met him a couple of weeks ago over in <anon type="place"/> and he was just dismissing it as a Trot because of his cap</u>
<u n="231" who="S0456">yeah well this is this is what I found so funny he's like er I kept saying people people will probably think I'm I'm a Corbynite now because I have the same cap I wore it before it was fashionable and I'm not going to stop it I would stop it if Cameron would wear it</u>
<u n="232" who="S0463" trans="overlap">yeah there's never been a Trot you know he's he's</u>
<u n="233" who="S0456">yeah but Trot is just dismissive of anything that isn't what he wants</u>
<u n="234" who="S0463">I know but he's just old Labour</u>
<u n="235" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0463">he's he's he's good Labour he's he's there's nothing extreme about him</u>
<u n="237" who="S0456">yeah well as the young people say yeah you think Corbyn is <vocal desc="laugh"/> is extreme it's like or radical it's like well you cannot really have been around for that long and be the radical radical you have to be a very British kind of radical</u>
<u n="238" who="S0463">he's your perfect erm Orwellian kind of and I mean not in nineteen eighty-four</u>
<u n="239" who="S0456">no</u>
<u n="240" who="S0463">but I mean the Lion and Lion and the Unicorn</u>
<u n="241" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0463">perfect mild-mannered erm British revolutionary</u>
<u n="243" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0463">you know he's all you want</u>
<u n="245" who="S0456">he drinks his tea</u>
<u n="246" who="S0463">yeah and who sat at the feet of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for many years <unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0463">you know these are good hearted people you know they're not bloody extremists</u>
<u n="249" who="S0456">do you think do you think the the whole fast lane thing as they said that was <trunc>Cor</trunc> er that was Osborne's attempt to have an early flick at Corbyn to say look there's traitor I mean how many people really do think that we do need Trident in order to defend the realm of the kingdom</u>
<u n="250" who="S0463">I don't know I don't know in the eighties it was a really big deal and</u>
<u n="251" who="S0456">yeah but then communism was still</u>
<u n="252" who="S0463">it was the Cold War was still there</u>
<u n="253" who="S0456">yeah yeah no</u>
<u n="254" who="S0463">well it was definitely a vote loser for Labour and that is the <unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0456" trans="overlap">no but <unclear/> I mean <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0463">well I think the interesting thing was the Scottish people clearly don't don't want it</u>
<u n="257" who="S0456">yes</u>
<u n="258" who="S0463">of course erm so that in itself is interesting</u>
<u n="259" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0463">no it's I think we're on the real real cusp and I can't the optimistic side of me says this grassroots movement which is what it is in support of Corbyn is the first real sign of the social media age in British parliamentary politics maybe SNP was as well actually when the broadsheet and the tabloid media are becoming less influential</u>
<u n="261" who="S0456">mm which you will want given what they are like</u>
<u n="262" who="S0463">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
