<text id="STGP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:34:57</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0208</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home, Leeds</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Mattresses, lectures, university topics</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting about general stuff</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0208">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0202">like I really like that cos like <trunc>so</trunc> like it doesn't matter what you study at some point you're going to find it boring and like that's okay but it's nice when the tutors make an effort to make you like it</u>
<u n="2" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm mm definitely</u>
<u n="3" who="S0202">because I think there's nothing worse than sitting there doing something that you really fucking hate and the person who's teaching it you is such a boring bastard that you know like it just makes it worse <pause dur="short"/> do you just want to sit down here for ten minutes I just need to transfer some money to someone</u>
<u n="4" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0202">back in a sec I'll just need to <unclear/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0208">right could you get my phone from the living room please?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0208">thanks</u>
<event desc="0202 leaves"/>
<u n="9" who="S0208"><pause dur="long"/> your mattress is way comfortable than mine</u>
<u n="10" who="S0202">it's really comfy innit? I don't think I'm gonna change my mattress but erm he is coming round one day next week em to look at the mattresses so if you want a new one?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0208">I I do because there are some points where I roll over and I have like a big sharp point in my back and it's the mattress</u>
<u n="12" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0208">and I try moving and it's just</u>
<u n="14" who="S0202">erm maybe erm here's an idea get some er fake blood and put a stain on it on the mattress because erm it being uncomfy they're not gonna change it but if it's unhygienic they'll change it</u>
<u n="15" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0202">so and then if they don't change it it's not real blood anyway so it doesn't matter but they will change it if there's a stain like that on it cos it's unhygienic</u>
<u n="17" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0202">and whatnot but oh it's so nice having nice neighbors and like getting on with your flat mates</u>
<u n="19" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I know so happy about it I've not even been here a week yet and I'm just so content</u>
<u n="20" who="S0202">yeah me too</u>
<u n="21" who="S0208">about everything</u>
<u n="22" who="S0202">I don't even care that it's not the nicest of houses cos it's just so it's cozy it's always warm here and we've got nice neighbors we've got nice flat mates I'm so happy</u>
<u n="23" who="S0208">yeah we're really lucky</u>
<u n="24" who="S0202">I I know I keep saying this but we are going to have arguments cos everyone has arguments when they live together but the fact of the matter is we <trunc>li</trunc>live with such nice people</u>
<u n="25" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0202">that they're not going to be arguments like last year do you know what I mean like?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0208">they won't be arguments will they? they'll be like little bit of like not being okay with everything but</u>
<u n="28" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0208">oh</u>
<u n="30" who="S0202">erm <pause dur="short"/> right okay so I've got to send cos I bought some more Herbal Life but my friend bought it me erm for erm cos he gets fifty per cent discount and I get thirty-five per cent</u>
<u n="31" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0202">so I'm like erm do you mind buying erm some and I'll send you the money so I was gonna transfer it it can't it's not he can't accept erm payments at the moment for his bank so I've got to send it via Paypal</u>
<u n="33" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0202">pay <unclear/> hundred and forty <unclear/> mm GBP continue <pause dur="long"/> okay so I'm sending a friend or family erm oh I'm just going to send fuck it erm <pause dur="long"/> ah I erm spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like do you I was saying I worried about stuff about stuff about us being engaged and stuff I just told him what I worried about like that I worried that I made a mistake like he <trunc>w</trunc> like what if one day we fell out of love or he weren't the one and stuff and he's like it's okay to be scared about that</u>
<u n="35" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0202">cos I just explained to him for him it's alright cos he has like a a solid family like his mum and dad and never going to get divorced like they've been together years and stuff like that but for me it's different because like I don't have that</u>
<u n="37" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0202">and I think that's why I'm so scared</u>
<u n="39" who="S0208">it's cos you've seen how bad it can be</u>
<u n="40" who="S0202">yeah and I think that's why I was so worried about it but and I worried about telling <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos I didn't want to hurt his feelings and him think that like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I didn't want him to think that I don't love him or I do or it's too soon or anything like that cos I don't think it were too soon it were perfect timing but like he <trunc>w</trunc> I was just scared that I'd hurt his feelings do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0208">yeah but he's way too understanding for that to happen anyway</u>
<u n="42" who="S0202">ah yeah definitely but it were nice to talk to him about it like and just off my chest</u>
<u n="43" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0202">cos now I feel better like I'm not worried about it</u>
<u n="45" who="S0208">good</u>
<u n="46" who="S0202">cos he he understand like he were really understanding about it and he was just like it's one of the only things that you've ever worried about that isn't stupid</u>
<u n="47" who="S0208">oh bless him</u>
<u n="48" who="S0202">and like it's like thank you for being understanding cos it's not you or anything like that it's just I'm scared that it might it might not work or stuff like that and I'm just</u>
<u n="49" who="S0208">that is a natural reaction anyway when you make a big commitment obviously every single thing that you could ever worry about sort of comes in one go doesn't it?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0208">I can't <trunc>s</trunc> talk from experience but it would just seem like a natural reaction to me</u>
<u n="52" who="S0202">but yeah so what is that? <pause dur="long"/> debit card what is it you are asking me for? is that expiry date or? <pause dur="long"/> CSC it just says <pause dur="long"/> ah yeah why is it not working? <pause dur="long"/> what is going on? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="53" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0202">okay so I'm going to try and <pause dur="short"/> in fact I'm going to try and <pause dur="long"/> did you did you have a good time then?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0208">with my dad?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0202">yeah did you have a good time?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0202">nice to see him</u>
<u n="59" who="S0208">nice to see him when he's more relaxed about thing as well cos a lot of things have been on his mind worrying him since his trip in England like seeing my grandad and knowing that he's okay and I guess seeing that I'm okay with the house</u>
<u n="60" who="S0202">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="62" who="S0202">okay so it's <pause dur="long"/> ah right that's why it doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> save <pause dur="long"/> oh right okay so I've got it linked to a different PayPpl account then that's why it's not working log out <pause dur="short"/> okay erm <pause dur="long"/> hope that's the right password I bet it's not <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> yay <pause dur="short"/> bank account linked okay send money to a friend oh there we go <pause dur="short"/> send money to a friend <pause dur="long"/> okay <pause dur="long"/> do you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who took us out <trunc>f</trunc> drinking that time for free</u>
<u n="63" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0202">erm that's who was who has bought it for me</u>
<u n="65" who="S0208">ah he's such a sweetheart that was a really fun night</u>
<u n="66" who="S0202">yeah and he's been in fucking Vegas this year the <trunc>j</trunc>jammy bastard <pause dur="long"/> oh wait there what is that? no I don't oh yeah that's the one</u>
<u n="67" who="S0208">mm this seems interesting on that erm <unclear>fucking lost science</unclear> it says does my voice really sound like that and it's an article saying have you ever wondered why</u>
<u n="68" who="S0202">right tell me the answer</u>
<u n="69" who="S0208">er we all hear our own voice as a more deep and resonant version than how others perceive it but why exactly is that? put simply it has to do with the difference between air conducted versus bone conducted bone sound transmission so it's basically because we hear our own voice going through our bones it come out different than people who hear it through the air interesting <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0202">oh he's so cut my lecturer oh right done but yeah a hundred and forty quid but what I've bought is I've bought two erm mint choc chips which'll last me like six weeks I've bought all my tablets and I've bought Carlson protein bars and I've bought this herb it's called herbal aloe concentrate and basically what it is is er it helps with your digestion</u>
<u n="71" who="S0208">eight</u>
<u n="72" who="S0202">which I have a problem with so I just thought like I'll get some it's all fifty per cent off so</u>
<u n="73" who="S0208">well you'd end up buying it at some point or other anyway so it's a better price</u>
<u n="74" who="S0202">I just bought it all at once yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0202">well I can ask him any time and he'll do it for me cos like obviously we're friends</u>
<u n="77" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0202">we met through Herbal Life but we are friends he keeps <unclear>blagging</unclear> me to try and start it again and it's like well I haven't got time like</u>
<u n="79" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0202">the uni uni work and stuff</u>
<u n="81" who="S0208">you tried to do it last year didn't you and you only managed to sell it to one person</u>
<u n="82" who="S0202">yeah one one were interested cos it's fucking students</u>
<u n="83" who="S0208">it's uni yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0202">like the majority of my friend base is students and I don't have time to be going backwards and forward to <anon type="place"/> to sell like to give it them or to like talk to them about it</u>
<u n="85" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0202">and people trust you more if you do it face to face cos it does work otherwise I wouldn't buy it myself but when people are spending so much money on something it's better if you see them face to face rather than over the internet where they think you're scamming them</u>
<u n="87" who="S0208">yeah definitely definitely definitely</u>
<u n="88" who="S0202">cos obviously that I'm not doing that but people don't know that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0208">yeah everyone's a little bit well skeptical aren't they</u>
<u n="90" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0208">whenever they try something new</u>
<u n="92" who="S0202">yeah of course</u>
<u n="93" who="S0208">someone's trying to sell them something everyone's automatically skeptical</u>
<u n="94" who="S0202">yeah definitely I'm just going to go and put erm the washer on spin I'll be back in a sec</u>
<u n="95" who="S0208">alright <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0202">put the heating on it's so fucking cold</u>
<u n="97" who="S0208">yeah this video's hilarious</u>
<u n="98" who="S0202"><unclear/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0208">it's just some guy with his earphones in the tube and he's just having a cracking time by himself</u>
<u n="100" who="S0202">oh a Chinese guy?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0208">erm no just a guy literally</u>
<u n="102" who="S0202">oh yeah I've seen that one yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0208">it's so funny</u>
<u n="104" who="S0202">erm we get erm free you've already bought your protection for your laptop haven't you?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0208">erm if I what you mean like against viruses and stuff?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0202">oh right okay</u>
<u n="109" who="S0208">I have a free one through erm my dad's old something like software that he used to get or whatever works on the computer at home <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0202">mm <pause dur="long"/> so erm we should definitely have a night out next week though</u>
<u n="111" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0202">what time are you in on Fridays?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0208">I'm not in on Fridays</u>
<u n="114" who="S0202">do you want to go out on Thursday night?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0208">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="116" who="S0202">to <trunc>W</trunc> er <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0208">definitely yeah I'll ask if erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> want to come with us</u>
<u n="118" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0208">that'd be nice and also we can invite other people like we can go in a group or</u>
<u n="120" who="S0202">yeah whatever</u>
<u n="121" who="S0208">yeah or we should go like as a house I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> probably won't cos they're in at nine AM but we could ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's a nice group to go out in</u>
<u n="122" who="S0202">yeah I really dislike white <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I really dislike her</u>
<u n="123" who="S0208">haven't I told you that since the start though? that there's something off about her</u>
<u n="124" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah I I felt yeah I felt that from the start though as well</u>
<u n="125" who="S0208">and you kept saying like give her the benefit of the doubt and you were like it's just cos you don't know each other but it's just <trunc>def</trunc> there's definitely something off about her</u>
<u n="126" who="S0202" trans="overlap">she yeah she's there's <trunc>de</trunc> she's not very nice</u>
<u n="127" who="S0208">she's just a bit</u>
<u n="128" who="S0202">she's just not very nice person like <trunc>sh</trunc> like whenever they go out like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would invite me but whoever <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s there she never invites me or you and it like and whenever like we all go out like varsity she were with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she didn't want to come like I think she's just a jealous person I think she's jealous that we're we're all good friends and she doesn't like it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0208">but I mean like but not saying this is a bad way but I was friends with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> before <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was</u>
<u n="130" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0208">so <unclear/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0202">she's just not a very nice girl I think that's what it is like and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to worship her and if anyone ever said anything about her bad then she would be like shut the fuck ups sort of thing but now she's more like she's like no yeah I agree cos she's she's like since she's got with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she's changed</u>
<u n="133" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0202">like even <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> admits that she</u>
<u n="135" who="S0208">yeah but no like I just always got the feeling that like I kind of knew we wouldn't be friends because when you get that vibe off someone it doesn't really matter like you're not going to be friends with everyone but I <unclear/> that she wasn't interested in trying to become my friend or anything so I tried a few times being nice to her and making conversation I wasn't really getting much back so I just thought oh alright then I don't really care</u>
<u n="136" who="S0202" trans="overlap">she's not a very nice person like when they came to that engagement party they left because of her</u>
<u n="137" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0202">cos like</u>
<u n="139" who="S0208">yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bless her she was like I really wanted to stay</u>
<u n="140" who="S0202">she's like I really wanted to stay and I <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not the sort of girl that just lies</u>
<u n="141" who="S0208">no</u>
<u n="142" who="S0202">like I I feel like I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really well and I know that she's not like that she's a nice person</u>
<u n="143" who="S0208">no she's a sweetheart there's not a bad bone in her body</u>
<u n="144" who="S0202">yeah and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is just like well you're gonna have to get a taxi back to my house there's no taxis you don't have key and like she just made everyone leave</u>
<u n="145" who="S0208">were they staying at <anon type="place"/> that night?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0202">yeah I said to them you can stay at my house and like and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were like yeah but all your stuff's at mine and like oh I can take them tomorrow and get it and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like making every excuse sort of like why the fuck are you such a cunt like why are you being so mean like?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0208">ruining it for everyone</u>
<u n="148" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0208">like if the other girls didn't want to stay they have a voice</u>
<u n="150" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0208">like you just say I'm gonna go home now like no one cares or like they care but it's not</u>
<u n="152" who="S0202">yeah but like I'm not gonna try and blag them to stay</u>
<u n="153" who="S0208">no it's like if if the other girls wanted to go then all they had to say was yeah we're just gonna go now it's wasn't you know you don't need a spokesperson</u>
<u n="154" who="S0202">yeah but like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like she is very er she's very easily swayed</u>
<u n="155" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0202">like and she does and she did want to leave because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanted to leave and that's what Rachel's like and I understand that me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> aren't really that close anyway and I don't really care about that cos she's annoying but like I understood that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did actually want to leave but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were making them and was like you're such a bitch like why are you being so rude like it's my party I've invited you</u>
<u n="157" who="S0208" trans="overlap"><unclear/> but no I know what you mean but like I'm as awful as this sounds I'm glad that you see it as well cos I was feeling really paranoid</u>
<u n="158" who="S0202">no I do see it</u>
<u n="159" who="S0208">and I was like I don't I don't want to feel paranoid and I was like I don't I don't want to feel paranoid that someone doesn't like me cos it's an awful feeling</u>
<u n="160" who="S0202">yeah it is awful</u>
<u n="161" who="S0208">especially when no one else sees it and no one and agrees with you and stuff you do think that you're just going crackers</u>
<u n="162" who="S0202">but I was just giving her the benefit of the doubt</u>
<u n="163" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0202">like cos I've I've always got that vibe off them but I would give them the benefit of the doubt cos I am like maybe it's just me being paranoid because I am a very paranoid person I'm insecure I know that</u>
<u n="165" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0202">and like every single time I've been out even for her birthday right? she was actually really mean she I was meant she was meant to be picking me up when she picked every up from the train station</u>
<u n="167" who="S0208">right</u>
<u n="168" who="S0202">and then she said I'm picking them up and I'll have to drop them off to come and get you so do you mind just like making your own way to my house on your own like and she said that last minute like at five o'clock she's meant to be picking me up at half five and then I found out that they all went out for a meal didn't invite me didn't ask me to go and then like she was just like oh you need to get a taxi to my house like I was like okay</u>
<u n="169" who="S0208">she just doesn't really care does she? she doesn't</u>
<u n="170" who="S0202">no and I was <trunc>ju</trunc> got the feeling that I weren't wanted and I was just like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0208">that's an awful feeling though isn't it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0202">and I was like why are you being so fucking mean? like what what problem have you got exactly against me like</u>
<u n="173" who="S0208">yeah I think that she's just not really interested in going outside of her circle like making the effort with new people which you know fair enough I don't care</u>
<u n="174" who="S0202">but no need to be fucking rude don't invite me if you don't want me there</u>
<u n="175" who="S0208">yeah but yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0202">if you're gonna make me feel like that</u>
<u n="177" who="S0208">that's that's exactly what I was going to say not everyone is gonna like you you're not gonna be everyone's cup of tea but like don't don't make an effort to like invite them to things just to purposely make them feel unwelcome</u>
<u n="178" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0208">it's like I wouldn't be offended if like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for example wanted to do a birthday thing and like didn't want me to be there I'd be like okay</u>
<u n="180" who="S0202">that's fine</u>
<u n="181" who="S0208"><trunc>bu</trunc> it mean but like it's better than</u>
<u n="182" who="S0202">being there and feeling like you're not wanted</u>
<u n="183" who="S0208">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="184" who="S0202">but yeah like I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about it and when me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were on our way to Chesterfield and she were like she's such a bitch</u>
<u n="185" who="S0208">wow</u>
<u n="186" who="S0202">and I've never heard <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> heard <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> say that about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she used to worship <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but ever since <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had got with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she said she's changed she's not the same person they were</u>
<u n="187" who="S0208">that's a shame though cos they were friends weren't they?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0202">yeah like really close friends but like</u>
<u n="189" who="S0208">what happened?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0202">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was really mean to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the first part the start of their relationship like he was really like he was really I don't know like he was just really rude to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like he'd say stuff to her and like he was using her at first and then obviously they started going out but like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has never really forgiven him she doesn't really like him</u>
<u n="191" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0202">because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> changes when she's with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she's not a nice girl erm and like well fair enough but she still wouldn't let anyone say anything bad about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but then when she said that to me on her way to Chester I was just like well er it's obviously not just me that thinks she's a cunt then</u>
<u n="193" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0202">cos it weren't cos and at the end of the night everyone just left me everyone left me I didn't have a phone and one minute I was with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and like er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said about her going I'm okay and I stood there and then I went to the toilet I came back and they were all gone they just left</u>
<u n="195" who="S0208">that's awful</u>
<u n="196" who="S0202">and like I was like <trunc>wa</trunc> I didn't have a phone or anything I couldn't ring a taxi I had nothing</u>
<u n="197" who="S0208">yeah what did you do?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0202">so I <trunc>li</trunc> I literally just left the club went to the pie shop had some pie and then got Andy to ring me a taxi</u>
<u n="199" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0202">it was so fucking cruel I was like why did you do that? why did you just leave? if you don't like me fair me fair enough but there's no need to be fucking horrible</u>
<u n="201" who="S0208">yeah or like if</u>
<u n="202" who="S0202">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were battered so I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't do it like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0208">yeah cos I was gonna say sometimes people will just assume that someone else had said something and then just sort of like go do you know I mean?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0202">yeah it had nothing to do with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I know that cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were battered like absolutely battered especially after she lost her phone she got even more battered</u>
<u n="205" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0202">like I didn't <trunc>bl</trunc>blame <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for it but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I were just like why you knew I wasn't there</u>
<u n="207" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0202">like it were your idea to leave to go back to your house</u>
<u n="209" who="S0208">she just didn't care</u>
<u n="210" who="S0202">and she just didn't care I was just like you're such a horrible person like I don't want to be your friend</u>
<u n="211" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0202">but like if you don't like someone you don't like someone there's no need to be fucking horrible to them but like I always make an effort to like to talk to them or something we're never gonna be nasty to her like cos that's stooping to her level but that's what she's like so just be wary like if you ever out on a night out and she's there then don't let them leave you</u>
<u n="213" who="S0208">I'm not particularly like I don't really well I don't really like her I don't have any desire to get to know her better or anything</u>
<u n="214" who="S0202">no I mean like if you're with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0202">just watch because like</u>
<u n="217" who="S0208">yeah yeah yeah I'll be careful</u>
<u n="218" who="S0202">make sure they don't leave you</u>
<u n="219" who="S0208">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> usually really good so</u>
<u n="220" who="S0202">yeah she's she's not a very nice person like I haven't got nothing against her but I just don't like her she's just not my type of person like I would never consider her a friend or trust her</u>
<u n="221" who="S0208">what's that you're putting on?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0202">erm protect and protect and perfect just er cream</u>
<u n="223" who="S0208">that's nice</u>
<u n="224" who="S0202">to stop me getting wrinkled cos I'm getting to that age now where I need to start looking after my skin</u>
<u n="225" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0202">fucking old oh it's such a nice feeling living in a house where it's not awkward and horrible</u>
<u n="227" who="S0208">I know</u>
<u n="228" who="S0202">but like I've learnt a lot from the year that we spent with them like</u>
<u n="229" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0202">I've learnt a lot myself and a lot about living with other people</u>
<u n="231" who="S0208">yeah I'm obviously not glad that it happened but</u>
<u n="232" who="S0202">obviously</u>
<u n="233" who="S0208">it's taught me a lot</u>
<u n="234" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0208">so I mean everyone's well it's a fact of life you know you've got to take lessons from your life experiences</u>
<u n="236" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0208">it's a shame it happened but</u>
<u n="238" who="S0202">ah yeah it were horrible when it happened I just going to put my <unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0208">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0202">I know I I mean I've learnt to let something go like I've learned that like if it requires a big deal to me made the make it but if it doesn't then let it go</u>
<u n="241" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0202">and like stuff like that like and I've also learnt to have a think about stuff before I do them if that makes sense so like before you text someone or have a go at them or something think about it first</u>
<u n="243" who="S0208">yeah it's not a bad thing to learn though</u>
<u n="244" who="S0202">no and like patience as well I've learned a lot of patience cos I thought well like <unclear/> and stuff like instead of having a go at them and like going mad about stuff I've just like just thought do you know what it's not worth it</u>
<u n="245" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0202">like just ask them nicely and then if they don't move it then just move it yourself or just put it somewhere where they can get it like it's not a big deal it's not something worth arguing about or falling out over so why make it into that sort of thing</u>
<u n="247" who="S0208">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="248" who="S0202">and I'm really glad that they that I had that opportunity to learn that I mean I wish I hadn't had to learn it in the way that I did but we did so at least we've both taken something from it</u>
<u n="249" who="S0208">yeah it's not like it happened and it ruined us it happened and it made us better people it made the other half worse so I mean</u>
<u n="250" who="S0202">but it's it also it's made this situation so much nicer</u>
<u n="251" who="S0208">yeah cos we can now appreciate a good situation cos we've had such a bad one before</u>
<u n="252" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah cos we can appreciate it more yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0208">yeah not taking it for granted</u>
<u n="254" who="S0202">no <unclear/> got like four bottles of mascara now</u>
<u n="255" who="S0208">I'm gonna have to buy some more soon it's gone gloopy already</u>
<u n="256" who="S0202">have you tried this one of mine before?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0208">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="258" who="S0202">you should try it cos it's really really good stuff</u>
<u n="259" who="S0208">I'll give it a go yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0202">you should try the one that I've opened and then if you like it you can have this one unopened one and just give me the money for it it's only seven pound</u>
<u n="261" who="S0208">that's what I spend on <unclear/> anyway so</u>
<u n="262" who="S0202">so it's not a lot of money</u>
<u n="263" who="S0208">thanks</u>
<u n="264" who="S0202">I need a new makeup bag I really hate this one cos it's just a nightmare to find anything so what's happened now with your rent with your dad? what have you decided? cos you did tell me last night but I forgot?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0208">erm basically if ever I'm in a situation where I know I won't have enough so like say towards Christmas if by some weird reason I have no money left give him a little bit or warning and he'll pop it in for erm and then basically I owe him eight hundred pounds because I paid</u>
<u n="266" who="S0202">you paid the first two</u>
<u n="267" who="S0208">the first two before I got my loan through erm but that's gonna be sorted out at Christmas when I go back</u>
<u n="268" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0208">and I'm just going to transfer everything back that I owe him but erm I'm paying for it he actually let me like have my grown up say</u>
<u n="270" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0208">so I'm just well I was planning on doing that anyway so it's all good</u>
<u n="272" who="S0202">oh bless him I said to him last night do you miss do you miss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and I'm like yeah I really do miss her</u>
<u n="273" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0202">mm but like even when I were travelling and working in New York and stuff I'd only be apart with her from like five days like so they've obviously just missed each other haven't they cos he left just before she got back and obviously she gave him a lift but <unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0208">they've only yeah they're only seen each other for that brief time</u>
<u n="276" who="S0202">I want to get some of that eyeliner you've got</u>
<u n="277" who="S0208">it's it's so good and so cheap</u>
<u n="278" who="S0202">it is very good cos that is permanent</u>
<u n="279" who="S0208">do you still have do you still have my one?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0202">yeah it's on there</u>
<u n="281" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0202">erm it's that one's permanent it's good for a night out but like just for everyday like it's a nightmare to get off like it doesn't come off for like two days</u>
<u n="283" who="S0208">yeah that's why I hate waterproof mascara and stuff it is good for a night out when you're dancing and sweating and stuff but I just can't wear it it rips my eyelashes out when I try and take it off</u>
<u n="284" who="S0202">yeah yeah but yeah erm me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are going to book our flights soon for France</u>
<u n="285" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0202">I've <trunc>persu</trunc> I've persuaded him cos he wanted to go like skiing or something and I was like well we can't we can't go skiing at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s but we can go sledging we can do loads of stuff round there</u>
<u n="287" who="S0208">you can go skiing at mine</u>
<u n="288" who="S0202">can you?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you have the Alps</u>
<u n="291" who="S0208">you don't have Alps you have the Pyrenees we've got all the clothes and stuff that you need</u>
<u n="292" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0208">so when you get up there you just rent boots and skis for the day</u>
<u n="294" who="S0202">really? ah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0208">yeah just get get a day pass</u>
<u n="296" who="S0202">ah we should do that</u>
<u n="297" who="S0208">I</u>
<u n="298" who="S0202">that's so cool</u>
<u n="299" who="S0208">I don't ski but only because I had a skiing accident and I've been terrified to do it and because I didn't start doing it straight away</u>
<u n="300" who="S0202">yeah it's we'll only be going down beginner ones anyway</u>
<u n="301" who="S0208">yeah well like there's the <trunc>da</trunc> the day pass that we usually get well that I used to get lets you go up into the red sloes so you get to do beginner green and then blue and then no blue then green then red but I wouldn't I didn't pay for the black pass because they're obviously I wasn't doing black ones because they're really difficult like you got to the top of the mountain and there's trees and stuff to dodge and you have to be a fucking good skier to do that</u>
<u n="302" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0208">and it's expensive</u>
<u n="304" who="S0202">yeah and you need to be confident enough to do that as well</u>
<u n="305" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0202"><unclear/> good skier</u>
<u n="307" who="S0208">but you are like more than welcome to do that like I don't want to be a party pooper and like not join in on the fun but I just don't I really don't enjoy it</u>
<u n="308" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0208">but I don't mind other people going like he</u>
<u n="310" who="S0202">we'll be able to borrow one of your mum's car or dad's cars won't we? or will we have to rent one?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0208">erm probably best renting one it'll be cheaper because we'd have to put you well my parents would have to put you on insurance</u>
<u n="312" who="S0202">okay yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0208">and that would probably be more expensive than renting a car yourselves</u>
<u n="314" who="S0202">yeah we'll rent one anyway</u>
<u n="315" who="S0208">cos then yeah you can go off and do your own things</u>
<u n="316" who="S0202">like cos obviously I want to spend some time with you guys and I want to show <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like why I love you so much like I want him to be there</u>
<u n="317" who="S0208">yeah but you going off and doing your own things you can always like book a hotel or like get a chalet or something for a week and go skiing and stuff because like we can do our own things and we can enjoy our time together but while <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not broken up for Christmas I'm going be at <anon type="place"/> seeing him and</u>
<u n="318" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0208">doing stuff</u>
<u n="320" who="S0202">I'll see what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to do so we might just stay with you for the week anyway like not really doing much cos your mum and dad will take us sledging and stuff</u>
<u n="321" who="S0208">yeah I mean if if it's good snow like it has been previously then you can just do it erm you don't have to drive to the mountains for it cos we had really really like it was just a shit winter snow wise when you were out</u>
<u n="322" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0208">erm but previous years we've been able to just walk up the hill next to us and just sled down that you literally don't even have to drive to the Mountains to go sledging</u>
<u n="324" who="S0202"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would love that</u>
<u n="325" who="S0208">so it is good fun but it's the it's the thing that annoys me like going to the mountains I always feel so ill when I get there because of the roads you have to take to get there</u>
<u n="326" who="S0202">right yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0208">whereas I could enjoy myself if we're just going to the hill like just walking distance</u>
<u n="328" who="S0202">yeah you don't have to get in the car do you?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0208">yeah why is there no sound</u>
<u n="330" who="S0202">I love cleaning my makeup bag</u>
<u n="331" who="S0208">why is there no sound?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0202">ah have you clicked on a link on Facebook?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0202">it it's does that all the time it's broken like Facebook it's fucking shit these new updates that they've been doing are shit</u>
<u n="335" who="S0208">yeah pointless have to exit and reload it just watching the thing of like girl fails funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0202">oh this is so funny</u>
<u n="337" who="S0208">yeah her hair comes off doesn't it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0202">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0208">idiot</u>
<u n="340" who="S0202">no wonder she bleaches it so much <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="341" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0202">she fell off</u>
<u n="343" who="S0208">yeah the mum fell off and the little kid is like I've got to get my bike didn't care about the mum</u>
<u n="344" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
