<text id="STK7">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:19:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0487 S0488</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc></rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics></topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0487">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>Undergraduate</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Hindi -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0488">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Hindi -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0487">type of thing but at things like that you do actually really need like a hot drink and everyone was like storming the tables and there was like loads of like tea <unclear/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0488">and did people but I thought it was like at a park</u>
<u n="3" who="S0487">yeah yeah they like put it in a corner but</u>
<u n="4" who="S0488" trans="overlap">did a lot of people drink?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0487">yeah most people were like</u>
<u n="6" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but this and also like <trunc>t</trunc> for it be er like an open pub is quite like hard</u>
<u n="7" who="S0487">no but no one would there were so many obviously it was like you could</u>
<u n="8" who="S0488">yeah it was like they say</u>
<u n="9" who="S0487" trans="overlap">there was no way and they were wearing black it's like the <unclear/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0488" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah like erm who are those people that are <unclear/> looking so happy?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0487">yeah it was like oh</u>
<u n="12" who="S0488">well but see I would have thought they'd do like wear colours thing</u>
<u n="13" who="S0487">no like <pause dur="short"/> I didn't get any like invitation cos I knew it was happening and I don't know what the invitation said</u>
<u n="14" who="S0488">like no bitchiness <vocal desc="laugh"/> and no talking about like your credit cards</u>
<u n="15" who="S0487">but did I tell you I <unclear/> with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0488">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0487">cos basically</u>
<u n="18" who="S0488">oh this headscarf thing?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0487">no that was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god</u>
<u n="21" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah that was like oh</u>
<u n="22" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/> another thing</u>
<u n="23" who="S0487">no basically there's this girl <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we were always enemies we were like arch enemies and</u>
<u n="24" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0487">but she was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s best friend as well and we like were really jealous and possessive of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0488">really?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0487">and erm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0488" trans="overlap">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="29" who="S0487">yeah and it was like this she was like I just we were like chalk and cheese and we just hated each other and she was really tall and like from <anon type="place"/> and really blonde and she wasn't like <pause dur="short"/> a mean girl but she was like <pause dur="short"/> but we just</u>
<u n="30" who="S0488" trans="overlap">bit square</u>
<u n="31" who="S0487">we just hated each other but like mainly as well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like I remember like there was this pivotal thing when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had like I think it was her fourteenth and she like invited <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> instead of me and it cos it was like be too awkward if we both went erm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0488">was it that bad?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0487">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0487">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah and I remember once like in year seven</u>
<u n="36" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0487">I was bitching the whole way home from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum drove us</u>
<u n="38" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0487">back from <anon type="place"/> and the whole way home I was bitching about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum like stopped the car and she was like cos I was being really childish and I was like her <unclear/> is just her head's really big</u>
<u n="40" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum stopped the car on the highway and was like you know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is a real English rose she's a really pure beautiful English rose and I was like</u>
<u n="42" who="S0488" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0487">yeah and it was like this</u>
<u n="44" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but you were <trunc>li</trunc> eleven</u>
<u n="45" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were like arch enemies and I remember once she like</u>
<u n="46" who="S0488" trans="overlap">was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0487">and she thought I was like a lesbian she was like really homophobic and weird erm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0488">so she was basically she was like quite square but nothing like she wasn't</u>
<u n="49" who="S0487" trans="overlap">no but she had this like</u>
<u n="50" who="S0488" trans="overlap">brilliant but she was really</u>
<u n="51" who="S0487" trans="overlap">hate for me she would always like stare at me like that and we like just hated each other erm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this is so classic <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0487">yeah and and at the funeral it was so bizarre like I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> basically I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0488">were you like?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0487"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah I was just like</u>
<u n="56" who="S0488" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0487"><unclear>fuck</unclear></u>
<u n="58" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0487">yeah I said what are you doing here? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0487">no I so</u>
<u n="62" who="S0488" trans="overlap">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at the disco like that kind of like</u>
<u n="63" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah I was like what made you think you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no erm I saw basically <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I didn't really clock I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but it was like <trunc>m</trunc> I dunno it was just kind of eyes went through her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there and I was like but we were standing in a really tight circle and everyone had left the church and like I was just like crying and I was like talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she was like hugging me and <trunc>bei</trunc> really nice and we were saying like we should meet up and it's so sad and then like me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were just like <pause dur="short"/> she just almost like staring at me really weirdly and like I was like I just didn't say anything and I was <trunc>ju</trunc> always like it was just so weird none of us said anything we didn't say like even hi</u>
<u n="66" who="S0488">I thought you would have like hugged</u>
<u n="67" who="S0487">I know it but</u>
<u n="68" who="S0488" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="69" who="S0487" trans="overlap">it wasn't like hate</u>
<u n="70" who="S0488">it would have been</u>
<u n="71" who="S0487" trans="overlap">it was like</u>
<u n="72" who="S0488" trans="overlap">the moment where you like hug and be like I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="73" who="S0487">I know</u>
<u n="74" who="S0488" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0487">that's I was like we were both waiting for it but I I couldn't tell if she was like I couldn't tell if it was like <pause dur="short"/> what she was thinking</u>
<u n="76" who="S0488">but</u>
<u n="77" who="S0487" trans="overlap">or if she thought like what a bitch she didn't say hi</u>
<u n="78" who="S0488">did she read at the funeral?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0487">no</u>
<u n="80" who="S0488">do you think maybe she was <unclear>like you read</unclear> or not? do you think that's?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0487" trans="overlap">but I don't know cos it think like I don't know if people knew how like close they <pause dur="short"/> ah I don't know it was so weird</u>
<u n="82" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but <trunc>w</trunc> did they go to like primary school together?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0487">no they were like <unclear/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0488">but then how did like you both meet?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0487">we like were it was like <trunc>s</trunc> me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were in like English and geography</u>
<u n="86" who="S0488" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="87" who="S0487">but we were all the same form and it was like who's going to sit next to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and we'd be like</u>
<u n="88" who="S0488">really?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0487" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0488" trans="overlap">was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like literally that popular?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0487">no me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were like</u>
<u n="92" who="S0488">oh</u>
<u n="93" who="S0487" trans="overlap">we didn't hated each other basically</u>
<u n="94" who="S0488">but do you think it was partly jealousy over <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0487">well it was like <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely <pause dur="long"/> but isn't that really like strange? <pause dur="short"/> I just don't know what that moment meant I like always think about it and it's like I do really regret not saying anything so then at like I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so she like I was like engaged in a conversation and she like didn't when the conversation finished <pause dur="short"/> she just was staring at me so weirdly the <pause dur="short"/> and like we just never said hi and we it wasn't friendly it wasn't like a warm feeling but it was a cold it was like <pause dur="short"/> it was so weird <pause dur="short"/> it like I can't describe it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0488">but maybe it was her just accepting <pause dur="short"/> maybe it was like accepting like <pause dur="short"/> this is it like we can't hate each other now and that was it or something</u>
<u n="97" who="S0487">no but it wasn't that like</u>
<u n="98" who="S0488" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it wasn't that nice</u>
<u n="99" who="S0487" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0488">it was literally just like confused</u>
<u n="101" who="S0487">it was like really like</u>
<u n="102" who="S0488" trans="overlap">maybe it was literally like one of you should have said something in the moment when and you missed it</u>
<u n="103" who="S0487">yeah basically ah but the funeral was <pause dur="short"/> it was really nicely done though it wasn't like and the wake it was so it like wakes are really nice just see everyone and it's quite nicely social like everyone it's like everyone knows this one person and you're all there for the same reason and you're all like feeling the same emotions</u>
<u n="104" who="S0488">imagine being like a funeral crasher</u>
<u n="105" who="S0487">being what?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0488">like a professional <trunc>fu</trunc> you know like the wedding crashers? a funeral crasher <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0487">there's a film called that</u>
<u n="108" who="S0488">the funeral crasher?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0488">just to get like free drinks and like make friends</u>
<u n="111" who="S0487">mum would so be one</u>
<u n="112" who="S0488">yeah mum like loves death</u>
<u n="113" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0488">no she does though she like really loves drama like the</u>
<u n="115" who="S0487" trans="overlap">mum should be like she to get it out of her she should write like Agatha Christies</u>
<u n="116" who="S0488">or like she should work in like a mortuary</u>
<u n="117" who="S0487"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but you know mum was telling like on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s funeral</u>
<u n="119" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0488">apparently erm this like woman who was really she was friends with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but mum like always hated her</u>
<u n="121" who="S0487">oh I what and she came and was like we have to <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0488" trans="overlap">yeah and it was like before she'd actually been cremated and it was like not a good time</u>
<u n="123" who="S0487">that's so weird</u>
<u n="124" who="S0488" trans="overlap">and <trunc>appar</trunc> yeah and then they gave mum the ring and she was like I'll take those</u>
<u n="125" who="S0487">oh <pause dur="short"/> there are some people who are just like death <unclear>monkey</unclear></u>
<u n="126" who="S0488">oh I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> in erm there's this writer called Augusten Burroughs I don't know if you've read Running with Scissors or any of his books but he's a really good writer he's like amazing</u>
<u n="127" who="S0487">who?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0488">Augusten Burroughs</u>
<u n="129" who="S0487">no</u>
<u n="130" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but his books are about his life but it's not like boring autobiography it's literally like one chapter will be all about like the time he like had sex in a mortuary cos he got this boyfriend who was like worked in one</u>
<u n="131" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0488">and erm how at first he found it really creepy that this guy like no he was like an erm embalmer and then like <trunc>h</trunc> the guy like he they like he like gave him a blow job like and all <trunc>th</trunc> like around all the bodies or something but like it's all true and like when he was like twelve cos he had this <trunc>cr</trunc>crazy hippy mum</u>
<u n="133" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0488" trans="overlap">she sent him to live with his psychologist <trunc>h</trunc> no with her psychiatrist and the psychiatrist was really weird and crazy and like then he he like groomed him and stuff</u>
<u n="135" who="S0487">really?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0488">and like the names have been changed but it's all true and the <trunc>psychologi</trunc> the <trunc>psychia</trunc> because <pause dur="short"/> augusten Burroughs's thing is that it's like all true he doesn't write about fiction he writes things that have <trunc>ha</trunc> has happened in his life but he does change names</u>
<u n="137" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0488">erm he got sued the psychiatrist sued him and said like you've ruined my business and like it's <trunc>n</trunc>none of it's true and you have to like say in the like media this isn't true</u>
<u n="139" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0488">erm but Augusten Burroughs like refused and just paid him loads of money because was like no it's true this is my</u>
<u n="141" who="S0487" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0488">principles and then he like</u>
<u n="143" who="S0487">oh</u>
<u n="144" who="S0488">he like was like this is erm this is like a victory for free speech and stuff</u>
<u n="145" who="S0487">wow</u>
<u n="146" who="S0488">cos he didn't wanna he didn't wanna like go back and <pause dur="short"/> cos that's like his thing is that he <trunc>wri</trunc></u>
<u n="147" who="S0487" trans="overlap">what like because of money now?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0488">yeah so he paid him like I don't think it was like it was like er fifty thousand dollars that that actually doesn't seem like that much</u>
<u n="149" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0488">but like or something like that and but like he just refused to like accept he just refused to say <vocal desc="laugh"/> it wasn't true <pause dur="short"/> but I think</u>
<u n="151" who="S0487" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="152" who="S0488" trans="overlap">the point was that that it was kind of done with the psychiatrist is like he was saying even though my name's been changed everyone will know it's me</u>
<u n="153" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0488">but then it's well now everyone will know it's you</u>
<u n="155" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0488" trans="overlap">and not just like your family and friends cos he could have just moved to a new town</u>
<u n="157" who="S0487">what so did the psychiatrist like do stuff? or was it more just like</u>
<u n="158" who="S0488">I don't yeah I think it was like</u>
<u n="159" who="S0487">a <unclear>hand on the bum</unclear></u>
<u n="160" who="S0488">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> obviously if it was that serious like police would be involved <pause dur="short"/> but it was like semi serious</u>
<u n="161" who="S0487">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0488" trans="overlap">so all a bit weird</u>
<u n="163" who="S0487">sounds really cool <pause dur="long"/> it was so weird it was so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it was like you know I was telling you like before <pause dur="short"/> when they did that special thing at the British Museum? <pause dur="short"/> er the Natural History Museum and then like they just made <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that really crude picture of like her a a dinosaur like having sex with it or something</u>
<u n="164" who="S0488">oh my god that is like the weirdest thing wasn't that for her?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0487" trans="overlap">did you see it? and she like really didn't like it</u>
<u n="166" who="S0488" trans="overlap">for her birthday?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0487" trans="overlap">and when we got home we were like oh</u>
<u n="168" who="S0488">was that her birthday or something?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0487">no it was like cos she was ill and it was like her last like they wanted to like treat her and er like it was really nice amazing to arrange the thing at the Science Museum but then she said it was like <pause dur="short"/> she like loved it but then like they'd be like <unclear>cock</unclear> and like the scientist was like cos she'd like arranged she'd like got permission from work cos they sent like a really sad email like said our friend's like dying and she like loves your museum and stuff and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said yeah when I got there</u>
<u n="170" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but also like it's so bad because <pause dur="short"/> now in the future if that happens again <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0488">they're gonna be like oh well if it's like last time</u>
<u n="173" who="S0487">there's so <unclear/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but was it a sleepover?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0487">no <trunc>l</trunc>like basically I came from <anon type="place"/> in like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s Ferrari <vocal desc="laugh"/> and erm I yeah I missed the like going to the thing but they were in <anon type="place"/> er in <anon type="place"/> like having a <trunc>pi</trunc>pizza and I got there like at the end and it was like so</u>
<u n="176" who="S0488" trans="overlap">oh and everyone</u>
<u n="177" who="S0487" trans="overlap">I mean how</u>
<u n="178" who="S0487" trans="overlap">was like smoking outside?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0487">yeah and drinking beer and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like erm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0488" trans="overlap">couldn't yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0487" trans="overlap">they were just kind of in joking a bit as well about like their boyfriends and it was like <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing? and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like showed me the thing and they were all like isn't it great? and me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were like and it was like I it was like yeah you've <trunc>ye</trunc> cos I think before there was no one who like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0488" trans="overlap">do you think her boyfriend would have been like</u>
<u n="183" who="S0487">I think <pause dur="short"/> no I think he would just be like <pause dur="short"/> her it was just really cringe and like why? what's the point? like leave <unclear>now</unclear> and then we got home and we were like oh</u>
<u n="184" who="S0488">yeah like cringe</u>
<u n="185" who="S0487">like so <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0488" trans="overlap">did she show her mum? or is that do you think it was embarrassing?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0487" trans="overlap">I think she was really embarrassed <pause dur="short"/> no I think she did show her mum afterwards it's I mean she was really open about like anything to do with sex</u>
<u n="188" who="S0488">what and her mum's like you poor thing</u>
<u n="189" who="S0487">I wasn't there when she showed her mum but I remember she was I think she was embarrassed that they'd taken they'd like made her like</u>
<u n="190" who="S0488">the effort</u>
<u n="191" who="S0487">no and they made her like do a photo like holding it up I think she was worried like she didn't want it to be on Facebook <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0488">did you stay the night at hers that night?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0487">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I did <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0488">was she eating a lot at the end?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0487">er yeah cos she was not at the end but in the summer cos she was having all that hemp so she</u>
<u n="196" who="S0488" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0487" trans="overlap">had the munchies</u>
<u n="198" who="S0488">mm mm <pause dur="long"/> do you think her mum wanted to her to get treatment?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0487">would have what?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0488">wanted her to get treatment? <pause dur="short"/> like it wasn't like the dad <pause dur="short"/> pushed that on her?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0487">no I think like <pause dur="short"/> I think the mum at first wanted but also knew that the possibilities of recovery were so low and the <trunc>d</trunc> the <trunc>d</trunc> <unclear>meditation</unclear> it it definitely would do <trunc>eith</trunc> whether you survive or not was so damaging that it's like yes she wanted her to go for treatment cos there's always hope and as a parent any way of like keeping them alive that's like instinct but then I think it was also like <pause dur="short"/> she really</u>
<u n="202" who="S0488" trans="overlap">it's</u>
<u n="203" who="S0487" trans="overlap">just respected that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was so strong and like</u>
<u n="204" who="S0488">was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really like?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0487"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like amazing she was like I know like <pause dur="short"/> I don't want I <trunc>s</trunc> I saw the <trunc>ve</trunc> like what those teenagers were like with no hair like vegetables I want like if I'm gonna go I wanna be strong and like be myself and I've had so much treatment and <trunc>n</trunc> I want to be natural and eat natural food and like <pause dur="short"/> I don't trust what the doctors are saying and I'm completely like she was so <pause dur="short"/> she was like there was no doubt</u>
<u n="206" who="S0488">so do you think her mum was just <trunc>li</trunc> okay what like you <trunc>thi</trunc></u>
<u n="207" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0488">do you think?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0487" trans="overlap">and it's like</u>
<u n="210" who="S0488" trans="overlap">she didn't even argue?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0487">I think for like a few weeks it was like a big thing like obviously I I'm sure her mum like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how she</u>
<u n="212" who="S0488">but do you think she thinks about it now or do you think she's not like that?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0487">I think she does but not in a way of like like erm <pause dur="long"/> I just don't think it's like <pause dur="short"/> I don't think she thinks like <pause dur="short"/> there was any <pause dur="short"/> cos with the type of cancer she had the the success rates were so low and it's like is it a success rate if you can't talk for like <pause dur="short"/> you can't like talk and like you're such a vegetable that you're still in hospital for years and like?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0488">is it literally like that? would it</u>
<u n="215" who="S0487">from the chemo it's like</u>
<u n="216" who="S0488">literally like years later you're still a shell?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0487">yeah it's like you're just so weak and like <pause dur="short"/> yes some people get over it but also how many of them have been dealing with cancer since they were six? every year like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had you know I <trunc>thi</trunc> <trunc>a</trunc>and I think also for her parents it's like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it's different when it's like your first time it's like she'd had so many chemo like she'd been through it all and they'd like know that experience and then this wasn't even that wasn't even the worst type of cancer and like I think yeah if it's your first cancer then you're definitely gonna go for the treatment but when you've like been plagued with it for like <pause dur="short"/> fourteen years</u>
<u n="218" who="S0488">but I think like her brother that like cos like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was talking about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and she was like losing a sibling is like the worst thing in the world and she was saying like I think it's probably worse</u>
<u n="219" who="S0487">losing a child?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0488">yeah I don't know if she said that or like losing a parent or losing like a partner she said</u>
<u n="221" who="S0487">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0488">like your husband or whatever and she's like I still think about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> all the time it's like but for them</u>
<u n="223" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0488">to be like that young is just like</u>
<u n="225" who="S0487">so that's like really the worst</u>
<u n="226" who="S0488">and like there's only <trunc>h</trunc> two of them</u>
<u n="227" who="S0487">and they were so close</u>
<u n="228" who="S0488">really?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0487">they were really <pause dur="short"/> they were so close</u>
<u n="230" who="S0488">I guess for him like <pause dur="short"/> probably like having a girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> like to have like a <trunc>si</trunc> like another relationship with a girl</u>
<u n="231" who="S0487">yeah like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> mum was when I like went <trunc>rou</trunc> cos I was going round for dinner before I <pause dur="short"/> mm yeah like in the winter and she was saying she just said like in the car like she's just so scared he'll never be able to love again and she was</u>
<u n="232" who="S0488" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0487" trans="overlap">like gonna freeze up forever and like he just <pause dur="short"/> I dunno he's just he's so sad like we were talking about he cos he's always wanted to go to Australia and he has like an uncle there and then like we were talking about like swimming there and he was like <pause dur="short"/> why would you swim when there are so many sharks? what's the point? yeah swimming is nice but you know why would you wanna put yourself in that danger? I would never swim there and it was like really like closed</u>
<u n="234" who="S0488">the thing is though like I think <pause dur="long"/> is he going to uni do you know?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0487">well no cos he's like has to he didn't pass one of his I think he did like English GCSE and he's due in college but like <trunc>di</trunc> he's like knows the school really well he's been there since nursery like <anon type="place"/> high school</u>
<u n="236" who="S0488">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0487">like <anon type="place"/> community school so goes from like</u>
<u n="238" who="S0488" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0487" trans="overlap"><unclear>it's state</unclear> but so the teachers are letting him do like just take as long as he needs so he's like seventeen but he's doing I think he's doing animation</u>
<u n="240" who="S0488">oh that's cool</u>
<u n="241" who="S0487" trans="overlap">and like art but slowly trying to retake his maths and English I think</u>
<u n="242" who="S0488">so young <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">I really wanna <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> shall we like get in bed and watch it?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah we should make soup</u>
<u n="245" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">shall we make soup instead of microwave?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah I've <unclear/> but like not very much</u>
<u n="247" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">oh no <pause dur="short"/> we could have pasta</u>
<u n="248" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">we could</u>
<u n="249" who="S0487" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">bit late just can't just feel really lazy</u>
<u n="250" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">let's just have soup with cheddar and cheese with the cheddar</u>
<u n="251" who="S0487" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah and loads of cheddar</u>
<u n="252" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah the whole</u>
<u n="253" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">I think there's only one roll though</u>
<u n="254" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">ah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">boo boo <vocal desc="laugh"/> okay just have loads of basic cheddar</u>
<u n="256" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">just eat like loads of cheddar</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
