<text id="STNX">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:35:36</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Babies, teaching, friends</topics>
		<activity>Couple chat about friends</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0144">okay it's on</u>
<u n="2" who="S0024">do I really need</u>
<u n="3" who="S0144" trans="overlap">if I mute it? hang on a minute does that mean <pause dur="short"/> oh no I hope all these recordings I've done can hear what we said</u>
<u n="4" who="S0024">mm that's just the speaker</u>
<u n="5" who="S0144">is it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0024">yeah you gonna plug it in but er I <pause dur="short"/> I need my I haven't got long actually because I'm supposed to go er to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s erm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0024">have a look at her bicycle <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144">but she's got an old one you don't want that</u>
<u n="12" who="S0024">I know I was thinking more about it I might just go <trunc>o</trunc> like go over</u>
<u n="13" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>li</trunc> like an old granny bicycle</u>
<u n="14" who="S0024">no that's no good for me is it I</u>
<u n="15" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="16" who="S0024">especially if you're not very good at riding a bike you need a good one</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> they're really hard to ride those ones</u>
<u n="18" who="S0024">okay well she just offered it for free for me to have a go on and I'll just go and have a look</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144">you shouldn't do it with your toe</u>
<u n="20" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> really? what just in case it gets dirty or something?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144">well no cos we're bound to</u>
<u n="22" who="S0024">catch it catch the</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144" trans="overlap">you know if you put your foot down or something quickly</u>
<u n="24" who="S0024" trans="overlap">if I <trunc>ca</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> mm if I catch the lint and then it could stick and then rip</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144">er yeah I wouldn't do it</u>
<u n="26" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay well I'll text her and say well let's leave it for now it's just I didn't want her to <pause dur="short"/> forget oh that's nice coffee I'd better not have that one <pause dur="short"/> yeah woo what's that? it's a Snickers</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144">what were you saying about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0024">I've forgotten</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144">about her kissing</u>
<u n="30" who="S0024">oh she's erm ever since we did <trunc>th</trunc> er no she kissed me on the cheek right by my ear cos it makes me laugh sometimes cos it tickles <pause dur="short"/> I was saying you should clean shave one day and she if she does it to you cos she won't do it if you've got like the little bit of stubble</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0024">it's not the same because you've the cos you feel like her smooth skin</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0024">against yours and it tickles and she just does it later then she sticks her tongue out and then slobbers all over you</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0024">it's really cute</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0024">look at her we've got to do something about this</u>
<u n="39" who="S0144">I know I'm gonna have to go mozzie hunting tonight</u>
<u n="40" who="S0024">the oh I can't believe it I'm so embarrassed because yesterday she had what two mozzie bites</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0024">and I checked her room and I thought I checked her room and now look at her she's got them all over her head</u>
<u n="43" who="S0144">I know</u>
<u n="44" who="S0024" trans="overlap">she went to play play with everybody today <pause dur="short"/> and it's just like oh I don't know I just feel a bit</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144">mm looks like we left her out in the woods</u>
<u n="46" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well there's nothing you can do if you can't find the mosquito what can you do? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying well you need to be careful of dengue I said there's no dengue here she's erm what did she say? she said oh well it's <anon type="place"/> and it's in <anon type="place"/> so why wouldn't it be here?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh really it's in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0024">apparently</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">oh shit</u>
<u n="50" who="S0024">but then I think these bites she's been getting at night anyway so I don't think I haven't seen any daytime ones really</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144">I thought dengue was more tropical</u>
<u n="52" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I've never heard er well I didn't hear that I don't know where she got</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I dunno</u>
<u n="56" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that from</u>
<u n="57" who="S0144">well they haven't said anything have they to us about dengue?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0024">well I don't know I stopped opening the dengue emails cos you said they were <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0144">yeah that was the <anon type="place"/> campus yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0024">well I stopped opening the emails so whether they said dengue has come</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0024">to <anon type="place"/> I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> anyway we'll have to sort that out tonight I was wondering whether to try those mosquito nets again shove them over the top of her bed</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0024">but then you've got to <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="65" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I'll go round the house tonight <pause dur="short"/> well in a bit</u>
<u n="66" who="S0024">these ones here that have got her head <pause dur="short"/> that's at night</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0024">and <pause dur="short"/> they are the tiny tiny those tiny tiny ones</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144">yeah I know you can't get them they're really difficult</u>
<u n="70" who="S0024">they fly though the back you're like</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah and they're so small you can't even see them</u>
<u n="72" who="S0024">no <event desc="sound of baby"/> I know we've got to find that nasty little bugger in your room er? gotta find him</u>
<u n="73" who="S0144">he's had a right feast out of you hasn't he?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so anyway yeah make sure we do that tonight and then erm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0144" trans="overlap">how were your classes?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0024">oh they're lovely <pause dur="short"/> they're really really nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> really nice yeah I really like actually that <trunc>ar</trunc> that erm reading and writing class that I just now I did erm they're international communication students and they're so different from the engineering students</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0024">really they are <pause dur="short"/> the engineering students <pause dur="short"/> you know I was really battling to get through the class I don't know it just seemed more natural how er somehow with the international communication students</u>
<u n="79" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0024">it really did <pause dur="short"/> like they were discussing answers and they saw the purpose of discussing</u>
<u n="81" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0024">why they thought something of a reading text why why the answer is what it is</u>
<u n="83" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0024">you know why it isn't the other A B C</u>
<u n="85" who="S0144">and the others don't care they just wanna know what the answer is</u>
<u n="86" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah they just don't <trunc>car</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0144">that's as far as they think is important</u>
<u n="88" who="S0024">yeah maybe I dunno but they've got some training</u>
<u n="89" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well since they're engineering it's <pause dur="short"/> there's a right answer and a wrong answer when once you've got the answer from the</u>
<u n="90" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0144" trans="overlap">reading doesn't matter why</u>
<u n="92" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0144" trans="overlap">they'll discuss it it's got no importance <vocal desc="laugh"/> they don't do that in engineering do they?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0024">so how do I make that important to them</u>
<u n="95" who="S0144">well you don't but</u>
<u n="96" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that process? mm I know what you mean it's</u>
<u n="97" who="S0144">it's very Chinese and very very scientific as well</u>
<u n="98" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0144">but <pause dur="short"/> scientific in a Chinese way <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and it's not as say it's not like humanities is it where people are more open to discuss?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> I need to get them in practice</u>
<u n="103" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0024">erm they emailed me about the American student today</u>
<u n="105" who="S0144">mm what did they say?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> excuse me erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've just er got a mouthful sorry mm <pause dur="short"/> let me finish</u>
<u n="107" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0144">you put the whole thing in your mouth?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0024">no I only put a little bit <pause dur="short"/> now I'm embarrassed like what it sounds like</u>
<u n="111" who="S0144">what? what do you mean what it sounds like?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0024">me eating <pause dur="short"/> it's not a normal eating</u>
<u n="113" who="S0144">oh on the recording?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it's more of a I don't know anyway anyway it's gone now I'm not gonna eat any more <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> emailed and said well I don't even know why she's in preliminary year she <trunc>sho</trunc> she shouldn't be doing it <pause dur="short"/> should just go straight into university</u>
<u n="115" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0024">as someone who's had at least a <pause dur="short"/> a solid background in education like we would you do your A levels you go to university you don't have to do preliminary year if you don't want to</u>
<u n="117" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="118" who="S0024">unless you've got really really bad grades</u>
<u n="119" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144">yeah but</u>
<u n="122" who="S0024" trans="overlap">hey</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144">what does what does she want to study?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0024">it's engineering she's in engineering she does she wants to do erm oh I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> oh I can't remember maybe she needs to do the maths modules or something</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144">well is she gonna speak to someone about it then?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0024">yeah well I sent her to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she's been going through her tutors saying what where she can go and er god I agree with her but I had to say in the car well this is academic reading and writing you're going to learn something which she will learn something I mean you're you're gonna learn loads really</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">yeah but yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but it's not the type of</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but she's paying seven grand for this</u>
<u n="130" who="S0024">mm yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0144">for for learning a couple of things that you didn't know</u>
<u n="132" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/> yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144">so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0024">well</u>
<u n="135" who="S0144" trans="overlap">a year of your life</u>
<u n="136" who="S0024">if you're not studying academic I dunno if you're not studying applied linguistics at university if you're doing engineering why would you want to know that?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0024">she knows how to write a report</u>
<u n="139" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0024">that's that</u>
<u n="141" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0024">she she'll do it better than anyone else by the end of the year</u>
<u n="143" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0024">still she can do it now she <vocal desc="laugh"/> she said to me can I just take the exam now and see see what I get? if I do really well then why should I do the course?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0024">straight oh god it was so sad she was sitting there she <trunc>wa</trunc> like and she sat where she sat with the students who were really struggling which didn't help so every <trunc>ti</trunc></u>
<u n="147" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what again?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0024">like in</u>
<u n="149" who="S0144" trans="overlap">in <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no this was yesterday</u>
<u n="151" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="152" who="S0024">and erm I said to <pause dur="short"/> you know and oh I was like right <pause dur="short"/> erm I've forgotten <trunc>hi</trunc> his name who was sitting next to her work with work with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm talk tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> why the answer is what it is and <pause dur="short"/> and then I <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she she kind of lost interest in helping them because it was the lower students</u>
<u n="153" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0024">I think she wouldn't mind with the higher students she's sitting next to this student who is struggling already with</u>
<u n="155" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well make sure they don't sit next to each other then</u>
<u n="156" who="S0024">yeah well how? if she's late she's late into class I can't save a seat for her</u>
<u n="157" who="S0144">why? <pause dur="short"/> if it's this extreme it's quite an extreme case</u>
<u n="158" who="S0024">save a seat for her where? next to other students next to me? I dunno</u>
<u n="159" who="S0144">hide a chair <pause dur="short"/> take a chair away from one of the tables</u>
<u n="160" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0144">and if she's always the last one to come in like hide it behind your desk <pause dur="short"/> and then you can say oh have you got a chair? oh here you go and just stick it where you want it to go</u>
<u n="162" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but she shouldn't be late I'm sorry</u>
<u n="163" who="S0144">no but <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> all the Chinese students are getting there ten minutes early at the moment</u>
<u n="164" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0144">so</u>
<u n="166" who="S0024">yeah they're</u>
<u n="167" who="S0144">they're really early</u>
<u n="168" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah might be an idea <pause dur="short"/> even if she's facing away from me</u>
<u n="169" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0024"><vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0024"><vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0144">and what else have you done today?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0024">well I came back here well I went I had a class at nine <pause dur="short"/> printed out managed to print out I'd just got my computer fixed today <pause dur="short"/> came back breastfed er went for a walk round the block to try and find something I can't remember what</u>
<u n="175" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0024">erm so I walked all the way around the block <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="177" who="S0144">you can't remember what you were looking for?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0024">oh I was going to go in the supermarket and get <pause dur="long"/> I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well it couldn't have been very important then</u>
<u n="180" who="S0024">no but for some reason I decided to walk all the way round the block before coming home for lunch</u>
<u n="181" who="S0144">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it was a really long way longer than I remember <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0144">yeah that's a horrible walk that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0024">yeah so I don't know why I did that oh I know I wanted to get her some Thai noodles</u>
<u n="185" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0024">but whenever I go past they're never doing them <pause dur="short"/> so I think they're only an evening thing I've given up now there was no food stores there at lunchtime well about twenty quarter to twelve so I'm gonna give up <vocal desc="laugh"/> I really like those noodles that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> buys all the time but</u>
<u n="187" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0024">dunno almost need to know when they're gonna set up <pause dur="short"/> set up the shop</u>
<u n="189" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/> yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="192" who="S0024">I was gonna buy the nanny some noodles for lunch cos I thought she might have a busy day</u>
<u n="193" who="S0144">mm so whose house does she go round to?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0024">I think as far as I can gather she went round <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house</u>
<u n="195" who="S0144">who's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is the Irish girl who's married to the Brazilian who just arrived with a three-month-old baby and a two-year-old</u>
<u n="197" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0024">very nice <pause dur="short"/> very nice</u>
<u n="199" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0024">she was erm she was struggling a bit settling in because they moved quite a lot around</u>
<u n="201" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024">so <vocal desc="nonsense"/> so they yeah that's who I I was going round I gave her vitamin B and stuff drops for the kids stuff like that she was a bit worried but now they've all settled in together they're having they're going round each other's every week now Tuesday morning <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was gonna go <pause dur="short"/> erm but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just found out that her friend is the nanny of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">oh okay</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024">so <pause dur="short"/> er so</u>
<u n="205" who="S0144">that's</u>
<u n="206" who="S0024" trans="overlap">she went round there <pause dur="short"/> so she knows her so she got invited somehow <vocal desc="laugh"/> I so I told you she can go and meet everybody and I don't know maybe through <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said no I I told her go and meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know the baby's aren't that er different in age <pause dur="short"/> and erm yeah she met with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and the little little <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is <pause dur="short"/> holding onto furniture and shuffling</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144">oh really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">she's doing the shuffle</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024">whatever you call it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0024">eight months old <pause dur="short"/> so clever aren't they?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0144">eight months? I thought she looked is she only two months older?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="218" who="S0024">she can't do that much more than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really she can sit up she's a little bit stronger but that's it</u>
<u n="219" who="S0144">well she's bigger isn't she yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0024">not that much bigger <pause dur="short"/> she is definitely stronger <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is more bouncy</u>
<u n="221" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s baby is a bit more <pause dur="short"/> placid just happy to chill out <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to do do do doesn't she?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0024">do do do?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0144">yeah she's gonna be er all over the place</u>
<u n="226" who="S0024">so that was quite a busy day and then I went to pay the rent <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't pay the <trunc>na</trunc> the nanny fee to the agency because apparently because it's a business you need to take your passport and do it at the counter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="228" who="S0024">so I thought one thing at a time and I bought that</u>
<u n="229" who="S0144" trans="overlap">haven't got a passport</u>
<u n="230" who="S0024">er?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0144">haven't got a passport</u>
<u n="232" who="S0024">oh well I'll have to write to them and explain erm <pause dur="short"/> and er oh by the bank oh god had to had to cover my face up it just really chemically you know they're building out there?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0024">oh it stank it was so bad it's it's a good job you two didn't come <pause dur="short"/> like it gave me almost an instant headache <pause dur="short"/> and then I was stupid enough to go to the supermarket afterwards which <vocal desc="laugh"/> didn't help <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it was that kind of chemicals</u>
<u n="235" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I spoke to that girl who came from <anon type="place"/> the university erm one of the new girls used to work in <anon type="place"/> university she said the pollution there is really bad</u>
<u n="237" who="S0144">in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0024"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0144">oh mm <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0024">l<anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0144">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0024">yeah yeah she said the</u>
<u n="243" who="S0144">or <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="244" who="S0024">yeah it's something like that she said it's much better here</u>
<u n="245" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0024">she was a bit she was monitoring it all last year</u>
<u n="247" who="S0144">better here?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0144">jesus christ must be really bad <vocal desc="laugh"/> <event desc="sound of baby"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0024">yeah well today's alright</u>
<u n="251" who="S0144">it's been alright this week</u>
<u n="252" who="S0024" trans="overlap">been alright yeah this week's been fine it's still been been a a bit hazy but I think</u>
<u n="253" who="S0144">oh man</u>
<u n="254" who="S0024">is that one? did you get one?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0144">I saw it</u>
<u n="256" who="S0024">have they come out?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0144">but they erm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0024">they've come out <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0144">it was tiny</u>
<u n="260" who="S0024">er oh</u>
<u n="261" who="S0144" trans="overlap">really tiny</u>
<u n="262" who="S0024">we need your fast hands</u>
<u n="263" who="S0144">yeah I missed him</u>
<u n="264" who="S0024">fast drumming hands get these mosquitos they're they're not sitting on the walls either are they? cos the big ones it's the big ones that sit on the ceilings so</u>
<u n="265" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0024">mm yeah so wow that was flat out today what did you do? like my lunch was literally coming here breastfeed</u>
<u n="267" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0024">eat the noodles go</u>
<u n="269" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0024">I didn't stop for <unclear/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0144">yeah I <pause dur="short"/> well I finished two I had two classes so I finished at one</u>
<u n="272" who="S0024">that's good</u>
<u n="273" who="S0144">and then had lunch and planned for tomorrow</u>
<u n="274" who="S0024">are you planned for tomorrow?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0024">I'm not</u>
<u n="277" who="S0144">it's easy took me ten minutes</u>
<u n="278" who="S0024"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0144">seriously it's easy</u>
<u n="280" who="S0024">well cos we done it last year?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I remember looking at it last year going oh this is quite difficult but no it's easy cos you we know what's coming next now we know the purpose <pause dur="short"/> the level that they they've got to know it <pause dur="short"/> the level they've got to know like the <trunc>lev</trunc> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0024">er? start again</u>
<u n="283" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0024">I don't get it</u>
<u n="285" who="S0144">we know that <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0024">you remember er er all what we saw er last year</u>
<u n="287" who="S0144">I can't remember how to speak English <unclear/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0144">we know what's coming</u>
<u n="290" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0144">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I finished yeah <pause dur="short"/> left work at two <pause dur="short"/> which is not bad is it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0024">no not bad at all</u>
<u n="293" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and then I bumped into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he said well do you fancy a quick beer?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0144">I go okay then so I went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0024">huh <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0024">afternoon beers</u>
<u n="299" who="S0144">I only had one <pause dur="short"/> had a really nice chat</u>
<u n="300" who="S0024">it sounds nice yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0144">just erm er politics we were talking about</u>
<u n="302" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a nice <unclear>name</unclear></u>
<u n="303" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we were talking about</u>
<u n="304" who="S0024">hey</u>
<u n="305" who="S0144">propaganda and stuff</u>
<u n="306" who="S0024">yeah?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0024">is he in the band?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="310" who="S0024" trans="overlap">or is he kind of out of it? no singer?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0144" trans="overlap">he's kind of out of it</u>
<u n="312" who="S0024">have you got a singer?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0024">why is he er and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't do it? <vocal desc="misc"/> oh I feel sorry for him really but then you've got to choose people just like the drummer you can't</u>
<u n="315" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you feel sorry for the drummer but</u>
<u n="317" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0024">what can you do? can't have everybody can you?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0144">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s better for like big gigs like if they're in <anon type="place"/> and they're in a club <vocal desc="misc"/> and they're in there doing a big gig with a a drum kit</u>
<u n="320" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0144">and everything</u>
<u n="322" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0144">then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would be great</u>
<u n="324" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0144">but I think the smaller gigs like things like wedding events</u>
<u n="326" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/> yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0144"><anon type="place"/> I I dunno</u>
<u n="328" who="S0024">well I don't know I've never seen him have I? so</u>
<u n="329" who="S0144">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0024"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah so I've <trunc>s</trunc> I'm supposed to been getting texts all day from this <trunc>a</trunc>agency</u>
<u n="332" who="S0024">really? <pause dur="short"/> so this agency has got all of your numbers and they're just texting all of you?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0144">well no no they're going through <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0024">they're going through <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is just forwarding messages?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0024">wow</u>
<u n="337" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0024">this Friday</u>
<u n="339" who="S0144">so <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="340" who="S0024" trans="overlap">is this</u>
<u n="341" who="S0144" trans="overlap">this Friday hasn't been confirmed yet but erm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0024">when's <anon type="place"/>? the hotel?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> is next week</u>
<u n="344" who="S0024">next week so this Friday this Sunday <pause dur="short"/> next Friday?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0024">is it? is that right?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0024">god you've got to know how to</u>
<u n="349" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so far</u>
<u n="350" who="S0024">are you putting all this in your phone in the dates?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0024">you're gonna start forgetting if you're doing gigs</u>
<u n="353" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0024">different places and everything that's amazing it really is if you can earn a few <pause dur="short"/> pennies as well whilst playing</u>
<u n="355" who="S0144">yeah yeah it's great</u>
<u n="356" who="S0024" trans="overlap">ah and everybody wants to do it?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0024">the band</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/> ah that's really nice</u>
<u n="361" who="S0144">and the agency said you know I mean at the moment we're not getting paid very much</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="363" who="S0144">something like sixty quid each</u>
<u n="364" who="S0024">yeah bargain I would say</u>
<u n="365" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="366" who="S0024" trans="overlap">are you sure the agency's gonna up the price?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0144">but we're only playing for about twenty minutes</u>
<u n="368" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0144">so it's not bad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0144">but it's the travel and it's the waiting around</u>
<u n="372" who="S0024" trans="overlap">where is the wedding?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0144">cos they want us to do two sets of like ten minutes each or something</u>
<u n="374" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah yeah when's the wedding?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0144">er I well I don't even know if it is a wedding <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he thinks it might be a wedding</u>
<u n="376" who="S0024">you're not sure?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0144">and the one on Sunday I don't know what it is someone said something about a car launch or</u>
<u n="378" who="S0024">well</u>
<u n="379" who="S0144" trans="overlap">something</u>
<u n="380" who="S0024">just see how it goes</u>
<u n="381" who="S0144">so this could really escalate</u>
<u n="382" who="S0024">yeah I know</u>
<u n="383" who="S0144">it's already gone a bit crazy</u>
<u n="384" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <shift new="singing"/> row row row the boat gently down the stream <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0144">mm and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0144">erm he's showing some interesting in getting me to play with it cos he's in a band now <pause dur="short"/> and he's forming another band</u>
<u n="388" who="S0024">you can't be in two bands and it and go</u>
<u n="389" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0024">all over the place</u>
<u n="391" who="S0144">yeah you can</u>
<u n="392" who="S0024">not if you're getting paid like</u>
<u n="393" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0024">four pounds a week it's gonna be hard</u>
<u n="395" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="396" who="S0024">you'll you'll burn yourself up</u>
<u n="397" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0024">well</u>
<u n="399" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I'm not gonna do too much anyway cos I need to spend time with you two</u>
<u n="400" who="S0024">erm didn't you try a band with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> before and it didn't work?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0144">I didn't try anything I talked about it</u>
<u n="402" who="S0024">exactly it didn't work</u>
<u n="403" who="S0144">no but now he's in a Chinese rock</u>
<u n="404" who="S0024">you had a meeting</u>
<u n="405" who="S0144">he's in a Chinese rock band now but he didn't like it cos it was too heavy</u>
<u n="406" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="407" who="S0144">he's more of a folk singer</u>
<u n="408" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0144">and he's going through this the same agency</u>
<u n="410" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0144">so we've kind of all agreed that we're just gonna use all of us so we've got <pause dur="short"/> well he's</u>
<u n="412" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0144">a folk singer and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a folk singer</u>
<u n="414" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0144">and an acoustic guitarist <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can play the lead there's this other guy down there that can play bass</u>
<u n="416" who="S0024">hang on why isn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> plays bass</u>
<u n="418" who="S0024">in the other band?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0144">I dunno</u>
<u n="420" who="S0024">why not?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0144">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> erm because I think maybe <pause dur="short"/> I dunno maybe cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> kind of takes the lead with his vocals</u>
<u n="422" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0144">I think he wants to be the frontman</u>
<u n="424" who="S0024">mm what does everybody think about that?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0144">they haven't talked about it it's</u>
<u n="426" who="S0024">mm <vocal desc="misc"/> mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0144">I dunno</u>
<u n="428" who="S0024">well instead of splitting off into two bands can't you just be one band and then take turns?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0144">dunno if we make one big band <pause dur="short"/> er?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0024">then take turns at doing the vocals <pause dur="short"/> you don't need the same vocalist all the time if they're</u>
<u n="431" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is</u>
<u n="432" who="S0024" trans="overlap">playing guitars</u>
<u n="433" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got his own stuff as well and the songs</u>
<u n="434" who="S0024">so has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0024">oh they're different styles?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0024">mm <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0144">so you've got two drummers two bassists</u>
<u n="440" who="S0024">so you've got two bands</u>
<u n="441" who="S0144">two</u>
<u n="442" who="S0024">basically who's the</u>
<u n="443" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no we haven't</u>
<u n="444" who="S0024" trans="overlap">second bassist?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0144">we haven't got another lead guitarist</u>
<u n="446" who="S0024">who's the second bassist?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0144">erm <pause dur="short"/> er this older guy who</u>
<u n="448" who="S0024">I</u>
<u n="449" who="S0144" trans="overlap">teaches somewhere</u>
<u n="450" who="S0024">I thought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> played lead guitar</u>
<u n="451" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="452" who="S0024">no? he's pretty good at guitar</u>
<u n="453" who="S0144">yeah well he's acoustic</u>
<u n="454" who="S0024">oh I'm well I'm confused I need to come and see your band so that I know what you're going on about <pause dur="short"/> I've no idea who's who</u>
<u n="455" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0024">or anything I didn't even know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0144">no?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="459" who="S0144">erm and then I got back here at three o'clock no half three</u>
<u n="460" who="S0024">yeah oh hiccup</u>
<u n="461" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and then we sent the nanny home</u>
<u n="462" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0024">did you say bye bye nanny?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0144">been playing with er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ever since</u>
<u n="466" who="S0024">ah have you had a nice time?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0144">well I thought she was gonna go to sleep but she hasn't</u>
<u n="468" who="S0024">what time is it now?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0144">er must be about five</u>
<u n="470" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> she usually has a little nap doesn't she? otherwise we've got to keep her up till seven</u>
<u n="471" who="S0144">yeah she normally has a little nap</u>
<u n="472" who="S0024" trans="overlap">stay awake <pause dur="short"/> erm I was wondering if you want to take her to <anon type="place"/> with me or something</u>
<u n="473" who="S0144">what now?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0024">well there's two hours we've got to entertain her for two hours yesterday I did exercises with her <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>t</trunc> like it's our two hours I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I just thought maybe we could buy her</u>
<u n="475" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0024" trans="overlap">a bouncy thing</u>
<u n="477" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0024">I dunno</u>
<u n="479" who="S0144">what time is it exactly?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0024">ah yeah it does make a bit of a difference doesn't it? like <pause dur="short"/> cos I reckon that Mothercare thing</u>
<u n="481" who="S0144">I think we'd need at least</u>
<u n="482" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that would be really expensive</u>
<u n="483" who="S0144">an hour and half</u>
<u n="484" who="S0024">half past right that's too tight?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0144">pushing it</u>
<u n="486" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="487" who="S0144">she gets really grumpy at half six</u>
<u n="488" who="S0024">alright well I'll just sit here before I go I might go over to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and have a cup of tea oh keep us busy won't it?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0144">yeah yeah pop over there</u>
<u n="490" who="S0024">yeah well <trunc>ju</trunc> just cos you know she offered her bike and</u>
<u n="491" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's not a good idea with your toe though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's just asking for trouble</u>
<u n="492" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="493" who="S0144">you've only just <pause dur="short"/> and you've got it all bandaged up</u>
<u n="494" who="S0024">I know it's going to be</u>
<u n="495" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and you can get</u>
<u n="496" who="S0024" trans="overlap">sore patches too but that</u>
<u n="497" who="S0144" trans="overlap">if you bang it or it gets dirty you're</u>
<u n="498" who="S0024" trans="overlap">marching around</u>
<u n="499" who="S0144" trans="overlap">gonna be fucked</u>
<u n="500" who="S0024">I'm marching around but</u>
<u n="501" who="S0144">yeah but that's in a really <pause dur="short"/> if that gets infected you're in trouble</u>
<u n="502" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but walking back at lunchtime I know that I've got long lunches I'm so lucky <pause dur="short"/> like walking back at lunchtime breastfeeding then walking all the way back to work is quite a well <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's fine I'm getting fit which is good I need to lose a few pounds <vocal desc="laugh"/> I want to lose nearly a stone really</u>
<u n="503" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="504" who="S0024">you know just be toning up and stuff and stop eating Snickers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0144">yeah you need to</u>
<u n="506" who="S0024">but erm <pause dur="short"/> want to lose a stone but <pause dur="short"/> that's still a long way like if it were a bicycle that's good for my other muscles anyway <pause dur="short"/> instead of you know I might look at? I forgot I forgot all about this pram it's a bicycle pram did I ever tell you about this bicycle pram? oh and it's got it on Amazon and I did check just I remember checking before she was born I think when or when we were looking for prams yeah when we were <trunc>lo</trunc> we were searching for prams this bicycle pram it's like a erm three-wheeler thing and the pram is on the front so that she's in front of you cos I hate bicycles where they're behind you</u>
<u n="507" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0024">don't like that</u>
<u n="509" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="510" who="S0024">you wanna be able to see them</u>
<u n="511" who="S0144" trans="overlap">wanna know if they're still there or not</u>
<u n="512" who="S0024">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0024">make sure they haven't fallen off <event desc="sound of baby"/> oh it's okay it's okay are you getting all grizzly cos we're talking then? mm we'll play a game in a minute yeah? erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah they've got er I was thinking of having a look again because they sell them on the Chinese one</u>
<u n="515" who="S0144">oh really?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0024">yeah erm quite expensive but then if I was to buy a proper bike <pause dur="short"/> like a proper bike that's two hundred pounds anyway</u>
<u n="517" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0024">so I've anyway I'm gonna have a look again and I can't remember how much they were but it's kind of like a three-wheeler sturdy</u>
<u n="519" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0024">it's like a sturdy one erm <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's like riding a rickshaw or something</u>
<u n="521" who="S0144">how how big will they be?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0024">well no they can go up to three or four years old five years old</u>
<u n="523" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you can get yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you can get ones</u>
<u n="525" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what you just put them in a basket?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0024">you put them in the front it's like a pram chair in the front three like a three-wheeler pram <pause dur="short"/> and then you've got your bicycle kind of like on the back and it's more of a so one of those sloping bicycles that you would have in a gym or something where you where you can lean back and relax and just kind of <pause dur="short"/> just pedal rather than upright bicycle</u>
<u n="527" who="S0144">you'll have to show me a picture</u>
<u n="528" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I haven't looked at it for ages but I suddenly thought <pause dur="short"/> you know if I want like if I want to take her anywhere I'm gonna like there's no point me going out and buying a bicycle and then she's nearly sitting up and then in two months' time I go right <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> let's go we want to go to the mall and cos that's a bicycle lane the whole way down fine <event desc="sound of baby"/> oh I know it's a bicycle lane all the way down and then I thought well why do I want an ordinary bike? but I want a bike maybe that you would want to ride with her too</u>
<u n="529" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0024">so you would have to feel happy riding it <pause dur="short"/> you don't care what you look like do you?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="532" who="S0024">but maybe we won't get a pink one <pause dur="short"/> but everything is <anon type="place"/> is pink if you've got a girl <vocal desc="misc"/> otherwise they think you're a boy</u>
<u n="533" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="534" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/> they all think she's a boy just cos she hasn't got any hair</u>
<u n="535" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0024">but she doesn't even look like a boy</u>
<u n="537" who="S0144">yeah I showed them the</u>
<u n="538" who="S0024">she's wearing pink socks</u>
<u n="539" who="S0144">the new class I had today</u>
<u n="540" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0144">I showed them well it was on my front page and a picture of her playing the guitar</u>
<u n="542" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0144">and they were like ah he's lovely</u>
<u n="544" who="S0024"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0144">it's a girl</u>
<u n="546" who="S0024">did you say that?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0144">yeah jokingly</u>
<u n="548" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did they say why they thought it was a boy? cos she was clearly</u>
<u n="549" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well everyone thinks she's a boy cos she hasn't got any hair so that's why we have to dress her in pink <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0024">but she won't <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah she's wearing pink in the picture but they still thought</u>
<u n="552" who="S0024">that's weird</u>
<u n="553" who="S0144" trans="overlap">she was a boy</u>
<u n="554" who="S0024">isn't it because</u>
<u n="555" who="S0144">cos I wouldn't say her face looks like a boy at all</u>
<u n="556" who="S0024">no me neither <pause dur="short"/> oh me neither</u>
<u n="557" who="S0144">but it's</u>
<u n="558" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and then she wears all these frills and stuff</u>
<u n="559" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it's just the hair isn't it?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0024">it is because she wears bows like not like not like really tacky bows but you know that those pretty dresses that she's got she wears a dress <pause dur="short"/> she gets goes outside and they say she boy</u>
<u n="561" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0024">they say their first thing is the hair</u>
<u n="563" who="S0144">yeah it's weird yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0024">their second thing is the colour here at home it would be <pause dur="short"/> she's wearing bows and frills and is in pink</u>
<u n="565" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0024">that is that's er definitely a girl</u>
<u n="567" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0024">but you wouldn't say anything different would you you'd <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's funny <pause dur="short"/> funny isn't it you'll get some hair and then you'll be beautiful but maybe she can't be a baby model till she gets her hair I don't know <pause dur="short"/> could you be a baby model? Have you got time to do all this stuff we're planning on doing?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0144">yeah well you need to email that agency some pictures of her</u>
<u n="570" who="S0024">yeah okay yeah well I want to do some work this evening I want to get into the habit I'm not going out until I've got my kind of a bit more of a routine going in the evenings <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> I've got quite a lot to sort out quite a lot of emails to do quite a lot of photos to organise</u>
<u n="571" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0024">yeah lots of things <pause dur="short"/> so I'm not gonna go out until that's done cos the girls wanna go out one day when's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0144">sometime this week</u>
<u n="574" who="S0024">this week? oh my god really? I thought it was the nineteenth what's the date today?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0144">well the nineteenth is Friday isn't it?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0024">her birthday's on a Wednesday is it tomorrow?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0144">tomorrow</u>
<u n="578" who="S0024">is it? <pause dur="long"/> oh really?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0024">I thought it was next week</u>
<u n="581" who="S0144">no I thought it was this week</u>
<u n="582" who="S0024">oh god I'll have to have a look</u>
<u n="583" who="S0144">text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and ask her <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0024">well</u>
<u n="585" who="S0144">and then it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday on Saturday</u>
<u n="586" who="S0024">are you doing your band on Saturday?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0144">no I don't know what's going on <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm really confused</u>
<u n="588" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh they're doing a barbeque aren't they?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0144">barbeque but I thought I thought <pause dur="short"/> we might be oh that's another thing <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> texted asking if we've got any photos of the band so <pause dur="short"/> and we don't really</u>
<u n="590" who="S0024">so you've gotta do some</u>
<u n="591" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well they <trunc>ha</trunc> they had some professional done ones done with the other drummer but</u>
<u n="592" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0144">but they haven't gone one with me</u>
<u n="594" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0144">so we might have to do a photo shoot at the weekend <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0024">right okay who's gonna do that for you?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0144">er?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0024"><anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> will they do it for you?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0144">be <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0024">okay that's alright as long as they're doing it well if they're organising it all it's easy all you have to do is show up</u>
<u n="601" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0024">in your best T-shirt</u>
<u n="603" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do you know <event desc="unintelligible"/> he's gonna be famous</u>
<u n="605" who="S0144">cos the pictures they've got down the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh my god you gonna be famous</u>
<u n="607" who="S0144">no I'm not <pause dur="short"/> I don't wanna be famous <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0024">you'll be famous in this town in the town</u>
<u n="609" who="S0144">what a town of six million people?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you already are <pause dur="short"/> you already are famous here with <pause dur="short"/> here's the drummer <pause dur="short"/> yeah are you gonna be a drummer? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gonna be a drummer too</u>
<u n="611" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0024"><vocal desc="nonsense"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0144" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> what else was gonna say? <pause dur="short"/> er got something else to tell you I've forgotten</u>
<u n="614" who="S0024">it's quite funny having these different lives and then kind of getting together I like it</u>
<u n="615" who="S0144">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0024">well it's better than well where were we? <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="618" who="S0024" trans="overlap">where we were <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="place"/> wasn't that it was pretty good erm <pause dur="short"/> but we did the same kind of things every day same <pause dur="short"/> so all <pause dur="short"/> don't know yeah well we did no in <anon type="place"/> we did different things <pause dur="short"/> I had my market and different</u>
<u n="619" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0024">going out different <trunc>vill</trunc> <anon type="place"/> that was it</u>
<u n="621" who="S0144"><anon type="place"/> was awful for that</u>
<u n="622" who="S0024">well at <anon type="place"/> we just hung out together</u>
<u n="623" who="S0144">there was nothing</u>
<u n="624" who="S0024">so we didn't go</u>
<u n="625" who="S0144" trans="overlap">really</u>
<u n="626" who="S0024">to different places did we and then meet up and</u>
<u n="627" who="S0144">no</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="628" who="S0024">oh it's okay it's okay</u>
<u n="629" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s moving there</u>
<u n="630" who="S0024">to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0144">in er or where was it? <anon type="place"/> no <anon type="place"/> she's going</u>
<u n="632" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know I've really got she</u>
<u n="633" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="634" who="S0024">she put some things about the Tunisian revolution on Facebook and I haven't managed to get on Facebook at all nothing works for me</u>
<u n="635" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="636" who="S0024">why but how come you can get on Facebook and I can't?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0144">well it usually takes about five hours to get on it</u>
<u n="638" who="S0024">oh well I haven't got the patience <pause dur="short"/> but I'm sure people must be wondering how <event desc="sound of baby"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0024">oh it's okay let's play a game <pause dur="short"/> wee let's sit down here <pause dur="short"/> there we go there we go <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="nonsense"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/> dragon <vocal desc="laugh"/> what was I gonna say? yeah er I haven't written back to her have you written to her about that? she posted pictures of us during the Tunisian revolution</u>
<u n="641" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I liked it</u>
<u n="642" who="S0024">you liked it</u>
<u n="643" who="S0144">was I supposed to say something?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0024">well I wanted to do more <event desc="sound of phone"/> because erm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0144">whose phone is that?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I haven't got any pictures</u>
<u n="647" who="S0144">is that my phone? that's your phone</u>
<u n="648" who="S0024">oh it's mine that would be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0024">yeah okay</u>
<u n="651" who="S0144">I'll turn this off now</u>
<u n="652" who="S0024">hello</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
