<text id="STQF">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:21</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0266 S0267 S0310</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Acquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>Having a personal shopper; preparing for a marriage event in a church; roots -where these two ladies came from; description of the personal shopping experience and result; colours that suit; shoes and styles of shoes; dress accessories</topics>
		<activity>The experience of having a personal shopper</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0266">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Almondsbury, Gloucestershire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0267">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bristol</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Zambia</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>29</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>PA secretary</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0310">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stockton-on-tees</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>NE</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Careers advisor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0266">just to make sure this is I think that's okay it's recording okay so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you were going to tell us about your experience of personal shopping</u>
<u n="2" who="S0267">yes well the reason for personal shopping was because my daughter's getting married in December</u>
<u n="3" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0267">and erm wanted an outfit as the mother of the bride but I really don't want to stand out in front of anyone else I I don't don't I just hate that sort of thing</u>
<u n="5" who="S0310">yes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0267">and <unclear/> and I'm not happy with my weight cos I haven't been able to get onto the diet thing you know every Monday comes and I start and by Tuesday Wednesday it's off so wasn't really happy and I've gone up definitely a dress and a half size so eh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she arranged for a personal shopping experience for herself myself and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who is my my step erm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0266">sister-in-law</u>
<u n="8" who="S0267">sister-in-law yeah but not actually</u>
<u n="9" who="S0266">right</u>
<u n="10" who="S0267">so she's she's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s partner my brother-in-law's partner</u>
<u n="11" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="12" who="S0267">so the three of us went off and I was not you know I thought it was really nice of her to do this</u>
<u n="13" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0267">but actually it wasn't what I wanted and I'd want to shop by myself not with two two friends that are going to say this is lovely and then hate because I should be should be in a bright colour or whatever and I don't</u>
<u n="15" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="16" who="S0267">anyway I'd started out and have you ever been to a personal shopper?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0266">no no I haven't</u>
<u n="18" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/> dress shopping</u>
<u n="19" who="S0310">well I've had very few occasions to actually get dressed up erm I mean one niece's wedding and that's basically it but my son is engaged has just got engaged</u>
<u n="20" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="22" who="S0310">so so there is going to be a wedding coming up so this is of great interest to me your experience</u>
<u n="23" who="S0267" trans="overlap">well I think it's a really good thing to do and I wouldn't have done it eh on my own or even contemplated it because I'd never think anybody else is going to know really what I want to dress in</u>
<u n="24" who="S0310">yes</u>
<u n="25" who="S0267">but erm so when? there no date's been set?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0310" trans="overlap">they haven't set a date it might even be two thousand and sixteen</u>
<u n="27" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0310">but erm one of the things that's quite daunting is that it's going to be in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0267">oh crikey</u>
<u n="30" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0267">how does that come about?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0310">erm because that's where her family eh go</u>
<u n="33" who="S0267">oh</u>
<u n="34" who="S0310">and in fact although erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> live in <anon type="place"/> she's only just moved to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she was a server there so although she's lost her residence in <anon type="place"/> she and her parents are well known so she meets the criteria</u>
<u n="35" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0310">because of course they must get hundreds of requests to get married in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0267" trans="overlap">I'm sure I'm sure but if you have an attachment to I think <unclear/> the bandsman read out for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s weekend and they managed not to be at any one of them</u>
<u n="38" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="39" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0267">oh and you believe him?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0310">yes I've heard them at least once I think in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yeah well so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I went along this Sunday erm and heard them read and erm it was you know it was quite exciting to hear them read just cos</u>
<u n="43" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="44" who="S0267">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm vicar said that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was a server and of course she was you know if you are a server or you have some connection with the church it's lovely yeah it's lovely</u>
<u n="45" who="S0310" trans="overlap">aha <pause dur="short"/> family link yes yes yes yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually was at school with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> my son</u>
<u n="46" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0310">mm mm I mean we knew the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> before we even moved here because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s class and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s class</u>
<u n="48" who="S0267" trans="overlap">did you? <pause dur="short"/> at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0267">oh right okay so where where do you come from?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0310">well we were living in <anon type="place"/> then</u>
<u n="52" who="S0267">I came from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0310">do you?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0267">yes well not really but I was er brought up abroad and then when I was fifteen er fourteen actually we came back to <anon type="place"/> and then my parents moved out to the country which of course <anon type="place"/> was was then</u>
<u n="55" who="S0266" trans="overlap">as was yes yes</u>
<u n="56" who="S0267">and erm so in those days not like today where you you know you perhaps move around or don't move around schools you'd still drive in from here through to <anon type="place"/> wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0267">but erm every time we moved we moved to the local school so you know I had about ten schools actually but erm yeah so we moved out to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0310">aha yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0267" trans="overlap">and that's where I lived for a while and then got married so er and then came out this way because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> belongs here you know his family come from <anon type="place"/> so erm yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yes yes yes mm mm <pause dur="short"/> ah so shall we go back to your personal shopping experience?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yes let's do that ah as I say not happy to have done it really but erm because they organised it friends organised it I thought well I'll just have to go along</u>
<u n="63" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0267">and eh I just really trussed myself up in something that was going to try and hold me in a little bit erm and the lady came in and as you say you have this personal erm you know cubicle which is big enough for all of us to sit down <pause dur="short"/> no tea or anything though which is a shame but I guess that could go over the clothes I don't know</u>
<u n="65" who="S0310">yes</u>
<u n="66" who="S0267">but erm so we sat down and she was very good the person who was doing it was very good she listened erm she said what colour would you like? and I said black because it's just my favourite colour to dress <unclear/> and this wedding is late afternoon so it's going to be an evening dress now to me I my little black dress is what I want and I'm also dressed because I wanted her to recognise straight away what I like because I think they'll clock you won't they and think oh what's she wearing now?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="68" who="S0267">so I wore a shift dress and that's what I'm happiest in is a shift dress of any kind black sequin evening whatever erm so she said black hmm and I said well I can dress it up with a lovely necklace or whatever er and a little coat or something like a jacket but my favourite would be black anyway she went away and she duly brought a little black dress which was the first thing to try on and there were other colours erm a bright a teal blue which in fact suited me I never knew it would do or never thought it would do but it did but it was just like a carnival dress it just was not me so ah but the black dress was an instant fit I just she just had my figure straight away and I thought I've never look so good in a black dress ah anyway but she said no no you can't do that for mother of the bride that's a no no so erm that was put aside and I said but I'll buy it as my little black dress so it was put aside for me it was the first one I tried that she brought in erm then another <unclear/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0266" trans="overlap">can I just interrupt a second? do do you like builder's tea? or do you want earl grey or something fancy?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0267" trans="overlap">builder's tea</u>
<u n="71" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes builder's is <unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0267">sugar?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0267">yeah no sugar</u>
<u n="74" who="S0266">milk? you put your own milk in that be okay?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0310">that would be fine</u>
<u n="76" who="S0266">sorry to interrupt yeah so the next dress</u>
<u n="77" who="S0267">and eh so the next dress was a there was a red one and I'm good with red but it just didn't really do anything and I kept wanting to go back to the black dress</u>
<u n="78" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0267">anyway she moved on to the other two <unclear/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0266">I was going to say so yes</u>
<u n="81" who="S0310">were they? were they inputting comments and was that satisfactory? or was that?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0267" trans="overlap">erm yes I I think I'd have preferred to do one one on one but actually erm yeah they were saying that looks lovely or that looks lovely and they liked the teal</u>
<u n="83" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0267">well I still felt overdressed</u>
<u n="85" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0267">so erm although everyone seemed to like that the best it was not for me</u>
<u n="87" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0267">eh anyway we she moved onto these two and seven dresses were brought out and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said can I try that black dress? and erm I said yes you can but it I'm going it's going to be my little black dress</u>
<u n="89" who="S0310"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0267">anyway I have never seen her look so beautiful in a dress it was just just perfect figure for <unclear/> and whereas she's short and I'm tall we actually had the same middle figure</u>
<u n="91" who="S0310">right</u>
<u n="92" who="S0267">erm and so I thought well she'll just have to have this and so she is wearing that little <trunc>bla</trunc>black dress and I went online afterwards and bought my own copy so we'll have to be at different <trunc>plac</trunc>places for this dress to be worn</u>
<u n="93" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0267">this shared dress but erm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0266" trans="overlap">how much milk did you say?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0267">oh that's fine thank you and then erm she brought in some other clothes for them</u>
<u n="97" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yep lovely</u>
<u n="99" who="S0267">and one of them was a jumpsuit and as soon as it came off the rack I said I can I try that? just stuck up my hand straight away and said can I have that? so I put it on and I felt fine that was for me and it's a jumpsuit with very</u>
<u n="100" who="S0266" trans="overlap">jumpsuit?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yep so I'm wearing long which is what the mother mother-in-law is wearing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is wearing long and I'm wearing long</u>
<u n="102" who="S0310" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="103" who="S0267">and other people can wear long that would be lovely erm but it's it's long but of course it's wide legged</u>
<u n="104" who="S0310">yes right</u>
<u n="105" who="S0267">so it is like a long dress but it is definitely it's <unclear/> dressy actually but er I'm going to buy a <unclear/> which I think will do better justice</u>
<u n="106" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0267">and it has a <unclear>nude</unclear> lace over black and three quarter <unclear>steeped</unclear></u>
<u n="108" who="S0310">oh right</u>
<u n="109" who="S0267">so I just thought I I hung about in it in the dressing room for quite a while and I thought still shows a bit of a tummy though so I need to do a bit more work in the diet sort of thing but erm I <unclear/> and I wanted to wear that so I bought it and that's what I'm wearing so <unclear/> so I would honestly say <unclear/> because I was surprised she had my <trunc>fig</trunc>figure so <unclear/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0310" trans="overlap">fantastic thank you yes yes</u>
<u n="111" who="S0267">so <trunc>wh</trunc>what things do you usually like? what dresses?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0310">I mean funny that you mention teal because those sorts of bluey greeny colours I would always sort of you know everything that I wore for work was around those sorts of colours</u>
<u n="113" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yeah well you've got green eyes green blue eyes</u>
<u n="114" who="S0310" trans="overlap">erm that yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0266"><trunc>mi</trunc>mine was tealy greeny</u>
<u n="116" who="S0267">it was it was beautiful</u>
<u n="117" who="S0266">well it <trunc>wa</trunc> it wasn't that I'd have looked at and thought oh I want that</u>
<u n="118" who="S0267">no</u>
<u n="119" who="S0266">it's just she put it on me and</u>
<u n="120" who="S0267">actually your hair colour you know I think has something to do with it</u>
<u n="121" who="S0266">I don't know</u>
<u n="122" who="S0267">so you know <unclear/> it goes I think it's a good colour on most people I think actually</u>
<u n="123" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0267">erm but this was fussy yours wasn't actually it just it was a really nice <unclear/> no it wasn't it was beautiful</u>
<u n="125" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0267">but this was actually but you know those erm ribbon <trunc>cr</trunc>criss cross designs at the moment?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0266">oh yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0267">it's one of those yeah but you know it just <unclear/></u>
<u n="130" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="132" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0267">and then they went up in a fee just <trunc>bef</trunc> you know in front of the knees and I don't like that I I have to on the knee or below and this one went up just like that and I thought you know</u>
<u n="134" who="S0310" trans="overlap">no yes yes</u>
<u n="135" who="S0267">actually I felt like a fish I did</u>
<u n="136" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0266"><unclear/> that colour there that is that the one you're talking about?</u>
<u n="138" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0310" trans="overlap">oh yes that is a really nice colour</u>
<u n="140" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yes yeah no it isn't</u>
<u n="141" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and it isn't it wasn't fashionable particularly cos it was really difficult to get shoes that colour</u>
<u n="142" who="S0267" trans="overlap">no but the length of it is beautiful</u>
<u n="143" who="S0310">yes yes</u>
<u n="144" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh I don't know it's not a dress I'd have looked at <unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0267" trans="overlap">what size shoes do you fit?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0266">erm six and a half to seven</u>
<u n="147" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0267">oh no good</u>
<u n="149" who="S0266">why?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0267" trans="overlap">but I'm not having a teal dress anyway but eh those were beautiful shoes</u>
<u n="151" who="S0266">yeah and luckily they were half price</u>
<u n="152" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0266">and I bought them two days before <unclear/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0310">did you get shoes as well then?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0267">no I didn't I again I took erm shoes with a erm a heel which I could hardly walk around in</u>
<u n="157" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0267">but actually the erm jumpsuit leg length hem length erm was just brushing the ground on that so I am going to have to get a proper pair of shoes that are that high but comfortable</u>
<u n="159" who="S0310">mm mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0267">so erm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0266">that's not easy</u>
<u n="162" who="S0267">it's not easy no</u>
<u n="163" who="S0266">cos I couldn't I was terrified how I was going to walk in the shoes</u>
<u n="164" who="S0267" trans="overlap">or have them taken up in that yeah mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0267">but you are also outside in the grass so you have to</u>
<u n="167" who="S0310" trans="overlap">I mean I</u>
<u n="168" who="S0266" trans="overlap">no it's in the gravel as well</u>
<u n="169" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0266">cos you sink in gravel</u>
<u n="171" who="S0267">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0310">I mean years ago people used to wear high heels didn't we have to wear high heels to work and look at them</u>
<u n="174" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0310">i've got one pair I still have and I look at them and think this is ridiculous</u>
<u n="176" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0267">well I <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0266" trans="overlap">do you do you wear high heels now? you don't know</u>
<u n="179" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no not at all</u>
<u n="180" who="S0266">no</u>
<u n="181" who="S0267">I do but not <trunc>y</trunc>you know sort of erm not huge ones and not stilettos they're more chunky but they're still very high <unclear/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0267">but it's the erm I think as <unclear/> at home in children and you're just in your erm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0266">casual clothes or <unclear/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0267" trans="overlap">casual erm what do you call them? I like to call them tackys erm <unclear/> erm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0310">flatties I suppose are they? <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0266">what do you mean trainers?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0267">trainers trainers you know erm well <unclear/> I don't wear trainers but I mean you know going out you maybe wear trainers or little pumps</u>
<u n="191" who="S0310" trans="overlap">oh mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0266">flatties</u>
<u n="193" who="S0310">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0267">yes yeah but erm your arches go down every time so actually you cannot get them back up to the you know difficult over time so you get <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0310">it's a fashion thing too isn't it? I mean my daughter doesn't wear high heels</u>
<u n="197" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0310">I don't think very many of them do except for</u>
<u n="199" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0310">a very special occasions so they don't wear them on a daily basis like we used to at that age</u>
<u n="201" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0266">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0267">actually <unclear/> our age do actually you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0267">she's on stilettos she's still <unclear/> yes yes wherever she goes she's got heels stiletto heels</u>
<u n="206" who="S0266" trans="overlap">she's not</u>
<u n="207" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0266">but so many people of our age group now have got bunions and things from wearing stilettos and goodness knows what</u>
<u n="209" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> people I know have operations for bunions</u>
<u n="210" who="S0310">yes yes</u>
<u n="211" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0310">but apparently there is now a school of thought which says that's nothing to do with the shoes you wear it's genetic</u>
<u n="213" who="S0267">really?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0266">oh really?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0267" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0266">interesting what did you do in your work? erm your career? <unclear/> health?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0310" trans="overlap">erm well well I I wasn't erm I didn't follow through the linguistic side erm but no I was a university careers adviser</u>
<u n="221" who="S0266">oh really?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0310">mm mm so until last summer I was at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0266">oh were you?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0310">been there for twenty-three years</u>
<u n="225" who="S0266">oh really?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0266">gosh</u>
<u n="228" who="S0310">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0266">wow we should have known you when our children were dithering not making decisions</u>
<u n="230" who="S0310">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0267">and did they make the same <unclear>ones as</unclear> they're doing now</u>
<u n="232" who="S0310">sorry?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0267">I wonder if they made the <unclear/> to the same decisions they made</u>
<u n="234" who="S0310">no not at all my eldest didn't <pause dur="short"/> didn't do anything</u>
<u n="235" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did politics and then changed to pharmacy</u>
<u n="236" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0267">so yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0267"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> stuck with music <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a mum</u>
<u n="240" who="S0310">yes</u>
<u n="241" who="S0266">so <trunc>ha</trunc>have we finished that bit about personal shopping?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0267">we probably have I I did come away thinking you know how you still feel the event is that massive or you are that big in that particular event or <unclear>main</unclear> er particular event</u>
<u n="243" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="244" who="S0267">erm I came away thinking yep I'll have it and that's my back up but actually I'll probably wear it I want to wear it I just <unclear>need to</unclear></u>
<u n="245" who="S0266">did you find it at all sort of erm threatening having other people there with you? would you have rather</u>
<u n="246" who="S0267">no not threatening erm I er</u>
<u n="247" who="S0266">or discomforting?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0267" trans="overlap">I wasn't I didn't actually look forward to it maybe discomforting yeah not at the time though cos it was a bit of fun with all three of us er but I knew really that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would love me to have got the outfit so I felt pressured in that way <unclear/> that I would have to buy <unclear/> eh as soon as the jumpsuit came out there that's the one</u>
<u n="249" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="250" who="S0267">so</u>
<u n="251" who="S0266">and are you going to wear anything on your head? are you?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0267">no I I just feel I've got fine hair and as soon as I put a hat on or anything that it just just you know it just flattens it's yeah silly</u>
<u n="253" who="S0310" trans="overlap">flattens it yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0267">so I may may just get a little diamante something or other <unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0266">cos this this woman who made my <unclear/> she makes them for people like Princess Anne and goodness knows what</u>
<u n="256" who="S0267">really?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0266">and eh she's really nice we go to her house and I thought she would you know cost a fortune and it was thirty quid</u>
<u n="258" who="S0310" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="259" who="S0267">really?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0266">mm she was amazing it's the second time she's done it for me</u>
<u n="261" who="S0267" trans="overlap">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I kind of recommend her in a way cos you can go to her and</u>
<u n="263" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0266">just show her what you're wearing and she'll she she's you know there were these people coming in and taking away stuff that was going to be worn by obviously very special people</u>
<u n="265" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0267">mm wow</u>
<u n="267" who="S0266">agents or whatever they are shops and erm and and I saw a few cheques written out for much more money than she was charging me about six times as much</u>
<u n="268" who="S0267" trans="overlap">wow gosh</u>
<u n="269" who="S0266">but she's she's into it not just for the money so if you're just a sort of person off the street</u>
<u n="270" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><unclear/> mm mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0267" trans="overlap">well for me I mean it's an evening do so I'm not going to be wearing a hat or a <unclear/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0266">no</u>
<u n="273" who="S0267">you know yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0266">so it's just shoes now?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0267">it is just shoes and a nice little clutch bag I think erm oh no and a jacket cos I can't you know you'd have to have a <trunc>j</trunc> ah this has got a little keyhole at the back as well</u>
<u n="276" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0267">which I didn't realise till I was taking it off I thought <unclear/> and erm but I'd I need a jacket in the church <unclear/> sort of</u>
<u n="278" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0266">did they not suggest a jacket <unclear/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0267">no well this was the very end and we'd been there from nine A.M <pause dur="short"/>till twelve because the three hours have to so say an hour</u>
<u n="281" who="S0266">oh they they were being dressed as well</u>
<u n="282" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0267">yeah they were being dressed and they bought the well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is wearing the little black dress to the wedding and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> strangely enough bought another black dress so there'll be a lot of black being worn I think erm you know glitzy erm necklaces and stuff so</u>
<u n="284" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0266">oh right I didn't realise the other three were buying as well</u>
<u n="286" who="S0267">yes yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0310">so that means the hour is the standard what you book is it's an hour is it?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/> pressure on it is yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="290" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0267">but to be honest if you find a dress <trunc>yo</trunc>you know as I say the first one I tried is the one I love the dress <unclear/> those sort of three outfits they didn't all look nice they you know she just had</u>
<u n="292" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="293" who="S0267">had the knack but erm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0266">this was John Lewis</u>
<u n="295" who="S0267">this was John Lewis yeah yeah mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0310">mm yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0266">that's very promising actually</u>
<u n="298" who="S0267">it is the other thing I was thinking was I didn't really want another reason for not really wanting to do this was erm I knew that John Lewis in in <anon type="place"/> isn't as eh hasn't got as much as if you went to <anon type="place"/> you know House of Fraser <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="300" who="S0266" trans="overlap">or Diana Tout and</u>
<u n="301" who="S0267">so I knew what they were going to show me were either a <trunc>Pha</trunc> this happens to be a Phase Eight outfit but they're named labels you know and one of the guests could be wearing it you know that's that's where I find a trouble in my mind about it really how many other jumpsuits are going to be there?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="303" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm that's a slight worry <pause dur="short"/> yes yes</u>
<u n="304" who="S0266">I think that was my fear as well</u>
<u n="305" who="S0267">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0266">that's why I wanted it made</u>
<u n="307" who="S0267" trans="overlap">cos Phase Eight is a popular erm label over all the generations even younger people so I am a little bit worried about this</u>
<u n="308" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yes yes no cos you'll personalise it so</u>
<u n="310" who="S0267">well I'll have a <unclear/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0310">mm yeah so what sort of finish is that going to be? what sort of fabric would that be?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0267">it'd be better if it were satin I think to give it some kind of a lift for the evening</u>
<u n="313" who="S0266">mm and what colour?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0267" trans="overlap">and so if you've got <trunc>on</trunc> black I would go for black</u>
<u n="315" who="S0266">cos you could do <trunc>s</trunc> really bright colour and then a pair of shoes to match or is that too daring?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/> top the top is nude lace over the black</u>
<u n="317" who="S0266">oh right yeah sorry I was thinking it was all black</u>
<u n="318" who="S0267">yeah erm mm so probably black you don't have one do you?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0266">but you could sell one quite easily</u>
<u n="320" who="S0267">could I?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0266">or I could help you I mean I'd have thought it's like the the sort of <unclear/> used to have you'd do a wide piece</u>
<u n="322" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yeah well I was going to go downstairs and go to but I don't know how much <unclear/> are actually</u>
<u n="323" who="S0266" trans="overlap">they're probably cheaper than you can make them for</u>
<u n="324" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yeah yes cos it's really just a pleated fabric isn't it?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm that's something <unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0266" trans="overlap">pleated? would it be pleated?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0310">I imagine it as being pleated</u>
<u n="328" who="S0266">I'm thinking of a sort of straight satin band around</u>
<u n="329" who="S0310">yes I mean pleated in a sort of horizontal sense</u>
<u n="330" who="S0267">it is yeah they are actually</u>
<u n="331" who="S0266">are they?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0267">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but you can have them just plain can't you? or do you want? oh that makes it a bit more complicated doesn't it for sowing</u>
<u n="334" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0266">what? actual pleats flapping over and going round?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0267" trans="overlap">well that's what I imagine <unclear/> quite wrong</u>
<u n="337" who="S0310">I've yeah well I've seen them with pleats and I've seen them with er soft pleating</u>
<u n="338" who="S0266">mm yes</u>
<u n="339" who="S0310">as if it's one thing but folds</u>
<u n="340" who="S0266">yes yes oh right</u>
<u n="341" who="S0267">mm I need to investigate that and a jacket and shoes and a clutch bag mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0266">so you're all sorted?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0267">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0266" trans="overlap">that's a huge relief oh have another biscuit you'll be fine</u>
<u n="345" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0266"><unclear/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0310">the only time I've really gone to buy anything was as I said for my niece's wedding and erm my daughter's very good actually I mean she understands me perfectly and she'll say just try it on <vocal desc="laugh"/> because everything I would say no I don't think so</u>
<u n="348" who="S0267" trans="overlap">and you're looking <unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0310">oh no I don't think so mother just try it on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm yeah right eh</u>
<u n="351" who="S0267"><unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0266">I think yeah I think it must be twenty minutes now erm</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
