<text id="STV6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:15:47</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house, Cambs</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>New research findings into getting a good night’s sleep, going camping, getting lost in a city, finding a good route into a city, and discussing a pilot’s flying ability. </topics>
		<activity>A couple eating lunch and discussing every day things. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0261">erm this guy who had kind of <pause dur="short"/> discovered this thing about how you sleep and how your body is and how it relates to earth and erm he was an electrician and erm so when you have got electricity you have to make it go back to the earth you make it ground you go to go you have to connect it to the ground</u>
<u n="2" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and so <pause dur="short"/> he is kind of old and he is in pain and <pause dur="short"/> he noticed how much kind of electricity there just is around you and stuff</u>
<u n="4" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="5" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and he started thinking about it and he was thinking about how humans aren't really connected to the earth they're not connected to the ground</u>
<u n="6" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0261" trans="overlap">like they used to be yeah because you walk around with shoes that are insulated erm and that you drive places that you are in buildings yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so your body your feet don't really touch the ground yeah they're insulated from the ground <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> what he erm because there was all this electricity around he found it out in his bedroom there was a lot of electricity coming from his walls and the appliances and all this kind of stuff</u>
<u n="10" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="11" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so what he did was he erm <pause dur="short"/> created this thing that helped insulate him from erm <pause dur="short"/> from from the electricity so he was in a kind of an electricity neutral zone yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0261">which he called a grounding mat yeah so this thing <pause dur="short"/> helped his body avoid the electricity I think is what they are kind of suggesting and erm after years of being on medication he had to take medication to be able to go to sleep he erm <pause dur="short"/> he found out that <pause dur="short"/> on the first night that he used this thing he slept without his medication for the first time in years yeah and erm <pause dur="short"/> so people did a few more studies into this kind of stuff and the effectiveness of ground mats and stuff erm the same people who are <pause dur="short"/> physically not that well and their bodies have got a lot of inflammation in them and you can measure how much inflammation or where the inflammation is by using heat sensors</u>
<u n="14" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0261" trans="overlap">because your body is inflamed it is giving off heat around these sites yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0261">so they simply had one of those coloured</u>
<u n="18" who="S0262" trans="overlap">like infrared or something</u>
<u n="19" who="S0261">those colour vision type</u>
<u n="20" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0261">matches</u>
<u n="22" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0261">of erm how people look after having <pause dur="short"/> you know the <trunc>th</trunc> the comparison between before and afters yeah of being grounded and not grounded</u>
<u n="24" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0261">and <pause dur="short"/> that inflammation goes away <pause dur="short"/> so it shows quite a big impact right so I was kind of thinking that <pause dur="short"/> since we have been back from our trip <pause dur="short"/> and my body's more stiff than it used to be even though we used to move around a lot and do a lot of physical stuff</u>
<u n="26" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0261">erm and it made me think <pause dur="short"/> when we were travelling we were connected to the ground quite a lot</u>
<u n="28" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and we slept on the ground</u>
<u n="30" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0261">like you know swag and stuff</u>
<u n="32" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0261">and we were a lot closer to that and I <trunc>almo</trunc> always kind of think <pause dur="short"/> most of the time we had a really good sleep at night</u>
<u n="34" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0261">yeah even though it was not in a bed</u>
<u n="36" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0261">not in a house all of that kind of stuff right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0261">so it made me wonder whether there was kind of a connection in that <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="40" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0261">the idea of just simply <pause dur="short"/> being more on the land</u>
<u n="42" who="S0262">mm yeah I mean we used to do a lot of beach walking</u>
<u n="43" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0262" trans="overlap">didn't we? so</u>
<u n="45" who="S0261">take your shoes off</u>
<u n="46" who="S0262">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah and sort of being in the sea and being connected with nature and being away from a lot of electricity</u>
<u n="47" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0262">because we really weren't really very near electricity quite a lot of the time you know</u>
<u n="49" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0262" trans="overlap">because we were well away from houses and buildings <pause dur="short"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0261" trans="overlap">it's an interesting thought innit?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0262">mm it is yeah it is and especially what <trunc>I</trunc> I notice is in a place like this house where things are left on standby</u>
<u n="53" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0262">there is like some kind of low level hum</u>
<u n="55" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0262">of these erm you know machines</u>
<u n="57" who="S0261" trans="overlap">appliances</u>
<u n="58" who="S0262">well appliances yeah left on <pause dur="short"/> particularly televisions</u>
<u n="59" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0262">and those Sky boxes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0262">erm and I think it would be interesting if you just turned everything off and got into a habit of not really having anything on standby</u>
<u n="63" who="S0261">you don't need it on at night time</u>
<u n="64" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="65" who="S0261">erm you just turn it off at the wall</u>
<u n="66" who="S0262">well dad used to have this thing when you know when mum was alive that she had so many different appliances in the living room stacked on top of each other</u>
<u n="67" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that he'd actually have you know programmed for it for everything to switch off at night</u>
<u n="69" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0262">no no standby I don't know what happened to that idea erm I will have to ask him but yeah I mean I think it really helped not having anything electrical in your bedroom while you're sleeping</u>
<u n="71" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0262">but I still think yeah I think there are in a way too many appliances in this house that <pause dur="short"/> are sort of conducting electricity</u>
<u n="73" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0262">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think that's it that's <trunc>prob</trunc> I mean that's probably why going camping is so <pause dur="short"/> relaxing too you know it's erm it is it's getting away from electricity</u>
<u n="75" who="S0261">yeah it is interesting that I hadn't thought of it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="76" who="S0262">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="77" who="S0261">but even I wonder if you just kind of got into the habit of not erm <pause dur="short"/> walking around with your shoes on when you are inside <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and when you are outside when it is like warm enough and that just down on the grass <pause dur="short"/> you don't really need your shoes on</u>
<u n="80" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0261">if you are at home and that</u>
<u n="82" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0261">and so you just kind of <pause dur="short"/> get that feeling of the earth</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262">mm yeah <event desc="sound of aeroplane"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0261">I wonder what that is?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">a plane</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="87" who="S0261">don't you think it sounds like an old plane?</u>
<event desc="sound of aeroplane noise"/>
<u n="88" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="long"/> it's quite hot again</u>
<u n="89" who="S0261">yeah it is nice <pause dur="short"/> you can see the shadow's kind of coming over quite a bit now isn't it? in our autumn</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0261">it is only like a couple of weeks ago the shadow was back close to the house so there was a lot more lawn to lie around on</u>
<u n="92" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0261">and now it is just like well half of it</u>
<u n="94" who="S0262">I know the clocks go whatever backwards forwards twenty-sixth October I think</u>
<u n="95" who="S0261">oh there's another whole month</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0261">wow</u>
<u n="98" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0261">okay <pause dur="long"/> yeah well it is not I suppose it is still what <pause dur="short"/> when its get dark? seven o'clock at the moment?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262">mm well even just after</u>
<u n="101" who="S0261">mm yeah okay so it is not too much to worry about time-wise at the moment</u>
<u n="102" who="S0262"><vocal desc="misc"/> excuse me</u>
<u n="103" who="S0261">that was charming <pause dur="short"/> appreciation of your food mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0262">it could have been a lot worse</u>
<u n="105" who="S0261">a Frenchman would be proud of you</u>
<u n="106" who="S0262">yeah the Japanese or Chinese or something like that</u>
<u n="107" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262">erm I got quite lost actually going into <anon type="place"/> and coming out of <anon type="place"/> yesterday it was quite strange getting lost <pause dur="short"/> really not kind of knowing where I was going to end up I kind of had a vague idea of the orientation but really didn't know how these roads were meant to be working together so what I did was I wanted to go up to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think I came off on the wrong turning I came off the first turning after you get onto the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0262">then there's this roundabout it looked like it was the <anon type="place"/> or something that takes you into <anon type="place"/> then I realised just as I was going into the town at exactly the time when people were picking up their children <pause dur="short"/> so I was sort of around <anon type="place"/> I thought oh I will cut through to try to get up to <anon type="place"/> you know where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives</u>
<u n="111" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0262">so I took some kind of road called <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="113" who="S0261">uh huh</u>
<u n="114" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's sort of around the backs of the backs</u>
<u n="115" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0262">and that's actually where all the schools are so I got completely and utterly clogged through <unclear>chocca</unclear> with all these mums and dads picking up their kids</u>
<u n="117" who="S0261">oh</u>
<u n="118" who="S0262">and then I came up to this other road and it was quite a good road because it is the road where <anon type="place"/> starts and there is erm erm park spots on the side of the road up until five you have to pay and then after that you don't have to pay</u>
<u n="119" who="S0261">okay</u>
<u n="120" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so what I did is I arrived at half past four paid my fifty P for thirty minutes and that was it for the whole night I only paid fifty P for parking and all I had to do was then walk past you know where we went to the solicitor and the <anon type="place"/> hall</u>
<u n="121" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I just walked down that hillish thing</u>
<u n="123" who="S0261">and then it is straight down</u>
<u n="124" who="S0262">and straight down into town</u>
<u n="125" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0262">okay you know it's about a ten minute walk</u>
<u n="127" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0262">it was quite straightforward though</u>
<u n="129" who="S0261">it is not too far down to the <anon type="place"/> is it?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0262">not at all</u>
<u n="131" who="S0261">on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0262">so that's kind of quite a good little spot so anyway I was coming home at night and I just thought oh I will just drive right up that road erm thinking that I was gonna be on <anon type="place"/> and then I was about to join the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0261">oh</u>
<u n="134" who="S0262">oh my god and then I saw this erm sign for the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="136" who="S0262"><unclear>I thought</unclear> oh okay that's something I do know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0262">I'll  go off there thankfully I kind of managed to figure out that I needed to move towards <anon type="place"/> because I know where that is</u>
<u n="139" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="140" who="S0262">and then from <anon type="place"/> I got to <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> I got out to <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> out</u>
<u n="141" who="S0261">so you came round that way</u>
<u n="142" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so I came really on the back roads</u>
<u n="143" who="S0261">yeah okay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0262">but it was a little kind of strange not really feeling like</u>
<u n="145" who="S0261">you knew where you were going</u>
<u n="146" who="S0262" trans="overlap">is this gonna work out?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0261">so you could have also erm headed back into town if you come past the <anon type="place"/> and then turned onto the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0262">yeah that's where I thought I was going to be but I actually looked at the map</u>
<event desc="sound of aeroplane"/>
<u n="149" who="S0261">it's a biplane</u>
<u n="150" who="S0262">ah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<event desc="sound of aeroplane"/>
<u n="151" who="S0261">I hope he is not going to erm kind of conk out like the other one did the other day</u>
<u n="152" who="S0262">that would be fun wouldn't it? we should make some friends with some pilots at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I am just going to go for a little pootle on <trunc>Satu</trunc>Saturday afternoon would you like to come with me? yes please <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah so anyway the roads up that way I mean what I figured out is if you do approach it from that direction it is actually really good because there those roads are not as I don't think they are not as well used as the one up our way like the one that takes you through <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know that's such a massive thing cos you come off the <anon type="place"/> you've got a massive roundabout you're gonna go into <anon type="place"/> then you have got to get into <anon type="place"/> well it's the most direct route but I think it can take forever <pause dur="short"/> when it's really busy in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so what I thought is I'll go through <anon type="place"/> go up the <anon type="place"/> and try and get in get in loop in that way</u>
<u n="153" who="S0261">yeah okay</u>
<u n="154" who="S0262">and I think on a on a on a not not at the school you know picky uppy time it's actually fine</u>
<u n="155" who="S0261">going in on the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0262">yeah I think it is it is just you have got to pick your time</u>
<u n="157" who="S0261">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0262">but it is quite good to know that erm <pause dur="short"/> you can park up there from five o'clock there's quite a lot of spaces off the side of the road you're not going to get done and you don't have to pay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and I think that's great because otherwise I've been parking in the <anon type="place"/> car park and you have to still pay up until seven o'clock on a Monday to Saturday and that's four pounds for two hours <pause dur="short"/> which is no good</u>
<event desc="sound of aeroplane"/>
<u n="161" who="S0261">and you've still got <trunc>abo</trunc> it sounds like they're out playing today <pause dur="short"/> that's like the third plane isn't it? is it the same guy that's done a funny loop?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0262">no I think he's a different <unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0262">having fun over there</u>
<u n="165" who="S0261" trans="overlap">he's kind of a noisier one</u>
<u n="166" who="S0262">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<event desc="sound of aeroplane"/>
<u n="167" who="S0262">its funny how they do that isn't it?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0261">wow he's kind of going down straight into the ground</u>
<u n="169" who="S0262">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0261">I hope he's gonna pull up</u>
<u n="171" who="S0262">oh look he is look oh look he's doing an acrobat look there you go yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0261">is he doing a circle loop the loop?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah well he did one of those uppy downy ones</u>
<u n="174" who="S0261"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he did an uppy downy one <pause dur="short"/> he's an uppy downy kind of pilot is he?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="short"/> maybe he is learning <pause dur="short"/> oh it's really a lovely day now <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite tempted to erm <pause dur="short"/> stay out here</u>
<u n="176" who="S0261">that's fine stay out here</u>
<u n="177" who="S0262">mm it's rather lovely</u>
<u n="178" who="S0261">you've got the lawnmower brigade on again</u>
<u n="179" who="S0262">yeah that's</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
