<text id="STZ3">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:44:14</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0203</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In a bar</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Sports, uni, work, bands</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting about general stuff</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0203">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0203">wanna see what I'm looking at</u>
<u n="2" who="S0202">there you go</u>
<u n="3" who="S0203">cool</u>
<u n="4" who="S0202"><unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="5" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="6" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="7" who="S0202">having fun?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0203">I didn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0202">you what?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0203">I didn't <unclear/> that <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0202">I know I've seen it</u>
<u n="12" who="S0203">oh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0202">no joking</u>
<u n="14" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0202">I smoke so much when I am fucking when I've had a drink I smoke a lot but normally I smoke like five a day <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0202">nice my <unclear>story</unclear> had</u>
<u n="18" who="S0203">oh I didn't think about that <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think you win there</u>
<u n="19" who="S0202">you what?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0203">I think you won there <vocal desc="laugh"/> I haven't looked or anything</u>
<u n="21" who="S0202"><unclear>loom</unclear> bands oh yeah can you remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0203">mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0202">like that fat one who were a bit retarded</u>
<u n="24" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0202">well I was at her house last night</u>
<u n="26" who="S0203">oh right</u>
<u n="27" who="S0202">do you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0202">so he is erm looking after his <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his parents' business while they are on holiday</u>
<u n="30" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0202">erm and he is in their house <pause dur="short"/> so one of my friends sent me a Snapchat of erm <pause dur="short"/> loom bands and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like oh look at you need to see these these loom bands sort of thing so like oh okay then and erm <pause dur="short"/> so I went upstairs going oh my god Pokémon Harry Potter everything <pause dur="short"/> so I took a picture of it put <unclear>on a</unclear> story and I was just like this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who can't like do anything</u>
<u n="32" who="S0203" trans="overlap">she's really creative</u>
<u n="33" who="S0202">that involves common sense and apparently she used to be really really clever</u>
<u n="34" who="S0203">oh right</u>
<u n="35" who="S0202">like mega clever but then obviously if you were a nerd when you were in school you don't have friends so she pretended that she were really dumb and then she pretended for that long that she became dumb</u>
<u n="36" who="S0203">that's what <unclear>it sounds like</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0202">and apparently that's what happened she pretended for so long she became dumb</u>
<u n="38" who="S0203">cos she is really like ditzy sort of thing like <pause dur="short"/> but I can see why she would do that and I could see how it would happen</u>
<u n="39" who="S0202">but apparently she used to be really clever</u>
<u n="40" who="S0203">right so did I</u>
<u n="41" who="S0202">yeah me <pause dur="short"/> too before I got</u>
<u n="42" who="S0203">drink</u>
<u n="43" who="S0202">drink in my life <vocal desc="laugh"/> how weird is it through right you go to university right and <pause dur="short"/> you sort of <pause dur="long"/> you <trunc>do</trunc>don't have you you have <unclear/> from your parents when you go to university but you went when you were twenty-one I went when I was twenty-two <pause dur="short"/> so freedom to you is different what it is to an eighteen year old</u>
<u n="44" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0202">whose never had freedom and whose never drunk</u>
<u n="46" who="S0203" trans="overlap">eighteen I just thought about being able to go out and get fucked whenever you want</u>
<u n="47" who="S0202">yeah and not have to answer to your parents</u>
<u n="48" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0202">but you had that before you went to university</u>
<u n="50" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0202">so it's different right?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0202">and like you don't want to go out as much as</u>
<u n="54" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0202"><trunc>ever</trunc> like in fresher's week for instance</u>
<u n="56" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0202">like everyone's trying to get shitfaced every night cos it's new it's exciting</u>
<u n="58" who="S0203">I can't hack it any more</u>
<u n="59" who="S0202">I can't hack it and then you feel so fucking old and it's like oh my god I'm so old</u>
<u n="60" who="S0203">happens though don't it? we do get older <unclear/> be depressing and old</u>
<u n="61" who="S0202">I wanna be Peter Pan</u>
<u n="62" who="S0203"><unclear>dead now</unclear></u>
<u n="63" who="S0202">he is</u>
<u n="64" who="S0203">no good</u>
<u n="65" who="S0202"><trunc>Rob</trunc> I cried when I found out he were dead</u>
<u n="66" who="S0203">I could have cried I could have cried</u>
<u n="67" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I know that's really sad</u>
<u n="68" who="S0203">Robin Williams was a big part of my life</u>
<u n="69" who="S0202">he was me</u>
<u n="70" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I used to love improvisational comedy and he was like so sick at it I used to watch him <unclear/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0202">he was the master of it he created it</u>
<u n="72" who="S0203">er so when he died I was like christ that's like a huge part of what I used to watch and what I used to love</u>
<u n="73" who="S0202">it were a massive part of my childhood like</u>
<u n="74" who="S0203">it made me feel really bad but erm I reckon that's gonna be happening quite a lot more often now I reckon a lot of other people that we used to love will start dying</u>
<u n="75" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0203">like my my favourite er guitarist when I was like sixteen was Eric Clapton but he's like seventy odd now he's gonna die</u>
<u n="77" who="S0202">he's gonna die soon in the next ten or twenty years</u>
<u n="78" who="S0203">cos he used to abuse drugs so much then that they're all gonna be a lot iller than they should do <pause dur="short"/> so I reckon people like that are gonna start dying soon and that's gonna be gutting for me Paul McCartney</u>
<u n="79" who="S0202">oh I love Paul McCartney I love The Beatles <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> there's two people in my whole life that I know that love The Beatles as much as I do my dad and one of my friends er we're not really friends any more but cos we've grown apart</u>
<u n="80" who="S0203" trans="overlap">and now and now me</u>
<u n="81" who="S0202">and now you like The Beatles to me like do you know when <pause dur="short"/>  like I loved The Spice Girls when I was growing up cos I was a teenage girl blah blah blah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0203">can I tell you <unclear>I still do</unclear></u>
<u n="83" who="S0202">me too</u>
<u n="84" who="S0203">I I've have got The Best of The Spice Girls on</u>
<u n="85" who="S0202">I've got all their albums I've got all the well I don't have the album I have their albums now but I used to have the cassettes</u>
<u n="86" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0202">and like</u>
<u n="88" who="S0203">that that dates you cos I had the CD <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0202">yeah I had the cassettes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0203" trans="overlap">you had the cassettes <unclear/> just a bit older than me</u>
<u n="91" who="S0202">two years difference <pause dur="short"/> but like I just I just look back now and I think music back in the day inverted commas whatever like used to when you were younger your whole life revolved around music sort of thing you were <pause dur="short"/> if you if you were a goth you listened to like</u>
<u n="92" who="S0203" trans="overlap">that's what you look like innit</u>
<u n="93" who="S0202">Sabbath that what you look like blah blah blah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0203">it takes on your whole persona don't it?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0202">yeah your whole</u>
<u n="96" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/> cos I live around music music people say it but music is my life like you my career music's what I do for fun music's what I do when I'm bored you know everything I</u>
<u n="97" who="S0202" trans="overlap">your degree</u>
<u n="98" who="S0203">everything I do is revolving around music so it is my life so if I if erm people die like Eric Clapton or something it really affects me and if</u>
<u n="99" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0203">and obviously it affects people er who were I don't like to say but <unclear>normal</unclear> like non <unclear/> non-musicians</u>
<u n="101" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah I know what you mean non-musicians yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0203">but it affects me just a tiny bit more and it's gonna <unclear/> them at some point</u>
<u n="103" who="S0202">cos your creativity comes from that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0203">yeah other and I I find it hard to identify because I'm not artistic I can't I can write stories but I'm a bit of a writer but I'm not like creative in many other ways so it all comes out when <unclear>you</unclear> do a song so my my granddad he's creative through dance yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> so what he does he just</u>
<u n="105" who="S0202" trans="overlap">right your granddad?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0203">my granddad</u>
<u n="107" who="S0202">how old is he?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0203">like sixty odd</u>
<u n="109" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0203">he's <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> so er I respect that but like when people do say like oh well music is my life or whatever I kind of go it's not your life it's not your life</u>
<u n="111" who="S0202" trans="overlap">is it though? is it though?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0203">even to me I could still survive without music</u>
<u n="113" who="S0202">no I couldn't</u>
<u n="114" who="S0203">I'd find summut to do even though</u>
<u n="115" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I couldn't I'd rather be blind than deaf</u>
<u n="116" who="S0203">really?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0202">yeah cos like</u>
<u n="118" who="S0203">I think I think I would agree with that because I'm nearly blind today</u>
<u n="119" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah me too</u>
<u n="120" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0202">but like I don't know actually though because if I'm given a choice to be born blind or to be born deaf I would choose I would be born deaf like because I wouldn't know about music I wouldn't know what it sounded like but</u>
<u n="122" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I don't think you'd miss it though because like okay well you're Stevie Wonder who's a brilliant musician who were born blind</u>
<u n="123" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0203">will he have ever missed being able to see because he never he never had any concept of actually what</u>
<u n="125" who="S0202">you wouldn't miss it cos you've never had it</u>
<u n="126" who="S0203"><unclear/> you don't know what seeing is so how could you ever people describe it to you how do you describe <unclear/> like when people say oh it's really colourful or whatever you know what's the colour? you don't know</u>
<u n="127" who="S0202">feel like one of my <trunc>frie</trunc> my best friends is deaf</u>
<u n="128" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="129" who="S0202">and when we're out at nightclubs and stuff and she dances and stuff like that like she doesn't actually know what it sounds like she can like she's not she is profoundly deaf but</u>
<u n="130" who="S0203">she gets the vibrations like yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0202" trans="overlap">vibrations so she can sort of tell a tune but like personally like I know what things look like so say like I turn sixty and someone gave me a choice you can either be deaf or you can be blind well I already know what colours are I already know what people look like okay</u>
<u n="132" who="S0203">you could you could deal with it a bit more</u>
<u n="133" who="S0202">you could deal with it more but if you think that you'll have never you'll never hear music again you'll never hear people you love speak</u>
<u n="134" who="S0203">yeah for me</u>
<u n="135" who="S0202">but then seeing them</u>
<u n="136" who="S0203" trans="overlap">for me for me it'd be hard cos obviously I love music so much but I don't know I I do like seeing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0203">even though even though without <unclear/> I'm pretty much blind</u>
<u n="139" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0203">like I still do love</u>
<u n="141" who="S0202">but that's the thing can you could you cope with being deaf and blind?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0203">no no I've always said if I lost a couple of limbs like say if I lost my legs or if I lost my arms or something</u>
<u n="143" who="S0202">I'd want to die</u>
<u n="144" who="S0203">I yeah I'd would I wouldn't be able to do it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0202">I could not think of anything worse than being paralysed</u>
<u n="146" who="S0203">I'm not strong enough to be able to <unclear>survive</unclear> that sort of thing like</u>
<u n="147" who="S0202">no me either</u>
<u n="148" who="S0203">I'd give up</u>
<u n="149" who="S0202">like I could not my my worst nightmare is probably being paralysed like being</u>
<u n="150" who="S0203" trans="overlap">well the worst ones are when they're paralysed but</u>
<u n="151" who="S0202" trans="overlap">trapped in your own body and you can't say or speak or</u>
<u n="152" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah but if they got me in one of them computers where my eyes could point at it and like make a like a you know make a <unclear/> kill me now kill me now with like</u>
<u n="153" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah like my mum used to work for Age Concern and erm she had a few patients who were erm trapped in their own bodies so to speak so they were completely paralysed and the only way they could <trunc>commun</trunc>communicate was their eyes and she'd say if that that ever happens to me just kill me because</u>
<u n="154" who="S0203">the the thing is when you do something like that in this country I don't know I mean it's not legal to do that but then you have to go to prison for doing that to someone that you love which is wrong if they</u>
<u n="155" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0203">it should be an incredibly thorough procedure and then right at the end of it you should be able to like kill someone that you love or whatever but it would have to be the most strictest procedure ever like you'd have to go through do they wanna do it? they'll have to find this this and this they'll have to</u>
<u n="157" who="S0202">but if they're paralysed they can't sign it</u>
<u n="158" who="S0203">I know but that that's the thing is like but you couldn't do it any other way because if they didn't have all that you could just go round killing your relatives for you know your inheritance or whatever so you've got that side of it and then there's that thing of erm you could do it abroad in Sweden they <unclear/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah but then you come back home and you get prosecuted for it</u>
<u n="160" who="S0203">so</u>
<u n="161" who="S0202">I think me me personally when I get to like a certain age like forty or fifty I am going to write a will and I'm going to have a will saying if I get these diseases or I can't do this then I want you to take me to Switzerland and wherever</u>
<u n="162" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0202">but there's gonna be a clause in my will or contract or whatever that will say you can tell anyone what you're doing</u>
<u n="164" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="165" who="S0202">and you can't blame yourself sort of thing</u>
<u n="166" who="S0203">it just always is</u>
<u n="167" who="S0202" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="168" who="S0203">got a nice family trip to Switzerland with your paralysed relative they go <unclear/> do like <unclear/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and they die naturally yeah but I can't think of anything worse than being trapped</u>
<u n="170" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0202">what?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0203"><unclear/> going out and he did get really drunk so</u>
<u n="173" who="S0202">yeah should go out <vocal desc="cough"/> okay I've got two options for you <pause dur="short"/> two that's it that's it we can <trunc>spec</trunc> we can drink the rest of this go to my house have Bacardi JD <unclear/> loads of mixers</u>
<u n="174" who="S0203">a party now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0202"><unclear/> though cos I don't think anyone</u>
<u n="176" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0202">do you know anyone who would come?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0203">I've got <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've got mates that would come but not that would want to come <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0202">oh okay me too and we can do that and go out and around town after when we're hammered</u>
<u n="180" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0202">and no one gives a shit or we could stay here drink more and then go out after but the thing is we're gonna spend shit loads of fucking money</u>
<u n="182" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0202">which I don't have and you probably don't have</u>
<u n="184" who="S0203">yeah whatever whatever</u>
<u n="185" who="S0202">do you wanna go out drinking or do you wanna go home?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0203">I whatever's cheaper</u>
<u n="187" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0203">I'm gonna <unclear/> I've never been and I've never been like this so I can't really deal with it either</u>
<u n="189" who="S0202">yeah so</u>
<u n="190" who="S0203">like when people say to me do you wanna do stuff and I'm like</u>
<u n="191" who="S0202">erm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0203">I really can't cos I've got no money left</u>
<u n="193" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0203">I've never been in this situation I've I've always had a bit I've always worked <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0202">yeah me too</u>
<u n="196" who="S0203">I've not had a job and they</u>
<u n="197" who="S0202">you know I <unclear/> about now like drinking</u>
<u n="198" who="S0203">I've got a couple of mates but not necessarily mates that I want <unclear/> to sit here and chill out</u>
<u n="199" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0203">I'd rather me and you chill out</u>
<u n="201" who="S0202">yeah me too cos I could get erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0203" trans="overlap">ah I don't like I don't like <unclear>them</unclear> people</u>
<u n="203" who="S0202">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="204" who="S0203">they they can be your mates like I say I've got no problem with having</u>
<u n="205" who="S0202" trans="overlap">have you seen this? I've not been on my Facebook for four hours</u>
<u n="206" who="S0203">everyone wants to be your friend <unclear/> I I bet all them friend requests are boys boy boy boy</u>
<u n="207" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0203">boy knew it</u>
<u n="209" who="S0202">why though?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0203">what?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0202">I don't see it like</u>
<u n="212" who="S0203" trans="overlap">they might just look at you and think oh wow I'd smash that</u>
<u n="213" who="S0202">I I don't get it personally I oh right okay I commented on a uni lad mag thing earlier</u>
<u n="214" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0202">you know the lad bible?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0202">I follow it cos I'm technically a lad I love everything they post and <unclear/> was saying erm first year students never change their bed sheets I'm like excuse me okay I change by bed sheets every week no fail</u>
<u n="218" who="S0203">I probably two weeks for me but that isn't <unclear>a lot really</unclear> I they can be a bit smelly bed sheets for a while</u>
<u n="219" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so I put excuse me <unclear/> this is my first year and I change my bedding every week and have one sexual partner so like excuse me you look amazing I wouldn't mind if you change your bed shit and he would she should really change her bed shit</u>
<u n="220" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0202">be more <unclear/> oh my god don't lie bitch are you looking for more partners cos <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> would you call a girl you don't know a bitch? oh he's sticking up for me ah and of <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/> all these people are looking at you</u>
<u n="223" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><unclear/> clean <unclear/> white and change it maybe it's because you're engaged would you like a second? at least that's <unclear/> erm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0203">ah all these dirty old men are sat there going oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0202" trans="overlap">how do I reply to er reply there we go</u>
<u n="226" who="S0203"><unclear/> put a comment on it she'll <unclear>show you</unclear> it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've only been engaged for one month <pause dur="short"/> no <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> sorry I don't live up to your porno expections expectations</u>
<u n="228" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0202">I feel like I'm I'm erm starting a war here</u>
<u n="230" who="S0203">you'll get some hate mail on there yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0202" trans="overlap">eighteen people said like excuse me but you look amazing I wouldn't mind if you changed your bed shit eighteen people liked that apparently I look amazing saying I look at myself in the mirror and I don't see that though</u>
<u n="232" who="S0203">I'm glad maybe <unclear>you should</unclear></u>
<u n="233" who="S0202">no but like do you look in your <trunc>mir</trunc> do you look in a mirror and think</u>
<u n="234" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0202">I love this about myself no I don't either <pause dur="long"/> oh my god oh <pause dur="short"/> oh I get a new phone soon</u>
<event desc="background talk"/> <pause dur="long"/>
<u n="236" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I look at <unclear/> and went</u>
<u n="237" who="S0202">like what? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> but no <unclear/> amazing</u>
<u n="238" who="S0203">like a <unclear/> eighteen</u>
<u n="239" who="S0202">oh I don't</u>
<u n="240" who="S0203" trans="overlap">probably a thousand people have read that and gone I I like her but I daren't I daren't blag it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="241" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh this guy is called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so he's obviously foreign and he's he's spelling erm she as in shit</u>
<u n="242" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0202">and he's put here where is it? why would you call it call a girl you don't know a bitch? and then he</u>
<u n="244" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0202">he's trying to say if you care that much about clean bed shits why don't you change it</u>
<u n="246" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0203">bed shit</u>
<u n="248" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0203">where's he from?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0202">oh er</u>
<u n="251" who="S0203">I bet he I bet he's a foreigner</u>
<u n="252" who="S0202">would you like a <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> which one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0203"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0202">I think he's Polish</u>
<u n="255" who="S0203">what is that <unclear>Lidl</unclear></u>
<u n="256" who="S0202">cos he looks he look walk he works at Lidl and he looks eastern European I've got then oh I don't know</u>
<u n="257" who="S0203">well he's definitely some sort of minority</u>
<u n="258" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0203">yeah course he is</u>
<u n="260" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> where is that?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0203">I think we can take</u>
<u n="262" who="S0202">take right go back</u>
<u n="263" who="S0203">wow he's got this</u>
<u n="264" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0203"><unclear>Russia</unclear> like Serbian</u>
<u n="266" who="S0202">Serbian</u>
<u n="267" who="S0203">Serb in the islands that's where he comes from</u>
<u n="268" who="S0202">oh <unclear>married</unclear></u>
<u n="269" who="S0203">there you go</u>
<u n="270" who="S0202">Serbian</u>
<u n="271" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0202">anyone would think I'm fucking a Serb this is so funny <foreign lang="srp">zlato cashmogu</foreign> what does that mean on here?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0202">have you got get your phone out</u>
<u n="276" who="S0203">I'm not <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0202">no come on get it out I wanna know what it means <pause dur="short"/> go on Google <unclear/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0203">you can do it hold on too late for <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't care</u>
<u n="280" who="S0203">you type in things and</u>
<u n="281" who="S0202">I watch porn as well</u>
<u n="282" who="S0203" trans="overlap">no but right be like <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> I'm saying what <unclear/> dark</u>
<u n="283" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0203"><unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0202">okay are you ready for <unclear/> this is like erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0203">why are you looking up paedophiles?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0202">why are you looking up paedophiles are you looking for tips or what?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0203">I was <unclear/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0202">sounds like there you go so if the end's <unclear>taking on</unclear> a bit normally erm zlato zato</u>
<u n="291" who="S0203" trans="overlap">it's got to be summut like look at her big tits or something</u>
<u n="292" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0203">I'd let her come in my bedroom <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0202">cay mogu</u>
<u n="295" who="S0203">I'd let her shit in my bed</u>
<u n="296" who="S0202">esperanto what is that?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0203">it's <unclear/> innit?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0202">wait there no wait text language put into that <pause dur="long"/> no it's not doing it</u>
<u n="299" who="S0203">might just be flying <pause dur="short"/> madu and mogu</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="300" who="S0202">so funny I'm currently are you taking a photo? what? <pause dur="short"/> family ha I'm not in any of these photos what is she talking about? I don't <unclear/> finally a house <unclear/> on my wall Doncaster <unclear/> ah fucking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gay <unclear>fuck</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually thinks that erm I hate him he thinks that and it's actually true</u>
<u n="301" who="S0203">I do so <pause dur="short"/> he he's one of them people</u>
<u n="302" who="S0202" trans="overlap">he sounds like a dolphin you know what I can't stand? okay do me a favour <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if you are ever going to turn gay not that you ever will</u>
<u n="303" who="S0203">not <unclear/> on that</u>
<u n="304" who="S0202">yeah if you're ever going to turn gay please don't act like a gay person</u>
<u n="305" who="S0203">yeah I can't stay <unclear>it</unclear></u>
<u n="306" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I fucking hate it so much my uncle is gay he's been gay his whole life I'm sorry he actually only came out when he was twenty and only <unclear/> at the time cos he were like a student and blah blah blah so they <unclear/> living my mum and my dad who were his brother and he came out and we all knew he were gay but he came out anyway and erm he never changed personality he was still the same person</u>
<u n="307" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0202">but he had sex with men instead of women</u>
<u n="309" who="S0203">well it don't change anything</u>
<u n="310" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="311" who="S0203">as soon as they start <unclear>talking</unclear></u>
<u n="312" who="S0202" trans="overlap">as soon as as soon as they come out as gay they start acting differently and I just don't fucking get it why?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I don't get why I don't get why being gay affects your personality</u>
<u n="314" who="S0202">no I don't</u>
<u n="315" who="S0203">to the point where it's like</u>
<u n="316" who="S0202">or black or being black I'm not racist but in fucking America every black woman talks like oh damn girl you did not just say that like the fingers and the head going and it's like just because you're black you don't need to act it this is why people dislike</u>
<u n="317" who="S0203">yeah because you live up to the stereotype</u>
<u n="318" who="S0202">yeah you live up to it</u>
<u n="319" who="S0203">it's now get this one down a self fulfilment prophecy I didn't know <unclear/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> they get stuck in the vicious circle of poverty and they do not know otherwise how to act <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0202">definitely</u>
<u n="321" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just saying big words now</u>
<u n="322" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0203">er no it's because erm they are brought up around like the stereotype that they are supposed to be fulfilling</u>
<u n="324" who="S0202">but I fucking hate that though like why would you want to be a stereotype? why do you live up to that?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah but if you think about it I'm quite a stereotype</u>
<u n="326" who="S0202">why? why are you a stereotype? tell explain to me how</u>
<u n="327" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I'm a stereotypical I'm a stereotypical hippy musician me I'm telling you right now</u>
<u n="328" who="S0202">no you're not though</u>
<u n="329" who="S0203">I am</u>
<u n="330" who="S0202">because if you if you</u>
<u n="331" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I talk about life and its meaning and shit like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no but if you no you're a stereotypical student</u>
<u n="333" who="S0203">yeah yeah I'd agree with that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0202">I'm a stereotypical student but my point is like you don't live up to that purposefully it's just the fact that you've been exposed to education and that's why you talk about it whereas uneducated people make these stereotypes <unclear/> students cos they're not educated</u>
<u n="335" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah but but but these black people they've been brought up all their lives they're around people like that so they're gonna act like that they're gonna they're gonna be</u>
<u n="336" who="S0202">I know but if you look at it er</u>
<u n="337" who="S0203">I know it looks daft</u>
<u n="338" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I've I</u>
<u n="339" who="S0203">and you know I agree with it but</u>
<u n="340" who="S0202">I recently been watching something called Mad Men it's like a sixties TV show niggers is what they're called in that TV show</u>
<u n="341" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="342" who="S0202">okay so black people not niggers but that's what they used to call them just saying</u>
<u n="343" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0202">erm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0203">get that on record <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0202">but it</u>
<u n="347" who="S0203">not racist</u>
<u n="348" who="S0202">I'm not racist no but like so back in the day blah blah blah do you want one?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0203">yeah alright</u>
<u n="350" who="S0202">so they used to call people niggers and that was erm a <trunc>derog</trunc> it was a derogatory term</u>
<u n="351" who="S0203" trans="overlap">it was acceptable and they and they could still say it</u>
<u n="352" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it was acceptable because niggers AKA black people coloured people whatever is politically correct today like they used to call them that because that was their name because it's politically correct no one agreed with being black blah blah blah but what I don't understand is today like Jay-Z or any rapper they <unclear/> say oh my nigger my nigger blah blah blah Morgan Freeman came out and said why do you call each other niggers?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0203">the best thing to do would be to just not use it and it'll go away and you'd lose all <unclear/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0202">exactly but the fact that they use it they make it a normal term</u>
<u n="355" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the same thing with what gay people have done where they've said the word fag and made it become er if you say they use queer for each other and stuff like that er it's they're trying to use it to <unclear/> to empower each other so they use it as like a <unclear/> we're using this supposedly offensive term against each other and it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's like a massive fuck you innit? well <unclear>in</unclear> America</u>
<u n="357" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they've taken ridiculous like turn now where they use it all the time for no reason</u>
<u n="358" who="S0202">in America we wore erm we were in Toronto and the taxi driver was taking us to the bus station to get on the greyhound and erm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0203">you got a greyhound?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0202">it was fucking awesome</u>
<u n="361" who="S0203">they're like a <unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0202" trans="overlap">do you know do you know who owned them? <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0203">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos they're always like they all just like</u>
<u n="364" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0203">they're all just like megabuses aren't they? where they just take you <unclear/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0202">but better better</u>
<u n="367" who="S0203">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0202">so to rent a car from New York to Niagara was a thousand bucks but to get on er bus to Niagara were a hundred and twenty dollars between us so sixty dollars each erm wifi leather seats reclines everything plug sockets everything you could want and they turn the lights off quiet as fuck on the bus whatever but erm can't remember what I was going to say</u>
<u n="369" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0202">what was I talking about?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0203">black people <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0202">no wait right so I went to Niagara falls stayed there for a day and a half got a taxi to erm from our hotel to the bus station in Niagara to go to Toronto and the guy in the taxi as soon as I got in like oh where you going? like where you going when you get to the bus station like oh we're going to Toronto blah blah blah and like oh okay are you going for the queer festival? I were like excuse me? and like ah are you going to the queers they're having a parade</u>
<u n="373" who="S0203">do they use that all the time up there?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0202">wait for it so he was saying oh are you going to <unclear/> parade? are you going to see the queers? all this all that and I were like excuse me but what are you talking about? like that's really offensive and he was like ah I'm talking about like lesbians gays and stuff like that they're having a a two million strong parade in Toronto like it's Canada Day and erm the the gay pride thing like oh okay yeah we're not going to see that it just so happens that we've landed on it like oh okay then well the dykes and the queers do a really good parade and it's good fun and stuff like that and I was just like thinking to myself why the fuck are you calling them dykes? do you not like lesbians or what like</u>
<u n="375" who="S0203">that's just the done thing</u>
<u n="376" who="S0202">and I were really offended yeah and I and I thought why the fuck are you calling them this? and we got to Toronto and we got to our hotel we dumped all our shit well it were a hotel it weren't a hotel it were a hostel we had two beds in one room</u>
<u n="377" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/> fucking hotel</u>
<u n="378" who="S0202">and that were it like but in Toronto there's no air con and its like forty degrees to was fucking horrible</u>
<u n="379" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0202">two single beds one of them had a wooden bar under the mattress and the mattress wasn't good enough to cover the wooden bar so you were laying on one bar all night it were fucking shit so we were like in Toronto we were sat in this bar all day like drinking and this old this this old guy walked past with with his little dog and erm he were like <unclear/> outside of our window cos I wanted to stroke his dog and</u>
<u n="381" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0202">all that yeah yeah innuendos yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0203" trans="overlap">like <unclear>getting</unclear> your paws on a dog and I was like what?</u>
<u n="384" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0203">I wanted to stroke his</u>
<u n="386" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but he was so cute</u>
<u n="387" who="S0203">dog alright</u>
<u n="388" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0202">it was so cute though and it it like walked past me and I went oh let me stroke it</u>
<u n="390" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0202">not your penis your dog blah blah and it <unclear/> on this guy and basically we thought he had autism cos <unclear/> has autism he's autistic but</u>
<u n="392" who="S0203">this guy looked like he did have a little bit of a <unclear/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no just he acted like he did so like you know when you're talking to some random stranger in the street and you're just like oh okay I wanna go home now</u>
<u n="394" who="S0203" trans="overlap">probably <unclear/> you're a bit weird or something like you get <unclear>up to go</unclear></u>
<u n="395" who="S0202">yeah well look you're talking to a stranger and you're like oh I'm gonna get off now blah blah blah like normally that's what happens just like five seconds ten seconds whatever and they're like ah I'm <trunc>ju</trunc> I'm gonna go now anyway nice speaking to you see you later but he didn't do that he stood talking to us for half an hour outside this window even though we were like <pause dur="short"/> okay see you later sort of thing and he kept he he said to us said ah I'm just gonna drop my dog off I might see you later I'm coming back into the parade and he actually came back ten minutes later without his dog and he kind of sat with us the whole night <pause dur="short"/> and he were calling gay people queers or dykes and we were just like this is so fucking offensive like</u>
<u n="396" who="S0203">is that how they live over there?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0202">but apparently that's what they call them <pause dur="short"/> they call themselves dykes and queers and it was called the queer and dyke festival</u>
<u n="398" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right</u>
<u n="399" who="S0202">and but to me to me it was <trunc>offen</trunc>offensive as fuck when that</u>
<u n="400" who="S0203" trans="overlap">so you get offended but they were loving it over there</u>
<u n="401" who="S0202">that's what they call each other like they call each other dykes or queers and I was like that's really offensive in England and trying to explain that to erm a Canadian or an American is like what? like why is that offensive? and I was like well in England we <unclear>see it</unclear> as a derogatory term</u>
<u n="402" who="S0203">perhaps over there they're a bit more lenient with that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="403" who="S0202">apparently I've heard they use it over there like that because they use it they use it's like nigger</u>
<u n="404" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0202">nigger used to be a term of you're not in my social class go back to your fucking pit and clean your fucking floors</u>
<u n="406" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0202">it's the same as dyke or queer</u>
<u n="408" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0202">but in England obviously that's offensive and English people get offended pretty easily compared to Americans</u>
<u n="410" who="S0203">yeah we like to think we're a bit better than everyone else they try and correct everyone</u>
<u n="411" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah you correct everyone don't you right? and that's what it is like the people the queers <pause dur="short"/> inverted commas and dykes inverted commas not a gay</u>
<u n="412" who="S0203">not racist</u>
<u n="413" who="S0202">not racist or gayist <pause dur="short"/> erm we say that as like oh you fucking dyke or oh you fucking queer fuck off back to your gay hole</u>
<u n="414" who="S0203" trans="overlap">you said that I'd never say that like it it sounds like I'm being all like self righteous and that but I've never called anyone it if if they were being if a gay person were really getting on with me I'd never go you queer</u>
<u n="415" who="S0202">no I wouldn't but</u>
<u n="416" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/> fucking <unclear/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0202">the <unclear/> society would say</u>
<u n="418" who="S0203">yeah maybe but I I personally would never use that I can honestly say I probably would pick on someone's worst physical attribute so if someone was like er someone had like a big mole I'd be like get away from me you big moley fuck or something like that like you would do that but I wouldn't ever ever go for their sexuality I don't think</u>
<u n="419" who="S0202">no but that's what they used to do</u>
<u n="420" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="421" who="S0202">like before it became norm they used to call them queers or dykes</u>
<u n="422" who="S0203" trans="overlap">everyone everyone's gay now it don't matter</u>
<u n="423" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0203">if someone's gay if you if I call someone a gay person it's part of them like</u>
<u n="425" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's part of them yeah <unclear>part of society</unclear></u>
<u n="426" who="S0203" trans="overlap">everyone's done gay stuff I'm sure you've got with a girl</u>
<u n="427" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0203">I've I've <vocal desc="laugh"/> I definitely have got with boys</u>
<u n="429" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0202">tell me a story</u>
<u n="432" who="S0203">er we were at some festival and there were these two birds next to us and we were like oh lesbians and we were like oh they're lesbians and we were like me and my mate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were like oh yeah course you are and they're like oh no we really are like we're <unclear/> and we were like yeah but you're probably just drunk birds who get with each other sort of thing so it was like oh if you get with him we'll get naked and start <unclear/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0202">American Pie</u>
<u n="434" who="S0203">start fingering each other yeah well no kinda like that yeah but <unclear/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you remember in that scene where they got put in that <unclear/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <trunc>Doncas</trunc>Doncaster Live er when I was sixteen erm so we were watching a band called go audio so I think it was either fifteen or sixteen for me me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and a lad called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were watching er this band and he <unclear>prefers</unclear> all The Doors shit and me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are like whatever he said I'll I'll they said oh I'll we'll get naked if you do er get with each other so I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was like oh no no way I'm <unclear/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0203">these two birds stripped off butt naked yeah started like lesing up and that and we were all me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are like love it like this is sick and they we're like oh you two might as well join in just before we did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes er oh do you two want a drink of water? one of them said yeah and he was like oh right I'll just water over your tits he started fucking chucking water all over them so they were all watery like covered in water and naked started getting fucking <unclear/> they'll never get up from that <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was and then erm at <anon type="place"/> in two thousand and twelve we were er like watching</u>
<u n="439" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I love it how you remember the years I don't remember any year for anything</u>
<u n="440" who="S0203">I know what I know what festivals I know I used to have the band on so I know what years I've been to yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0203">I know what years I've been to them all but in <anon type="place"/> in two thousand and twelve erm me and might have been <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I don't know I don't want to going on record cos I'm not a lair but er</u>
<u n="443" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0203">me and me I think it was</u>
<u n="445" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no one's actually gonna listen to this you know that right?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah someone will</u>
<u n="447" who="S0202">no they won't are you joking?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0203">this'll be evidence in court this at some point</u>
<u n="449" who="S0202">yeah I'm sure it will</u>
<u n="450" who="S0203"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you are racist listen to this</u>
<u n="451" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0203"><unclear/> and they'll edit everything out but that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0202">yeah <unclear>context</unclear> and all that niggers you fucking niggers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0203">but erm me and whoever are watching this band and there are two birds behind us and all they've got on is like black pants and er nipple tape</u>
<u n="455" who="S0202">so like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on a regular night</u>
<u n="456" who="S0203">no no just literally proper on the nipples and that were it</u>
<u n="457" who="S0202">so like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on a regular night</u>
<u n="458" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah but you know what I mean? just like black pants and just like nipple tape and me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are turning around like oh look at this anyway this guy bent over in front of them and goes oh jump on me back jump on me back so this girl like a big high or whatever jumps on his back and he <unclear>don't think he</unclear> looks strong enough to like get her up on his back so it's like like like up his back like ah trying to hold on like</u>
<u n="459" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0203">at least hold me up sort of thing he's not <unclear/> ah gonna do it for about four minutes we were watching this awkward awkward like situation thing like what is going on here? and she she like he like let her down and he turned round to her like ah I love you ah you're like you're the one and all this and she's like fuck me like it's a festival like you just</u>
<u n="461" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's a bit intense</u>
<u n="462" who="S0203">you do jump on someone's back if someone like that's just part of the done thing like</u>
<u n="463" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0203">but he's like proper reading a lot into it sort of thing like I love you and she's like oh right okay I'm not sorry I didn't think of you like that started stepping away and <unclear/> get get on my back I love you and I wanna be with you and all this and me and I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos we went <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s quite like protective over women I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like mate leave her alone sort of thing and he's like no get out of my way mate I love her and all this trying to proper like</u>
<u n="465" who="S0202" trans="overlap">were you on drugs?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0203">I don't know probably</u>
<u n="467" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0203" trans="overlap">the girl started getting scared and that we were like <unclear/> they were lesbians</u>
<u n="469" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I went I went to see erm I went to see Kings of Leon erm two thousand and eleven at Manchester Cricket Ground</u>
<u n="470" who="S0203">alright</u>
<u n="471" who="S0202">it was supposed to be <unclear>MAN</unclear> Area but erm it</u>
<u n="472" who="S0203">Old Trafford Cricket Ground or was it</u>
<u n="473" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0203">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0202">Old Trafford I think so what's the other one?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0203">like cos there's Old Trafford football there's Old Trafford for cricket as well</u>
<u n="477" who="S0202">cricket it were it were a cricket ground I don't know</u>
<u n="478" who="S0203">it would have been that one</u>
<u n="479" who="S0202">so anyway we were supposed to go to the MAN Arena but the tickets sold out so fast that like they sold out in seconds so we upgraded like and got a better venue and this all like Kings of Leon first album like good Kings of Leon not recent cos they've gone so mainstream they're shit</u>
<u n="480" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0202">personally I think so erm we went to this erm and I were with my ex-boyfriend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and all his mates and they're all faggots and I'm not being a gayist here</u>
<u n="482" who="S0203">not gayist?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0202">not gayist</u>
<u n="484" who="S0203"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0202">but they were all faggots like they were quite happy to go in at the last minute stand at the back of the crowd and I was like no I wanna be at the fucking front I wanna be able to let <trunc>le</trunc> Kings of Leon sweat on me</u>
<u n="486" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0202">that's how much I wanted to see them so I they were all still drinking I went right I'm gonna try and get to the front and they're like oh fuck off you're never gonna do it you're never gonna do it I got four I got three rows behind the front so there were three rows and then there were me and our row and I were on my own and there were this girl next to me she were fucking hammered absolutely fucking hammered and like she became my new best friend because</u>
<u n="488" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah like you do</u>
<u n="489" who="S0202">yeah like you do in festivals or gigs or whatever</u>
<u n="490" who="S0203" trans="overlap"><unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="491" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0203">you <unclear>look after</unclear> someone or whatever</u>
<u n="493" who="S0202">you become friends with people don't you? unless you're a shy fuck and don't speak to anyone and sit in a corner so anyway I were dancing with this girl she were putting she were putting her arm around me she were getting on my back and I were getting on her back and we were best friends and then next thing I know there were like <trunc>mas</trunc> shoe felt really warm and I'm like what the fuck is that? and I turn around and this guy has got his fucking cock out he's pissing on my foot and I had decathlons on do you know what decathlons are?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0203">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0202">er fucking white decathlons on</u>
<u n="496" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0202">so he wasn't pissing on my shoe he's pissing into my shoe because there's that much foot hanging out and it's so loose around the edges not like a vagina but you know unless you have a big one unless you have a big one</u>
<u n="498" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I'm familiar with <unclear>that</unclear> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0202">so it was so and he was just pissing on my fucking foot and I turned round and said what the fuck are you doing? and he was like oh I'm just having a piss love and I'm like well you just fucking pissed on my foot and he started laughing and I fucking lost my temper so I kicked him in the bollocks I was like you fucking wanna do that again? and his girlfriend come up to me and she were like why the fuck did you kick him in the bollocks? I went well he pissed on my shoe on my foot and it's like oh okay then</u>
<u n="500" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0202">and like high fived me and walked off and like that is the worst experience I've ever had but the best fucking music thing that I've ever been to ever</u>
<u n="502" who="S0203">thank god</u>
<u n="503" who="S0202">it were fucking amazing cos like do you know when you listen to bands on the radio or singles or albums</u>
<u n="504" who="S0203" trans="overlap">nowhere near as good as live</u>
<u n="505" who="S0202">it is innit? no but you listen to some people and they sound amazing on the CD but when you go and see them live it's fucking shit like the sound not the experience the sound is shit but Kings of Leon fucking better than their album</u>
<u n="506" who="S0203">really?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0202">better</u>
<u n="508" who="S0203">I <unclear>haven't</unclear> seen them my only only band I haven't <unclear/> actually seen all my favourite bands now apart from Arctic Monkeys</u>
<u n="509" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I know them personally</u>
<u n="510" who="S0203"><unclear/> I might <unclear/> er</u>
<u n="511" who="S0202">I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0203">really?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0202">personally my erm ex-boyfriend used to go to school with him and they're still best friends now</u>
<u n="514" who="S0203">oh cool</u>
<u n="515" who="S0202">and the whole time that we were going out a few year ago now they were just becoming famous</u>
<u n="516" who="S0203">cool</u>
<u n="517" who="S0202">so he used to hang around with all my friends er my boyfriend's friends sorry and erm he used to come out on like nights out and stuff and no one used to know who we were and then as soon as they hit the big time he became a cunt weren't interested in his old friends just interested in his new bigger boys who were like his friends and shit and he drives around now in where my ex-boyfriend lives erm <anon type="place"/> in a muscle car in a fucking suit all the time thinking he's the fucking dogs bollocks he's actually a fucking cunt</u>
<u n="518" who="S0203">I can I can believe that yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0202" trans="overlap">since since he became famous he's become a fucking massive knobhead</u>
<u n="520" who="S0203" trans="overlap">I'd like I'd like I'd like to think I wouldn't do that yeah but you can never tell look it happens to you you can never you can never think about what actually</u>
<u n="521" who="S0202">would you let it change you?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0203">I don't think I'd like to think I wouldn't but you don't know like I would never say oh I definitely wouldn't cos</u>
<u n="523" who="S0202">you don't know do you?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0203" trans="overlap">like if there's that much pressure and stuff like that happens to you and there's that much stuff happening like them you don't know how you change I've changed since</u>
<u n="525" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you change in a way but</u>
<u n="526" who="S0203">you get more cocky</u>
<u n="527" who="S0202">personally like as a as a Yorkshire person and as a nice guy like you don't you you don't have you don't</u>
<u n="528" who="S0203" trans="overlap">yeah but he might have been a nice guy</u>
<u n="529" who="S0202">no but he wasn't he was always cocky</u>
<u n="530" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="531" who="S0202">he was a nice guy but he was always cocky like as soon as he cos I knew him before he went into his band and like proper in a band like performing like you are</u>
<u n="532" who="S0203">yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0202">like because he always had a band but he were never like as cocky as he were until he came <trunc>be</trunc>became the Arctic Monkeys</u>
<u n="534" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="535" who="S0202">so he became cocky after soon as they got their first big kig gig they got on the erm <trunc>rad</trunc> BBC Radio Live as like a new <unclear/> starter band as soon as he did that he became cocky</u>
<u n="536" who="S0203">oh right I know people that have done that as well</u>
<u n="537" who="S0202" trans="overlap">his first erm video so it was the same sort of time he went on BBC Radio Live and had his first video at the same time and became cocky</u>
<u n="538" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="539" who="S0202">and he's changed so like</u>
<u n="540" who="S0203">see we've done that</u>
<u n="541" who="S0202">but you're not cocky you're not you've not changed</u>
<u n="542" who="S0203">I like to think I won't but people can get the wrong impression from you just from one one performance and that if you if you say the wrong thing like cos you've got to remember as well you knew him quite well so you obviously got quite a good judge of him</u>
<u n="543" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0203">but if I perform once in thirty er in a thirty minute set all anyone's ever gonna see of me there might be twenty people there they might all watch me and I might say one bad thing like that I didn't really mean and it might make a lasting impression</u>
<u n="545" who="S0202" trans="overlap">or it might come across</u>
<u n="546" who="S0203">and they might just think of him as oh it's that arsehole after that one night</u>
<u n="547" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah but I knew him personally and he were always cocky</u>
<u n="548" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="549" who="S0202">and as soon as he became <trunc>fa</trunc> well he didn't he didn't become famous he erm he got on BBC and he had his erm first music video first single</u>
<u n="550" who="S0203">right</u>
<u n="551" who="S0202">and <vocal desc="cough"/> that as soon as his video was finished recording that's when he became cocky like I'm fucking better than you you're a cunt like fuck off sort of thing and like he were just</u>
<u n="552" who="S0203">I've heard stories like that about him as well he's <unclear/> cocky</u>
<u n="553" who="S0202" trans="overlap">he he used to be a nice guy but go on go fucking leaving midway conversation</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
