<text id="SU6W">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:21:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0022 S0023</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers’ home, Hungerford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Personality traits,   spiritual journeys, soul mates, visiting periods in history, imaginary parties</topics>
		<activity>Husband and wife having coffee, talking about real and imaginary situations</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements, apologizing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0022">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kettering, Northamptonshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hungerford, Berkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>PA to director</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- Advanced; Spanish -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0023">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Taplow, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hungerford, Berkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>IT consultant</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0023">yeah we're recording now <pause dur="short"/> go ahead</u>
<u n="2" who="S0022" trans="overlap">shall we check that it works?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0023">no it'll be fine</u>
<u n="4" who="S0022">okay <pause dur="short"/> alright <pause dur="short"/> which of your personality traits would you most like to change?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0023">most like to change <pause dur="short"/> the my my lack of memory <pause dur="short"/> I've got a terrible memory</u>
<u n="6" who="S0022" trans="overlap">that's not a personality trait</u>
<u n="7" who="S0023">well it probably isn't no <pause dur="short"/> that's the first thing that comes to mind <pause dur="short"/> unless you think unless it's my laziness in trying to remember that makes me have a bad memory <pause dur="short"/> which it could be <pause dur="short"/> aha <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> personality trait that well one doesn't like to admit to one's faults <pause dur="short"/> that's a tricky one</u>
<u n="8" who="S0022">oh well I think it's a virtue being able to admit to one's faults isn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0023" trans="overlap">what would I like to change? Yeah I suppose it would be it would be good but then you see if you've got the faults and you know what they are why don't you do something about them? That's the</u>
<u n="10" who="S0022">well</u>
<u n="11" who="S0023">that's embarrassing then isn't it</u>
<u n="12" who="S0022">well not necessarily <pause dur="short"/> for example I think</u>
<u n="13" who="S0023"><unclear/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0022">I the what I'd most like to change is my sort of temper stroke speaking before I engage my brain</u>
<u n="15" who="S0023">oh</u>
<u n="16" who="S0022">and it's really really hard but I think I'm definitely better <pause dur="short"/> but it's really really hard cos the thing is you don't see it coming <pause dur="short"/> it's not as if you feel it coming <pause dur="short"/> well if I do feel my temper coming on I can do something about it <pause dur="short"/> but but often I find that I've said something and it's not until after I've said it I thought oh why did I say that <pause dur="short"/> but it's done in the spur of the moment <pause dur="short"/> so it's really I mean it sounds as though I'm making an excuse but it is really really hard so that's why I spend half my life apologising <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="17" who="S0023">oh I don't think it's quite that much honey</u>
<u n="18" who="S0022">well it is definitely better than it was <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="19" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0022">but it's still <pause dur="short"/> it's still there a bit</u>
<u n="21" who="S0023" trans="overlap">well that reminds me  that reminds me  of a a flaw that I used to have and obviously don't have any more though my my describing it is never er as not having it any more it is in fact an instance of it <pause dur="short"/> sort of</u>
<u n="22" who="S0022">it's arrogance</u>
<u n="23" who="S0023">well it is actually yes <pause dur="short"/> I used to be a little bit</u>
<u n="24" who="S0022">yeah you're definitely better than you used to be</u>
<u n="25" who="S0023">yes I used to think I knew everything and that everyone else was silly and um yeah I think I've stopped believing that now and I think I'm one could be secure in one's ideas</u>
<u n="26" who="S0022">yeah certainly take pride in yourself</u>
<u n="27" who="S0023" trans="overlap">and yet also open to other people's</u>
<u n="28" who="S0022">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="29" who="S0023">and and you do have to judge people and see if they know if they have reason valid in their ideas <pause dur="short"/> and if they do that's fine and if they don't well that's their business</u>
<u n="30" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0023">um but you know you have to accept that everyone's got their own independent ideas and how they've arrived at them is often a bit different from yours</u>
<u n="32" who="S0022">yes</u>
<u n="33" who="S0023">um but it but you mustn't be go the other way and be on self-conflict</u>
<u n="34" who="S0022" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="35" who="S0023">what's the opposite of arrogant?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0022">er well</u>
<u n="37" who="S0023">simpering perhaps or is that too much?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0022" trans="overlap">no no no no no that's not no <pause dur="short"/> simpering is when you're like a  to someone <pause dur="short"/> um what's the opposite of arrogant? It's <trunc>pro</trunc> it's probably um well it's like being really humble but that's sort of modest maybe</u>
<u n="39" who="S0023">oh okay modest yeah that sounds about right</u>
<u n="40" who="S0022">erm but I think it's a fine line because I think arrogance is clearly sort of an unattractive trait with people <pause dur="short"/> but so is false modesty cos that's just annoying</u>
<u n="41" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0022">Cos it just feels as if they're looking for you to say no you're not really you're brilliant</u>
<u n="43" who="S0023"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0022">and that's annoying <pause dur="short"/> I think it's to find the the sort of the fine line between what you think between having confidence</u>
<u n="45" who="S0023">ah yes</u>
<u n="46" who="S0022">and not this it's um quite hard</u>
<u n="47" who="S0023">I'm sure there's a line of poetry I can't remember which is along the lines of um</u>
<u n="48" who="S0022">that's probably from If or something isn't it?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> knowing all knowing your strengths and your weaknesses and drawing the line between them</u>
<u n="50" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0023">where you you're honest about yourself basically</u>
<u n="52" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0023">er yeah well that's a good thing to have</u>
<u n="54" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0023">so I suppose still sometimes arrogant <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I get too er angry although I do sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I did swear at a bloke at work the other day just because he was sitting in my chair <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't really my chair because we had hot-desking but I'd had a hard journey and I sometimes do lose my temper a bit when it comes to because of the travel and stuff <pause dur="short"/> it's not really a very good excuse <pause dur="short"/> nice a very nice bloke</u>
<u n="56" who="S0022">did you apologise afterwards?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0023">yeah I did later you know</u>
<u n="58" who="S0022">oh good <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Cos that's half the battle</u>
<u n="59" who="S0023">but we're all in the same barrel there and it's because if it happens to be a bad day and everyone's in and there's no chairs then it's just <event desc="sound of blowing raspberry"/> How can you get on with your work? It's just frustrating</u>
<u n="60" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0023">and er you think why do I have to fight for the right to sit down and get on with my job <pause dur="short"/> it's just insane</u>
<u n="62" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0023">so I'm giving that job up soon which is a good thing</u>
<u n="64" who="S0022">that's good</u>
<u n="65" who="S0023">yeah anyway</u>
<u n="66" who="S0022">Good right <pause dur="short"/> do you want to ask me a question?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0023">oh yes I'd love to ask you a question <pause dur="short"/> will you marry me? Oh no we've done that one already <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="68" who="S0022">actually you did propose to me when I was wearing tracksuit bottoms <pause dur="short"/> that's <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> Nice <pause dur="short"/> go on</u>
<u n="69" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah well that that that bird is won I thought funnily</u>
<u n="70" who="S0022">that's gonna that's going to present a lovely image isn't it <pause dur="short"/> anyway go on <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you decided to go on a spiritual journey</u>
<u n="72" who="S0022">ooh</u>
<u n="73" who="S0023">where would you go and what would you do?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0022">ooh <pause dur="short"/> now that's fairly interesting</u>
<u n="75" who="S0023">isn't it</u>
<u n="76" who="S0022">A spiritual journey?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0023">yeah What is that?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0022">well I'll tell you what I <trunc>fe</trunc></u>
<u n="79" who="S0023">it doesn't have to be spas does it? Just go and</u>
<u n="80" who="S0022">no although that could be interesting as such</u>
<u n="81" who="S0023">that's what comes to my mind anyway go on</u>
<u n="82" who="S0022">what I actually this is quite funny but when I think of when you say spiritual I think of religion</u>
<u n="83" who="S0023">do you?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0022" trans="overlap">what I have done a couple of times is um on Good Friday in London they have a well march isn't the right word but they have a sort of procession</u>
<u n="85" who="S0023">mm mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0022">that goes from oh the Methodist outside the Methodist hall</u>
<u n="87" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0022">up to <pause dur="short"/> is it to Westminster Abbey? I think it's to Westminster Abbey and then to Westminster Cathedral <pause dur="short"/> in other words you're going from three different types of <unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> three different types of Christianity <pause dur="short"/> well yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0022" trans="overlap">so I went there one time <pause dur="short"/> I went there probably I don't know five years ago</u>
<u n="91" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0022">and then I went another time with my mum <pause dur="short"/> and the funny thing is that now um I really although I might put Christian on forms I really I'm not a practising Christian <pause dur="short"/> and I I you know I'll go to church at Christmas and Easter and stuff but when I've been on those I've been so I've found them so moving <pause dur="short"/> and the last one I went on I think I cried</u>
<u n="93" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="94" who="S0022">um cos I think</u>
<u n="95" who="S0023">why is that do you think?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0022">well I think the crucifixion story is so moving and <trunc>car</trunc> erm what's his name? Cardinal erm Murphy O'Connor <pause dur="short"/> he's the head of the Catholic Church</u>
<u n="97" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0022">he was er he gave a little talk <pause dur="short"/> and I found that very very moving so that's when I spoke to that's what I thought he'd done <pause dur="short"/> erm if I were going oh erm I'm not sure</u>
<u n="99" who="S0023">I guess you could take it to mean some place that you go not because you wanna see the sites or have a rest but somewhere where you go to enhance your your spirit where you go purely for sort of <trunc>pp</trunc> I don't know spiritual <trunc>de</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it could mean anywhere that you go to enhance your um your consciousness as opposed to just physically relaxing</u>
<u n="100" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0023">so what would you say?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0022">huh <pause dur="short"/> I really don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's not normally a <trunc>part</trunc> I don't normally think about er spiritual matters are not normally something that I'd particularly think about <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0023">maybe you should</u>
<u n="104" who="S0022">maybe I should</u>
<u n="105" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0022">um <pause dur="short"/> ooh I don't know I'm gonna leave too big a gap <trunc>some</trunc> on the recording if I think about it <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> what about you?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0023">yeah I I picked this out cos I wasn't sure what my own answer was and thought it was an interesting question <pause dur="short"/> but if you yeah you know had the time to do it <pause dur="short"/> a spiritual journey somewhere somewhere you would go some things you would do whereby you would just focus on improving your own spirit meaning your um er it's hard to describe actually isn't it?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0023">your consciousness and your your feelings about yourself and um yeah it's a good question <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it does tend to be to do with religion and you say oh I'd go to the top of a mountain and um achieve enlightenment</u>
<u n="110" who="S0022" trans="overlap">but I think on the other hand I mean you could um I think if you  if you  think of a figure that you really really admire <pause dur="short"/> if you look if you think of um yeah if you think of a figure that you really admire <pause dur="short"/> I mean it could even I mean you don't tend to think of um business as spirituality but do you remember when I met you you used to read those books? Every morning you read a book <pause dur="short"/> an autobiography</u>
<u n="111" who="S0023" trans="overlap">biographies <pause dur="short"/> yeah usually yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0022">um about and so cos you said to me and you said to me yeah read a biography and a biography of people you admire and you said you read that in the morning so that you'd start the day</u>
<u n="113" who="S0023">mm mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0022">you'd read it over breakfast and you'd start the day feeling inspired</u>
<u n="115" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0022">which I think was brilliant and um that in a way could be it's not I don't think it's what we'd sort of traditionally think of as spiritual but if it's something that gives you more motivation more sort of zest for life then well why not?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's true <pause dur="short"/> so that's made me think actually you could look at it in a broader way and I'd say say for example going to er Florence I could see that as a spiritual journey cos I really love the art they've got there</u>
<u n="118" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0023">and I would go there purely with the purpose of trying to enhance my er enjoyment of life through art and I definitely would I'd consider that</u>
<u n="120" who="S0022">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and ice cream</u>
<u n="121" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0023">yeah that as well</u>
<u n="124" who="S0022">we should do that we should go back there</u>
<u n="125" who="S0023"><unclear/> ice cream <unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0022">the Euro's good this year apparently</u>
<u n="127" who="S0023">it's better than it was</u>
<u n="128" who="S0022" trans="overlap">it's supposed to be a good year for going to Europe because the Euro has has gone down finally</u>
<u n="129" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> compared to the pound <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0022">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="131" who="S0023">yeah we should go and write that down as a suggestion for a holiday</u>
<u n="132" who="S0022">no we should if this <trunc>bar</trunc></u>
<u n="133" who="S0023">it's true</u>
<u n="134" who="S0022">I mean if this barge thing isn't going to work out then maybe we should go to Florence</u>
<u n="135" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> although they have barges in Venice but that's a different kind of barge</u>
<u n="136" who="S0022">A different sort of barge</u>
<u n="137" who="S0023">someone else does all the punting as well</u>
<u n="138" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0023">yeah spiritual that's interesting but then on the other hand see what's the opposite? The opposite of spiritual is material <pause dur="short"/> so you could say you go on to a beach to relax and that is genuinely physically relaxing but then even that is relaxing your mind you know human beings are both aren't they</u>
<u n="140" who="S0022" trans="overlap">but then if you're really you know what it's like if you're really um say you've had a really hard time at work and you're just all you can feel physically sort of</u>
<event desc="sound of phone beeping"/>
<u n="141" who="S0022">oh dear that's my phone <pause dur="short"/> you can feel sort of physically tense but you've also got your mind sort of whirling with all these things and then if you then go to somewhere like a spa or a beach whatever <pause dur="short"/> I don't know is that? Can you count that as spiritual? What I'm thinking of is</u>
<u n="142" who="S0023">not really</u>
<u n="143" who="S0022">okay <pause dur="short"/> right okay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0023">well I'm just reading out the question it says spiritual journey so not spiritual relaxation</u>
<u n="145" who="S0022">yeah okay</u>
<u n="146" who="S0023">spiritual journey implies er you know a beginning and an end and it's</u>
<u n="147" who="S0022">I can't see myself going I can't see myself doing meditation or going to a convent or or any anything traditionally spiritual</u>
<u n="148" who="S0023" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="149" who="S0022">I don't really feel <pause dur="short"/> I think it would be I think it could be good to reflect on various things but I don't really feel the <unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0023" trans="overlap">you know you could have a spiritual journey on the barge through the you know er through the  through the  English countryside if you</u>
<u n="151" who="S0022">you mean hug a tree?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0023">yeah something like that</u>
<u n="153" who="S0022">yeah you could do but um anyway</u>
<u n="154" who="S0023" trans="overlap">anyway let's do another one</u>
<u n="155" who="S0022">okay</u>
<u n="156" who="S0023">oh it's your turn now</u>
<u n="157" who="S0022">right let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> what have we got? Okay we've done that one <pause dur="short"/> ah here's a romantic one</u>
<u n="158" who="S0023">what?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0022">is there only one soul mate for each person?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0023">well there is for me at the moment and I would  I would  not expect there to be anyone that could equal your wonderfulness darling so</u>
<u n="161" who="S0022">ah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0023">um I don't know is it true if you know something <unclear/> you think well you know touch wood such a thing would never happen but if anything happened to you then maybe if I'm searching long and hard I might find someone who would come a bit up to your standard <pause dur="short"/> but um I think we're very very compatible</u>
<u n="163" who="S0022">yeah but do you think that?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0023">I mean why would that be true what it says in the question? Only if you believe in some higher power that's picked people out to be pairs which I don't</u>
<u n="165" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see I don't believe it's true <pause dur="short"/> I think the thing is when you and I met we had we were obviously compatible at a certain level</u>
<u n="166" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0022">but you I think you</u>
<u n="168" who="S0023">we have changed</u>
<u n="169" who="S0022">yeah you grow more towards or apart from each other</u>
<u n="170" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's true</u>
<u n="171" who="S0022">um <pause dur="short"/> and yeah it I I don't I think that if you find a sort of perfect relationship with one person then to be able to expect that again is obviously gonna be harder <pause dur="short"/> but then ah mm but then I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but I no I don't  I don't  think that there's only one soul-mate no <pause dur="short"/> I think you you meet people you sort of grow into each other as it were</u>
<u n="172" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think I'd agree with that <pause dur="short"/> it's a funny idea though that there is <pause dur="short"/> I mean where does that come from?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0022">well it's a sort of romantic idea isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why because it it um</u>
<u n="174" who="S0023">well why is it romantic?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0022">maybe it isn't <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="176" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0022">maybe it's more romantic that there isn't</u>
<u n="178" who="S0023">yeah well I think it's more romantic to say that you know as we've just you you've just said you have to work towards it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0022">it's it's like that thing thing from Louis De Bernieres <pause dur="short"/> do you remember that reading that we had at our wedding and was it said it's like you're two  you're two  trees but your roots are entwined together</u>
<u n="180" who="S0023">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think as you said it's more <trunc>th</trunc> there's a lot of it that comes when you meet it's about whether you decide to grow your roots towards each other <pause dur="short"/> it it is a conscious decision a lot of it</u>
<u n="181" who="S0022">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know that definitely when um it's quite interesting because my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when I met her she was going out with um a chappy who was a bit older than her</u>
<u n="182" who="S0023" trans="overlap">was older than her yeah you said</u>
<u n="183" who="S0022">um quite sort of sensible and then when she um started when she finished her relationship with him and then she went she started going out with other people she became much less so um much less sort of she was more sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0023" trans="overlap">did she mirror the people she went out with? <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yes she did and I think at the same time it that that she split up with her um her original boyfriend I met you and we sort of I I could see quite clearly that we sort of became less alike because I became more like you and she became more like her <unclear/> so yep</u>
<u n="186" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> mm interesting <pause dur="short"/> is it my go now?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0022">yes it is</u>
<u n="188" who="S0023">right <pause dur="short"/> my next one is</u>
<u n="189" who="S0022">please don't think I'm rude if I read my text message while you're you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh how shocking <pause dur="short"/> what historical <pause dur="short"/> I hope you're paying attention <pause dur="short"/> shall I wait until you're paying attention?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0022">oh this is from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> sorry I'll read it out to you</u>
<u n="192" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh yeah what does it say?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0022"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it was really lovely thanks we went to see David Hockney exhibition mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0023">oh yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0022">had tea at had lunch at Fortnum and Mason and then a tour around West Minister Abbey <pause dur="short"/> it was absolutely fab <pause dur="short"/> how are you both?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0022">I hope that she got my message I hope I didn't leave it no I couldn't have left it on the wrong phone <pause dur="short"/> oh well never mind</u>
<u n="198" who="S0023">oh well she's um said something now that's good</u>
<u n="199" who="S0022">but she's yeah good <pause dur="short"/> she's had a nice day but anyway yes go on</u>
<u n="200" who="S0023" trans="overlap">that's good yeah <pause dur="short"/> so what historical time period would you most like to visit?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0022">ah ha ha ha</u>
<u n="202" who="S0023" trans="overlap">similar to the question we did the other day but not quite the same thing</u>
<u n="203" who="S0022" trans="overlap">to visit</u>
<u n="204" who="S0023">it's not about where you were born you just get to visit and come back so imagine you had a time machine and you could jump in it and it wouldn't cost you anything and you could go in and you could do what you wanted to <pause dur="short"/> you could stay for say you know um a week or two weeks <pause dur="short"/> and you'd be perfectly safe you know <pause dur="short"/> well assuming you didn't get blown up</u>
<u n="205" who="S0022"><unclear/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0023">what would you the most curious to go and witness <trunc>fir</trunc> first hand?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0022" trans="overlap">ahh <pause dur="short"/> that's interesting</u>
<u n="208" who="S0023">but you only have a couple of weeks is what we're saying <pause dur="short"/> we're not saying you could visit it and live there that's a different question</u>
<u n="209" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0023">so you get to be at a certain time at a certain place for two weeks <pause dur="short"/> what would you do?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0022">erm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0023">I better think about my own answer actually</u>
<u n="213" who="S0022">that's really  that's really  interesting <pause dur="short"/> well in some ways I'd like to go and visit an earlier <trunc>p</trunc> period in history</u>
<u n="214" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0022">oh I'll tell you what it'd be nice  it'd be nice  to well I was going to say it would be nice to go to do things of biblical times</u>
<u n="216" who="S0023">oh yeah like what?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0022">see Jesus</u>
<u n="218" who="S0023">well there you go now that would be interesting</u>
<u n="219" who="S0022">that would be fun</u>
<u n="220" who="S0023">that would be really interesting</u>
<u n="221" who="S0022">very fun wouldn't it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0023">you could find out some of the facts wouldn't you</u>
<u n="223" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0023">God that would be fun then you could come back and tell everybody what was actually true</u>
<u n="225" who="S0022">yes</u>
<u n="226" who="S0023">he was a very bad carpenter or he kept hitting his thumb or something</u>
<u n="227" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0023">I don't know</u>
<u n="229" who="S0022">um well it that's right in some ways I'd like to go back to a really really early period because I don't know about you but sometimes this sounds really stupid but</u>
<u n="230" who="S0023">mm mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0022">sometime with really  with really  early periods of history although obviously we know they're factual because you know there's evidence for them</u>
<u n="232" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0022">but I kind of think well they're so far away that I can't imagine that they were real</u>
<u n="234" who="S0023">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0022">I know they were but anyway</u>
<u n="236" who="S0023">sure</u>
<u n="237" who="S0022">but then <trunc>a</trunc> another part of me thinks well it'd be nice to go when you had to a time of sort of peace and prosperity and you had a nice ruler</u>
<u n="238" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0022">I kind of think I'd be quite interesting to to to go um say when I kind of think it's quite nice to visit around Tudor times when Henry the Eighth was on the throne <pause dur="short"/> but it wouldn't really because I don't think life was particularly peaceful under him and that you're always afraid your head er your head would get chopped off</u>
<u n="240" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0022">erm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0023">you don't have to live there don't forget</u>
<u n="243" who="S0022">no</u>
<u n="244" who="S0023">this is only a question of being there</u>
<u n="245" who="S0022">oh oh I'm really not sure</u>
<u n="246" who="S0023">just for just to be somewhere</u>
<u n="247" who="S0022">um</u>
<u n="248" who="S0023">I don't think in this  in this  scenario you can actually be anybody you want you can just imagine that you can visit</u>
<u n="249" who="S0022">no</u>
<u n="250" who="S0023">and they wouldn't see you as being a foreigner or whatever</u>
<u n="251" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="252" who="S0023">you could just witness something <pause dur="short"/> you could just be there and witness or be there for an atmosphere or for a a period</u>
<u n="253" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0023">I suppose you could ask people questions and stuff when you were there <pause dur="short"/> you could interact with them</u>
<u n="255" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0023">as if you were a local</u>
<u n="257" who="S0022">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm maybe if there was a queen on the throne</u>
<u n="258" who="S0023" trans="overlap">I <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0022">Cos that would be <pause dur="short"/> maybe one of the early queens that would be really interesting</u>
<u n="260" who="S0023">really?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0022">I mean the first sort of <trunc>coc</trunc> crowned queen of course was Elizabeth the First so that you know would be quite interesting</u>
<u n="262" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0022">anyway</u>
<u n="264" who="S0023">yeah then you'd be round er the period of Shakespeare <pause dur="short"/> imagine that</u>
<u n="265" who="S0022">ooh</u>
<u n="266" who="S0023">imagine seeing one of Shakespeare's plays put on for the first time <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't that be incredible?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0022">that would be interesting yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I that's I hadn't thought of that but I'd love to see people like Richard Burbage putting forward his</u>
<u n="269" who="S0022" trans="overlap">oh yeah that would be really good yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0023">just like in Shakespeare in Love but the real thing you know with the first presentation</u>
<u n="271" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0023">Cos he wrote you know Shakespeare wrote the plays with these people in mind as actors</u>
<u n="273" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0023">he wrote it for them because he knew their strengths and wanted to show them off and vice versa</u>
<u n="275" who="S0022">okay</u>
<u n="276" who="S0023">that would be amazing actually</u>
<u n="277" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0023">yeah that's true <pause dur="short"/> I had a thought but I'm not quite sure how it would work out <pause dur="short"/> it'd be really cool <pause dur="short"/> I'd have loved to <trunc>see</trunc> have been around when the moon landings were happening</u>
<u n="279" who="S0022">ooh yeah that would be bliss</u>
<u n="280" who="S0023">the the ideal thing is to want to be on the moon yourself but I don't think that's included in the question</u>
<u n="281" who="S0022">no</u>
<u n="282" who="S0023">it's not like being the astronaut <pause dur="short"/> the best you could hope for would be say camped out at Cape Canaveral or where ever it was watching the rocket go off er and so on <pause dur="short"/> that would be  that would be  cool</u>
<u n="283" who="S0022">but can you imagine how their wives must have felt er and their families <pause dur="short"/> they must have been</u>
<u n="284" who="S0023">stressed out</u>
<u n="285" who="S0022">absolutely ah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0023">and all the TV coverage and some of the press it must have been very difficult</u>
<u n="287" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah it must have been a nightmare <pause dur="short"/> but I don't think you know those programmes that were on a couple of years ago?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0023">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0022">I don't think many of them managed to survive unfortunately</u>
<u n="290" who="S0023">no</u>
<u n="291" who="S0022">um</u>
<u n="292" who="S0023">no but there was a lot of pressure  lot of pressure  on them</u>
<u n="293" who="S0022" trans="overlap">oh and there was this huge I think when they came back from the moon the men were all like sort of celebrities and oh the temptation <unclear/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0023" trans="overlap">the trouble is when more time goes on like that when no one else has been there the more it's sort of hyped up</u>
<u n="295" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0023">because it is still exceptional what they've done <pause dur="short"/> even the Chinese and Russians and everyone else haven't done it yet <pause dur="short"/> no one's done it and it's nearly forty years ago now</u>
<u n="297" who="S0022">oh sorry going back to the last period</u>
<u n="298" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0022">sorry I'm changing the subject now</u>
<u n="300" who="S0023" trans="overlap">that's alright</u>
<u n="301" who="S0022">you know going back to the period in history we're still on the same question actually</u>
<u n="302" who="S0023">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0022">when I um used to teach there was a question we use to do a similar thing to these to promote conversation and there was a question</u>
<u n="304" who="S0023">mm mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0022">that said if you slightly different if you could go back in history and change one thing what would it be?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0023">oh yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0022">and I hadn't thought of this but almost everyone said and now say what you think they would say</u>
<u n="308" who="S0023">they would say er kill Adolf Hitler as a <unclear/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0022">yes</u>
<u n="310" who="S0023">yes I knew that</u>
<u n="311" who="S0022">I I didn't think of that but they all said they would kill Adolf Hitler or stop him being born</u>
<u n="312" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that wouldn't make any difference unfortunately</u>
<u n="313" who="S0022" trans="overlap">I never thought of that <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="314" who="S0023">he was very very bad person but the ideas if you know enough about German history which I arrogantly I think I do <pause dur="short"/> having read the Ominous Parallels there was someone <trunc>el</trunc> someone else would have come in to</u>
<u n="315" who="S0022">oh yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0023">maybe not quite with as much charisma but they want the the the it was such a statused institution Germany <pause dur="short"/> it was and he was just picking up the atmosphere and the er the sort of preparation that had been going on for ages</u>
<u n="317" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0023">so um he was in the right place at the right time no doubt about it but you know the Nazi party wasn't him and everyone going oh Hitler's so brilliant and so strong I hadn't thought of that <pause dur="short"/> no no no they all wanted to do what he did</u>
<u n="319" who="S0022" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="320" who="S0023">which um was essentially about making Germany bigger for the sake of it</u>
<u n="321" who="S0022">mm <pause dur="short"/> how are we doing for time by the way <pause dur="short"/> oh twenty minutes and six seconds</u>
<u n="322" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> why don't we do one more just to sort of give a bit extra</u>
<u n="323" who="S0022">okay</u>
<u n="324" who="S0023">do a quick one</u>
<u n="325" who="S0022">um is it you or me?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0023">you</u>
<u n="327" who="S0022">erm oh okay right here's right you get a minute to answer this question</u>
<u n="328" who="S0023">yep</u>
<u n="329" who="S0022">if money were no object what <trunc>kind</trunc> er kind of party would you throw and where?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0023">what kind of party?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0023">I would throw a party in Outer Space</u>
<u n="333" who="S0022">I thought you'd say that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0023">or at least be in the light atmosphere if anyone wants to be practical <pause dur="short"/> perhaps in a space station <pause dur="short"/> yeah there you go <pause dur="short"/> so I would take my friends up to the space station and we'd have jelly and ice cream floating about the cabin and the fun would be trying to eat it without making a total mess <pause dur="short"/> and then the rest of the fun would be looking out of the window and going that's amazing and then the other fun would just be floating about <pause dur="short"/> that's what I'd do <pause dur="short"/> yours?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0022">okay well what what springs to mind when I was reading that Alice King book she wrote about um a party I think it was for <unclear/> and they were somewhere like Versailles</u>
<u n="336" who="S0023">ah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0022">or I just have this I have this vision of this sort of beautiful summer evening everyone looking gorgeous</u>
<u n="338" who="S0023">mm mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0022">in beautiful gardens in France</u>
<u n="340" who="S0023">oh okay</u>
<u n="341" who="S0022">with loads of Champagne <pause dur="short"/> but I also think a bouncy castle would be <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0023" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You could have a fair sized bouncy castle</u>
<u n="343" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0023">you can have a like made up one</u>
<u n="345" who="S0022">yeah there you go</u>
<u n="346" who="S0023">that's a brilliant one <pause dur="short"/> I think that's enough now</u>
<u n="347" who="S0022" trans="overlap">okay that's probably enough of that isn't it?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0023">jolly good</u>
</body>
</text>
