<text id="SUH7">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:28:19</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-11-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0402 S0403 S0405</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Upton Court Grammar School</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Music, movies, physics</topics>
		<activity>Talking about music with friends after school</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0402">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Southall</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>16 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0403">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Staines</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>19 years 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0405">
				<exactage>17</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Slough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Slough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years and 6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0403">what do you listen to? do you listen to anyone?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0405">erm ah Taylor Swift's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> she actually released a new album</u>
<u n="3" who="S0402" trans="overlap">you actually filming it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0405">yeah it is recording now <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>I actually like</u>
<u n="5" who="S0402" trans="overlap">how long's it been recording for?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0405">er two minutes now <pause dur="short"/> okay erm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0402"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this is just a whole heap of shit man</u>
<u n="8" who="S0405">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0402">might even cut that out</u>
<u n="10" who="S0405">they're not going to like this material okay erm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0402">I just wanna say for the record I nearly fell off the table</u>
<u n="12" who="S0405">yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0402" trans="overlap">so I I don't swear a lot I just <unclear/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0405" trans="overlap">they're they're listening to you right now</u>
<u n="15" who="S0403">disclaimership</u>
<u n="16" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0405">okay erm no no no what</u>
<u n="18" who="S0402">I'm not a bad person</u>
<u n="19" who="S0405">have you seen the Hobbit trailer <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? or at least</u>
<u n="20" who="S0403" trans="overlap">the new one?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0405">yeah there was a new one like</u>
<u n="22" who="S0403">I've not</u>
<u n="23" who="S0405">a couple of day ago watch it erm alright <trunc>le</trunc>let's talk about</u>
<u n="24" who="S0402">should we give our names? should we call ourselves like Mr X or something?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0405" trans="overlap">er it's just no Mr X <vocal desc="laugh"/> use our real names like</u>
<u n="26" who="S0403" trans="overlap">John Smith we're all John Smith</u>
<u n="27" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0405">we're all John Smith</u>
<u n="29" who="S0402">oh I <trunc>k</trunc> I I just need another <unclear/> just need another <unclear/> and just use the name there cos like they'll wipe <unclear/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0405" trans="overlap">that'll be alright actually have you watched Pulp Fiction?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0403">I have</u>
<u n="32" who="S0405">yes yes three people watched Pulp Fiction</u>
<u n="33" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0405">okay I watched I watched <trunc>anoth</trunc>another review about it yesterday cos I I watched it like three times now it's so good I like it more than Fight Club <unclear>honestly</unclear></u>
<u n="35" who="S0402" trans="overlap">and I like Fight Club</u>
<u n="36" who="S0405">I I like I was amazed by Fight Club</u>
<u n="37" who="S0402">I was amazed by Pulp Fiction</u>
<u n="38" who="S0405">and then I told him to watch Fight Club</u>
<u n="39" who="S0402">I told him to watch Pulp Fiction</u>
<u n="40" who="S0405">I'm now amazed by Pulp Fiction</u>
<u n="41" who="S0403" trans="overlap">Pulp Fiction's like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0402">I'm now amazed by Fight Club</u>
<u n="43" who="S0405" trans="overlap">every minute of Pulp Fiction is so well made</u>
<u n="44" who="S0402">not not not the parts where there's like random sex scenes and</u>
<u n="45" who="S0405" trans="overlap">no the thing is no that that all has a secret <trunc>l</trunc> not a secret tone a tone and a a motif that it's trying to trying to portray</u>
<u n="46" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah but it's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah what about the rape scene? what is that trying to portray?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah it's showing eh erm it's okay let me think about this erm the the rape scene was <pause dur="short"/> one of us <unclear/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0403" trans="overlap">it just seems that people's <unclear/> people like it so much it seems like it's just taking the mick</u>
<u n="50" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0403">cos bits of it are just rubbish like</u>
<u n="52" who="S0405" trans="overlap">I think it it was a <trunc>com</trunc> I think it was a mixture between comedy and a bit of satire</u>
<u n="53" who="S0402" trans="overlap">you know Tarantino <pause dur="short"/> it's not basically it's <unclear>not</unclear> it's ultra-violent</u>
<u n="54" who="S0405" trans="overlap">the fact that a mob a mob dealer was getting raped</u>
<u n="55" who="S0402">no no the point is you haven't seen Django yet</u>
<u n="56" who="S0405">no I haven't seen Django</u>
<u n="57" who="S0402" trans="overlap">or any like kill Kill Bill and all that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0403">Kill Bill's amazing</u>
<u n="59" who="S0402">basically <trunc>ta</trunc> I haven't seen it but Tarantino's it's like Tarantino's go-to thing</u>
<u n="60" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0402">oh er erm Inglorious Basterds</u>
<u n="62" who="S0405" trans="overlap">he's he he's done it best <unclear>anyway</unclear></u>
<u n="63" who="S0402" trans="overlap">Tarantino's go-to is making ultra-violent movies ultra-violent <pause dur="short"/> if you go?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0405" trans="overlap">but in a in but in a better way than say Michael Bay does which is action and women</u>
<u n="65" who="S0403" trans="overlap">what's an ultra-violent film?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0402">like <unclear>well yeah</unclear> but</u>
<u n="67" who="S0405" trans="overlap">just very violent</u>
<u n="68" who="S0402">yeah like</u>
<u n="69" who="S0403">oh ultra <unclear>violet</unclear>?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0405">violent</u>
<u n="71" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0402"><unclear/> violent yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0405">erm no no</u>
<u n="74" who="S0403">UV lighting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0405">Tarantino I he he tries to put a message across I I</u>
<u n="76" who="S0402">he doesn't he doesn't really</u>
<u n="77" who="S0405">no okay he does it</u>
<u n="78" who="S0402" trans="overlap">alright think about Django yeah?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0405">but he does it well that's the point</u>
<u n="80" who="S0402">have you seen <trunc>dja</trunc> you haven't seen Django it's basically about a black slave getting revenge</u>
<u n="81" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> okay well every every every director has a bad eh good and bad films <unclear>honestly</unclear></u>
<u n="82" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no hang on a second that was a great film</u>
<u n="83" who="S0405">oh really?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0402">not saying it's a <trunc>ba</trunc> it's a great film</u>
<u n="85" who="S0405">okay okay so so so what's the problem with that if you make good films? and it's the thing with erm <pause dur="short"/> the thing with Fight Club is <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>I <pause dur="short"/> read the book and I'd like Fight Club erm for the messages I think it's trying to put across but I think too many people</u>
<u n="86" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the acting's good the acting's good</u>
<u n="87" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah Edward Norton and Brad Pitt amazing that really got me into Brad Pitt like</u>
<u n="88" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0405">you know what I mean <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc>that's a different <unclear/> but</u>
<u n="90" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0405">I got deep into Brad Pitt erm okay</u>
<u n="93" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0405">eh I'll start I'll start again erm what was I going to say? yeah <unclear/> I think people interpreted it to be and it got criticism for the fact that it's it's it's a film that encourages erm it encourages violence fighting masculine attitudes eh eh towards as in it's masculine to fight and take back your humanity personally I don't think that's what Chuck Palahniuk was trying to put across</u>
<u n="95" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah yeah they've taken the wrong message</u>
<u n="96" who="S0405">people just are getting the wrong message <trunc>i</trunc> the name of the it is Fight Club it's all about oh wow when you fight you become a man and men are being</u>
<u n="97" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="98" who="S0405">men should go home</u>
<u n="99" who="S0402" trans="overlap">but that whole <trunc>evolu</trunc> <unclear/> the whole evolution of Fight Club is where they didn't end as Fight Club they're just Project Mayhem didn't it?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0405">yeah that's true that's true</u>
<u n="101" who="S0403" trans="overlap">isn't it sort of based it seems like communist revolution type they call the proletariat or call the you know? the chefs and <trunc>pe</trunc></u>
<u n="102" who="S0405" trans="overlap">proletariat</u>
<u n="103" who="S0402" trans="overlap">but yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0403">all the like they all sort of group together</u>
<u n="105" who="S0405" trans="overlap">the workers</u>
<u n="106" who="S0402">yeah yeah <unclear/> no it was more than that because like it was just people felt run down</u>
<u n="107" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0402">they felt like that as though the system had screwed them over</u>
<u n="109" who="S0403" trans="overlap">that's fair enough yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's cool yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0402">sort of like that's why they blew up the credit card companies</u>
<u n="111" who="S0405">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0402">cos they were sick of er</u>
<u n="113" who="S0405" trans="overlap">when he tried to blow those up</u>
<u n="114" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah I guess it is revolution style</u>
<u n="115" who="S0403">revolutionary type <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah he was saying take back your take back your <pause dur="short"/> your er what you what it means to be human for you and he you know people just thought that meant fighting and stuff but you know? like like when he was describing how erm he said self-improvement is masturbation as in improving yourself is is pointless and worthless and it only is for yourself it's it's trying to say that you are everything you need to be</u>
<u n="117" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0405">we just think that oh we need to improve ourselves by becoming hench and becoming ah a Gucci model</u>
<u n="119" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah I I <trunc>do</trunc> I I don't I don't a hundred percent believe in that because to say that you're perfect the way you are I guess it's like if you say that ah it's a really nice thing to say to someone</u>
<u n="120" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0402">and it gives them a lot of self-confidence but to be honest if you're you know get diabetes or something it was your fault that you have like type two diabetes</u>
<u n="122" who="S0405">not all but yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0402">yeah I know</u>
<u n="124" who="S0403" trans="overlap">but it sort of like it seems to be sort of it's like how in religion you know you ask for forgiveness from god you sort of</u>
<u n="125" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0403">it's like scapegoating it's not taking responsibility and you're not improving yourself if you you know say you're finding it hard</u>
<u n="127" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear>change</unclear> that's why</u>
<u n="129" who="S0402" trans="overlap">but everyone has the capacity to improve it's just I guess Fight Club's way of thinking about it is being free</u>
<u n="130" who="S0405" trans="overlap">but that's why that's why he says</u>
<u n="131" who="S0402">I ain't cos even then <trunc>se</trunc> their self-improvement was letting go of all of their erm prerequisite and then</u>
<u n="132" who="S0405" trans="overlap">self-destruction that's what he says</u>
<u n="133" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="134" who="S0405">self-destruction is is the root to humanity humanity's success but</u>
<u n="135" who="S0402">yeah but even then that's that's a form of self-improvement cos they try and that was that's what he <trunc>believe</trunc> that's what Tyler Durden believed was</u>
<u n="136" who="S0405" trans="overlap">but that that's that's getting <trunc>deep</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0402">erm <trunc>h</trunc> the the way he could self-improve himself</u>
<u n="138" who="S0405">yeah a different a a a point that a point that me and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> talked about yesterday was erm the fact erm Tyler Durden talks about people shouldn't be packing themselves into gyms and</u>
<u n="139" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0405">trying to be perfect and yet Brad Pitt is pretty much the <unclear/> of a hench guy who fights and he's attractive to women</u>
<u n="141" who="S0402" trans="overlap">and he's <trunc>mar</trunc> he's married to Angelina Jolie <pause dur="short"/> it's true</u>
<u n="142" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah exactly erm <trunc>e</trunc>even the Tyler Durden figure is so you know? maybe AI said that that was probably due to the there's more homoerotic themes in in the book it's much it's much more about Edward Norton character is attracted to Tyler Durden erm but then also Christian thought that is was the point of view that erm he thinks that it shows Edward Norton has already been sort of erm er influenced by society to believe that that is the perfect image cos Tyler Durden was perfect in his mind</u>
<u n="143" who="S0402">oh yeah well he says that he says that</u>
<u n="144" who="S0405" trans="overlap">so maybe he's already <unclear>there</unclear> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="145" who="S0402" trans="overlap">cos he says like I fight the way you want to I talk the way you want</u>
<u n="146" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0402">like F asterisk C K the way you want</u>
<u n="148" who="S0405">straight to</u>
<u n="149" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0403">well said</u>
<u n="151" who="S0402">keeping it clean here</u>
<u n="152" who="S0405">oh right oh <trunc>ri</trunc> oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0405">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0403" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>it's like</unclear></u>
<u n="156" who="S0405">I <unclear/> the thing I like about I can enjoy Pulp Fiction more now I I say I I I just find it so funny intrinsically</u>
<u n="157" who="S0402" trans="overlap">ah yeah it's hilarious but there's always that's like low or high pleasure that's like the lower that no you find it <trunc>hilar</trunc> but there's something something like amazing to me about something that's such a high level of thinking that you're actually like questioning rather than</u>
<u n="158" who="S0405">Pulp Fiction made me question things</u>
<u n="159" who="S0402">like?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0405"><unclear/> Samuel L Jackson the whole the whole movie is about chance the whole movie</u>
<u n="161" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah it's very hard yeah it's <trunc>ve</trunc> it's very hard to question something when you have Samuel L Jackson</u>
<u n="162" who="S0405" trans="overlap">the whole movie's about grunting and like you know</u>
<u n="163" who="S0402">shooting people in the face</u>
<u n="164" who="S0403" trans="overlap">it's just what's it? it's just Mr Tarantino trying to get some what's it you know? catchy lines that everyone will <trunc>re</trunc> oh you know replay <unclear/> trying to make money that's the whole point</u>
<u n="165" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah that that is true <trunc>e</trunc> isn't yeah but isn't <trunc>any</trunc> everything influenced by <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0403" trans="overlap">I think it's</u>
<u n="167" who="S0402">I guess</u>
<u n="168" who="S0403">I suppose yeah but <unclear/> there's no</u>
<u n="169" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I you've got to think of the purpose of the writer I mean cos</u>
<u n="170" who="S0403">it's like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0402">I don't know it eh I don't know the writer but did he write the book wanting to make a profit? or did he just write it just cos he just wanted to write it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0405">who? Palahniuk? for with er Fight Club?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0402">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0405">eh <trunc>a</trunc> I think he <trunc>wa</trunc> I think it was his first hit book and he really wanted to send a message</u>
<u n="175" who="S0402">okay well if it was sending a message then I can understand that slightly more than erm er Pulp Fiction <unclear/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0403" trans="overlap">exactly Pulp Fiction is meant to be entertaining</u>
<u n="177" who="S0402">yeah Pulp Fiction was meant to be entertaining whereas er er Fight Club was meant to be thought-provoking <pause dur="short"/> that's the difference</u>
<u n="178" who="S0405">yeah okay</u>
<u n="179" who="S0402" trans="overlap">Fight Club was meant to actually make you stop</u>
<u n="180" who="S0405" trans="overlap">you're you're like comparing two different things but</u>
<u n="181" who="S0402">no I know I know that's what <unclear/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0405">yeah that's why we can't but erm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0402">obviously there's no definitive answer as to what is a better film but</u>
<u n="184" who="S0405">no no it's like everything is objective but erm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0402">IMDB says</u>
<u n="186" who="S0405">IMDB <unclear/></u>
<u n="187" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0405">ruin their career thingy erm er</u>
<u n="189" who="S0403">better question is the music in Pulp Fiction good? the music?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0402">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0405">yeah it's <unclear>better</unclear></u>
<u n="192" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's the most important part</u>
<u n="193" who="S0405" trans="overlap">but <trunc>end</trunc> but ending</u>
<u n="194" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> yeah get down on it <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="195" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0405">and the music they talk about erm the <trunc>en</trunc> the ending credit <trunc>sc</trunc> eh music to Fight Club that's the song that was downloaded so much more is it's like erm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0403">what is it? is it?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0405"><shift new="singing"/> where is my mind? where is my mind? <shift new="normal"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0402"><unclear/> <shift new="singing"/> get down on it dede dede <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0405">I don't think that anywhere is better but it it it it got to it was such a good song I'll <trunc>p</trunc> I'll play it if I can it's <trunc>s</trunc> it's such a good song</u>
<u n="201" who="S0403">it's like he does like Chuck Berry ah it's incredible music</u>
<u n="202" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Chuck Berry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah I know I know it's like it's like a Guardians of the Galaxy soundtrack</u>
<u n="204" who="S0402">ah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0405">and and the theme behind</u>
<u n="206" who="S0402" trans="overlap">that's the <trunc>ma</trunc> the most amazing soundtrack ever</u>
<u n="207" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0403" trans="overlap">which one?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0402">Guardians of the Galaxy</u>
<u n="210" who="S0405">have you watched <trunc>guar</trunc></u>
<u n="211" who="S0403" trans="overlap">I've <trunc>ne</trunc> I've never seen it</u>
<u n="212" who="S0405">you have to see it it is the best <trunc>ma</trunc> I I I we're massive Marvel fans</u>
<u n="213" who="S0402" trans="overlap">it is I we're yeah well yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0405">and we both love that it's my favourite Marvel <unclear>movie</unclear></u>
<u n="215" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I I I'm confused whether that or erm Days of Future Past I suppose <unclear>best</unclear> Marvel</u>
<u n="216" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> it was okay</u>
<u n="217" who="S0402">it's the best in that it it's the best in</u>
<u n="218" who="S0405" trans="overlap">why did that? it was another Wolverine movie it really was all about Wolverine</u>
<u n="219" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I don't know no no no no it wasn't about that it wasn't</u>
<u n="220" who="S0405" trans="overlap">it was as much a Wolverine movie as</u>
<u n="221" who="S0402">it <trunc>wa</trunc> no no it was like Wolverine like in the X-Men movies</u>
<u n="222" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0402">where he had like he was the he was basically the main character</u>
<u n="224" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0402">but he <trunc>di</trunc> it it was far from the Wolverine movie cos cos I you know the more the best bit was the bits between McAvoy and Fassbender</u>
<u n="226" who="S0405">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="227" who="S0402" trans="overlap">but they were they were my favourite parts of the movie</u>
<u n="228" who="S0405">okay</u>
<u n="229" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear/> quick guy quick guy he was brilliant</u>
<u n="230" who="S0402">yeah Quicksilver</u>
<u n="231" who="S0405">Quicksilver er you you know they added that right at the end it wasn't actually something that they</u>
<u n="232" who="S0403" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0405">yeah and and and and the Quicksilver that's going to be in the Age of <trunc>ar</trunc> Ultron is going to be so much worse</u>
<u n="234" who="S0402" trans="overlap">age yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0405">than erm cos you know Age of <trunc>u</trunc>Ultron Avengers two that's coming out</u>
<u n="236" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0403">oh yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0405">there's there's a they they they're also having Quicksilver but they're not making him a <trunc>mu</trunc> a mutant they're making him a <unclear>miracle</unclear> they call him</u>
<u n="239" who="S0403">right</u>
<u n="240" who="S0405">erm because of rights and and stuff</u>
<u n="241" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0405">cos Fox owns the rights to Avengers and</u>
<u n="243" who="S0402" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah Fox <trunc>ow</trunc> yeah I know but they they kind of do kind of don't</u>
<u n="244" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0402">because</u>
<u n="246" who="S0405">no no but as in they can't combine them and I I'm just saying they've set the bar so high</u>
<u n="247" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah I know but no but the point is here <unclear/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0405">er yeah <trunc>the</trunc>they've set the bar so high for Quicksilver and erm there's Quicksilver's going to be in erm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0402">yeah cos that cos that Quicksilver was comedy Quicksilver</u>
<u n="250" who="S0403"><unclear/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0402">yeah <trunc>a</trunc><trunc>a</trunc> but the</u>
<u n="253" who="S0405" trans="overlap">but his <unclear>action scene</unclear> was amazing</u>
<u n="254" who="S0402">yeah I know the <unclear/> but yeah exactly the that that was <unclear>great</unclear> music great music again</u>
<u n="255" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><trunc>tha</trunc><trunc>tha</trunc>that's one of the best <unclear/> ah do you? yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0402" trans="overlap">you know the part where he runs around?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0405" trans="overlap">Time in a Bottle Time in a Bottle</u>
<u n="258" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah <shift new="singing"/> I could put time in a bottle <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0405">it's so good it's so good</u>
<u n="260" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0405">erm yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0402">and he just runs around and starts flicking stuff and moving guns around</u>
<u n="263" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0405">physics in that scene was legit as well</u>
<u n="265" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0405">ah <trunc>the</trunc><trunc>the</trunc>they kept the physics fairly fairly legit with that scene as well I know</u>
<u n="267" who="S0402" trans="overlap">erm okay if you want? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0405">no yeah yeah yeah yeah <trunc>the</trunc>they're <unclear/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0403" trans="overlap">I mean the problem with</u>
<u n="270" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I mean F equals M A so</u>
<u n="271" who="S0403">the problem with</u>
<u n="272" who="S0402" trans="overlap">his acceleration is awesome</u>
<u n="273" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah no <unclear/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0403" trans="overlap">the problem with <unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0402" trans="overlap">ah ah because when he moves the arm his acceleration doing that is like like amazingly massive so the mass of that arm times that acceleration is gonna like just decimate the guy's face</u>
<u n="277" who="S0405" trans="overlap">it's going to</u>
<u n="278" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0405" trans="overlap">and that's a good idea that's what he did <unclear/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no he no no no I mean like it would like punch a hole in his face</u>
<u n="281" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0403">when he runs</u>
<u n="283" who="S0402">it's like that yeah yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0403">yeah but when he runs how come the the air resistance doesn't rip his skin off like</u>
<u n="285" who="S0405">because he wears that those goggles</u>
<u n="286" who="S0403" trans="overlap">or like er you know?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and those headphones it's the headphones</u>
<u n="288" who="S0403">he's a mutant and how don't his clothes shatter to pieces like?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0402">or yeah and the floor why didn't the floor crush? when he runs on that <unclear/> along the walls <pause dur="short"/> it's like <unclear/> innit?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0405" trans="overlap">okay you know that? the <trunc>a</trunc> you know the question everyone you know the question everyone wants the answer to?</u>
<u n="291" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">see you guys</u>
<u n="292" who="S0403" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">see you next week mate yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0405" trans="overlap">see you erm you know that song Time in a Bottle?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0405">if he was going at that speed how could they play that song at that <unclear/>? did he speed that song up about a hundred times and then play it back? so do you see what I'm saying?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0402">well no because time is a time is relative time is relative the faster you go the closer you get to the speed of light the more time slows down</u>
<u n="297" who="S0405" trans="overlap">cos he</u>
<u n="298" who="S0402">so <trunc>tho</trunc>those those headphones that are are part of or on his erm the the object that's him are moving at the same speed as him</u>
<u n="299" who="S0405" trans="overlap">he was <pause dur="short"/> no way was he running round and it was going at so what what would he going to <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0402" trans="overlap">so technically yeah yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0402">no no no no</u>
<u n="303" who="S0403">to real people it would sound a lot slower</u>
<u n="304" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0403">but if he sped if he sped up super quick I think it <unclear/> it would sound normal to him</u>
<u n="306" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's what I'm saying is that what he did?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no no no no no it's not that no because time is <trunc>rel</trunc> so the faster you go</u>
<u n="308" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0402">the er the more time slows down but but relative you to you you won't see a difference cos you know? you around you but everyone else</u>
<u n="310" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0402">erm will see you going fast you would see everyone else going slow</u>
<u n="312" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0402" trans="overlap">the headphones which are part of him</u>
<u n="314" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0402">erm because he they're they're moving at the exact same speed as him</u>
<u n="316" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0402">he hears them at at the exact same speed everyone else hears them slower no faster relative to to him</u>
<u n="318" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0402">it's just physics</u>
<u n="321" who="S0403">it's messy</u>
<u n="322" who="S0405">yeah yeah I I won't understand that</u>
<u n="323" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0405" trans="overlap">that's that's fair enough</u>
<u n="325" who="S0403" trans="overlap">it's effort</u>
<u n="326" who="S0405">no <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>it's just it's just funny to me to imagine he sped that up like however many times</u>
<u n="327" who="S0402" trans="overlap">it's like yeah no he didn't need to</u>
<u n="328" who="S0405">think think he would</u>
<u n="329" who="S0402">no he <trunc>di</trunc> wouldn't need to because he's yeah cos as he as he <unclear/> time is relative to him</u>
<u n="330" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0403">so it's speeding up for him cos he?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0403">ah I see I see</u>
<u n="334" who="S0402">no what? yeah well yeah <unclear/> to him it doesn't change at all</u>
<u n="335" who="S0403">that's cool it's pretty cool</u>
<u n="336" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah it's like the classic Einstein thought experiment with the er</u>
<u n="337" who="S0403">which one? the</u>
<u n="338" who="S0402" trans="overlap">the <trunc>ne</trunc> bouncing the neutron up and down is it? eh bouncing a proton up and down it's like erm eh so eh Mr and Mrs Einstein</u>
<u n="339" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0402">classic isn't it? eh so they both have clocks and the erm like the pendulum of the clock is a photon and it bounced up and down between two plates and that's how you use cos that that never changes that the speed of that photon</u>
<u n="341" who="S0403">right</u>
<u n="342" who="S0402">erm you you can calculate time precisely right?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0403">okay</u>
<u n="344" who="S0402">so it's moving up and down and then so you know what the interval is and you can calculate time precisely and he theorised that</u>
<u n="345" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear>electrical</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0402">if he was eh running eh if he was flying near the speed of light? that erm that and he <trunc>w</trunc> and he was moving? that photon would need to cover that distance compared to that distance hence why</u>
<u n="347" who="S0403" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="348" who="S0402">erm it would it would seem cos to to him that photon is moving at the same rate to him himself but to everyone else it's moving that distance hence must be slower so erm the entire world is seemingly slower so so by him moving faster he slows down the world around him but compared to everyone else</u>
<u n="349" who="S0403">that's amazing</u>
<u n="350" who="S0405">everything speeds up I think you mean? because if it covers that distance it needs to move quickly</u>
<u n="351" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah sorry yeah yeah yeah sorry</u>
<u n="352" who="S0405">so yeah yeah yeah okay</u>
<u n="353" who="S0403">that's cool</u>
<u n="354" who="S0402">yeah that's just like sort of one of his classic thought experiments</u>
<u n="355" who="S0403">it's like Schrodinger's cat that's sick and I think I can understand it as well</u>
<u n="356" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I know <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>it's it's a way of thinking</u>
<u n="357" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><trunc>i</trunc>it's kind of</u>
<u n="358" who="S0403" trans="overlap">that's weird like</u>
<u n="359" who="S0405" trans="overlap">it's it's a way of thinking</u>
<u n="360" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah it I know the</u>
<u n="361" who="S0405" trans="overlap">at least the way my brother tried to explain it to me</u>
<u n="362" who="S0402" trans="overlap">the the pop culture way of thinking of it is just like the cat can be both dead and alive which it can't</u>
<u n="363" who="S0403">it's so cool cause okay for the record</u>
<u n="364" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0403">you have a cat?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0403">in a box?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0405" trans="overlap">in a box yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0402">there's a fifty percent chance</u>
<u n="370" who="S0403">with a some dynamite which has fifty percent chance of blowing up</u>
<u n="371" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0403">and <pause dur="short"/> then and so after and the dynamite's in the box so no one can know if it's blown up</u>
<u n="373" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0403">so therefore is the cat dead or alive?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0403">before you open the</u>
<u n="377" who="S0405" trans="overlap">why can't it be both dead and alive?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0403">cos it can't</u>
<u n="379" who="S0405">it can why not?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0403">well it can't</u>
<u n="381" who="S0405">like in the sense</u>
<u n="382" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no no no the whole point</u>
<u n="383" who="S0403" trans="overlap">through our common sense it cannot but <unclear>through</unclear> quantum physics it can why not?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0402" trans="overlap">the whole point it was that it yeah I know because the whole point is it's meant to be an allegory for the particle wave duality</u>
<u n="385" who="S0403">right right</u>
<u n="386" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="387" who="S0402">yeah so a <trunc>wa</trunc> a wave can be both a particle and <unclear/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0403" trans="overlap">love the way The Big Bang Theory turns it into into a relationship paradigm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0402">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0403">by we can be both dating and not dating</u>
<u n="391" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0403">the way Leonard and Penny did it</u>
<u n="393" who="S0402" trans="overlap">so so a wave can't be a particle at the same time as it is a wave but given <trunc>i</trunc>it's undefined up until the point where you define it</u>
<u n="394" who="S0403">but <trunc>ho</trunc> mm how how does us seeing it? how does us measuring it make a difference?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0402">because</u>
<u n="396" who="S0403">cos therefore that implies our thoughts have physical impact</u>
<u n="397" who="S0402">no <unclear/> our physical impact because it's the way we measure it cos you you think of erm the photoelectric effect</u>
<u n="398" who="S0403">right</u>
<u n="399" who="S0402">that can only happen when it's a particle so it must be a particle that's hitting the thing but whereas erm like a when a a a wave erm like reflects a particles can't reflect like that</u>
<u n="400" who="S0403">right right</u>
<u n="401" who="S0402">so erm it's like it's undefined so the cat is both dead and alive it's it's kind of it's not it doesn't mean that it's both dead and alive at the same time it just means that it's undefined</u>
<u n="402" who="S0405" trans="overlap">right it means it's neither</u>
<u n="403" who="S0402">yeah it's neither</u>
<u n="404" who="S0403">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0402">so it's a completely undefined as what it is up until the moment that you make it define itself</u>
<u n="406" who="S0403">mm undefined is very similar to like how here's a question what's one divided by zero?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0402">yeah it's undefined</u>
<u n="408" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0403">exactly yeah and it's and it's not infinity because if you approach it on a a Y equals one <unclear/> graph it approaches infinity</u>
<u n="410" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0403">but the reason we don't say equals infinity because normally if something approaches something we just say equals that</u>
<u n="412" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0402">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0403">but the reason</u>
<u n="416" who="S0405" trans="overlap">it doesn't it actually never does</u>
<u n="417" who="S0403">cos it well it approaches it but and if if it if that was it we'd say it equals infinity</u>
<u n="418" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0403">but it approaches different numbers depending which way you <trunc>lo</trunc> you come from</u>
<u n="420" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah right yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0403" trans="overlap">if you come from the bottom it approaches minus infinity which is completely different and</u>
<u n="422" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0403">there's some <trunc>ot</trunc> there's some other sums where you can make it approach zero or one or anything really</u>
<u n="424" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0402" trans="overlap">well yeah well</u>
<u n="426" who="S0403">therefore it's undefined and it doesn't have a limit like</u>
<u n="427" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah yes</u>
<u n="428" who="S0405">oh man <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0403"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I guess that's where where physics starts to make sense when</u>
<u n="431" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it's Friday</u>
<u n="432" who="S0402"><trunc>i</trunc>it physics makes so little sense that it starts to make sense again</u>
<u n="433" who="S0405" trans="overlap">no no it right right right</u>
<u n="434" who="S0402" trans="overlap">that's like that point <unclear/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0403">I think it's just you hear it so much you start to believe it</u>
<u n="436" who="S0405">fair</u>
<u n="437" who="S0402">yeah well no I I can kind of get Schrodinger's cat I don't know well obviously</u>
<u n="438" who="S0403" trans="overlap">why do you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0402">we don't get the mechanics of it</u>
<u n="440" who="S0403">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0402">because you know we we we can't because er by the very nature of trying to understand the mechanics of it you change the mechanics of it</u>
<u n="442" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0402">yeah that's the <trunc>i</trunc> that's the that's the issue isn't it? so we can never know if it's</u>
<u n="445" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0402">I guess feasibly it could be both dead and alive but I don't think that would really from a physics standpoint hold but so it's more likely to by undefined up until that point</u>
<u n="447" who="S0403">do you have any idea how we understand what photons are like? cos we obviously we can't see them</u>
<u n="448" who="S0402">yeah erm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is it still a theory or?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0403" trans="overlap">well cos the moment they hit your light they're gone they're eye your eye they're gone</u>
<u n="451" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0402">yeah yeah yeah eh that's the that's the whole Heisenberg uncertainty theorem isn't it?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0402">that you can never know a a position and eh momentum at the same time</u>
<u n="455" who="S0405" trans="overlap">god damn it</u>
<u n="456" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah it's cool isn't it?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0402">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0403">the more you <trunc>c</trunc> closer you get to one the <unclear/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah and and you can do that with anything so like I think a woman famously tried to get out of a speeding ticket because she used <unclear/> uncertainty theorem to say how did you know er where I was?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0405">really?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0402">cos you can't know my position and my erm my speed that accurately at the same time</u>
<u n="462" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0405" trans="overlap">that's just someone messing that's someone messing with their <unclear/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0402" trans="overlap">obviously they still gave her a ticket</u>
<u n="465" who="S0405">yeah I know it was like like anyone's going to buy that</u>
<u n="466" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear/> stupid guy you know? might just fall for it like <unclear/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0405">yeah look just to dumb this conversation down quite a lot is is this is more philosophy <trunc>do</trunc> oh well</u>
<u n="470" who="S0402">yeah yeah sure</u>
<u n="471" who="S0405">relating to philosophy is philosophy and talking about er hypothetical stuff pointless in itself</u>
<u n="472" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0405">or is?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0402">that's <unclear/> sorry that's basically what a physicist does anyway</u>
<u n="475" who="S0405">yeah yeah I know yeah exactly so why spend your life talking about something that is only going to be relative to people?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0402" trans="overlap">because they they actually have real life applications I mean if you think of a</u>
<u n="477" who="S0405">how many people think oh am I going to do this Schrodinger's cat? or this principle? or?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no no I know yeah I know I know you think it's completely mental but like you think of a quantum computer</u>
<u n="479" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0402">oh you you basically people <trunc>s</trunc> you know you know potheads have for years have been basically doing physics</u>
<u n="481" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0402">and <unclear/> and everyone says well there's no real life application that until you get to something like a a quantum computer</u>
<u n="483" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0402">which where you can have <trunc>a</trunc>an electron you know <trunc>s</trunc> you know you can split an electron can't you?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0403">I think you eh you give an electron like ten spins at once and you can measure them all at once or something and it <trunc>c</trunc>cos</u>
<u n="486" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah sick</u>
<u n="487" who="S0403">on a normal bit on a computer <unclear/> zero</u>
<u n="488" who="S0402" trans="overlap">that means there's ten electrons yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0403">but this can be like every number between one and zero at the same time</u>
<u n="490" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><trunc>te</trunc> <unclear/> cos each electron has a quantum number</u>
<u n="491" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0402">which is defined by its charge erm its eh position its eh energy level</u>
<u n="493" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0402">and eh its spin</u>
<u n="495" who="S0403">and you can measure all of them at once <unclear>it's like</unclear></u>
<u n="496" who="S0402" trans="overlap">so if it if it has if it has ten different spins that means it's effectively ten different electrons</u>
<u n="497" who="S0405">yeah oh right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0402" trans="overlap">which means that effectively you can do the times the amount of calculations <unclear/> time</u>
<u n="499" who="S0405">what so like when it's moving it changes its makeup or?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0403" trans="overlap">I I don't know how it works but</u>
<u n="501" who="S0402"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0403">you you give it a <trunc>s</trunc> like yeah somehow and it has lots of different qualities</u>
<u n="503" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0403">and you can measure each of them to get different stuff out</u>
<u n="505" who="S0402">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0405">right right</u>
<u n="507" who="S0403">and they reckon it'll be better to make like a brain-type computer</u>
<u n="508" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0403">because brains work more like that they work you know more complex and you know firing lots of things at once</u>
<u n="510" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0403">instead of just a linear</u>
<u n="512" who="S0405" trans="overlap">brain <unclear>fart</unclear> brain's mad</u>
<u n="513" who="S0403">so they reckon like they <vocal desc="laugh"/> the quantum computer it can do like five plus eight and that's like the best it can do in at the moment</u>
<u n="514" who="S0402"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0405">yeah? really?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0403">yeah yeah and it and it's like this big and costs like fifteen million quid yeah?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0405">do you think that will advance at the same rate computers have advanced?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0403">I think they'll advance faster</u>
<u n="519" who="S0405" trans="overlap">looks like looks like they are yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0403"><unclear/> we have computers to use as <unclear/> computers that we didn't have before</u>
<u n="521" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah oh that's amazing</u>
<u n="522" who="S0403">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0405" trans="overlap">so I'm again changing the subject maybe deliberately erm</u>
<u n="524" who="S0403" trans="overlap">and it's going to come back to physics again</u>
<u n="525" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0405">no no yeah we will <pause dur="short"/> we</u>
<u n="527" who="S0402" trans="overlap">it's like me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> talk where it's like everything reverts back to physics</u>
<u n="528" who="S0405">yeah I know erm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0402">and what happens in physics? it explodes there we go</u>
<u n="530" who="S0403" trans="overlap">so what sort of musics do you like?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah <unclear/> I I I think I think they want more erm they want a genuine and this is this is a genuine conversation</u>
<u n="532" who="S0402" trans="overlap">but this this is a genuine conversation</u>
<u n="533" who="S0403">we're just</u>
<u n="534" who="S0402">and I think they're going to be revelling in it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0405" trans="overlap">I don't think they care what we talk about</u>
<u n="537" who="S0403" trans="overlap">it's true we're just effing weird they're not going to want <unclear/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0405">no I know</u>
<u n="539" who="S0402"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0405">they're not going to listen to everything erm oh no they are though cos they're transcribing it so that's cool</u>
<u n="541" who="S0402" trans="overlap">well yeah they could be transcribing this</u>
<u n="542" who="S0405">they're going to turn everything we say into into er words erm there's seven minutes left of this half an hour recording</u>
<u n="543" who="S0403">that's pretty cool</u>
<u n="544" who="S0405">erm what was I saying? erm yeah what music do we like? okay erm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah do you just like <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0405" trans="overlap">cos I think we all completely have complete opposite <unclear>ends</unclear> erm I've changed a lot right now I'm probably still into hip-hop rap</u>
<u n="547" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">your gay face</u>
<u n="548" who="S0403" trans="overlap">oh my god <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0405">shut the shut the</u>
<u n="550" who="S0402">that's not music</u>
<u n="551" who="S0405">okay no not erm I don't like Nicki Minaj er what's that <trunc>bla</trunc>? ah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0403">has it got <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0402" trans="overlap">that Ice Cube thing? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="554" who="S0405">Lil Wayne Kanye Kanye's Kanye's okay</u>
<u n="555" who="S0402" trans="overlap">Kanye man Kanye Kanye's awful I just like him cos he's a prick</u>
<u n="556" who="S0405" trans="overlap">Kanye's <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>j</trunc> have you seen? yeah cos he's such a prick did you see what he did to Taylor Swift at the VMA awards</u>
<u n="557" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0405">when he took when he took the mic</u>
<u n="559" who="S0402" trans="overlap">it's like excuse me excuse me hi Taylor I have a lot of respect for you</u>
<u n="560" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0402">but Beyonce made an amazing video this year</u>
<u n="562" who="S0405"><trunc>ma</trunc><trunc>ma</trunc>made that moment history so it was at the VMA awards</u>
<u n="563" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0402" trans="overlap">ah it was</u>
<u n="565" who="S0405">it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0402">have you seen erm erm have you seen er Oasis er Liam Gallagher's reaction to that?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0403" trans="overlap">I know he go on what did he say? there's so many <unclear>reactions</unclear></u>
<u n="568" who="S0402" trans="overlap">eh he goes erm he goes <vocal desc="sigh"/> if <vocal desc="laugh"/> if I ever win another award again I'd personally invite him to come up there and see what I'd fucking do with the award</u>
<u n="569" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="570" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0405">so many <unclear/> would just like punch him so so <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc> have you seen it? it said Taylor Swift was received her first ever VMA</u>
<u n="572" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0405">and she was so grateful and cos she's a country singer</u>
<u n="574" who="S0403" trans="overlap">ah so happy yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0405">she <trunc>wa</trunc> it was like a teen who had got her dream come true</u>
<u n="576" who="S0402">and everyone just went ah except for Kanye West</u>
<u n="577" who="S0405" trans="overlap">and she went she was like ah thank you thank you</u>
<u n="578" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0405">Kanye drunk goes up</u>
<u n="580" who="S0402" trans="overlap">bursts onto the stage</u>
<u n="581" who="S0405">steals the mic she's like what is going on? and he was like <trunc>he</trunc><trunc>he</trunc><trunc>he</trunc><trunc>he</trunc>he said er wait <trunc>wha</trunc>? what's become the meme? he said erm I'm gonna let you finish</u>
<u n="582" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0405">that's what he said</u>
<u n="584" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0405">erm and then he said erm <trunc>beyo</trunc> he basically said Beyonce's video was better <unclear>she</unclear> it was it was for video of the year</u>
<u n="586" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah and I think she should have won</u>
<u n="587" who="S0405">and he said Beyonce's video was history and then he storms off</u>
<u n="588" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0405">erm and Taylor Swift doesn't say anything she's just like she's just like standing there and it's ah it's so sad</u>
<u n="590" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah she doesn't know what to do</u>
<u n="591" who="S0403"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's funny though so <unclear/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0405">and then he who gets the biggest backlash ever goes to Japan for a year makes no er er you know er <trunc>propaga</trunc> eh not propaganda</u>
<u n="593" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0405">erm er news conference whatever you want to call it erm no music he was just he was off for a whole year cos it was just the amount of crap he got</u>
<u n="595" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear>wow</unclear></u>
<u n="596" who="S0405">he's a prick he's he's a</u>
<u n="597" who="S0402" trans="overlap">ah yeah douchebag he's <trunc>w</trunc> he's <trunc>ma</trunc>married to a Kardashian so you come to expect that now</u>
<u n="598" who="S0405" trans="overlap">I know a Kardashian they're so perfect for each other it's</u>
<u n="599" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="600" who="S0405">ah I'm so happy I'm not ignorant or?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0403">I need to like expose myself to more of this gunk like you know? like Kardashians and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah I know literally I found myself two days ago I was just like oh what is this? and I knew <trunc>ka</trunc> I know Kanye cries a lot and and and has rants and stuff but</u>
<u n="603" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0405">but anyway what was I saying? so I like I'm a big fan of Eminem that's all I'm going to say</u>
<u n="605" who="S0402" trans="overlap">no ah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0403" trans="overlap">he's good actually I must be fair</u>
<u n="607" who="S0405" trans="overlap">I yeah I I</u>
<u n="608" who="S0402">my favourite is Will Smith and that's just it</u>
<u n="609" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah Will's ah funny that okay <trunc>there</trunc>there's a topic erm Will Smith criticised the way rap was heading erm</u>
<u n="610" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0405">early early two thousands</u>
<u n="612" who="S0402" trans="overlap">he doesn't swear at all</u>
<u n="613" who="S0405">I know</u>
<u n="614" who="S0402">in his rap and his rap is just like happiness in a rap</u>
<u n="615" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah I know yeah exactly</u>
<u n="616" who="S0402" trans="overlap">that should be a Subway advert</u>
<u n="617" who="S0405"><trunc>exac</trunc> so that was end of end of happiness in a rap</u>
<u n="618" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0402" trans="overlap">you heard it first</u>
<u n="620" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh I get it <unclear/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0403">patent <unclear/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0402">I'm patenting that one</u>
<u n="623" who="S0405">oh my god</u>
<u n="624" who="S0402" trans="overlap">transcribe that and send it to me please</u>
<u n="625" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0405">what happened was if you care? yeah Will Smith criticised erm basically the rap industry for <trunc>s</trunc> for becoming swearing</u>
<u n="627" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0405">and then then Tupac and Biggie died and then everything just went back to normal Eminem started swearing more and <trunc>i</trunc> eh it was</u>
<u n="629" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I the rap <unclear/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0405" trans="overlap">I just like <trunc>em</trunc> I I I I genuinely think <trunc>h</trunc>he he's he's <unclear/> eh genius is the wrong word and people hate it when you call idiots genius</u>
<u n="631" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0405">but yeah the the way he can er conjure rhymes and and then and</u>
<u n="633" who="S0403">well</u>
<u n="634" who="S0405">it's like <unclear/> in alliteration erm assonance and</u>
<u n="635" who="S0402" trans="overlap">well Pitbull's a genius Pitbull's a genius you know why? you know why Pitbull's a genius? he rhymed Kodak with Kodak</u>
<u n="636" who="S0405">yeah exactly he could rhyme orange with anything</u>
<u n="637" who="S0402" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0403">he probably doesn't what's it? even write it does he?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0405">no no he he writes his own songs and that's that's not just me</u>
<u n="640" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear>you sure</unclear>?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0405">he he he he's one of the few erm yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0403" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="643" who="S0402">sounds like you're fanboying here</u>
<u n="644" who="S0405">trust me I do I I <unclear/> he was amazing <unclear/> he he writes his own songs</u>
<u n="645" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0405">he he he genuinely writes his own his own lyrics the the thing that people do admit are usually stolen are erm they're called sampling of if you listen to any rap song</u>
<u n="648" who="S0402">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0405">usually the chorus is is it's not stolen it's given permission but it's from a different song like erm like <trunc>the</trunc>there's five Eminem songs there's there's one with a Dido verse that went became one of the biggest songs in the world called Stan and then</u>
<u n="650" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0405">you know? they stole off of erm Aerosmith well they didn't steal it they got permission you know?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0403">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0405" trans="overlap">so that's called sampling there's a big debate about that but generally rappers write their own lyrics though</u>
<u n="654" who="S0403">that's cool</u>
<u n="655" who="S0405">erm I can see I can see I've hated Eminem at times as well</u>
<u n="656" who="S0403">see Eminem like Not Afraid erm you know the Love the Way You Lie he did with?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0405">yeah with <trunc>rih</trunc> eh Rihanna</u>
<u n="658" who="S0403" trans="overlap">they were brilliant brilliant songs</u>
<u n="659" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah well they're they're two of his biggest songs cos</u>
<u n="660" who="S0403" trans="overlap">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="661" who="S0405">erm well at least at least now you know he's had some really awful albums</u>
<u n="662" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0405">and that he's he admits now for being as awful as you know? in that they're horrible bass lines horrible but pointless lyrics I mean I think there's pros to each album but I mean <vocal desc="misc"/> I like I just like Eminem for <trunc>it</trunc>it gives me a moods eh it really speaks to me like</u>
<u n="664" who="S0403">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="665" who="S0405">from the heart yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0403"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <unclear>that's deep shit</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0405">okay away from the hip-hop I like erm I got into Linkin Park more <trunc>re</trunc>recently</u>
<u n="668" who="S0403">okay yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0405">erm they had their ups and downs as well</u>
<u n="670" who="S0403">like when they did Numb and stuff Numb and New Divide they were they were brilliant yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah New Divide erm In the End er what I think that's sort of two thousand and seven onwards two er even later than that</u>
<u n="672" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0405">erm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0403">they are very good but like the newer stuff I've only heard one of their albums A Thousand Suns maybe?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah A Thousand Suns that erm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0403" trans="overlap">that was awful</u>
<u n="677" who="S0405">yeah yeah they were known for turning we're talking about Linkin Park</u>
<u n="678" who="S0402">oh</u>
<u n="679" who="S0405">erm Linkin Park were known for for having a really awful term like twenty ten to twenty twelve and now they've released another album erm er with with some well what I consider great songs Linkin Park songs</u>
<u n="680" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0405">they they they basically put dubstep in their music and</u>
<u n="682" who="S0402" trans="overlap">oh yeah I guess every er band goes through that phase where they have to do something</u>
<u n="683" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah change</u>
<u n="684" who="S0402">change so that it shows that there's differentiation in their music</u>
<u n="685" who="S0405">yeah I know that they're not just putting out the same it's like The Beatles never had to do it did they?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0403" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah I've never said song is awful but when I listen to that Linkin Park oh my it's just absolutely you know? <unclear/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0402" trans="overlap">so yeah I don't I don't like I don't like eh certain rap where these people just feel the need to swear</u>
<u n="688" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0402"><unclear/> unless and I don't like er <trunc>he</trunc>heavy metal rock or any <unclear>other</unclear> thing which people need to shout</u>
<u n="690" who="S0405">okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0403" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0402" trans="overlap">don't swear don't shout</u>
<u n="693" who="S0403">I suppose I suppose that's fair like <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0402" trans="overlap">I like I like a certain melody in music cos at the end they I can talk and swear a lot and I probably do</u>
<u n="695" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0403" trans="overlap">it's true</u>
<u n="697" who="S0402">so I does that make me any different?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0402" trans="overlap"><unclear/> shout and talk</u>
<u n="700" who="S0405">I I agree with you on that <unclear/> there are yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0403" trans="overlap">it's like a <unclear/> the thing with metal <trunc>a</trunc>and the main reason people like the proper screaming stuff is that er it's impressive because it's so</u>
<u n="702" who="S0405">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0403">hard to play</u>
<u n="704" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0403">and it's so <trunc>ins</trunc> cos the drums and the guitar that very few people on the planet can do that</u>
<u n="706" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0403">and that's the main reason it's popular</u>
<u n="708" who="S0405"><unclear/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0402" trans="overlap">do you think there's a certain amount of also like rebellion in it?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0403">yeah that's true and <unclear/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh yeah all music is</u>
<u n="712" who="S0402" trans="overlap">rock is like the ultimate like rebellion kind of thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0403">yeah well it was back in the sixties and it still is now really</u>
<u n="714" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> how it started</u>
<u n="715" who="S0402" trans="overlap">well I guess it it went from like</u>
<u n="716" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="717" who="S0402">I guess it went from</u>
<u n="718" who="S0405" trans="overlap">Beastie Boys</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
