<text id="SUHT">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:28:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>[unknown]</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>discussing Norwich vs. Cambridge, making plans to move to a different city/place. </topics>
		<activity>A couple having Sunday lunch and discussing cities. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0262">so Sunday lunch in <anon type="place"/> at the oldest pub in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0261">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="place"/> the one with the gremlin over the over the door <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wonder what that's about it's kind of their own little er <pause dur="short"/> signature to to the gargoyle is it?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0262">I think it's very <trunc>pre</trunc> it's very pretty</u>
<u n="4" who="S0261" trans="overlap">it's quite a mashup of a building isn't it?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0262">yeah it is a mashup of a building I do really like their flowers though I mean that's pretty impressive you need to know how to grow those sort of flowers and we're already what through summer?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0261">yeah but it was like really warm <pause dur="short"/> its got to be twenty degrees here today</u>
<u n="7" who="S0262">yeah it's unseasonably warm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0261">well that's the kind of the Indian summer isn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0262">cheers my love</u>
<u n="10" who="S0261">cheers to</u>
<u n="11" who="S0262" trans="overlap">to a day in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><unclear/> beer</u>
<u n="13" who="S0262">it's rather nice</u>
<u n="14" who="S0261" trans="overlap">what <unclear>sun dew beer</unclear> it's quite good isn't it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0262">ah this is one good thing about coming up here</u>
<u n="16" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0262">I can get my get my cider later on tonight</u>
<u n="18" who="S0261">oh I see so you've got it all planned out haven't you? get to lay around in my cider cider bath</u>
<u n="19" who="S0262">well considering how much we used to pay well I used to pay for a Norfolk Aspall cider well a Suffolk Aspall cider in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0262">that <anon type="place"/> pub</u>
<u n="22" who="S0261">well that was kind of</u>
<u n="23" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it was like eighteen dollars</u>
<u n="24" who="S0261">pretty bonkers wasn't it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0262">yeah it was it was bonkers</u>
<u n="26" who="S0261">and they just pitched themselves as a certain type of outfit didn't they?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0262">English British <pause dur="short"/> and it can't really cost that much to import those kind of ciders surely into the into Australia it's just that's right that's the mark-up cos there aren't as people doing it <pause dur="short"/> it can't can't cost that much</u>
<u n="28" who="S0261">well it doesn't cost that much they're just making a good kind of triple profit on it</u>
<u n="29" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0261">don't forget they've got to pay more tax in Australia for alcohol too</u>
<u n="31" who="S0262">yeah well I don't miss that <pause dur="short"/> so anyway I think that it's been quite a journey</u>
<u n="32" who="S0261">coming up here today?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0261">it was a lot quicker than I thought it would be</u>
<u n="35" who="S0262">I was thinking more about the journey we've been on for the past nine months</u>
<u n="36" who="S0261">nine months?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0261">oh is that your number did you grab a number?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0262">is that the beef and the lamb?</u>
<u n="40" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0262">oh that's ours thanks</u>
<u n="42" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">lamb?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0262">lamb shank is it? yep brilliant thank you</u>
<u n="44" who="S0261">and beef fantastic cheers mate</u>
<u n="45" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">alright sauces for you</u>
<u n="46" who="S0262">great thank you</u>
<u n="47" who="S0261" trans="overlap">brilliant</u>
<u n="48" who="S0262">that was fast</u>
<u n="49" who="S0261">erm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0262">wow</u>
<u n="51" who="S0261">a haggisy type thing</u>
<u n="52" who="S0262">mm lamb shank I haven't had a lamb shank in years</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="53" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">there we go</u>
<u n="54" who="S0262">great thank you</u>
<u n="55" who="S0261">oh brilliant thank you yeah I kind of didn't erm expect to be <pause dur="short"/> here to tell you the truth</u>
<u n="56" who="S0262">oh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> why's that?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0261">well I've only been up here a couple of times before and I kind of figured it was because it was struggle to come up this way</u>
<u n="58" who="S0262">mm mm mm I know what you mean</u>
<u n="59" who="S0261">and oh look at this <pause dur="short"/> it's like a big old truck</u>
<u n="60" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0261">a sightseeing tour so I've felt that they've just kind of come down here so they can check us out while we have a feed</u>
<u n="62" who="S0262">that's quite cute</u>
<u n="63" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0261">it's a lot more a thing to go</u>
<u n="66" who="S0262">mm I think so <pause dur="short"/> I think once you kind of get away from the shopping malls and that sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I think it's I think it's an alright place I mean there's a lot more going on than meets the eye</u>
<u n="67" who="S0261">well what meets the eye is pretty good anyway</u>
<u n="68" who="S0262">mm mm and I think in a way it's quite it's quite cute because I think the students here by and large sort of make a bit more of of of contributing to the sort of the scene</u>
<u n="69" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0262">where as in <anon type="place"/> if you got to <anon type="place"/> university you are you're kept you you know you sort of keep yourself to yourself erm and the things like <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> and whatnot is more for inside the university's entertainment</u>
<u n="71" who="S0261">do you think so?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0262">mm I think so I mean have you ever been along to a <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> production in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="74" who="S0262">no and that's a bit weird isn't it? considering how long we lived there</u>
<u n="75" who="S0261">in the past</u>
<u n="76" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0261">what's weird about it is just that it's not the kind of stuff that you want to go and see or?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0262">erm perhaps it's perhaps it is perhaps it's not but <pause dur="short"/> when I think of <anon type="place"/> I actually I don't get excited about the cultural the cultural elements to it and maybe I need to see it through a fresh pair of eyes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0261">well what's your picture of the erm of what happens at <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/>?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0262">I mean to be fair I don't I you know I don't know apart from the fact that you know the name is famous</u>
<u n="81" who="S0261">mm it carries a lot of history of a lot of kind of famous actors and presenters</u>
<u n="82" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262">and it finds people and finds talent it's good at nurturing talent</u>
<u n="85" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">so all I'm saying is that maybe I should go along one day to actually have a look <pause dur="short"/> and judge for myself</u>
<u n="87" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0262">but I think what I'm saying is that <pause dur="long"/> I've probably never really tried to engage with <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> quite on a sort of cultural level that maybe some other people choose to <pause dur="short"/> and that that's my own fault</u>
<u n="89" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262">so you know <pause dur="short"/> erm and it sort of annoys me in a way because there is there is obviously quite a lot going on</u>
<u n="91" who="S0261">that was random how did they do that? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0261">that's pretty cool</u>
<u n="94" who="S0262">and I think there is some you know there's some good stuff like that you know erm festival ideas and some of those things are free and <pause dur="short"/> I think we should tap into it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="95" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262">what do you think?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0261">well it depends on whether there's anything worthwhile on</u>
<u n="98" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that that actually when I say worthwhile that <pause dur="long"/> goes beyond looking at <pause dur="short"/> a lot ofstuff's just steeped in history and connected to us do you know?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0261">what's erm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0262">you <trunc>se</trunc> you mean the academic side is very to the fore here?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0261" trans="overlap">what what's new? what's</u>
<u n="104" who="S0262">I mean in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0261">well I'm simply looking at like that <anon type="place"/> kind of outfit</u>
<u n="106" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0261">for the erm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that that's a very specific clientele I'd say</u>
<u n="109" who="S0261">yeah but I mean</u>
<u n="110" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's quite music-focused</u>
<u n="111" who="S0261">and but pretty much most of it was kind of dealing with go and have a look at the history of this history of thatand the history of this</u>
<u n="112" who="S0262">I think that's how they get the funding</u>
<u n="113" who="S0261">you know <pause dur="short"/> but it means that it's supporting some of the old stuff and giving it a face and a name and a bringing it to an audience and so on and so on</u>
<u n="114" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0261">which is fine but <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm more interested in a cultural connection which is more about the people that are around today</u>
<u n="116" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0261">it's kind of like you could be standing in a crowd of people talking about history of <anon type="place"/> and yet not knowing anything about anybody around you</u>
<u n="118" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0261">and so what's the point in it?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I mean I've always found <anon type="place"/> to be very <pause dur="long"/> sometimes I think to me it just lacks a heart it lacks a soul it <trunc>la</trunc> it lacks a centre it lacks a place where everyone goes to hang out and I think maybe that is <anon type="place"/> in the summer or the <anon type="place"/> or whatever you know in the summer and I remember being sixteen or fifteen but I'm I'm not fifteen and sixteen anymore <pause dur="short"/> you know I need somewhere else to go to feel that sense of heart city <pause dur="short"/> and I struggle to find it</u>
<u n="121" who="S0261">well they have those kind of events like in summer like the <pause dur="short"/> they have the beer festivals and the <anon type="place"/> that kind of stuff you know</u>
<u n="122" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm I mean</u>
<u n="123" who="S0261">some of them are family-oriented some of them aren'tyou know</u>
<u n="124" who="S0262">I mean more regular feeling rather than once a year I mean of course they have <anon type="place"/> folk festival and all that which is very you know prestigious but I mean when you go into the city you make a beeline for somewhere and go oh I'm gonna go and see what's going on <pause dur="short"/> you know and have a sort of a racing heart oh I wonder what exciting things are happening</u>
<u n="125" who="S0262">well maybe it's a part of</u>
<u n="126" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and some cities have that</u>
<u n="127" who="S0261">yeah maybe it's part of the culture that you know what people are doing is mooching around and shopping</u>
<u n="128" who="S0262">yeah shopping mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="129" who="S0261">or that these kind of <trunc>co</trunc> erm gatherings and events are they are like I said they're kind of the <anon type="place"/> type of things or</u>
<u n="130" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="short"/> like the films in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0262">yeah I don't decry that I'm talking more about something all year round something that is more of a place of an opening it's not necessarily an event <pause dur="short"/> it's like going to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0262">I miss places like that where people congregate because they need to they want to feel something from each other not just shopping</u>
<u n="135" who="S0261">mm so so give me an example of a place anywhere that you've been thatkind of pulls that together</u>
<u n="136" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0261">so you're talking about <anon type="place"/> right?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0262">well you just said give me an example so I'm giving you one</u>
<u n="139" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="short"/> erm so I mean they're hubs because they're transport hubs you know and</u>
<u n="140" who="S0262">true yeah but they're also cultural hubs</u>
<u n="141" who="S0261">yeah so they've shanked to some kind of cultural connection around those hubs</u>
<u n="142" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0261"><anon type="place"/> the<anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0261">you've got erm some of that kind of I suppose bars you've got a square that's on the other side of of the quay</u>
<u n="146" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0261">but it's not actually in town but it's on harbour side right? so they've wrapped that around a feature</u>
<u n="148" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="long"/> so what kind of feature in <anon type="place"/> would they wrap that kind of thing around? erm you've kind of got like the river you've got the square you've got the colleges yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm but the thing is is that ironically the the colleges you have some kind of split so</u>
<u n="150" who="S0262">mm they do split the flow up quite a lotin the city</u>
<u n="151" who="S0261">but also they split split the culture and the society</u>
<u n="152" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0261">so <pause dur="short"/> although kind of the tourism is centered around some of the colleges the fact is is that they're they're not actually aligned yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0262">not really I don't feel they are</u>
<u n="155" who="S0261" trans="overlap">no?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0262">I mean I've shown people around <anon type="place"/> cos they're tourists and I'm meant to show them around and I've struggled to make it <trunc>so</trunc> seem <trunc>co</trunc>coherent</u>
<u n="157" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="short"/> so part of that is space</u>
<u n="158" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0261">and and and and layout</u>
<u n="160" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0261">and location</u>
<u n="162" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="short"/> and part of it is culture</u>
<u n="164" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0261">different cultures living together in the same place</u>
<u n="166" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0261">looking for different things erm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="168" who="S0262">see if you had to choose between say living in somewhere like <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> no if you had to choose between <trunc>Lo</trunc> no <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> well yeah let's start with that one <pause dur="short"/> how would you feel about you know <pause dur="short"/> living in a place that like this that's it's got a history but it's more provincial whereas <anon type="place"/> is very much on the map</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="169" who="S0261">well it depends on what you're looking for alright erm <pause dur="short"/> if you were here I mean as it presents itself it kind of feels like an interesting place</u>
<u n="170" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0261"><trunc>bu</trunc>but I've not lived here so I can't really kind of make a judgment</u>
<u n="172" who="S0262">no that's true</u>
<u n="173" who="S0261">in that way erm you know you can look at things on the surface but they may well be different when you're experiencing them over a long time</u>
<u n="174" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0261">erm and that it is off the beaten track</u>
<u n="176" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0261">so <pause dur="short"/> if you wanted to be connected <pause dur="short"/> I don't know you know we're used to being somewhere like a place like <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> or whatever or <anon type="place"/> where you can get to an airport easily and that airport can take you to places that you wanna go</u>
<u n="178" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0261">you know</u>
<u n="180" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0261">so <pause dur="short"/> if it meant that you know I'm sure you can fly certain places in Europe from <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="182" who="S0262">I know what you're saying I I know</u>
<u n="183" who="S0261">it's not hub-based so</u>
<u n="184" who="S0262">yeah yeah I mean like if your business depended on flying frequently you would want to be nearer to a well accessible to an airport like <anon type="place"/> because <anon type="place"/>'s bloody brilliant in most respects</u>
<u n="185" who="S0261">yeah because it gives you access to a lot of Europe pretty easily</u>
<u n="186" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0261">being in <anon type="place"/> is good for the same reason that it doesn't have to be the northern airport of <anon type="place"/> it can be any of them</u>
<u n="188" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0261">and on a good day if you want to get to <anon type="place"/> airport you can get there in under and hour</u>
<u n="190" who="S0262">mm yeah that's true</u>
<u n="191" who="S0261">so <pause dur="short"/> for some people that would be like living in <anon type="place"/> and trying to travel across <anon type="place"/> to get to these places</u>
<u n="192" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0261">and you you don't you live outside of it and you're connected differently so the point is how does it fit together with the way you feel connected with the location the place the culture so on and so on <pause dur="short"/> your particular needs or whatever you know?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0261">erm if your needs are you've got to be able to go to an airport once a month they're not gonna want to have to go from here to <anon type="place"/> as an example</u>
<u n="196" who="S0262">mm and conversely if you don't need to be somewhere going somewhere once once a month the payoff is something you might contemplate?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0261">well maybe yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0262">yeah I mean if you only knew you were flying two or three times a year from <anon type="place"/> that's why you wouldn't you know you wouldn't mark it out as oh I have to live live near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0261">I don't know how long it takes erm well you I suppose you just bomb it down the</u>
<u n="200" who="S0262">on the train</u>
<u n="201" who="S0261"><anon type="place"/> if you're gonna go to <anon type="place"/> coach</u>
<u n="202" who="S0262">yeah it's a coach</u>
<u n="203" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I imagine that journey is between an hour and an hour and a half</u>
<u n="204" who="S0262">I agree if you were a businessman and you had to fly nearly every week or every other week from <anon type="place"/> you would live in <anon type="place"/> but if you didn't actually have to fly every week or every month from <anon type="place"/> erm you could contemplate living a little bit further further afield</u>
<u n="205" who="S0261">maybe</u>
<u n="206" who="S0262" trans="overlap">cos your needs wouldn't be the same and also some people you know do have to fly from <anon type="place"/> but they choose not to live near an airport so it's all depending on you know I don't think your life is completely dictated by transport it does have an <trunc>im</trunc> it does have an impact <pause dur="short"/> but some people choose not to make it a big deal and others do yeah it just depends on your personality I guess you know if you like having ease of access to transport then you're gonna place yourself near a station where you can get to places</u>
<u n="207" who="S0261">yeah uh-huh</u>
<u n="208" who="S0262">erm <pause dur="short"/> but train travel's very expensive in this country so it's kind of not my choice of er of transport at the moment</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="209" who="S0261">well</u>
<u n="210" who="S0262" trans="overlap">if I can help it</u>
<u n="211" who="S0261">versus what other <trunc>op</trunc> er options?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0262">well there's buses and coaches and your own transport</u>
<u n="213" who="S0261">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> relative to time it depends on how you want to where you want to go parking time how long it takes versus cost and so you taking the train because it gets you quite often close to where you need to be</u>
<u n="214" who="S0262">yeah I agree but it's still if you haven't got the money in your pocket you're going to have to find another way of <trunc>transporta</trunc> transporting yourself you know? if people go I haven't got fifty quid to spend to go to London for the day day going back and forth or thirty-five or whatever it is you really do have no other option but looking at other transport systems like getting a coach you can get a coach into <anon type="place"/> for six pound fifty from <anon type="place"/>for a single</u>
<u n="215" who="S0261">and the journey takes probably two two and a half hours</u>
<u n="216" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0261">versus forty-five minutes</u>
<u n="218" who="S0262">yeah it does mean that you have to spend</u>
<u n="219" who="S0261">so</u>
<u n="220" who="S0262">more time travelling</u>
<u n="221" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so if you valued your time and you said your time was worth fifty quid an hour</u>
<u n="222" who="S0262">I know I'm just saying if you didn't have money in your pocket I find a lot of people don't necessarily have money in their pocket to spend on <trunc>tra</trunc> on trains</u>
<u n="223" who="S0261">oh yeah? is that right?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0262">yeah well if you were like yeah if you didn't have that much money you wouldn't be going on expensive train journeys</u>
<u n="225" who="S0261">is there something wrong with that bit?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0262">no I just couldn't fit it all in I'm full</u>
<u n="227" who="S0261">can I can I have it</u>
<u n="228" who="S0262">yeah course you can and also if you are erm not rushing about to get into <anon type="place"/> you have a choice which is do I take the cheaper option and give myself forty pounds to play with while I'm in <anon type="place"/> but take a longer time to get there? but I don't have to be there for a specific time I'm just going in to see friends or you know I'm going to do some kind of show or exhibition or whatever it is that you're looking for you might take the cheaper option just because it gives you more spending money while you're in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm so that's another thing I'm saying as well but anyway it really started off not <trunc>ne</trunc> really necessarily about <trunc>tra</trunc>transport it was more about <pause dur="short"/> how <anon type="place"/> has never really excited me I just still kind of can't really put my finger on why why it doesn't why it doesn't feel like it's an exciting place to be</u>
<u n="229" who="S0261">well I've always pinned that down to the fact that the bloody place is flat</u>
<u n="230" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="short"/> true</u>
<u n="231" who="S0261">right? <pause dur="short"/> grew up in a place which had hills and mountains and bush to walk in and <anon type="place"/> has none of that really</u>
<u n="232" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0261">so <pause dur="short"/> that's why I've never found it attractive like I never found a place like <anon type="place"/> attractive</u>
<u n="234" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0261">because the bloody place is flat you know so</u>
<u n="236" who="S0262" trans="overlap">hello <pause dur="short"/> yes that's great thank you very much that was lovely</u>
<u n="237" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah it was really nice thank you</u>
<u n="238" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">good thanks beautiful day</u>
<u n="239" who="S0262">it is it's great yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah it's nice and warm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's a nice <unclear/> to come out</u>
<u n="242" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">thank you</u>
<u n="245" who="S0261">yeah erm and that's what we were saying before we came over here from Australia that we were gonna look at places which carried the right environment a place that felt good to be in and I think for me that's where that connection is the connection is with the environment around you and then you look at the other things that relate to that yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0261">you imagine being in a place like <anon type="place"/> as nice as it is just imagine if it didn't have a harbour and didn't have beaches</u>
<u n="248" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0261">what kind of different place it might be</u>
<u n="250" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0261">you know? erm or that if you lived in <anon type="place"/> but you had to live out of the flat plains and in amongst suburbia so you were still thirty forty fifty kilometres away from the centre of the city <anon type="place"/> is not <anon type="place"/> out there it's a different place you know</u>
<u n="252" who="S0262" trans="overlap">too right it is yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0261">so that's kind of like living in <anon type="place"/> or in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0261">erm so when you go to places other places in Europe I mean <anon type="place"/> feels more like a European place because it's got some of kind of older heritage to it and stuff like that and and you feel that it's it's kind of there erm and <anon type="place"/> is a bit kind of bits and pieces about all that yeah? not as coherent so <pause dur="short"/> not not feeling like that it doesn't feel like it it has that kind of heart it doesn't have a very strong central heart I think that's just my feeling</u>
<u n="256" who="S0262">no that's exactly what I was saying twenty minutes ago</u>
<u n="257" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> so erm if you then take the environmental side of it a place with hills a place with some kind of water it's what we talked about you know a place that isn't necessarily a big city could be a big city or maybe not but certainly it's got kind of a central heart to it</u>
<u n="258" who="S0262">yeah where the people are friendly</u>
<u n="259" who="S0261" trans="overlap">a place where people want to be</u>
<u n="260" who="S0262">I think that makes a big difference to me</u>
<u n="261" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0262">I could probably forego the the whole mountains and thing erm if I felt that there was a a central hub of erm people who enjoy living in the city clearly are very proud of it want to make it something interesting and fun for people <pause dur="short"/> and have a friendly attitude I think that would be you know a much nicer place a much nicer experience</u>
<u n="263" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0262">because most of the time if you're working or whatever you are interacting with people</u>
<u n="265" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="266" who="S0262">and I think yeah I think you can get out into the countryside erm unless you live out in rural countryside where you probably want to get away from people erm being in the being in the heart of something in a city must be exciting because there's just so much going on <pause dur="short"/> so many different types of people to interact with</u>
<u n="267" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0262">so for me it's kind of like well if we can't live somewhere straightaway that's gonna be mountains and the lakes and the you know the things that we said would be important for us erm where else can we have as a stop gap which is you know interesting different but not <anon type="place"/> and not costing like the earth you know to to make happen <pause dur="short"/> see I don't mind having you know <anon type="place"/> as a base it doesn't bother me to have it as a base but it it it still <pause dur="short"/> it needs to be temporary</u>
<u n="269" who="S0261">of course it is temporary</u>
<u n="270" who="S0262">so I need <trunc>so</trunc> I need either a reason to pull away from it and say oh you know sorry we're not living there anymore because something's happened and we both need to go and live somewhere else which gives us an impetus to actually go up go go go away from <anon type="place"/> and get off our arses and go off and do something else</u>
<u n="271" who="S0261">yeah of course yeah that's always the way that I've been thinking</u>
<u n="272" who="S0262">yeah the reality is though is that we have to turn it into an implementation plan</u>
<u n="273" who="S0261">yes that's right</u>
<u n="274" who="S0262">and we've kind of stalled on that side <unclear>faffing</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so I'm still clocking it up in my head going well how do we implement this? how do we make it happen given what we know given our circumstances given our limitations what we have at the moment that we're really trying to just get by on various things</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
