<text id="SUU4">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0456 S0463</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s office, Joensuu, Finland</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Aquaintences</relationships>
		<topics>politics, football, the government, New Labour, Tony Blair, stake-</topics>
		<activity>Talking about football and politics</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, Inquiring, Anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0456">
				<exactage>44</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/ German</nat>
				<birthplace>Salzkotten</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>German</l1>
				<lingorig>English</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scouse</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Liverpool</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer (English Language and Literature)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0463">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scouse</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Liverpool</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>All my life</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Taxi Cab driver</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0463">how's the home?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0456">well I er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who teaches German popped in yesterday and she was saying oh yeah you probably won't hold that and it's it's closer to hers because she's opposite mine they have this wonderful idea to build a four-storey house or block of flats in the car park of an existing block of flats which must be very nice for the people who live there because they have been there for years I think <unclear/> and where do they park?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0463">mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0456">erm but she said nobody knows when it starts might be in two years who knows</u>
<u n="5" who="S0463">but it's okay so far?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0456">the new dog</u>
<u n="7" who="S0463">the move is the move is smooth everything is going?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0456">yeah yeah so far so far only one late washing machine so you notice the difference though because suddenly you can hear the traffic</u>
<u n="9" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0456">yeah that's that's bearable so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0463">so what are we to do?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0456">we are to talk guess guess you can guess what er what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked me the other day whether I'm Corbynised and I was just er you know why? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0463" trans="overlap">ah I see he should have asked me</u>
<u n="14" who="S0456">yeah hasn't he?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0463">er I might not have seen him since then but pretty obvious I am</u>
<u n="16" who="S0456">yeah he introduced himself as now you see me and then you don't because I I tend to retire gracefully it's like everybody expected you to retire disgracefully but er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0463">is he in today do you know?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0456">mm?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0463">was he in today?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0456">I've seen him yesterday I haven't seen him today</u>
<u n="21" who="S0463">I'm doing the course with him next week</u>
<u n="22" who="S0456">there are things on this week I mean even before officially we started the courses we are being taught erm I'm glad that I didn't have to start this week it's another it's another week to go before I have to face the music</u>
<u n="23" who="S0463">well we had to mourn the footy for a week</u>
<u n="24" who="S0456">yeah go on tell us about the footy</u>
<u n="25" who="S0463">did you not watch it?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0456">no</u>
<u n="27" who="S0463">it was dreadful I somehow didn't care so I was there I've written this season off</u>
<u n="28" who="S0456">well you know it was the first loss</u>
<u n="29" who="S0463">I know I am just it feels like he's a dead man walking</u>
<u n="30" who="S0456">well the the I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was the best the back four have basically yeah table football about <unclear/> mobile</u>
<u n="31" who="S0463">yes yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0456">it's it's</u>
<u n="33" who="S0463">I'm voting by the way I've become an affiliate member</u>
<u n="34" who="S0456">have they not checked you out yet?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0463">no cos I've never been a member of any other party</u>
<u n="36" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0463">and I have voted Labour</u>
<u n="38" who="S0456">but I mean it's it's fine you can vote Labour because they can't be</u>
<u n="39" who="S0463">but I've never voted any anything other than Labour</u>
<u n="40" who="S0456">they can't really check your voting record I think they just go by</u>
<u n="41" who="S0463" trans="overlap">well apparently they have been doing checking electoral registers</u>
<u n="42" who="S0456">but obviously if you are if you are able to vote in Britain and er but yeah it's usually on party grounds isn't it? make the hoo the hoo-ha about it it's that's that's only a small proportion of how many people has the Labour party now? four hundred thousand</u>
<u n="43" who="S0463" trans="overlap">yeah six hundred</u>
<u n="44" who="S0456">six hundred thousand I mean that's about sixty times as many as the Tories cos they're all dead</u>
<u n="45" who="S0463">or dying</u>
<u n="46" who="S0456">I mean it's a it's a it's a party of dead men walking I mean even my my surrogate mum has left them for UKIP because they were so dead in Birkenhead</u>
<u n="47" who="S0463" trans="overlap"><trunc>whe</trunc>where was she? in Birkenhead</u>
<u n="48" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this is well she was the youngest she is now sixty-six sixty-seven the youngest</u>
<u n="49" who="S0463">the thing that's most peculiar is that the core vote has always been essentially the ageing population obviously and those in the countryside and what do they offer people in the countryside? the infrastructure bill is basically saying we can <unclear>frack</unclear> wherever we want to</u>
<u n="50" who="S0456" trans="overlap">mm yeah well it's it's</u>
<u n="51" who="S0463">it seems to me that they're alienating the</u>
<u n="52" who="S0456" trans="overlap">subsidies no end isn't it? but you have to be a big landowner</u>
<u n="53" who="S0463">no but it seems to be that they're alienating the core voters yet the <unclear>masochists</unclear> are still voting for them</u>
<u n="54" who="S0456">yeah well because they've never voted anything else you know just cos why would they would vote for an industrial party erm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0463">but Labour's no longer an industrial party that's <unclear/> times</u>
<u n="56" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah but that's their sort of I mean the the I think that's that's something they haven't got</u>
<u n="57" who="S0463" trans="overlap">yeah but you're right it's the country that isn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0456">they haven't got er policies for the countryside what they the only thing that they have which I can remember from the manifesto might be about erm access via buses which is relevant but it's not the core issue</u>
<u n="59" who="S0463" trans="overlap">Labour <trunc>crea</trunc> Labour created the green belt</u>
<u n="60" who="S0456">well that's probably not er very <trunc>he</trunc> helpful for farmers because you know the the the it just means you can't sell your land for more</u>
<u n="61" who="S0463">no but it's helpful for in terms of preservation and conservation</u>
<u n="62" who="S0456">oh yeah that is</u>
<u n="63" who="S0463">which you know given the name of the conservative party has it's root in conservation</u>
<u n="64" who="S0456">yeah well it's the conservative and unionist party and that's very <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0463" trans="overlap">you be honest with you it's I I I I can only see the appeal of the Tories to erm corporate people</u>
<u n="66" who="S0456">oh yeah I mean it's it's blatant I suppose it's the spire in the castle or whatever it is it's it's the local known face and they just don't move</u>
<u n="67" who="S0463">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0456">erm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0463">well this is why this is why you always it's always difficult to feel sympathy for farmers isn't it? even though they're struggling like hell right now and by all rights we should feel a certain sympathy for them but</u>
<u n="70" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0463"><unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0456">that's I mean that's the other thing they er and it goes for everything the complete non-engagement by the Tories you know if you want to have better deals for farmers for fishermen all your core constituencies you want to be engaged in Europe I mean just saying oh that's Europe and then putting people I mean I don't even know who the foreign minister is I mean who cares? with this lot could be anyone it it could be Where's Wally?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0463" trans="overlap">well we but we know who Hilary likes now</u>
<u n="74" who="S0456">what <trunc>ca</trunc> the Qatarian?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0463" trans="overlap">drinking my water</u>
<u n="76" who="S0456" trans="overlap">oh sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry I just saw it waving at me I've got my own water that's my own</u>
<u n="77" who="S0463" trans="overlap">yeah you got you got some you got a change of register then at least for your tape</u>
<u n="78" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0463">no we know who Hilary likes now anyway the charming David did you read that?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0456">no I didn't read that</u>
<u n="81" who="S0463">David Miliband</u>
<u n="82" who="S0456">well you know he's isn't that what everybody said when erm when he went over the States that he er erm you know he was the equivalent to erm one of the big Democrats who would be let in and would get zillions of dollars in because he's charming everyone</u>
<u n="83" who="S0463">mm the prince over the water</u>
<u n="84" who="S0456">mm er but the thing is I suppose there's there's no way back for him into Britain it's it just doesn't work in Britain I suppose it works in other countries but</u>
<u n="85" who="S0463">in New Labour circles wasn't he regarded as a disappointment? someone who'd be over promoted by Blair and someone who they found intellectually lightweight that was my impression at the time</u>
<u n="86" who="S0456">yeah he was definitely pushed a lot by Blair you know he was the the the in the in-group the builder back of the Labour Party</u>
<u n="87" who="S0463">I know but his his career path did stall at one stage the idea was that when he was he was <trunc>wa</trunc> became one of the policy chiefs erm that he was actually found out er in that he had nothing to say and it was all platitudes</u>
<u n="88" who="S0456">yeah but yeah I mean that was the thing I mean I'm sure Ed Miliband had things to say and they just didn't</u>
<u n="89" who="S0463">they got lost</u>
<u n="90" who="S0456">come over and it was it was unfortunately if if you go by the bits and pieces that come out it sounds like erm Kinnock you know there were all kinds of bright young things around who wanted to be modern be electable but they were they were even wonkier in in both senses of the word <vocal desc="laugh"/> than Miliband and yeah it it lacks substance it just was too easily exposed</u>
<u n="91" who="S0463">it did I and I totally agree but I still think with erm if they had had a Blair type of figure in terms of charisma erm presenting that suite of policies I suspect they would have won</u>
<u n="92" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0463">erm the government so much of it is down to his personality even though I agree with what he said</u>
<u n="94" who="S0456">well if you look at what was it? it wasn't in The Times was it? what paper this is?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0463">well Labour increased their vote in the England</u>
<u n="96" who="S0456">yeah yeah unfortunately it increased it mostly where it already had er the secure seats</u>
<u n="97" who="S0463" trans="overlap">I know but</u>
<u n="98" who="S0456">but no the this this this in-depth survey that they did rather than asking loads of people when they did the focus groups erm former Labour voters that voted Tory ordered them in twenty fifteen probably twenty ten erm and there's a big residue of positive feeling towards Blair cos the the main issue clearly for the people on the left was the Iraq war</u>
<u n="99" who="S0463">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0456">which drowns out everything else</u>
<u n="101" who="S0463">poisoned the well</u>
<u n="102" who="S0456">yeah well of course for for Joe Bloggs he's not really interested in politics but he's interested in mortgage repayments whether they've got a good job whether they've got money in their pocket or feel like they can spend money</u>
<u n="103" who="S0463">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0456">of course you know the Blair years were the the the same thing as the Clinton years things were looking up all the time</u>
<u n="105" who="S0463" trans="overlap">I know I know I know I know and there was even a brief window very unusual in modern British history when we were at peace with the world</u>
<u n="106" who="S0456">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0463">before nine eleven and before Iraq even cos Afghanistan is not quite so big I don't think but mainly what I mean is what he inherited was between the troubles in Ireland</u>
<u n="108" who="S0456">yes</u>
<u n="109" who="S0463">and the foreign policy adventurism was a window of security and stability</u>
<u n="110" who="S0456">and the amount of effort that was put into Northern Ireland I mean it's like this lot nothing you know they're just like oh we want to cut and you can go hang</u>
<u n="111" who="S0463">oh party before country that's that's everything with this lot</u>
<u n="112" who="S0456">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0456">but yeah he's he's he's I mean Mandelson has <unclear/> returned having Mo Mowlam there who who's the people person but himself and spending so much time and energy and</u>
<u n="115" who="S0463" trans="overlap">mm I know he's not given much credit for that because of Major I'm not saying whether that's right or wrong I don't know how far Major had got but I think there's an issue when people look back</u>
<u n="116" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0463">it's coloured by the idea that Major had done a lot of the work</u>
<u n="118" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0463">which Blair himself acknowledges actually</u>
<u n="120" who="S0456">oh yeah yeah I mean the groundwork was there but as you can see now yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0463">he was committed I agree with you</u>
<u n="122" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah you cannot you can't you cannot just let things slip and er yeah I don't know if he was like I remember that was in the first year and people like Blunkett at the conference they just looked tired really really tired because the the amount of work that they tried to get through in a relatively short time and <trunc>y</trunc><trunc>yo</trunc> <trunc>the</trunc> this lot is just doing so much but nothing really happens that is positive erm and there's nothing is really thought through whereas you know certainly the early Blair years it was trying to involve they had the whole thing with stakeholders erm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0463">are you sure that wasn't just rhetoric?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0456">no because</u>
<u n="125" who="S0463">because it disappeared very quickly</u>
<u n="126" who="S0456">well the it it just was probably seen as as as a stupid word but it did work as in trying to get all the parties involved before things were actually enacted legislation apart from the things that were coming from Gordon Brown you know the massive <trunc>sur</trunc>surcharge on the utilities which was just a master stroke</u>
<u n="127" who="S0463">I I thought there was some real cynicism at that stage not that everything was bad by all means you know I'm not as perhaps as anti New Labour as you might think</u>
<u n="128" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0463">erm I'm certainly you know compared to this shower</u>
<u n="130" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0463">you know give me Blair every time erm but I thought I remember the kind of ideological thing that was going on in the kind of third way at the time and the language that was used around communitarianism and stakeholder community stakeholder societies and it was abandoned very very quickly and my own experience professionally of the use of the word stakeholders was that it was a way to bypass democracy</u>
<u n="132" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0463">because these people were already citizens and voters and constituents and what you actually had was sifting a few people who were a favoured few at the top of these communities with no mandate er and taking powers away from the local authorities and calling these new people stakeholders which was in essence quite anti-democratic</u>
<u n="134" who="S0456">mm mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0463">and I did have a real problem with this democratic centralism Blairism</u>
<u n="136" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0463">because it wasn't anything new they you know they were carrying on on a path from Thatcherism which was taking power from local authorities and I think that was a big mistake</u>
<u n="138" who="S0456">democratic centralism that brings me back parents but this was the father and I'm sure the card-carrying Tories of a student that I had and he was telling me that he student politics and he said he was working extremely well with the president of the union was Marxist but it was democratic centralism so it was</u>
<u n="139" who="S0463" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0456">and erm somebody else who used to be very very briefly a Labour councillor in Liverpool then of course Militant everybody was out he wasn't Militant but you know everybody was out the whole lot erm so yeah he had he definitely had this burning feeling of injustice there but he said I never trusted any of the north eastern lot because they are all democratic centralist Marxist and of course Mandelson Blair the whole chunk</u>
<u n="141" who="S0463" trans="overlap">Mandelson yeah yeah and er John Reid</u>
<u n="142" who="S0456">yeah doctor John Reid</u>
<u n="143" who="S0463"><vocal desc="laugh"/> defending all his moves</u>
<u n="144" who="S0456">yeah yeah what was it? it was sociology but I can't remember what it was on</u>
<u n="145" who="S0463">yeah so</u>
<u n="146" who="S0456">but he was he was definitely a bruiser and I don't know he he clearly</u>
<u n="147" who="S0463">he still is isn't he chairman of Celtic?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0463">have you not known him through your own</u>
<u n="150" who="S0456">I don't know</u>
<u n="151" who="S0463">he does have a position like that and he's just offending everyone still</u>
<u n="152" who="S0456">what have you</u>
<u n="153" who="S0463">he he's the type of guy who would cause an argument in an empty room</u>
<u n="154" who="S0456">he is he is I mean I have never met him in person but everything that I heard from people who who know him yes Scottish politics it is a small country after all</u>
<u n="155" who="S0463">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0456">it's <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's you wouldn't want him as your father-in-law <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0463">yeah interesting times anyway</u>
<u n="158" who="S0456">so you're your favourite Borini is off to Sunderland he seems to be so much happier now just in the promo pictures</u>
<u n="159" who="S0463">well I'm glad it's good for him it's good for the club it's cash</u>
<u n="160" who="S0456">yeah one million for</u>
<u n="161" who="S0463">got seven million for Borini</u>
<u n="162" who="S0456">no the we bought him for seven and sold him for eight</u>
<u n="163" who="S0463" trans="overlap">no no no we bought him for ten</u>
<u n="164" who="S0456">ah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0463">and sold him for eight it's alright</u>
<u n="166" who="S0456" trans="overlap">well at least if the loss is not massive so Balotelli will be on half wages</u>
<u n="167" who="S0463">I didn't I wasn't impressed by all that leaking of detail about Balotelli to the Echo</u>
<u n="168" who="S0456">what was?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0463">you know about how bad he was in training and how he was distracting other people and stuff like this because the reason I wasn't impressed by it was one you keep these things in the house and two he's still our player</u>
<u n="170" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0463">we should be looking to keep his value up there's just no sense in leaking stories</u>
<u n="172" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0463">but the club seems to be I can't work out whether it's just the times we live in where everyone is leaking in briefing it's just the kind of way to be or it was the current regime at the club who foster this atmosphere but it's not good</u>
<u n="174" who="S0456">yeah it was it was the oddest decision ever and it it just never worked full stop erm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0463">but leaking in briefing is no good anytime</u>
<u n="176" who="S0456">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> do you think do you think loads of old New Labour types started putting Liverpool for <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like of course this us</u>
<u n="177" who="S0463" trans="overlap">well they they they didn't invent spin no matter what people try and say</u>
<u n="178" who="S0456" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0463">Bernard Ingham was a master he was Thatcher's master of spin</u>
<u n="180" who="S0456">mm oh yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0463">it's always been there</u>
<u n="182" who="S0456">and yeah just read <unclear/> I mean they he he's definitely looking back at very very early twentieth century and obviously when there was no mass media spin didn't really matter because you know you would just have you're your house correspondence and it was all just via words I mean the the thing that it didn't matter how much JFK slept around because it was just never an issue that the press would touch full stop</u>
<u n="183" who="S0463" trans="overlap">I know I know I've read er Palimpsest</u>
<u n="184" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0463">and and I had no idea until I read that about</u>
<u n="186" who="S0456">his connections</u>
<u n="187" who="S0463">well no not just that about Candy's ill health</u>
<u n="188" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0463">he he had potentially two years to live anyway</u>
<u n="190" who="S0456">yeah it's it's interesting isn't it? it it's for him it was the war that probably did it for FDR was it childhood something he had? <trunc>con</trunc></u>
<u n="191" who="S0463">he had polio</u>
<u n="192" who="S0456">yeah polio</u>
<u n="193" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0456">and obviously it did kill him I mean it was the war would have killed him probably with with the kind of responsibility and anxiety and stress but</u>
<u n="195" who="S0463">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0456">you know it's it is quite amazing if you see a lot of people erm who you know the old the seventies generation of Labour MPs who were dragged out because Thatcher refused to pay up because she knew that she can eventually win by just killing Labour MPs that way this is why you know in the seventies they had to drag them in</u>
<u n="197" who="S0463">yes yes</u>
<u n="198" who="S0456">for votes because she refused pairing at one point not long after she became a leader a pairing system and of course if you have</u>
<u n="199" who="S0463">I never quite understand and this what the pairing system is</u>
<u n="200" who="S0456">pairing is if if an MP cannot come because of other commitments there would be an equivalent MP on the opposite side of the house who would also stay away</u>
<u n="201" who="S0463">oh okay</u>
<u n="202" who="S0456" trans="overlap">so you would have you would still have the equivalent of rater votes</u>
<u n="203" who="S0463">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0456">and it was very much a gentlemen's agreement and of course it comes to a tough lady and</u>
<u n="205" who="S0463" trans="overlap">well she no she <trunc>we</trunc> she was no gentlemen</u>
<u n="206" who="S0456">no erm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0463">yes because it was because one Labour MP couldn't get there wasn't it? it was on his deathbed basically</u>
<u n="208" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0463">but I didn't but I didn't know she had ended the</u>
<u n="210" who="S0456">yeah no Denis Healey wrote and spoke about that as well because you have you have to imagine they are people even if they're not your friends but people that you would see</u>
<u n="211" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0456">and obviously in the seventies she has a lot of people who who would be there until the last days they will be in safe seats there will be no reselection or anything</u>
<u n="213" who="S0463">oh my whole theory of Thatcherism is that it could only have emerged when it did because it was at that time when those who had fought in the war were vanishing from public life it couldn't have emerged before as a mass political movement because of those commitments to erm those who had fought in the war were so profound were so felt</u>
<u n="214" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0463">erm she you know erm his time came</u>
<u n="216" who="S0456">hence the title of the David Hare play on Kinnock The Absence of War and then the soliloquy the Kinnock character talks about the he will he wishes to be back in that time or the the common solidarity</u>
<u n="217" who="S0463" trans="overlap">I can't stand it any more I can't stand him any more</u>
<u n="218" who="S0456">Kinnock</u>
<u n="219" who="S0463">he's a weasel absolutely he's so such a wannabe Tory these days he's such an apologist I don't know if you heard him on he was on a number of Radio Four documentaries last year</u>
<u n="220" who="S0456">no</u>
<u n="221" who="S0463">er talking about the cabinet paper that releases in the eighties from eighty-three to eighty-four</u>
<u n="222" who="S0456">no I have missed all that you can tell me now</u>
<u n="223" who="S0463">oh he was just an utter weasel</u>
<u n="224" who="S0456"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0463">you know somehow you he supported er what Thatcher was doing and knew what she was what she was doing knew what Lawson was doing supported what Lawson was doing to his own political ends you know if they flopped over the miners all the time</u>
<u n="226" who="S0456">well yeah she was no he's in the box supposed to</u>
<u n="227" who="S0463">yeah just and you know what he was saying about Militant in Liverpool I dunno</u>
<u n="228" who="S0456">yeah comrade Kinnock</u>
<u n="229" who="S0463">yeah no time I have no time for the man you know I know he could deliver a good speech and he was right about certain things but erm seems to me that we're living through a period now where erm everyone can see that actually Thatcherism was wrong</u>
<u n="230" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0463">cos we can now see the results of Thatcherism</u>
<u n="232" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0463">because everyone makes the link don't they between Thatcherism two thousand and eight</u>
<u n="234" who="S0456">well I think</u>
<u n="235" who="S0463">it's a it's a historical block</u>
<u n="236" who="S0456" trans="overlap">I hope hopefully but really? I don't know not everyone we can see it but</u>
<u n="237" who="S0463">I think increasingly people can now I think as more and more scandals emerge erm as more and more kind of financial trauma's kind of</u>
<u n="238" who="S0456">plus the whole thing with paedophilia</u>
<u n="239" who="S0463">well that's what the scandal was yeah yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0456" trans="overlap">and the cover-up yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0463">and they were a a you know corrupt bunch</u>
<u n="242" who="S0456">yeah and of course housing is well</u>
<u n="243" who="S0463">you might think</u>
<u n="244" who="S0456">at the end of the crisis house prices go up again and it will be that night be Osborne's</u>
<u n="245" who="S0463">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0456">er <trunc>law</trunc> was it Lawson?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0463">yes it was Lawson <unclear/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0456">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0463">erm but again you know people are now saying perhaps right to buy wasn't such a good idea</u>
<u n="250" who="S0456">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0463">you know and you couldn't have had this conversation this wasn't part of the discourse</u>
<u n="252" who="S0456">mm</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
