<text id="SV3M">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:18:12</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Vegan restaurant in Rzeszow, Poland.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Social media, TV, podcasts.</topics>
		<activity> Two friends talking about various topics (see 9 above) over a meal in a vegan restaurant in Rzeszow, Poland.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0619">hello hi we're back</u>
<u n="2" who="S0618">hi</u>
<u n="3" who="S0619">erm what was I saying?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0618">mm you were saying about podcasts</u>
<u n="5" who="S0619">oh yes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0618">in serial</u>
<u n="7" who="S0619">serial ah so first season at the finish and this is the one about the the man who is in prison for the death of his ex-girlfriend er in 1999</u>
<u n="8" who="S0618">mm and this UK and true story?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0619">no it is in America it is a true story in America in oh a state I can't remember <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm and she's mm a journalist and she <pause dur="short"/> someone brought this case to her attention and said would you mind sort of writing about it? see if you can drum up some interest in it and if any sort of lawyers would potentially be interested er <pause dur="short"/> but she went further than that and she really examined every aspect of the case erm and this guy and you know they are still trying to get an er an appeal through and get you know a new trial with evidence that they are saying and they spoke to loads of lawyers loads of police and they said you know at the end of the series no spoilers <vocal desc="laugh"/> no spoilers</u>
<u n="10" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm probably not going to listen</u>
<u n="11" who="S0619">no I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's going to be an audience but the people can say by phone erm the pleasure is er <pause dur="short"/> you know erm mm do you think he is innocent or guilty of this crime that he's been in prison for sixteen years for? and all said we think he is innocent</u>
<u n="12" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/><pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="13" who="S0619">but the second series I wasn't really sure at first because it is so different just like the first series is you know not exactly well it is kind of star-crossed lovers he is from a Muslim family she is from a</u>
<u n="14" who="S0618">so this is a different case now?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="16" who="S0618">so what happened with the first one? did it go to appeal and did he get out?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0619">not yet they are still waiting</u>
<u n="18" who="S0618">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> to be continued right</u>
<u n="19" who="S0619">to be continued erm but that was you know teenagers they were seventeen or eighteen when it happened star-crossed lovers he is Muslim and she is Korean and their families didn't want them to be together erm and you know and blah blah blah but the second series is more high-profile it's about an American soldier who was camped or based in Afghanistan and he said he just walked away one day from the base he was supposed to be manning his position and he just did a runner from the army <pause dur="short"/> he was captured by the Taliban and held prisoner in different locations for five years tortured starved beaten for five years erm so I'm not really <trunc>sur</trunc> sure what erm he's going to be put on trial and possibly imprisoned in the States for you know running away</u>
<u n="20" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> good man mm <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> abandoning his post</u>
<u n="21" who="S0619">abandoning his post</u>
<u n="22" who="S0618">you'd think what more punishment could there be having been tortured by the Taliban?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0619">yeah but you know all the time that he was with the Taliban he was trying to collect intel find out information it was like <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>did</trunc> he didn't intend to be <vocal desc="laugh"/> picked up by the Taliban he just</u>
<u n="24" who="S0618">where did he think he was going to go in Afghanistan?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0619">well he was just hoping he would just be able to evade evade evade get to Pakistan and then sort of just you know hide away or go home and hide or whatever I don't know what he expected to happen but you know the sort of <pause dur="short"/> months after he had vanished you know the army and all the people based in <pause dur="short"/> all the soldiers based in that area had to drop whatever missions they were doing to search for this one man who didn't want to be found by the American army or by the or by the Taliban and you know this is <pause dur="short"/> it is the same woman from the series from the previous one who is the sort of journalist and she's listening to recorded calls between the soldier and er another journalist who spoke to him at the time and they became quite close and they spoke on the phone all the time <pause dur="short"/> erm but she is also speaking to the Taliban via an interpreter and she is like that was just me on the phone to the Taliban <vocal desc="laugh"/> so you know so at first I really didn't know if I sort of liked it because it is so different to anything <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really sure what the crime is or what she's investigating or trying to work out because it all seems pretty clear <pause dur="short"/> he left because of this because he didn't want to do it anymore and he was picked up by these people er and it was awful</u>
<u n="26" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh wow <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> as you do yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can understand that <pause dur="short"/> yeah they identified him as an enemy and punished him and blah blah blah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0619">well not identified him as only an enemy but <trunc>some</trunc> somebody of value</u>
<u n="28" who="S0618">yeah you see some of <unclear/> come to their country to kill their people so you can kind of understand people taking exception to that</u>
<u n="29" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I'm not really sure where it's going but as they've been erm releasing one episode every week people are coming forward in all different countries like in Afghanistan in Pakistan where he spent a lot of his sort of capture and anyone in the States and soldiers who he knew at the time and they are all sort of having their say <pause dur="short"/> so they've had to stagger it every two weeks so that they can</u>
<u n="30" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh wow <pause dur="short"/> what were these podcasts yeah?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="33" who="S0619">so like accumulate so it is really live</u>
<u n="34" who="S0618">interesting</u>
<u n="35" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yes</u>
<u n="36" who="S0618">so what's the purpose of the broadcast? is it you know who is producing it as a a media outlet er a radio station a?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0619">no it is just this woman</u>
<u n="38" who="S0618">this woman <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0619">this woman <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> from Serial erm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0618">this woman so Serial who produces that? is that like a Fox CBN News thing?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0619">no <pause dur="short"/> no no no it's just like this group of people and to get your podcast on the air you either pay for it or you get a sponsor so it is sponsored I think I'm not sure this season is but last season it was sponsored by Dropbox <pause dur="short"/> you know Dropbox so at the beginning they say er this is sponsored by Dropbox as Dropbox is X Y Z blah blah Dropbox is great thank you bye and now on with the programme just like that it is just like they have one advertiser and then that's it <pause dur="short"/> erm one advertisement and that's it</u>
<u n="42" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="43" who="S0619">yeah so it's <pause dur="short"/> it's an interesting type of you know er media I suppose and you know it is so different to watching things on TV and you've really got to focus and you can't do anything else you can't mess on your phone or you know because you will text</u>
<u n="44" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> because you're actively listening</u>
<u n="45" who="S0619">mm so it is really good for the gym or for walking around erm just when you've got nothing else to do</u>
<u n="46" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="47" who="S0619">but podcasts some are funny I was listening to another one and I was walking around and I was like I started laughing and I thought I'm going to get beat up if I'm just walking along the streets laughing hysterically to myself people are going to take offence</u>
<u n="48" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they will probably run away from you before they hit you</u>
<u n="49" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> who is this crazy laughing person? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0618">that's alright it is an English girl <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0619">I don't know why with a strange Russian accent <vocal desc="laugh"/> but yeah it's weird interestingly</u>
<u n="52" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm those podcasts sound interesting though</u>
<u n="53" who="S0619">yeah er</u>
<u n="54" who="S0618">mm I do like the way this whole sort of multimedia universe that we live in and open up new possibilities and new making new connections that aren't necessarily connected with the mainstream</u>
<u n="55" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it is just like listening to the radio it used to be but if you can't</u>
<u n="56" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> or the BBC got owned <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0619">I don't remember those days but you know what I mean but you know it like people who listen to The Archers erm <pause dur="short"/> all these cars are going to crash into each other here oh no they are alright they alright erm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0618">ha ha they sorted it</u>
<u n="59" who="S0619">erm like people who listen to The Archers but on like Iplayer because they missed it at the time or whatever <pause dur="short"/> I've got a friend who has got who sets her alarm on Sunday mornings so that just in time for The Archers and then the alarm clock turns on with The Archers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0618">wow <pause dur="long"/> that's dedication</u>
<u n="61" who="S0619">that is dedication so <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it is nice for like cooking because I always like music or I used to try to watch TV and cook but it was <trunc>get</trunc> it gets dangerous so podcasts and cooking</u>
<u n="62" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's the way to go it is interesting what you say about you can't live with your phone or do texts because you're so absorbed in your podcast and I found that <pause dur="short"/> suddenly I've become more sort of more conscious of that this last week or two also watching I was watching Endeavour a pre-Morse thing on erm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> iTV</u>
<u n="64" who="S0618">yeah if you go to STV player and you do it through Mozilla you don't get any adverts yeah anyway I was watching that and I kept having to rewind it because I was faffing about on WhatsApp erm on the the text and Viber and what have you messaging people then I thought what am I doing? am I watching telly? or am I communicating on my phone? make your mind up you can't do both so</u>
<u n="65" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so podcasts you've just got to ban it or pause it while you do whatever you need to do and then go back to it</u>
<u n="66" who="S0618">yeah I flick my phone onto airplane mode quite a lot now</u>
<u n="67" who="S0619">but that's good</u>
<u n="68" who="S0618">yeah and it charges quicker as well</u>
<u n="69" who="S0619">I've never been erm <pause dur="short"/> like I've been watching these Spanish films that's the same you can message on your phone because you don't know what's going on because you can't sort of like passively be watching it or be passively be listening you've really got to be looking at the screen all the time</u>
<u n="70" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> engage all the time really</u>
<u n="71" who="S0619">and we are losing this this like ability to concentrate or this er attention span and it's like what's that? oh it's a message</u>
<u n="72" who="S0618">yeah what I like about you is maybe it's because your phone is recording this I don't think it is but you are not looking at every text message you get when we go out</u>
<u n="73" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0618">and that's a general rule you don't do that and I like that</u>
<u n="75" who="S0619">a lot of the time I don't do that is because I don't have wi-fi so I'm actively prevented from using my phone</u>
<u n="76" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I find if I am in company if I go out for coffee or go out for a meal or something I don't want to be interrupted by text messages because I've gone out to see that person so I want to engage with their company I find it really incredibly rude erm my niece does it a lot actually you will be having a conversation and her phone goes bing and she cuts off the conversation and looks at it and I think well hello I am here <vocal desc="laugh"/> we were just you were halfway through saying something <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think she realises she does it you know it's quite unconscious</u>
<u n="77" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> no and it's a really normal thing to do a lot of my friends do it and you know we go out for dinner and you know everyone is you know like <pause dur="short"/> you are sat around the table in a restaurant and you have like a plate a knife and fork and phone</u>
<u n="78" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0619">you know like it's <trunc>co</trunc> like it's just part of the table arrangement yeah erm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's a good thing or a bad thing and I'm always suspicious of people who don't have Facebook and who don't use their phone very often <pause dur="short"/> or like people don't like sending messages <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hates WhatsApp and hates text messages and if I send him a text he will just immediately call me cos it is just easier for him and I think I kind of think oh that's you know that's very nice <vocal desc="laugh"/> instead of very erm <pause dur="short"/> primal <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know like <pause dur="short"/> back to erm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's fair enough <pause dur="short"/> yeah quite old-fashioned <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0619">yes gosh imagine using a phone for its original purpose how disgusting</u>
<u n="84" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> goodness <pause dur="short"/> to make a phone call oh dear</u>
<u n="85" who="S0619">I've not made a phone call for about five years <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0619">why on earth would I want to do that?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0618">you want to Facetime yes Skype yes a phone call goodness no</u>
<u n="89" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh no why would I want to do that?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0619">that's funny</u>
<u n="92" who="S0618">so why are you suspicious of people who don't engage with the technology in that way?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0619">no I <trunc>don</trunc> oh alright especially Facebook when people who go I don't want to be on the the internet I don't care what people are having for breakfast and you think oh oh come on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0619">I don't know I just think people are being sort of contentious for the sake of it and they would just be a lot happier if they just sort of <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to use it you don't have to sort of actively be a part of it but just have it there</u>
<u n="96" who="S0618">yeah I found my German friends and Polish friends are all my Facebook friends none of them post anything I call them lurkers they are Facebook lurkers</u>
<u n="97" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing wrong with lurking</u>
<u n="98" who="S0618">well I did have a phase where I blocked the lot of them <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I thought well if I can't see what you are up to because you are not posting then you are not going to see what I'm up to but you know I've gotten over myself and unblocked them all</u>
<u n="99" who="S0619">yeah one of my friends</u>
<u n="100" who="S0618">I suppose it was the cultural difference the Germans are very suspicious they sort of</u>
<u n="101" who="S0619">what so like the government is watching?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0618">yeah yeah I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my er Berlin friends were chasing the the Google <unclear>car</unclear> it's trying to google street in Berlin</u>
<u n="103" who="S0619">that's hilarious</u>
<u n="104" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0619">no I just <pause dur="short"/> I just think well <event desc="phone rings"/> why? what are you? why? it's not that big a deal er <event desc="phone rings"/> but someone on Twitter said if you win the lottery would you delete any social media accounts?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0619">and I thought oh I don't know</u>
<u n="108" who="S0618">not straightaway</u>
<u n="109" who="S0619">I don't know</u>
<u n="110" who="S0618">I think if I got a lot of begging letters and grovel unsolicited approaches from people for money I'd soon get rid of it because I wouldn't be doing with all of that guilt erm or to engage with that level of victimhood we were talking about earlier erm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how it I don't know because I I and my answer to that was I would just be a lurker I wouldn't ever post on any social media but I would just like to know what my friends are up to and you know I really enjoy Twitter and I would you know miss the jokes and what's going on in the world but don't draw attention to yourself and don't be part of it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it would change your relationships</u>
<u n="113" who="S0619">my friend at university once changed my Facebook status to oh I've just won two thousand pounds on a scratch card</u>
<u n="114" who="S0618">what your status?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0619">yeah FB it me and <pause dur="short"/> I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just got a strange number of texts that day oh hi how are you? what have you been up to?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0618">how are you today? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0619">it was only two thousand imaginary pounds <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0618">not even two thousands real pounds</u>
<u n="119" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not gonna give it to you <vocal desc="laugh"/> you don't even get a lollipop what are doing lurking around for crawling out the woodwork at two thousand imaginary pounds?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's really funny</u>
<u n="121" who="S0619">but imagine if you if you won like fifty million real pounds</u>
<u n="122" who="S0618">I'd like to think that my friends would text me or ring and say oh I hear you've won some money congratulations really delighted for you</u>
<u n="123" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and not go <pause dur="short"/> can I have something? or like just always <trunc>side</trunc> sidling around it like it's some big elephant in the room</u>
<u n="124" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah rather than how are you? <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's really funny</u>
<u n="125" who="S0619">it is just like fucking hell drinks are on you pal</u>
<u n="126" who="S0618">I would be tempted to try that <vocal desc="laugh"/> just to see what the reactions are that's really interesting</u>
<u n="127" who="S0619">I just won ten thousand <unclear/> on a scratch card</u>
<u n="128" who="S0618">well I will know what that will be well English people would say what's that then fifty P? <vocal desc="laugh"/> ten pound but no it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0619">it is really fun it was just like why have you all? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've not spoken to you for years <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's really interesting gosh you must be poor sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="130" who="S0618">I don't know I suppose er maybe there's a modicum of self-worth attached to knowing somebody or being connected with somebody who has something perceptibly wonderful like having won some money it's a bit like you know</u>
<u n="131" who="S0619">mm yeah the grass is always greener</u>
<u n="132" who="S0618">well I don't know it is like having a connection to a famous person erm that kind of a thing it's almost like a person's self-worth or status can go up a notch because of their association or connection with something perceptibly positive I don't know I just thought throw that out there</u>
<u n="133" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well so people wouldn't want to be a friend not on the off chance that you would get money but just because you've got a high-end social status than you did ten minutes before</u>
<u n="134" who="S0618">yeah because you've got some money mm hooray mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> good noises thank you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0618">I don't know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0619">I don't know either</u>
<u n="138" who="S0618">it's interesting</u>
<u n="139" who="S0619">what time is it?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0618">I think we can set up some little social experiments <pause dur="short"/> what time is it? oh we've got another hour on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0619">er on the clock <unclear/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0618"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0619">sorry do you want any cake or coffee or?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0618">I don't want any cake but I might get a coffee and I will definitely go and wee do you want cake or some coffee?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0619">no I don't want anything thank you I guess it won't have milk in it will it?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0618">do you want a cup of the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0619">what is the <unclear>bio</unclear> made of?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0618">cow milk</u>
<u n="149" who="S0619">is it?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0618">yeah oh that's true</u>
<u n="151" who="S0619">that's what I mean we are in a vegan place that's why I said</u>
<u n="152" who="S0618">ah it could be soya</u>
<u n="153" who="S0619">that's why I said what's your</u>
<u n="154" who="S0618">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="155" who="S0619">that's why I said maybe if we go</u>
<u n="156" who="S0618">you want to go regular coffee shop?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0619">I would like I would like actual milk from an actual animal rather than from a the rather from nuts or rice</u>
<u n="158" who="S0618">like an actual cow <pause dur="short"/> here's a thought and this is one of the reasons I don't drink milk as well as not</u>
<u n="159" who="S0619">oh don't say we're the only animals that drink milk from another animal?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0618">no I don't you know I don't really like it that much it does give me the runs if it have too much of it <vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry that's off the scale of need to know anyway</u>
<u n="161" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it is not for me <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't mind <vocal desc="laugh"/> for the people the people in the phone</u>
<u n="162" who="S0618">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> but for the <vocal desc="laugh"/> they will be fine man up woman up they will be fine I've completely lost my thread now</u>
<u n="163" who="S0619">why you don't like milk</u>
<u n="164" who="S0618">yes yeah thinking about you know really this stuff is for baby cows and I am not a baby cow</u>
<u n="165" who="S0619">I know but but for as long as there's been cows people have drunk their milk</u>
<u n="166" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah but no but <pause dur="short"/> have they?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0619">I think so</u>
<u n="168" who="S0618">I don't know which came first cows or humans?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0619">I don't know</u>
<u n="170" who="S0618">no I don't know</u>
<u n="171" who="S0619">we'll google it are you going to the toilet?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0618">we could google it yeah I will go to the loo</u>
<u n="173" who="S0619">okay er</u>
<u n="174" who="S0618">are doing the pause thing</u>
<u n="175" who="S0619">say bye</u>
<u n="176" who="S0618">bye</u>
<u n="177" who="S0619">bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
