<text id="SV4W">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:11:53</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0444</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Restaurant - Oxford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Food, habits, friends, relationships, work, future planning. </topics>
		<activity>Long over-due catch-up with old friend.  </activity>
		<conv_type>Disciussing, Explaining, Inquiring, Complaining, inviting, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0444">
				<exactage>25</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Oxford, UK</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Pearson marketing executive</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439">yeah do you like do you think that you are you looking for new jobs and stuff?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh it's it's still on track like it's I'm still on track to be looking at different things and</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0444">whatever like a recruiter got in touch this week and was like hey there's a job in <anon type="place"/> do you want it? no</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do I want a job where I already work?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="8" who="S0444">they were like oh yeah but I thought you'd be on at least kind of this amount of money I was like yeah me too</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">yeah I work in publishing what do you expect?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah like no</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">I'm making no money</u>
<u n="12" who="S0444">yeah erm so yeah but I think it's just it's just it was originally like September was my kind of deadline for definitely going but now I'm kind of like yeah maybe it's more likely to be December</u>
<u n="13" who="S0439">yeah cos these</u>
<u n="14" who="S0444" trans="overlap">because obviously I need to wait for <unclear/> come in I want to be well and working or better and working just alright</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah and it always always takes longer to get a job than what you expect</u>
<u n="16" who="S0444">yeah exactly it's that kind of thing where you know I've got to <vocal desc="cough"/> I've got to at least try and see what this new structure is like and if it's not what I like then er I've got a a valid reason to leave it isn't just I don't like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0444">you do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">yeah no definitely</u>
<u n="20" who="S0444">I I don't need a valid reason but it's just I don't know it's that kind of thing where</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0444">so much has changed that I'm kind of like let's see what it's like first it might actually be better cos they're putting more people on the subject or whatever it doesn't mean that I'm going to want to stay any longer but it means that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439" trans="overlap">how long is your notice period?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0444">two months</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="26" who="S0444">that's why so it's that kind of thing where I'm like okay</u>
<u n="27" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0444">that's why the like originally it was kind of September so obviously it's not September now</u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">I know September is creeping up so quickly my housemate the other day asked me what am I doing for Christmas? I was like it's July?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0444">so when is the lease on your flat?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0439">January</u>
<u n="32" who="S0444">January</u>
<u n="33" who="S0439">it did we it was six months then we extended it for another six months erm and so it's till Christmas till January but erm actually also a part of me is contemplating going to Australia</u>
<u n="34" who="S0444">what? what?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="36" who="S0444">every single time I see you there's a new plan I'm like what? I <unclear/> going to be the last one</u>
<u n="37" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know it's cos well cos one of my friends is she's living with erm she's living in <anon type="place"/> at the moment and she's erm she's Australian and her visa expires next June</u>
<u n="38" who="S0444">okay</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439">and she was like yeah come back with me and I was like oh yeah and then I was like actually maybe I could come back with you <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I'm just like contemplating whether to go back to Australia with her dunno could be fun</u>
<u n="40" who="S0444">right are you giving up the master's do you reckon?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">I think so I don't think it's worth the money if I can't get enough out of it it would have been fine but they moved the exam a month forward</u>
<u n="42" who="S0444" trans="overlap">especially if you have a life oh no oh no</u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">before my training</u>
<u n="44" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello</u>
<u n="45" who="S0444">hi</u>
<u n="46" who="S0439" trans="overlap">hi</u>
<u n="47" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">are you ready to order?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0439">yeah please could we have</u>
<u n="49" who="S0444">two Bellinis</u>
<u n="50" who="S0439">yeah two Bellinis er and then can I have the erm the the ham hock and chicken pie please?</u>
<u n="51" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah did you want any potatoes with that? cos it doesn't come with potato</u>
<u n="52" who="S0439">er no I'm good thank you it's fine</u>
<u n="53" who="S0444">and can I get the chargrilled</u>
<u n="54" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">minute steak</u>
<u n="55" who="S0444" trans="overlap">steak yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">did you want anything else?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0444">er</u>
<u n="58" who="S0439">can I get some</u>
<u n="59" who="S0444">can I get some</u>
<u n="60" who="S0439">yeah shall we have some green beans?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0444">yeah can I get some green beans with that?</u>
<u n="62" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah okay brilliant</u>
<u n="63" who="S0439">no I'm good</u>
<u n="64" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">do you want some water for the table?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0439">oh yeah that'd be great thank you</u>
<u n="66" who="S0444">yes please</u>
<u n="67" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0444">thank you very much</u>
<u n="69" who="S0439" trans="overlap">thanks very much I dunno it's just like with all my running training</u>
<u n="70" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">I have to run like three or four times a week and erm and I just don't know if they had left the the exam until the end of September I would have given it my best shot because it was after the Great North Run but I'd already signed up to do the Great North Run</u>
<u n="72" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0439">and I can't commit to I can't commit to it all it's too it's knackering me so and it I I had to pay another the next lump sum of money in August and I was like I don't feel comfortable paying out that much money and not doing it value so I'm going to revaluate and hopefully do it like actually do it as like a proper degree I think so</u>
<u n="74" who="S0444" trans="overlap">how are your mum and dad?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0439">er mumsie and dadsie are okay they are at the moment they are in well they're going to Wales tomorrow for a week and they're taking my grandma with them to WalesWales</u>
<u n="76" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah yeah Wales</u>
<u n="77" who="S0439">and then they are going coming back for like three days</u>
<u n="78" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439">and then going to Stockholm for a week so</u>
<u n="80" who="S0444">fair enough</u>
<u n="81" who="S0439">yeah I know they</u>
<u n="82" who="S0444">is that just their little holiday kind of thing?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0439">yeah it's weird it's like the moment that me and my sister sod off they like start you know like being crazy yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0444" trans="overlap">having a life</u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">and going on holiday and stuff</u>
<u n="86" who="S0444">why couldn't they be crazy when you know you were around?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0439">cos they had kids and they didn't have enough money <unclear>more or less</unclear> but</u>
<u n="88" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so how is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0439">she's actually a bit sad this week erm she you know she's got polycystic ovaries?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439">well basically she's been having to take hormones to reduce the tumours on her ovaries</u>
<u n="92" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0439">erm because they they're getting too big and they need to be op they might have to be operated on</u>
<u n="94" who="S0444">right okay</u>
<u n="95" who="S0439">erm so she's taking these hormones to try and shrink them but they're kind of all messing with her other hormones so</u>
<u n="96" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439">her serotonin levels were all up in the air place everything is going a bit haywire in her body and she's not she wasn't very happy this week I think she was a bit miserable but I rang I spoke obviously when I spoke to dad earlier he said he spoke to her and she was okay</u>
<u n="98" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah okay that's good</u>
<u n="99" who="S0439">so I'm hoping that she's alright I think she will be she's always an upbeat person it's just</u>
<u n="100" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's just that kind of getting used to it and</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">it's just yeah hormone changes so</u>
<u n="102" who="S0444">I mean come on if the if the pill can turn people crazy</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="104" who="S0444">then you know imagine what an actual full-on dose of hormones will do</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="106" who="S0444">like are you going to see her at some point soon?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0439">yeah we're hoping to go down for the last weekend in August the Bank Holiday weekend my mum's got some erm my mum and dad buy like ten tickets on the Eurostar</u>
<u n="108" who="S0444">okay yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">every year like a package erm and she's still got a few of those left left over to use so we're going to drive down in the that last Bank Holiday weekend and go visit her</u>
<u n="110" who="S0444">nice</u>
<u n="111" who="S0439">which will be very nice I love going to Paris and I miss it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0439">but I'm going to Barcelona</u>
<u n="114" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">I am going to Barcelona thank you</u>
<u n="116" who="S0444">when are you going?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439">erm my birthday weekend</u>
<u n="118" who="S0444">and who are you going with?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0439">me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the Australian and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the other Australian</u>
<u n="120" who="S0444">oh that'll be fun</u>
<u n="121" who="S0439">it'll be good it will be really fun</u>
<u n="122" who="S0444" trans="overlap">have you booked where you're staying yet?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439">no no no literally <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos they're Australian they've come over and they're only over for a certain amount of time they're trying to like make the most of being in Europe so they're travelling they do a lot of it so they've been to Greece they've been</u>
<u n="124" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah have you got any set plans and dates?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">er like they've done quite a lot thank you erm and they want to go to Barcelona and they were I was like well do you mind if I come next time? you know if you're going and she literally rang me on Thursday and was like me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are booking these flights if you want to come you know you're welcome to</u>
<u n="126" who="S0444">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439">and they and I rang <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and was like shall we go to Barcelona? and she was like yes so we randomly booked flights like that night but it was really weird they've gone for the flight on the afternoon of the Friday at four o'clock and they're coming back the afternoon of the Sunday so they're literally getting a day and like a day and a half there</u>
<u n="128" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I mean I've done that I have done that it is like feasible but it you've just got to choose what you want to do</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah but exactly but me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we booked the flights cos I had the day in lieu anyway so I'm taking the Friday off and we booked flights on the Thursday night and they were like thirty quid cheaper to go on the Thursday night and to come back on the Sunday</u>
<u n="130" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so why wouldn't you go then?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">cos you'd have to take a half day or a whole day on the Friday anyway because</u>
<u n="132" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah exactly where are you flying from?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0444">yeah you</u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">but you have to get to <anon type="place"/> for what like one o'clock two o'clock and if the flight's at four you know you still have to take like a half day and stuff so I was like me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just we're just like it doesn't make any sense and like yeah we had to pay for an extra night</u>
<u n="136" who="S0444">but</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439">but extra night or a <trunc>fl</trunc> more expensive flight you know? so yeah I'm going to Barcelona</u>
<u n="138" who="S0444">nice <pause dur="short"/> I love Barcelona</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">I have never been and I'm so excited</u>
<u n="140" who="S0444">I mean I am not your template of what to do in Barcelona so</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't want to know what you got up to in Barcelona</u>
<u n="142" who="S0444">no I I just drank sangria and had tapas sitting on the beach and walked</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's what me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are going to do apparently the beach isn't very good</u>
<u n="144" who="S0444">I quite liked it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439" trans="overlap">was it nice? I really want to see the sun go down</u>
<u n="146" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">sounds really sad I realise but</u>
<u n="148" who="S0444">no that's quite oh the let me know when you're well obviously you let me know when you're going but I think my guide book is hidden somewhere but I will try and root it out but you know there are there are lot of kind of cafes and things by the beach and then there's like a cable car that you can take</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/> I've heard the cable car yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0444">that's good because the cable car if you take it from the beach side over to the park you go near a rooftop bar that's actually quite nice cos you can see all obviously but you land pretty much there</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0444">so me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were like oh let's take a look at what this bar is like and it was actually alright so it was like</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">love a rooftop bar</u>
<u n="154" who="S0444">you know and you just look over the beach but you see the rest of Barcelona so it's like oh yeah that's that one that's that one that's that one</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439">that's cool</u>
<u n="156" who="S0444">cos obviously we didn't have we had what like a day and a half pretty much there</u>
<u n="157" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah cos that's why so me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have two and a half days and then I think in a way we're kind of happy that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are coming the next day because like we're not sure really what they want to do and we want to see some more cultural things and we're not sure if they just want to go and get drunk or</u>
<u n="158" who="S0444">yeah it's the kind of thing that if you want to go and see the Gaudi or you want to see some of the art museums then you can do</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah which I want to do</u>
<u n="160" who="S0444">like that was the bit that I couldn't do</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0444">like I managed to see some of the stuff but not all of it I still would <trunc>re</trunc> really recommend going and seeing the fountain</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439">are you which fountain?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0444">the <foreign lang="spa">Font magica</foreign>? I can never pronounce it but it's the one with the lights and the</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">ah I love a good old flashing <trunc>la</trunc> erm fountain</u>
<u n="166" who="S0444">it's it's better than Vegas</u>
<u n="167" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'm so sad really?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439">oh okay I'm going to see that</u>
<u n="170" who="S0444">erm basically what we did was go <vocal desc="cough"/> like six o'clock we went on the cable car drank on the rooftop bar walked through the park to then find the museum where there's all the kind of waterfalls and fountains and then at the bottom of those cascades it's the big fountain and then all the cascades</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'll have to have a look at it and does it go off like <trunc>e</trunc></u>
<u n="172" who="S0444">yeah regular like every half an hour fifteen minutes something like that so</u>
<u n="173" who="S0439" trans="overlap">regularly okay</u>
<u n="174" who="S0444">so yeah it's constant pretty much</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0444">it's tourist mad</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439">yeah I can imagine I can imagine it's rammed it would be quite nice to go at like eleven o'clock though like at night when it's not as busy</u>
<u n="178" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and it's actually cos like you know all we saw a few places that they're used to people coming at ten like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I ate pizza at at one in the morning</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439">yeah I can imagine I really can imagine but like me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> get there really late on the Thursday we get there like eleven o'clock</u>
<u n="180" who="S0444">that'll be fine</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">well that's what I thought and me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were like well we're going to be tired but at least we can have a lie in the next day and just explore and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will arrive at like eight or nine o'clock the next day and stuff so we have the whole day to ourselves and like to chill and drink and just relax and so I'm really excited about it</u>
<u n="182" who="S0444">and you get some sunshine</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">exactly and it's my birthday weekend where is there better to turn twenty-four?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you need to you need to learn thank you</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">thank you that's great</u>
<u n="186" who="S0444">you need to learn it's my birthday in Spanish</u>
<u n="187" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's my birthday cheers whoo</u>
<u n="188" who="S0444" trans="overlap">cheers my dear</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">happy birthday for tomorrow</u>
<u n="190" who="S0444">thank you dearest thank you for making the effort to come</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ooh this is nice oh no please don't thank me</u>
<u n="192" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I know you don't think it's an <trunc>e</trunc>effort but you know what I mean like there aren't many friends who would you know drive and leave work early some friends might but</u>
<u n="193" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I didn't come here for you I came here because I got to leave an hour early <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0444">very much better</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">yeah don't think it's because of you it's because I wanted to leave early I was like okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0444">that's fine you just you just wanted you just wanted to see me make a twit of myself falling down the stairs</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">I didn't no</u>
<u n="198" who="S0444" trans="overlap">at the concert which is possibly quite likely</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it'll be fine it'll be <trunc>fi</trunc> it'll be really nice to see you</u>
<u n="200" who="S0444" trans="overlap">sorry I'm just like ah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439">I know there's randomly chickens wandering around but erm I know like I don't come across as the most like I won't mock let's just say that I won't mock or anything</u>
<u n="202" who="S0444">yeah I know</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439">I'll get involved</u>
<u n="204" who="S0444">you you will get involved</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">I might mock a little bit but I will get involved at the same time</u>
<u n="206" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I am I am I am fully prepared for the mocking I've just had your voice in my head going oh god like <unclear/> the time</u>
<u n="207" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> if you see me in the audience with my head in my hands going like oh god</u>
<u n="208" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah or I can just imagine you will just say something to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that will crack them up and I'll be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> something inappropriate like usual</u>
<u n="210" who="S0444">yeah probs</u>
<u n="211" who="S0439">I know it's not my fault I'm just an inappropriate person</u>
<u n="212" who="S0444">you are but we love you for it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0439">yeah I know where the line is and occasionally I cross it but most of the time I I I do hold back</u>
<u n="214" who="S0444">ah no you'll be <trunc>al</trunc> you'll be you'll be more than fine you know you will you'll be especially if my parents are next to you</u>
<u n="215" who="S0439">yes exactly we went em me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> after last Friday night we saw each other on the Saturday and then we saw each other on the Sunday as well we went out for dinner on the Sunday and we all like oh we're so tired had a whole weekend of socialising and there was this girl on the Saturday night who was awful we were trying to explain her to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't out with us and she was this Essex girl and she was like had a awful accent she <trunc>ha</trunc> she wasn't wearing a bra</u>
<u n="216" who="S0444" trans="overlap">really? oh god</u>
<u n="217" who="S0439">I know you're like boobs everywhere she was like really like chavvy looking and she was like do you think with a figure like this I've had children? and we're like whoa okay erm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0444">forward</u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">erm exactly and she was just awful and erm so me when me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> met up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on Saturday she was like how is on Sunday she was like oh how was your <trunc>sa</trunc>Saturday night and stuff? and we were like well there was this really annoying girl and then as like the evening got on and on we started talking more <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just turned round and said like you know what those girls their their names were like complete stripper names and you know when you just hit a point where you know the proper bitching can start</u>
<u n="220" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439">like we'd all kind of been like tiptoeing around the proper bitching</u>
<u n="222" who="S0444">yeah and it was like bam</u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">and it's like bam we can now officially bitch <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was so good</u>
<u n="224" who="S0444">the seal has been broken</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">yeah cos we were all kind of just like yeah it was okay you know there's this girl but she's a bit annoying and you know like and like not her other friends like they were her there was this girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her friends were called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or something like that and we were just like they're literally prostitute names</u>
<u n="226" who="S0444">there's a have you seen Ted? the film Ted?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">oh yeah I have yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0444">and you seen the bit where he reels off <unclear/> prostitute that's what it's making me think of</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah exactly and I felt awful like with the Essex girl but like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hated her for some reason as well just like</u>
<u n="230" who="S0444">really?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">cos she just gave off this like amazingly common vibe you know like you don't want to judge people</u>
<u n="232" who="S0444">but yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0439">but she just made it so easy to because she was just so ridiculously common and Essex</u>
<u n="234" who="S0444" trans="overlap">stereotypical</u>
<u n="235" who="S0439">it was horrible</u>
<u n="236" who="S0444">note to self <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> must never move to Essex</u>
<u n="237" who="S0439">oh my god I think I'd die if I moved it's like you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0444">is he in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0439">yeah he was in <anon type="place"/> he was the one who got told off or not told off he was the one who like threatened his ex-girlfriend to beat her up and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's had like children with multiple women it's ridiculous but he's absolutely beautiful he's like got a stunning body erm and</u>
<u n="240" who="S0444">okay cos that forgives everything</u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">yeah obviously he's he's gorgeous like ah but he's from Essex so literally the moment he opens his mouth I feel like I want to like stab myself in the face <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was just like</u>
<u n="242" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll look at you but don't speak</u>
<u n="243" who="S0439">it's like yeah I would go on a date with you and just look at you but you just don't talk to me <vocal desc="laugh"/> not that I'm going on a date with him obviously cos you know</u>
<u n="244" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mapped it all out in her head</u>
<u n="245" who="S0439" trans="overlap">in my head it's all mapped out we'd have the perfect relationship if he never spoke <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0444">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh I've missed you</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he is a <trunc>be</trunc> he's got muscles and tattoos and a tan and</u>
<u n="248" who="S0444">oh no no no no no</u>
<u n="249" who="S0439">oh he's beautiful</u>
<u n="250" who="S0444">uh</u>
<u n="251" who="S0439">not that I'm superficial or anything</u>
<u n="252" who="S0444">no but a man has to look you know presentable</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="254" who="S0444">what's been going on with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0444">has he has he kind of called it off after the whole kind of flirty but then</u>
<u n="257" who="S0439">yeah what was the</u>
<u n="258" who="S0444" trans="overlap">really bitchy</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439" trans="overlap">when was what was the last thing I told you?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0444">so like you'd kind of been like er you know us being like yeah he's just being you know an idiot cos he's been really flirty and then he was like raving about his girlfriend it was like dude just</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I told him obviously to back off it was really inappropriate and then last week I don't know if I told you this he sent me a message being like oh yeah I'm sorry I haven't replied to you I'm moving into our apartment</u>
<u n="262" who="S0444">yeah that's yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah and I was just like okay and then he's like yeah I'm moving in with my girlfriend and like and he was like oh yeah I told her she was really brave and I was like some would say brave others would say stupid</u>
<u n="264" who="S0444" trans="overlap">say stupid</u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">each to their own and that was you know was the last thing he said cos he was like we're not all cynical like you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like I'm not cynical I just it's to nothing to do with cynicism I just don't trust people who give me a reason not to and I just left it at that cos it's basically just like I don't trust you</u>
<u n="266" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="268" who="S0444">and if there's and if you're going to be friends can you really be friends with someone you can't trust?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0439">it's just I just feel so sorry for his girlfriend like she's moving in with him and everything and then he's just like flirting with other people</u>
<u n="270" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I don't yeah I can't believe she moved from Australia she's moving in with him like I don't know</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439">it just it just makes me feel a bit embarrassed for her</u>
<u n="272" who="S0444">yeah but also not being funny but she's been with him for how long now?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0439">not even a year</u>
<u n="274" who="S0444">but long enough to be able to see through things</u>
<u n="275" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0444">it's long enough to pick up a vibe</u>
<u n="277" who="S0439">like no no</u>
<u n="278" who="S0444">and you don't know this girl and you don't know whether she's his equivalent</u>
<u n="279" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no not at all</u>
<u n="280" who="S0444">like you know what I mean? like you just don't know</u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">mm you just yeah it's kind of one of those things like if if my if I was seeing somebody and they were sending ex their ex text messages that he was sending me even though none of them were horrendously explicit</u>
<u n="282" who="S0444">yeah no</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">I still wouldn't be happy</u>
<u n="284" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was still like I remember like on the night that he asked or the day that he asked me out like the night before was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday so it was the kind of thing that comes up oh so-and-so has a birthday so I was like click on the profile it was like oh I shouldn't have done that like had a look through it but I was like er okay whatever</u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0444">and I was like do I send a message? because I've never gone a time without sending a message but I don't want to</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and it's and because because Facebook highlights it kind of one of those things that if I don't do it</u>
<u n="288" who="S0444">yeah but it's one of those weird things</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's so obvious</u>
<u n="290" who="S0444">so I look through the profile then decided not to but I kind of told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he was like er why did you why did you check it? and obviously started thinking why is she worried worried about her ex or whatever? so</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0444">so you know it's that I don't know like</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439">exes especially for like how long you were going or you were seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how long I was seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like they're always going to be important I think</u>
<u n="294" who="S0444">yeah if</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">but</u>
<u n="296" who="S0444">like I was thinking like you know if if they were ever in trouble we would try and help them but</u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">yeah of course</u>
<u n="298" who="S0444">we've both kind of drawn a line and been like no I'm never going back there again I think like</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah that's actually I</u>
<u n="300" who="S0444">we've both moved on</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439" trans="overlap">on yeah and in Harper Lee's book it was in like her new one it's really good erm there's one line that says erm the other woman has turned into the psychiatrist's couch or men make men make the other woman a psychiatrist couch and I was like</u>
<u n="302" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that is so right</u>
<u n="304" who="S0444">that and that is what you were becoming like</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah exactly <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was literally just coming to me with his problems and asking me to solve them</u>
<u n="306" who="S0444">that's not your job</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="308" who="S0444">if you had that as a job you would get paid for it</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">yeah and sadly I didn't get paid anything for it</u>
<u n="310" who="S0444">mm just just memories</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">just yeah it's like yeah I always would kind of like be interested in what's going on in his life you know like</u>
<u n="312" who="S0444">yeah you care about him</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">but I don't want to I don't I don't you know when you knew that you love someone and you have those feelings I know that I don't love him anymore</u>
<u n="314" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">and I know if I met him I wouldn't love him cos that's how I felt like I knew the other week cos when me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on Thursday that it wasn't really working and he kind of agreed and then we met up on the Saturday night</u>
<u n="316" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439">and this other girl in my friendship group was like really outrageously flirting with him and I realised if I had really liked him it would have bothered me and it didn't really bother me I was a little annoyed but not like</u>
<u n="318" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but not like hugely</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439" trans="overlap">massively yeah like you know if you really fancy somebody</u>
<u n="320" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">you go out of your way to be like around them and</u>
<u n="322" who="S0444">who is that? yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">yeah exactly it's really weird cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> fancies this guy who has a girlfriend and stuff</u>
<u n="324" who="S0444">okay okay</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">and she's just like really like infatuated with him properly infatuated with him she knows she can't do anything but it's so funny cos she's like I went to this barbecue just cos I thought he was going to be there and he wasn't there</u>
<u n="326" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah ah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439">and I was like ah but that's the kind of things you do if you really like someone isn't it? like</u>
<u n="328" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah it is</u>
<u n="329" who="S0439">I remember when I was at school and I fancied this guy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">and I literally used to like know his timetable schedule</u>
<u n="332" who="S0444">oh my god</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">so like when I was in a class he was I knew where he would be</u>
<u n="334" who="S0444" trans="overlap">stalking that's where the trouble starts</u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">well cos there was like certain classes where we like clashed or something or where like he would be somewhere where I would be and like I'd bump into him and stuff</u>
<u n="336" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah see that's okay I I stayed behind for DT coursework sessions just so I could talk to the guy that I kind of liked</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">yep</u>
<u n="338" who="S0444">yep</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439">we all do things like this</u>
<u n="340" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0444">standard</u>
<u n="342" who="S0439">very very weird</u>
<u n="343" who="S0444">yeah I miss being in school though there was a I didn't realise but er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but like erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had a girl in on work experience</u>
<u n="344" who="S0439">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0444">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had kind of said oh yeah we'll go out for lunch et cetera and er I hadn't realised that she wasn't actually a student she was an A Level</u>
<u n="346" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0444">student I was like so what are you saying? she was like I'm still dong my ASs I was like okay</u>
<u n="348" who="S0439">wow</u>
<u n="349" who="S0444">so I was like oh they've taken on someone young for work experience but hey it's probably just a work experience week</u>
<u n="350" who="S0439" trans="overlap">how long is the work of it's for the summer isn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0444" trans="overlap">like the work <trunc>ex</trunc> well it'd work experience week I think like you know just one of those things towards the end of term but erm I was like oh okay conversation changes</u>
<u n="352" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> er yeah how not to be inappropriate around a seventeen-year-old <vocal desc="laugh"/> but then again like a seventeen-year-olds are probably</u>
<u n="353" who="S0444">you know what</u>
<u n="354" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I know what I was like at seventeen</u>
<u n="355" who="S0444">oh my gosh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is so <pause dur="short"/> but but to say that she's got a mum that is tricky</u>
<u n="356" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she's what?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0444">to say she's got a mum that is <unclear>flaky</unclear></u>
<u n="358" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0444">lovely but flaky she's got such a level head on her shoulders</u>
<u n="360" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0444">I kid you not she was kind of she was kind of like mm I'm not sure about what I want to do I want to make sure that the degree that I choose is the one that I want to do</u>
<u n="362" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0444">cos she thought about doing graphic design and then a couple of weeks ago she turned round to me and she went no I think I want to do like European law with French or something</u>
<u n="364" who="S0439">wow</u>
<u n="365" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and I was like wow that's a bit of a change but what is it that you know? and she's kind of like well I need to get these grades and I was like well have you looked at these unis or have you googled this search term or this search term? and I was sat with her with all the university stuff and it was really it was really good and she has got a really level head like level head on her shoulders which is really good but I have no idea what's going on with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so basically</u>
<u n="366" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah what is going on with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so she's said I didn't have a clue that's why I was trying to kind of figure it out but like the guy was there and it was like well</u>
<u n="368" who="S0439">so weird so she was seeing some other guy so how long ago? that was like two weeks ago</u>
<u n="369" who="S0444" trans="overlap">right so she's been she's been like no so she's she's still with the guy that she was with a couple of months ago or a year ago or so she she's still with him obviously off and on</u>
<u n="370" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0444">but they got back together after their big break up and what have you and blah blah blah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0444">and then all of a sudden she's she through Facebook reconnects with this guy who was her friend from school</u>
<u n="374" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="375" who="S0444">turns out he's living in London great so they meet up they live in they when she goes to London they have a great time he comes to Oxford they have a great time erm and then you know she's been talking to me and she's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think I'm falling for him I was like okay</u>
<u n="376" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="377" who="S0444">and er but then obviously her boyfriend is still in the picture and then it's like okay then and then so this guy turned up they'd been skyping like every day and talking to each other all the time that they can so obviously like they like each other erm and I thought everything was going well like not as in like I don't know I didn't know whether they had crossed those lines or not or whether they were just hanging out but everything seemed okay he seems he seems like a nice guy he did all the washing up he says hi he's talkative</u>
<u n="378" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm so is that the guy who was there tonight?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0444">yes so erm and and he gets on with the kids like I think it's just like you know he's just my friend and I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's fine</u>
<u n="380" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0444">erm and then when she came back in that's why I was a bit like okay erm cos obviously it looked like she'd been <trunc>cr</trunc> like crying and I was like okay and then when I walked out the first time the guy was there and I was like alright what what's going on? he's still around but he's a bit I don't know and then like when I came back in she was in the kitchen and I was like are you okay? she just started crying she was like I'm just so tired</u>
<u n="382" who="S0439">what tonight?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0444">yeah as in like when I was coming back to get the washing cos I was like she's not okay and the kids aren't in I I hope that it's not you know nothing like</u>
<u n="384" who="S0439">major yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0444" trans="overlap">major erm so that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0439">so is she over with the boyfriend?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0444">no I don't know what the status is with the boyfriend</u>
<u n="388" who="S0439">this woman gets so much action it's ridiculous like how like she's a very good looking woman but still wow</u>
<u n="389" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but it's like I was like I was thinking it's such a it's such a hard thing if you've got like a man and this is the case I was thinking this earlier like and one of the other girls that I went to uni with absolutely stunningly beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful but they can never find the right guy because the guys that throw themselves at them and they're so adoring of them that they will mistake that for love or something different and then you know it's always hard to tell but yeah so I I don't particularly know what's going on cos she just went <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm so tired and started crying and went I'll talk to you about it later I was like alright you know where I am but you know obviously she won't come and talk to me about it</u>
<u n="390" who="S0439">oh no no welcome to like go and have a long chat with her don't worry about me</u>
<u n="391" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh no but she she won't no but she probably won't do if he's still staying</u>
<u n="392" who="S0439">oh yeah if he's staying over yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I don't I don't know whether it is to do with the boyfriend I don't know whether it's to do with the guy I don't know whether it's to do with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but she kind of no offence but she kind of always puts herself in these predicaments</u>
<u n="395" who="S0444">oh she so does like</u>
<u n="396" who="S0439">like she doesn't help herself it's just like</u>
<u n="397" who="S0444">this is what I was thinking I was like you know but I can understand it though because you know she is beautiful she's very talkative she's very sociable she's very chatty she's very amiable and she knows how to work people</u>
<u n="398" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0444">erm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0439">charismatic</u>
<u n="401" who="S0444">very very very charismatic and you know? I just I just don't know but I just hope that she's okay I'm just like she doesn't half run herself through the emotional mill like</u>
<u n="402" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0444">you know she was finally starting to get on her feet like she was made redundant and whatever</u>
<u n="404" who="S0439">yeah has she got a job now?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0444">yeah yeah yeah she's working at the university and that's going really well but</u>
<u n="406" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh cool</u>
<u n="407" who="S0444">it's it's the kind of thing where you know she's really put her back on her feet she was like no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm going to focus on me I'm going to focus on the kids I'm gonna be a better mother I'm going to be this this this and I was like cool alright</u>
<u n="408" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0444">so we'll just we'll just see I hope she's okay but it's probably just one of those things that'll blow over maybe it's not maybe it will be but I've <trunc>be</trunc> I've been through the waves enough times</u>
<u n="410" who="S0439">yeah I can imagine</u>
<u n="411" who="S0444">yeah okay</u>
<u n="412" who="S0439">drama</u>
<u n="413" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but you know it <trunc>do</trunc> it doesn't mean that you care about that person any less and you'll still go with them through any dramas that they will be but</u>
<u n="414" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah of course</u>
<u n="415" who="S0444">you know I'm just it's just you know and you've said this yourself it's hard to see someone in a situation where they're just going to hurt themselves but you know so we'll see but I don't think she probably won't confide in me or say anything until he's gone</u>
<u n="416" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah no yeah course yeah yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you know we'll see</u>
<u n="418" who="S0439">but how are you and Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? how's that going?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0439">is it all good?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0444">yeah he's he's good we're we're much better having time apart was actually really good</u>
<u n="422" who="S0439">yeah cos I know obviously the last time I saw you you were having a bit of a rough day with him?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh that's the yeah like yeah but I think we've kind of I think that's just the kind of thing where like I was still struggling with like you know what is an expectation of a relationship? what is a relationship? what what isn't a relationship? you know</u>
<u n="424" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0444">but erm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0439">I think a relationship is whatever you feel is comfortable for you and them at the time isn't it?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah exactly and to be honest we haven't really we haven't really figured it out or more to the point we didn't you know we understood that it would be different but we didn't understand how it would be different and it's the kind of thing that you know with communication it's like well I'm going to fly off the handle or like you know</u>
<u n="428" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0444">or you know and I think it's that kind of thing just been like actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all so the expectations that you have get rid of them because they're not in the situation it doesn't mean that you shouldn't aim for things or you know want things but all the expectations or baggage that you have from somebody else get rid of them</u>
<u n="430" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0444">you know? cos it's the kind of thing that like oh this is was different a lot of the time it wasn't like I was being clingy but I was constantly aware that at some point <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might turn around and not want to be with me especially when I got really quite erm</u>
<u n="432" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">minute steak</u>
<u n="433" who="S0444">yes please</u>
<u n="434" who="S0439">er ooh yum</u>
<u n="435" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">there you go</u>
<u n="436" who="S0439">that looks amazing thank you</u>
<u n="437" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's okay I'm just going to grab you a steak knife</u>
<u n="438" who="S0444">perfect thank you</u>
<u n="439" who="S0439">oh my god this looks so good</u>
<u n="440" who="S0444">do you want a chip?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0444">go for it I'm going to take a picture of it</u>
<u n="443" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="444" who="S0444">and send it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's on his erm mum's birthday meal so</u>
<u n="445" who="S0439">oh cool</u>
<u n="446" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">there you go</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439">oh my god this is so yummy</u>
<u n="448" who="S0444">cos before I'd have been like obviously he's <unclear/> but if he's got nothing else to do then why isn't he here? but then he was like it's my mum's birthday I was like yeah fair one</u>
<u n="449" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0444">I did not want her thinking that her erm birthday is less important than mine</u>
<u n="451" who="S0439">and also I was coming</u>
<u n="452" who="S0444" trans="overlap">erm oh yeah but we didn't know it at that point I was like oh yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no I'm kidding I'm kidding don't worry</u>
<u n="454" who="S0444">and then my parents went oh we're not coming until Saturday and I was like oh all good</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439">it was like on Friday night when I went out and got with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like why didn't you go back with him? I was like because I was going back with you and she was like what do you mean? I was like well I was I planned to go back with you</u>
<u n="456" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0439">you're my girlfriend</u>
<u n="458" who="S0444">so it's what you will do</u>
<u n="459" who="S0439">so that is what I will do yeah I'm not going to ditch you for a man what's going on here? mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0444">these chips are good mm thank you that's nice</u>
<u n="461" who="S0439">this is so nice I'm going to annihilate this so quickly say hi to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for me</u>
<u n="462" who="S0444">oh I will</u>
<u n="463" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> boy</u>
<u n="464" who="S0444">I was going to send a picture of the steak and be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says he and then I'm like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is not the steak</u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and the steak are one we are one thing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0444">right then he was like oh you're not going to talk to me tomorrow and I was like no I'll talk to you it'll just be a lot less than <unclear/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0439">yeah the thing is but like do you think? or no you're going out for dinner with your parents aren't you? but</u>
<u n="468" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0439">he can take you out for like a romantic thing on <trunc>Mo</trunc> Sunday? or you're going to go to <anon type="place"/> on Sunday are you alright?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0444">I'm going to <anon type="place"/> yeah sorry it's this cough I put a lot of salt on</u>
<u n="471" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0444">erm <pause dur="short"/> erm so I think tomorrow night we'll have a bit of time</u>
<u n="473" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0444">he knew what he was getting into when he went like I was kind of like are you sure? that's you know I was kind of like you know are you happy with that? like cos he was kind of like I'm just going to come up on the Saturday and leave on the Sunday cos he's not driving he's getting the <anon type="place"/> tube and I was like if you're sure you want to come up for a day and a bit feel free there's no pressure from me</u>
<u n="475" who="S0439">but you know with an hour it's <trunc>on</trunc> like it's not too far away is it?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0444">but it's more the fact that <pause dur="short"/> but no it's then getting out of London as well so</u>
<u n="477" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0444">it's more that kind of thing so I was like you know? just see how you go erm but erm yeah so we were talking about that we don't really know for sure but he said it's supposed to like you know but my clan have only been down to Oxford maybe once</u>
<u n="479" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0444">since I moved maybe twice <pause dur="short"/> and I'm never going to be a person to desert my family or friends they're always going to be more important</u>
<u n="481" who="S0439">mm I love how you call them your clan it's like such a northern thing to say</u>
<u n="482" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0439">my clan like William Wallis</u>
<u n="484" who="S0444">mm that and the parentals and the twinny have some green beans by the way</u>
<u n="485" who="S0439">be nice to see your twinny again</u>
<u n="486" who="S0444">mm twinny is doing well</u>
<u n="487" who="S0439">mm what what's twinny up to?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0444">she's still working at the primary school</u>
<u n="489" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0444">so they'll have just broken up today</u>
<u n="491" who="S0439">yay</u>
<u n="492" who="S0444">so she'll be happy about that she's also gone back to college and starting doing her maths and her English</u>
<u n="493" who="S0439">oh cool</u>
<u n="494" who="S0444">but starting from like the lowest levels</u>
<u n="495" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0444">but she's passed all her level one in English and been getting like top marks</u>
<u n="497" who="S0439">that's really good</u>
<u n="498" who="S0444">which is brilliant and she's actually you know she's going to <vocal desc="cough"/> college on time she's keeping loads of <unclear/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0439">are you alright?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0444">yeah just lots of salt</u>
<u n="501" who="S0439">mm that's really good bless her</u>
<u n="502" who="S0444">mm so yeah so she's got quite a lot of presents tomorrow</u>
<u n="503" who="S0439">I'm so so jealous like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s finished this week your sister has finished this week my mum has finished this week everybody's finished it's so annoying <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0444">if it makes you feel better I'm not</u>
<u n="505" who="S0439">yeah me neither <vocal desc="laugh"/> we can suffer together for the summer</u>
<u n="506" who="S0444">true</u>
<u n="507" who="S0439">although I love love love the fact that the roads are really really clear now</u>
<u n="508" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0439">that's the best thing about the summer</u>
<u n="510" who="S0444">mm I also <trunc>l</trunc> <trunc>fa</trunc> I also love the fact that I still get you on chat</u>
<u n="511" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0444">I love it how every single time there's a there's a note saying this person is not inside your organisation be careful what you say</u>
<u n="513" who="S0439">I know I'm like who cares? mm yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanders round our office now</u>
<u n="514" who="S0444">is that a bit weird?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0439">no he doesn't know who I am <pause dur="short"/> I always thought there was a rumour about him and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0444">I don't know</u>
<u n="517" who="S0439">I yeah but he's married with like children and stuff</u>
<u n="518" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="519" who="S0439">so I don't understand how that rumour can be true</u>
<u n="520" who="S0444">I erm on the train back from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0439">who did?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0444">on the train back from <anon type="place"/> guess who was two seats away from me?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0439">who?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0444">your favourite person with shoes</u>
<u n="525" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0444">mm mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0439">my favourite person oh with</u>
<u n="528" who="S0444">with shoes loves the shoes? also talks in a very loud accent</u>
<u n="529" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0444">yes</u>
<u n="531" who="S0439">oh god how did you accidently stumble across her?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I know I don't know it was a train in <anon type="place"/> it was like what are you doing up here like during the week?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0439">did you talk to her?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0444">kind of acknowledged each other and nodded</u>
<u n="535" who="S0439">yeah we're not going to sit together I don't want to spend my entire journey with you talking <pause dur="long"/> what does she even do now?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0444">head of the global learning programme</u>
<u n="537" who="S0439">wow sounds like an important title</u>
<u n="538" who="S0444" trans="overlap">whatever that is <pause dur="short"/> maybe I don't know what it is</u>
<u n="539" who="S0439">how is everyone? like is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still clocking along doing alright?</u>
<u n="540" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">how's it going guys?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0439">er really good I've nearly finished so yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0444" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="543" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's good</u>
<u n="544" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0439">are they making money? I assume they are</u>
<u n="546" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can be interested <unclear/> er qualifications things so</u>
<u n="547" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0444">so it's the kind of things where we don't know what our revenue's going to be for erm for a couple of years yet so</u>
<u n="549" who="S0439">people still loving <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? not liking him?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0444">I don't think there's much to <unclear/> on it to be honest</u>
<u n="551" who="S0439">really? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0444">we don't have as much contact with him as like the er like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or</u>
<u n="553" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0444">mainly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we have contact with</u>
<u n="555" who="S0439">good old <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0444">mm so yeah we've now got a tennis table table er a table tennis table</u>
<u n="557" who="S0439">really? where?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0444">you know as as you go out of reception?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0444">there's that little shady bit with the benches</u>
<u n="561" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0444">that little power station it's by there</u>
<u n="563" who="S0439">what like an outdoor one?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0439">oh cool so erm where you're sitting in the same place aren't you? you didn't move in the restructure?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0444">no no by everyone else who did</u>
<u n="567" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0444">like media research and marketing design are still in the same place as well</u>
<u n="569" who="S0439">I guess it's because media research was so small they didn't really know where to dump them then I guess actually project management was really small and they moved them</u>
<u n="570" who="S0444">mm do you talk to the team much?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0439">mm yeah I still contact I speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a bit cos I also have him on chat so I occasionally apparently <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is in a relationship with this guy so that's good</u>
<u n="572" who="S0444">which guy?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0439">I dunno just a guy she met I think he's quite old but</u>
<u n="574" who="S0444">oh okay</u>
<u n="575" who="S0439">you know each to their own erm everything's all ticking along apparently they're not erm re-recruiting for the project managers they're just leaving the three that there are and then they're going to let them literally just whittle down</u>
<u n="576" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="long"/> great</u>
<u n="577" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0444">what about the ones in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0439">erm ones in <anon type="place"/> erm that's still a big team but it's more corporate like they do all the corporate products they don't do products like <trunc>pro</trunc> like educational products they do like big <trunc>mo</trunc> like corporate projects and stuff like that <pause dur="long"/> so I have no idea</u>
<u n="580" who="S0444">would you like some more chips?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0439">I might nick a chip in a moment yes</u>
<u n="582" who="S0444">okay cos I'm going to pour them on my plate but</u>
<u n="583" who="S0439">I'm <trunc>so</trunc> I have literally annihilated this</u>
<u n="584" who="S0444" trans="overlap">just just grab</u>
<u n="585" who="S0439">I didn't even think I was this hungry <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="586" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="587" who="S0439">movie tonight are we movieing?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0444">maybe watch a movie I don't know how full we would be</u>
<u n="589" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0444">we'll have to choose something off Netflix</u>
<u n="591" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="592" who="S0444">er because my DVD player doesn't work</u>
<u n="593" who="S0439">to be fair Netflix has a lot of choice going on so I think we'll be fine</u>
<u n="594" who="S0444">unless you want to watch Celebrity MasterChef?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0439">strangely enough that actually sounds really funny</u>
<u n="596" who="S0444">I actually do love Celebrity MasterChef</u>
<u n="597" who="S0439">I really like MasterChef I'm always in denial about it but I really like it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0444">I love it I watched four episodes this week</u>
<u n="599" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0444">mm well what else am I supposed to do? I'm not allowed to go to the gym</u>
<u n="601" who="S0439">true <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0444">I can't go out massively socialising</u>
<u n="603" who="S0439">oh my god your social butterfly like inner self must be dying</u>
<u n="604" who="S0444">yeah but it's the kind of thing that on some level I know it's good for me</u>
<u n="605" who="S0439">mm definitely</u>
<u n="606" who="S0444">but also I knew that this weekend would be busy so</u>
<u n="607" who="S0439">yeah with all of us awesome people descending upon you <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0444">I was thinking that though just right before you arrive it's just you know how lucky I actually am you know? I have a nice group of people here but then you know friends like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0439" trans="overlap">me</u>
<u n="610" who="S0444">that are willing to travel and my clan and you know obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I'd never know what to class <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's not family and he's not a friend so</u>
<u n="611" who="S0439">he's your boyfriend</u>
<u n="612" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh he's my boyfriend oh damn it</u>
<u n="613" who="S0439">boyf</u>
<u n="614" who="S0444">I still get have to get used to that</u>
<u n="615" who="S0439">the boyf <pause dur="short"/> I think I have mini panic attacks every time I think of being in a relationship I'm twenty-three I can't deal with it</u>
<u n="616" who="S0444" trans="overlap">to be honest I <pause dur="short"/> I mean I am no expert and by no means do I think that it's perfect but</u>
<u n="617" who="S0439">whenever relationships are never <trunc>per</trunc> it's people who think that relationships should be perfect always the ones who are complete like morons</u>
<u n="618" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah I mean at the moment I make him happy he makes me happy we still have our own kind of lives it's the kind of thing where a lot of people are like oh so when are you going to move in together? it's like actually no we know that at some point we have to stop being <pause dur="short"/> completely separate people and have a life together but that time is not now like</u>
<u n="619" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="620" who="S0444">obviously we're together and we enjoy each other's company but it's I would never want to stand in the way of his career he would never want to stand in the way of mine</u>
<u n="621" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="622" who="S0444">he would never want to stand in the way of my friends and you know and I think that's the thing like it's a lot to do with the fact that like the expectation it wasn't even said it was kind of like oh I have to see you every week</u>
<u n="623" who="S0439">yeah exactly you definitely don't have to see that person every week</u>
<u n="624" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and it's like oh like and that's what I mean like we talk a lot but it's the kind of thing of knowing you know actually you know we went four weeks without seeing each other</u>
<u n="625" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="626" who="S0444">and you know it wasn't brilliant but</u>
<u n="627" who="S0439">it's not as bad as you think</u>
<u n="628" who="S0444">we were okay as soon as we saw each other we were you know we were okay and I mean I wasn't with it half the time anyway so you know you can't really judge but it was you think like we were both just like actually you know now that was know we can survive it</u>
<u n="629" who="S0439">I really enjoy having like time apart from people</u>
<u n="630" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it can it's more you know and it actually it's better to see people when you want to see them rather than when you feel like you have to</u>
<u n="631" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah cos then it becomes an obligation</u>
<u n="632" who="S0444">yeah and it's the kind of thing that I'm just like actually yeah to be fair when are you supposed to see your friends like you know? he doesn't have as many as me or you know meet them as often cos you know guy friendships are slightly different but</u>
<u n="633" who="S0439">yeah no but that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me like when I said to him like I'm not <trunc>re</trunc> you know something isn't working he's like no I agree something really isn't working but he turned around and said but I would still like to be your friend cos I actually don't have many friends in <anon type="place"/> I was like that's fine you know like I'm happy to be your friend I don't find it awkward you know like that's why I said to him I was like do you still want to go to this comedy thing together? cos we booked it when we were dating and he was like yeah I'd love to go and he came out on Saturday because I think people kind of don't really understand the importance of actually having friends</u>
<u n="634" who="S0444">definitely</u>
<u n="635" who="S0439">like I erm it was really good actually like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my housemate and like my best friend from school we obviously live together and like I we're having a girls' night next Friday we're going into town we're going out to dinner and she's going out into town with her some work colleagues</u>
<u n="636" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm mm oh okay</u>
<u n="637" who="S0439">and they're having a cocktail-making session at <anon type="place"/> but a lot of her work colleagues are like old so they're going to be going home quite early and she's still out and I was like well why don't you come out with us? you know come out with me and my girls you know like let's have fun have a girly night you get to meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you've never met her you know you get to meet the rest of my friends and she was like yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0444">but maybe that's a little bit intimidating though?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0439">well no no cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like she just doesn't do anything like erm last weekend her entire weekend was <trunc>ca</trunc> was erm the <anon type="place"/> big weekend it was three days of music festival chilling you know you sat in a park you ate drank just chilled with people listened to music had fireworks and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was over for one night and they didn't do anything they just went they just sat at home and I was like come to the big weekend there's fireworks it'll be a really awesome experience you know you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can get out of the house and she was like no we could but no and I was like okay fine and then I kind of I maybe was a bit sharp with her but I did it in a funny way I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come out with us on Friday because you know like you all you do is sit in your room and talk to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know like reality if you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> broke up</u>
<u n="640" who="S0444">what would you do?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0439">what would you do you know? you don't want to get back into that rut that you were before when you were going out and then you broke up and you kind of like she became really sociable again cos she didn't have a boyfriend and then the moment they got together she suddenly was like no no no I'm back with him I don't need my friends and I was like</u>
<u n="642" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah so what did she say to that? did she say anything to it?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0439">she didn't she was actually I thought she was going to go really angry about it actually but then the next night she came downstairs she sat in the kitchen with me for like a good two hours we had a really good nice like bond we had a really nice chat she was like oh yeah okay so next Friday you know I'm I'm really up for it I'll come out and meet your friends you know like we'll get a taxi back together it'll be really fun and I was like yeah this is my best like this is my friend I genuinely felt like I was losing her cos all she does is sit in her bedroom and talk to her boyfriend and it's just it's so nice to think that like you now that you <trunc>do</trunc> you appreciate the fact that you actually sometimes it's nice to have space and it's nice to just spend time with your friends</u>
<u n="644" who="S0444">and he said the and this is the thing he said the exact same thing not that either of us felt specifically but we were just like to be honest when we when we came into this neither of us wanted to you know give up our lives that we were having yes maybe less gallivanting for me would be good</u>
<u n="645" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0444">but it's like <unclear/> I regularly have you know the thinking that you said to your friend which was you know if I broke up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would my friendships still be the same?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0444">it's kind of well actually you've got to put the work in</u>
<u n="649" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0444">like you know and it's <unclear/> like you know my auntie and uncle in <anon type="place"/> I haven't seen well I haven't seen them in ages cos obviously when I was staying in <anon type="place"/> I was staying with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because you know he was a bit like oh why would you stay with them and not me? but then he kind of understands it's like but they're my family like I have to see them</u>
<u n="651" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0444">and I went <vocal desc="cough"/> so I I wasn't after you rang I was feeling fine and then all of a sudden it was like oh not feeling so good</u>
<u n="653" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="654" who="S0444">so I kind of stayed in bed most of the afternoon and I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm just going go to my auntie's cos I can rest there and then I'll go to <anon type="place"/> from central <anon type="place"/> in the morning you know so it all kind of worked out in the end</u>
<u n="655" who="S0439">yeah I'm so sorry about that</u>
<u n="656" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no no no I'm just like I think it's more I think it was like I said to you I was like I'm so because I'm being told not to overdo things</u>
<u n="657" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0444">or not to push through or not to do things I'm really hypersensitive to when other people say it so I was like don't like especially when it's things like your back I'm just like no cos if you ruin if you ruin that you could be ruined for months</u>
<u n="659" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I couldn't drive they day I did it like pushing the clutch down was so painful I tried basically to I nearly had to call someone to come and drive my car home for me I was in so much pain it's better now like it's a bit sore and a bit tender but I can move</u>
<u n="660" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0439">like the other day I genuinely couldn't even like bend down to like shave my legs it was horrible and like putting socks on like oh my god I never thought putting socks on would be a problem but it hurts so much</u>
<u n="662" who="S0444">no but that's what I mean you can't take that for granted it's just like you know I knew that you wouldn't make anything of it unless it was particularly bad like for you to ring me I knew you were ringing me because you were like I haven't heard from you or I rang you I was like sorry my phone was on silent and upstairs I'm terrible erm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0444">but erm when I rang you and you were like yeah I've hurt my back and I'm like yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wouldn't usually start a conversation about that</u>
<u n="665" who="S0439">I was so angry</u>
<u n="666" who="S0444">you were like you were like I'll do I'll come I'll come and I was like I love you but if you do that you're even more stupid than</u>
<u n="667" who="S0439">I was so angry about hurting it I was like it was my own stupidity completely</u>
<u n="668" who="S0444">it's just one of those things though</u>
<u n="669" who="S0439">yeah but</u>
<u n="670" who="S0444">you're getting better</u>
<u n="671" who="S0439">I am I did a session yesterday but he took it really really slow and everything so it was really nice erm yeah no it was good that you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are like doing well</u>
<u n="672" who="S0444">yeah we're okay like</u>
<u n="673" who="S0439">do you like are you really confident that it you're more than friends? like it's not yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0444">yeah like I mean he's really honest about it like he said a couple of weeks ago he was like look I know that that's one of the things that makes you different from being friends but you know I don't want that to be the only reason why you think that things are any different I'm like no it's not because the way that we are with each other it's it's it's not</u>
<u n="675" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0444">and you know I think that's one of the things you know there are days that you know he could be more</u>
<u n="677" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">are you all finished?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0439">yes thank you yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">how was everything?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0444">brilliant</u>
<u n="681" who="S0439">as you can see by the empty plates it was good</u>
<u n="682" who="S0444">it was disgusting</u>
<u n="683" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> vile</u>
<u n="684" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it was horrible</u>
<u n="685" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">did you want to see a dessert menu?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0444">please</u>
<u n="687" who="S0439">yes please</u>
<u n="688" who="S0444">I've been told that these desserts are pretty good so er</u>
<u n="689" who="S0439">they are</u>
<u n="690" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">they are amazing</u>
<u n="691" who="S0439">they are really good</u>
<u n="692" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you must come and give us all the recommendations apart from not everything on the menu</u>
<u n="693" who="S0439">a sample of everything</u>
<u n="694" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">chocolate sundae sticky toffee pudding</u>
<u n="695" who="S0439">I love sticky toffee pudding so much</u>
<u n="696" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh my god oh my word</u>
<u n="697" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">thank you</u>
<u n="699" who="S0439">thank you</u>
<u n="700" who="S0444">yeah but I mean like there are days when we feel more like your best friend than your like boyfriend but you know and</u>
<u n="701" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah of course yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0444">I've still got a lot to learn and he's still got a lot learn but actually you know I think it's more the fact that you know the thing is I know that if I fly off the handle he's not going to run away</u>
<u n="703" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0444">if I'm ill and I'm terrible and I look disgusting or you know I'm not feeling like me I'm not chirpy I'm not happy I'm not sociable cos he has you know he had me crying in his car many a time because I didn't want to go back to work erm and I didn't want to go back to <anon type="place"/> and I wanted to stay with him because that was where I felt like a normal human being erm you know he had to deal with that a lot and if a if a guy doesn't run with that and he blatantly tells you I am not running even though you tell him to</u>
<u n="705" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0444">you know it's like something that you get</u>
<u n="707" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he's a good boy</u>
<u n="708" who="S0444">more you get even more faith in what you have and it's the kind of thing that like you know it's just <trunc>re</trunc> you know it's <trunc>m</trunc> it's more now that I've stopped trying to overanalyse everything that things are actually a lot thank you</u>
<u n="709" who="S0439">thank you</u>
<u n="710" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">there you go</u>
<u n="711" who="S0439">great yeah it's all</u>
<u n="712" who="S0444">things are a lot easier so you know</u>
<u n="713" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's all just yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0444">we'll just we'll we'll see how it goes</u>
<u n="715" who="S0439">it's normally always to do with overanalysing things that's where it goes wrong I find anyway</u>
<u n="716" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you'll you'll love it I read Men Are from Mars Women Are from Venus and it explained a lot</u>
<u n="717" who="S0439">see I've read that book and I kind of part of me was like oh that makes sense and part of me was like oh this is complete bollocks</u>
<u n="718" who="S0444">yes that was my complete reaction and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like so what did you think about it? you know cos he knew that I would</u>
<u n="719" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0444">well I said the exact same thing I was like some of it I agree with some of it's absolute bollocks</u>
<u n="721" who="S0439">yeah some of it makes no sense</u>
<u n="722" who="S0444">and you know it's the perfect I I was I was quite sweet I did something quite sweet don't throw up you know it's the kind of thing that he says oh you know I think there's ninety-nine or a hundred and one ways to score points with a woman</u>
<u n="723" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0444">I was like here you go I don't agree with all these so here are the hundred and one ways that you score points with me so I wrote them all out while he was asleep</u>
<u n="725" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah a hundred and one?</u>
<u n="726" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0439">okay cos that's sad</u>
<u n="728" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and then he</u>
<u n="729" who="S0439">a hundred and one how how on earth is there a hundred and one things that score with you?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0444">cos it's just the small things like no it's not like</u>
<u n="731" who="S0439" trans="overlap">makes me a cup of tea</u>
<u n="732" who="S0444">all the things that you know have meant a lot like the fact that you know</u>
<u n="733" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0444">when I'm having a bad day he'll send me a picture of a bear waving he's like the bear still likes you</u>
<u n="735" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah no one else does but the bear does</u>
<u n="736" who="S0444">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="737" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0444">you know it's it's small things like that you know he's never going to be the world's biggest romantic speech writer</u>
<u n="739" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="740" who="S0444">but</u>
<u n="741" who="S0439">most men aren't though</u>
<u n="742" who="S0444">I'm starting to get used to the fact that you know he is not a girl</u>
<u n="743" who="S0439">yes</u>
<u n="744" who="S0444">he is not me</u>
<u n="745" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="746" who="S0444">as as great as he is</u>
<u n="747" who="S0439">men are not women</u>
<u n="748" who="S0444">he's not me yeah exactly and this is this is a lesson</u>
<u n="749" who="S0439">it is oh</u>
<u n="750" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah I I'm looking at the cheese menu why?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0439"><trunc>go</trunc> no no the dessert menu is at the top of that one you idiot it's there</u>
<u n="752" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh oh right it is oh god</u>
<u n="753" who="S0439">puddings <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0444">ah ooh</u>
<u n="755" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="756" who="S0444">ooh</u>
<u n="757" who="S0439">yum</u>
<u n="758" who="S0444">it will I'm really sad though the middle top line of the</u>
<u n="759" who="S0439">prosecco and peach jelly</u>
<u n="760" who="S0444">mm middle top line</u>
<u n="761" who="S0439">oh strawberry Eton mess</u>
<u n="762" who="S0444">yeah it's spelt wrong</u>
<u n="763" who="S0439">oh Eton's spelt wrong oh no Eton's supposed to be spelt wrong though I think it's supposed to be funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0444">is it? I don't know</u>
<u n="765" who="S0439">oh maybe not that's embarrassing if it is we'll go with it's supposed to be trying to be funny</u>
<u n="766" who="S0444">okay okay okay I'll go with you on that one</u>
<u n="767" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you think you've decided?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0439">did you decide? <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I think I have yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="770" who="S0439">what are you going to go for?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0444">er can I have the chocolate sundae please?</u>
<u n="772" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">you can</u>
<u n="773" who="S0439">can I have sticky toffee pudding please?</u>
<u n="774" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0439">can I also grab a coffee?</u>
<u n="776" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0439">erm do you want a coffee?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0444">I might do I'm just going to look now</u>
<u n="779" who="S0439">could I have a cappuccino please?</u>
<u n="780" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">you can</u>
<u n="781" who="S0439">thank you very much</u>
<u n="782" who="S0444">er can I get a decaf latte?</u>
<u n="783" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0439">a decaf latte?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0444">yeah I can't I can't have caffeine</u>
<u n="786" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="787" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm the same if I go out for dinner I have to have decaf as well otherwise I'll be awake till like three in the morning</u>
<u n="788" who="S0439">I was gonna ask for an extra shot <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah you have mine if you want them you can have mine</u>
<u n="790" who="S0439">okay so</u>
<u n="791" who="S0444">it's an ice cream van</u>
<u n="792" who="S0439">I know thank you</u>
<u n="793" who="S0444" trans="overlap">competition oh oh erm no I I actually you know can't eat or drink that many things with caffeine in them so</u>
<u n="794" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0444">you know coffee no no</u>
<u n="796" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I get that don't worry</u>
<u n="797" who="S0444">tea is also a no-no which is quite sad</u>
<u n="798" who="S0439">I was watching a Michael McIntyre episode not episode but like</u>
<u n="799" who="S0444">I love how the conversation is just so random</u>
<u n="800" who="S0439">I know I know our conversations just dot around don't they? and we'll kind of go off on a tangent and come back to what we were originally talking about</u>
<u n="801" who="S0444" trans="overlap">right let's start a serious conversation <unclear/></u>
<u n="802" who="S0439">Michael McIntyre</u>
<u n="803" who="S0444">Michael McIntyre</u>
<u n="804" who="S0439">well no he talks through caffeine it was like a sketch with him and he was talking about caffeine how like if your partner ever offered you a</u>
<u n="805" who="S0444">can you imagine him on caffeine?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0439">I know he's buzzing isn't he? but like he's like if your partner offers you a cup of coffee at eleven o'clock at night you'd be like what no? why do I want coffee at eleven o'clock at night you go to a restaurant everybody orders coffee at eleven o'clock at night it's just like why?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's all about the context it's like</u>
<u n="808" who="S0439">yeah why do people order coffee at the restaurant but they won't drink it at home? and I was like I drink it at home so it doesn't make sense but for other people I don't know</u>
<u n="809" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it really does though cos I will not choose to drink coffee</u>
<u n="810" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="811" who="S0444">unless I'm really really tired</u>
<u n="812" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0444">or it's a treat because I know that the coffee that I would have is not as good as the coffee that other people would give me like my auntie and uncle proper coffee connoisseurs I'm like if I go to theirs I have the coffee</u>
<u n="814" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah oh my god I would love to meet your aunt and uncle I love coffee</u>
<u n="815" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah I know well that's what I was going to say like erm the next time there's a V and A thing that we want to go to we can invite her along cos she's</u>
<u n="816" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah that's cool</u>
<u n="817" who="S0444">she's with the art fund and what have you so</u>
<u n="818" who="S0439">so many people have said to me like oh so what erm what are you doing in London? when I was going to visit you I was like I'm going to the Victoria and Albert museum they're like oh that's cool I'm like yeah I'm a member</u>
<u n="819" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think it's well cool</u>
<u n="820" who="S0439" trans="overlap">like I know me too</u>
<u n="821" who="S0444">cos I'm a co-member but</u>
<u n="822" who="S0439">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually is a member of the National Trust</u>
<u n="823" who="S0444">that is cool</u>
<u n="824" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know I know</u>
<u n="825" who="S0444">but the thing is that with <anon type="place"/> you have to be willing to drive towards places that are actual National Trust places</u>
<u n="826" who="S0439">yeah that's what he said he was like do you want to come on some National Trust days with me? I was like yes</u>
<u n="827" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah I'd love to go on a National Trust day with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="828" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="829" who="S0444">that'd be really fun</u>
<u n="830" who="S0439">he was like you're the only like one of the only people I can ask everybody else would laugh at me</u>
<u n="831" who="S0444">aw</u>
<u n="832" who="S0439">I was like no no no</u>
<u n="833" who="S0444">what a legend</u>
<u n="834" who="S0439">I'm a member of the Victoria and Albert museum you're member of the National Trust together we're like the oldest weirdest people we're like the weirdest twenty-three year olds</u>
<u n="835" who="S0444">it was it was really funny like erm er last weekend everybody was like ah so er they knew that I was busy on the Sunday so I wouldn't be around and they were like oh so what what are you doing? I was like I'm going to the V and A like with one of my best friends like you know it's just it's just one of the things that we do and they were like oh yeah what exhibit are you going to see? luckily this time is was not wedding dresses which it was on the first night that I met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="837" who="S0444">it was probably going to go in the wedding speech if there is one</u>
<u n="838" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0444">erm or one of your speeches <unclear/> I'll probably heckle from a table somewhere</u>
<u n="840" who="S0439">what what?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0444">yeah pretty much erm but er you know and I was like oh it's about shoes I'm like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his dad and his brother went well I'm glad we're not going there then</u>
<u n="842" who="S0439">so many people said that to me I was like I went to this Hollywood exhibition I went to this wedding dress exhibition I went to this couture icon McQueen exhibition I went shoe exhibition you hear some people are like that's really cool other people are just like</u>
<u n="843" who="S0444">why?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0439">that sounds shit it's like a Marmite <trunc>re</trunc>response isn't it?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0444">it really is but erm there's a Hepburn exhibition at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="846" who="S0439" trans="overlap">really? ooh</u>
<u n="847" who="S0444">I would love to go there</u>
<u n="848" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0444">like looking at all her stuff cos they've got like screenings and stuff like that as well as all of the old films even the ones that I haven't heard of</u>
<u n="850" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh my god yeah okay let me know I'd be up for that</u>
<u n="851" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so I was like ooh ooh there's loads of stuff going on for ages and they're tweeting about it like mad so</u>
<u n="852" who="S0439">I'd definitely go I like Audrey Hepburn's pretty</u>
<u n="853" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I love Audrey Hepburn it's like if I were Audrey Hepburn my life would be pretty much made like yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0439">it's like Victoria and Albert museum exhibitions are really cool cos my erm boss the American who I didn't think liked me originally but I think she's growing on me</u>
<u n="855" who="S0444">oh yeah that one the brownie points one</u>
<u n="856" who="S0439">yeah she erm she likes the Victoria and Albert museum and she went to the Alexander McQueen exhibition the shoe exhibition and stuff so it gives us something to like talk about</u>
<u n="857" who="S0444">yeah oh my auntie's going to the Alexander McQueen I think it might be tonight actually</u>
<u n="858" who="S0439">cos yeah you sent me that link they're extending it aren't they? cos it's so popular</u>
<u n="859" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah and they're doing a twenty-four hour kind of opening which is fab</u>
<u n="860" who="S0439">they must be making so much money out of that</u>
<u n="861" who="S0444">yeah but you can imagine how much money it actually costs to put on as well</u>
<u n="862" who="S0439">I was thinking that do they get like the clothes donated to them or do they have to pay there to exhibit them?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0444">erm could be a bit of both</u>
<u n="864" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0444">for particular pieces it could be a but usually stuff is like on loan</u>
<u n="866" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="867" who="S0444">that either they get their name published in the <unclear/> or you know there will be some dealing and bartering going on but you know it's the kind of thing that</u>
<u n="868" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah definitely it was actually an amazing exhibition wasn't it?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's such a I was trying to I was trying to explain to it my auntie cos like you know I was like I'm no fashion expert but</u>
<u n="870" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="871" who="S0444">the way that the exhibits were staged like I was trying to explain it to her that you know as you go in you think mm really?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="873" who="S0444">monochrome is a bit kind of basic but then as it goes on it gets more and more sophisticated and you'll go from one minute being in a room full of skulls</u>
<u n="874" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0444">to the next minute being in a really really bright red driven traditional more normal looking clothes</u>
<u n="876" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm exactly</u>
<u n="877" who="S0444">and then you'll go through to the big finale which is obviously the cabinet of curiosities</u>
<u n="878" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0444">and like I was a bit like there's there were too many people in there</u>
<u n="880" who="S0439">there was they let in too many people</u>
<u n="881" who="S0444" trans="overlap">to enjoy it</u>
<u n="882" who="S0439">I can understand why the wanted to get so many people through because so many people wanted to see the exhibition but</u>
<u n="883" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it was full I'm not being funny but I am being funny it's the kind of things where it's like people with prams don't do it</u>
<u n="884" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah no people with people with prams there are so many places they should not go</u>
<u n="885" who="S0444">I mean like I you know</u>
<u n="886" who="S0439">you can't discriminate but</u>
<u n="887" who="S0444" trans="overlap">definitely you should go but that with that many people</u>
<u n="888" who="S0439">but why would your kid even yeah? why would you take it? it's just</u>
<u n="889" who="S0444">well I suppose you have to but</u>
<u n="890" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0444">it's the kind of thing where it's like let them in at a time when there's not so many people walking round cos it's not just that you're kind of having to move a pram it's more like what if somebody trips or elbows or you know? it's just not safe</u>
<u n="892" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="893" who="S0444">but like</u>
<u n="894" who="S0439">they did let too many people in but it was a stunning exhibition wasn't it?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0444" trans="overlap">although my my auntie's niece on the other side of the family erm is doing her PhD in fashion like kind of history more textile kind of thing</u>
<u n="896" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0444">erm but she did a lot of work with the V and A and we were and she doesn't really talk that much but she definitely started talking about the exhibit and we actually had quite a bit of a conversation about it and it was great but you know erm</u>
<u n="898" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah it's it's just a really</u>
<u n="899" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's a really really good one I hope</u>
<u n="900" who="S0439" trans="overlap">stunning one</u>
<u n="901" who="S0444">but I honestly don't think it would have been as good if it hadn't have been in the Met cos it was the Met over in America</u>
<u n="902" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0444">that had staged it all and then we just nicked the staging so it was the kind of thing that if we hadn't have done if they hadn't have done it first we would never have come up with something so elaborate and so dramatic in a way</u>
<u n="904" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no it was that box of that box of curiosities at the end wasn't it? that was intense that was you just walked in and it felt like a creepy children's film but beautiful at the same time</u>
<u n="905" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and also yeah and also the bit that was just after the Kate Moss thing where</u>
<u n="906" who="S0439">yeah that was stunning</u>
<u n="907" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that was so cool</u>
<u n="908" who="S0439">that was so clever</u>
<u n="909" who="S0444">and then like you know I'm all about like I'm not really about the skulls or the random heads of things or</u>
<u n="910" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no and like that wildlife one you know like the African one I was a bit like no I would wear any of those</u>
<u n="911" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that was a bit like I'm a bit freaked out right now I mean</u>
<u n="912" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I don't think I would wear any of those clothes really but</u>
<u n="913" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no you wouldn't wear anything it was the most weird kind of dinosaur shoes that's like dinosaur egg shoes that's the only way I can describe them</u>
<u n="914" who="S0439">you can understand why Lady Gaga liked him so much</u>
<u n="915" who="S0444">oh yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0439">can't you? definitely right up her alley</u>
<u n="917" who="S0444">yeah but it I honestly think that you know I think this is this is what it said anyway in one of the kind of texts was that you know those and it was like I was saying to you before it was like those people were on such a different creative plane</u>
<u n="918" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0444">that no wonder they feel so isolated or so different or just on a different level it doesn't mean it's any better but it's a very different way of thinking and approaching things which is great</u>
<u n="920" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no mm</u>
<u n="921" who="S0444">but it also means that you know with great power they are</u>
<u n="922" who="S0439">yeah cos he obviously was so not messed up but there's something so bad</u>
<u n="923" who="S0444" trans="overlap">obviously so in turmoil like you know</u>
<u n="924" who="S0439">yeah yeah so sad that something happened like cos he killed himself didn't he? it's just</u>
<u n="925" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="926" who="S0439">it's a really sad thing oh my god these look amazing</u>
<u n="927" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="928" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">sticky toffee?</u>
<u n="929" who="S0439">yeah that's me thank you</u>
<u n="930" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">there you go I'll grab you a spoon</u>
<u n="931" who="S0439">brilliant thank you very much</u>
<u n="932" who="S0444">this looks amazing</u>
<u n="933" who="S0439">I know I told you the desserts here were good</u>
<u n="934" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="935" who="S0439">you didn't well you did believe actually so it's fine</u>
<u n="936" who="S0444">I did I was like give me pudding</u>
<u n="937" who="S0439">thank you</u>
<u n="938" who="S0444">thank you very much</u>
<u n="939" who="S0439">er <pause dur="short"/> you alright?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0444">yeah I was just thinking custard rather than ice cream</u>
<u n="941" who="S0439">I don't know I quite like I quite like the hot and the cold</u>
<u n="942" who="S0444">yeah sometimes it's good sometimes like I think in winter you definitely need the custard rather than the thing</u>
<u n="943" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="944" who="S0444">er er</u>
<u n="945" who="S0439">oh my <trunc>go</trunc> guess what? I don't know why this suddenly popped into my head</u>
<u n="946" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="947" who="S0439">and guess what I started watching recently?</u>
<u n="948" who="S0444">what?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0439">the Gilmore Girls</u>
<u n="950" who="S0444">really?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0439">the theme tune is now my phone ringtone</u>
<u n="952" who="S0444">oh my good grief</u>
<u n="953" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0444">erm I might go on watch it have you got Netflix?</u>
<u n="955" who="S0439">I do have Netflix yeah</u>
<u n="956" who="S0444">have you watched Sense Eight?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0439">I haven't but I've heard it's good</u>
<u n="958" who="S0444">it is good yeah it's a bit weird at first but you have to kind of stick with it</u>
<u n="959" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="960" who="S0444">but it is really good</u>
<u n="961" who="S0439">I heard that about it</u>
<u n="962" who="S0444">some of it <pause dur="short"/> some of it is a bit far-fetched</u>
<u n="963" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="964" who="S0444">but it knows that</u>
<u n="965" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="966" who="S0444">it's more that <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="967" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay the cappuccino?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0439">oh that's me please thank you</u>
<u n="969" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">there you go</u>
<u n="970" who="S0444">thank you</u>
<u n="971" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay thank you</u>
<u n="972" who="S0444">but it's also it's got about eight characters</u>
<u n="973" who="S0439">oh yeah it's not too many</u>
<u n="974" who="S0444">main characters</u>
<u n="975" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="976" who="S0444">but they interchange between their stories in a way that actually means that you relate to the series more that by the time of it you're not into it because of the story</u>
<u n="977" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="978" who="S0444">you're into it because of the characters</u>
<u n="979" who="S0439">yeah which to be fair is what you would want really isn't it? mm</u>
<u n="980" who="S0444">so</u>
<u n="981" who="S0439">I was watching Daredevil</u>
<u n="982" who="S0444">I love Daredevil</u>
<u n="983" who="S0439">do you love it?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0444">I really like it</u>
<u n="985" who="S0439">I I was kind of like on the fence about it I've still got two episodes to watch or one episode to go or something I I've been battling through it</u>
<u n="986" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="987" who="S0439">it was alright but I wouldn't say it's a <trunc>ma</trunc> I don't know I don't</u>
<u n="988" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>ve</trunc> it's very slow</u>
<u n="989" who="S0439">yeah definitely very slow erm also just really unrealistic I'm sorry but I realised it was a like based on a cartoon so that's fine <pause dur="short"/> not a cartoon like a graphic novel</u>
<u n="990" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you like take it up with Marvels not Netflix</u>
<u n="991" who="S0439">erm what else? also I watched Orange is the New Black</u>
<u n="992" who="S0444">what do you think?</u>
<u n="993" who="S0439">I haven't finished season three I've nearly finished season three</u>
<u n="994" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="995" who="S0439">it's not bad it's a bit gets a bit boring but</u>
<u n="996" who="S0444">yeah Piper bores me</u>
<u n="997" who="S0439">mm oh my god I want to punch Piper in the face</u>
<u n="998" who="S0444">oh and Alex</u>
<u n="999" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's no characters I particularly love but</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0444">mm I love Tasty</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0439">which one's Tasty?</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0444">that girl with the curly hair <pause dur="short"/> pretty hair rather like er</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah two of them look very similar don't they?</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0444" trans="overlap">the one who used to work in the library</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0439">oh yeah I like her she's good</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0444">and the one that spoke German</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0439">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0444">but that's what I like it's more the ensemble cast that are</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0444">carrying it now than the actual main characters</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0439">yeah Piper's just so whiny oh my god Piper shut up</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0444">but erm Red I love Red she's grown on me a lot more and the Spanish you know girls I find them hilarious</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0439">oh <trunc>go</trunc> I'm I'm <trunc>de</trunc> I like it's not really a new year's resolution cos it's halfway through the year but my half year resolution is to erm finish the like shows cos I always get halfway through and then never finish them</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0444">really?</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0444">I always have to finish them</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0439">I'm really bad</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1020" who="S0444">this is really good</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0439">I love how you are just like whacking your spoon in and it's like pulling out the entire thing <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> this is so nice</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0444">it's because the berries are at the bottom and I don't want to be left with the berries at the end</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0439">mm who would want to be left with berries uh fruit? what?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0444">that's why I'm hunting for the berries</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1026" who="S0444">like er</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0439">hunting for those berries they're hiding from you</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0444">they are honestly they're quite difficult to get out</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0439">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh caffeine</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1030" who="S0444">doing my happy food dance from side to side that's how you know that I'm like mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that's good good latte with ice cream</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0444">don't ask me why it's so good but it is I think it's the hot and the cold</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you can't beat like coffee and dessert</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0444">not like a good coffee</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0444">this is good coffee</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0439">yeah it really annoys me when someone offers me a coffee and then gives me like instant <vocal desc="laugh"/> I drink instant coffee but</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1039" who="S0439">it's not as good</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh yeah no it's not the same but</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0439">I do drink it but it's not as good</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0444">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1043" who="S0439">mm so obviously our winter holiday</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0439">are you planning any summer holidays any summer trips with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0444">em not at the moment I think I need to confirm my dad's been toying with the idea of going to Ireland</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0444">erm for a week originally we would have gone at Christmas</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0444">but my grandma's been slightly poorly so he kind of wants to go when she's we know that she's well rather than suffering the cold or something so I need to figure that out first</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0444">and to be honest I don't feel right telling work that I'm on a <unclear/> I'm going on holiday</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0439">yeah exactly yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0444">so I think it's more going to be towards autumn winter <trunc>bre</trunc> I've got quite a lot of holiday left I've got about two or three weeks left</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0439">wow yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0444">so I've got quite a lot to use up so it's kind of like mm I can go on holiday all the time</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0439">and also you can take a like a nice long Christmas can't you? if you wanted</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm yeah it depends it depends where we are to be honest</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0444">erm if we're just in one place then that's fine but if we're in two places it makes more sense to take a longer break</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and it depends if you get a new job</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0444">oh true <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0439">scary times</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0439">to be fair it was this time last year that I started looking and new jobs and stuff so</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0444">yeah to be fair it's just changed so much in a year it's kind of like your brain just needs to process all the change first</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0439">mm yeah you don't want to end up in like them taking you to a like advantage of you again do you? and like falling back into that like situation</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0444">no definitely not but it was quite nice</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0439">what having time off or?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0444">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1072" who="S0444">but the team the team I worked with in <anon type="place"/> who I got on really well with you'd really rate them</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0439">mm so you think you might want to move to the <anon type="place"/> office is that something that they could maybe like work out for you?</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0444">they could but I don't think they would well they might do now that we've changed the managing structure</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0444">cos technically I wouldn't really be reporting into to anyone that often anyway so</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0444">and there is a precedent tattoo <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did it last year</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0439">huh?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0444">tattoo <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did it last year</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0439">really he moved to London</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0444" trans="overlap">where he moved to London</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0444">so there is a precedent erm but they're they're really funny like they will tell they're very blunt you would you would rate them they're very very funny and er they they like me so that's good</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0439" trans="overlap">obviously everybody likes you</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0444">but you know? they were a lot better to me than the marketing department they were much nicer to me in terms of when I got back all of them were instantly on chat like once they seen I sent an email to one of them oh my gosh you're back what are we going to do without you? like this is this is crazy we don't want you to leave ever</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0444">or like you know it's the kind of thing or like all of them kind of emailed me and when <unclear/> was like hey hope you're rested up and feeling better they don't know what was wrong but they know that</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0439">that something happened</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0444">yeah and erm</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0439">shit went down</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0444">yeah and it was kind of thing that I sent an email going hey I'm not going to be around for a little while erm you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be taking over blah blah blah erm as soon as I sent that email within about three minutes the national sales manager was ringing me going are you okay?</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0444">are you going home? go and get some TLC I'll meet you for a <trunc>co</trunc> cos she lives nearby near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0439">oh that's cool</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0444">she's like I'll meet you for a coffee if you want but if you don't that's fine but just keep in touch while you're off not about work but just let us know how you are?</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0444">erm and then you know it was kind of they were like oh my gosh it was only when you were gone that we realised how good and how quickly and how well you do things</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0444">because the stuff that we you would usually get done in a day it took two or three meetings for other people to get their heads round like what is that?</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0439">also not just stopping you well stopping you but that couple who sat next to us were the weirdest couple what was?</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0444">they were odd</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0439">they were really bizarre like he spent the whole time on his mobile she looked liked she'd rather be like anywhere but here oh he's coming back wait there stop talking <vocal desc="laugh"/> stop talking</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0444">like please please please stop</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> anyway yes yeah but you are really good at your job and I think that's what they needed to be like told didn't they?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0444">well like <anon type="place"/> got it <anon type="place"/> not so much but</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0439">do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and stuff still work there?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0444">yeah er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has just been promoted</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tattoo <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0444" trans="overlap">tattoo <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1111" who="S0439">what's he what's he got promoted in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0444">digital services manager whatever that is</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0439">did that cause a bit of tension between him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at all?</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0444">I don't know because nobody really wanted that job</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0444">and they all got told that they should apply for it and everyone was like meh erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is pregnant</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0439">oh the ginger-haired woman who got married a few years ago?</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0444">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's alright I think he just wants more money which is fair enough</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0439" trans="overlap">everybody wants more money yeah</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no but it's fair enough after like five seven? seven? is it seven years?</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah wow he's been on the same salary for seven years?</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0444">not the same subject but the same</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no the same salary kind of thing</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0444">well it would keep going up I'm assuming but not very much</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah but not very much</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0444">and what was interesting was that this restructure it was like no I don't believe in giving people pay rises within their roles like not as in like substantial ones I I believe they should just be paid for their role</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0439">who said that?</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0444">the ber marketing director</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0439">bollocks</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0444">in which case I one of my questions to them is are you going to make it transparent what the salary bands are? because I know that I deserve to be paid a damn lot more than I have been because I would argue okay yeah maybe I'm not doing the extra projects that other senior execs are doing</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0439">you're busy as hell</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but I am busy as hell and I'm doing a lot more than some of them have been doing</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0444">I mean everybody is ber busy and flat out right now which is you know there's no comparison but it's not like I think I should be promoted I just think I deserve a little bit more <trunc>mo</trunc>money to make it feasible erm you know or at least an inducement to stay so I think if it was the kind of thing that I was like right I've got this job offer what do you want to do?</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0439">I think you should leave anyway</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0444">oh yeah I know</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't you're not happy and it like you obviously now you're getting a bit better and you were worked too hard but if you were crying in a car because you didn't want to go back to work you should not be spending your twenties crying in a car hating your job</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah exactly doing that no of course not but it's also that kind of thing that it's more that I've got to I feel that I've got to prove that I'm well enough to do the work that I've got</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0439">yeah of course you do yeah</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0444">and feel comfortable within it myself but also from that lesson be like no I'm not doing that</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0439">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0444">and it's one of the things that I'm like right okay you've got this restructure but what are you wanting me to do? because I will tell you flat out if it's not if it's too much</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0444">you know I'm just like I will tell you flat out if it's too much and you've already got the warning of why that's not a good thing so you can't do that again anymore you can't just pile it on and expect me to be okay with it</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0444">if you do you know and marketing were blaming <anon type="place"/> which wasn't fair at all they were like oh they put too much on you and I'm like it's not them it's actually you</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0439">yeah you've done this to me</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0444">you're the idiots who've done it</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0444">but you know like I feel less I feel so much less bothered</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0444">about it not in a bad way not as in like I don't want to do well or I don't want to do my job I still you know enjoy my job I'm good at it but I just don't care as much anymore I'm not as invested or like feel that it's all on me</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0439">yeah it's not all on you yeah</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0444">well that's what I mean it's that kind of thing I'm just like actually now it's like <trunc>me</trunc> you know the reason why I don't really want to look at the job that the recruiter's given me it's because it's for a technology company that deals with different porous materials that's not really me</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0444">but it's waiting for that right opportunity to come along the er the <trunc>mar</trunc> the marketing execs library job looks good but I'm I wouldn't feel right applying for a job when I'm on sick leave or when I'm just coming back from sick leave</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no not at all</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0444">that would be okay some people would be like yeah that's a wise move but <trunc>other</trunc> but I would feel dishonest being like yeah I can</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0439">yeah of course</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0444">I can go for a full-time role but I've just been off work</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0439">but I've just been ill yeah</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0444">yeah it's it's just not</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0444">it's not a good thing it's much better for me to be like yeah okay there was one period of illness that I had while I've been working over the last three years er I got the help that I needed I put the tactics and the management skills in place</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0439">you've learnt from it and you're sorted</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0444">exactly do you know what I mean? that's a much more positive story to give rather than I'm still on <unclear/></u>
<u n="1167" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0444">you know if I were going for any job like supermarket retail office you know temp job</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0439">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0444">it'd be alright but no I want a job that you know I'm interested but I know that I also need to scale what the job's going to be and if I don't get myself</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
