<text id="SVBH">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:27:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0083 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Family, travelling</topics>
		<activity>Friends cooking and eating dinner, chatting, watching a movie</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0083">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Essex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0083">there's fruit in this?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0084">yeah in the jam</u>
<u n="3" who="S0083">fruit in the jam in the juice in anything really</u>
<u n="4" who="S0084">yoghurts</u>
<u n="5" who="S0083">yes <pause dur="short"/> it shouldn't be there</u>
<u n="6" who="S0084">I don't like the yoghurts with bits in</u>
<u n="7" who="S0083">with bits in <pause dur="short"/> I mean they're it's fruit</u>
<u n="8" who="S0084">yeah it's</u>
<u n="9" who="S0083">you're meant to eat fruit</u>
<u n="10" who="S0084">fruit <pause dur="short"/> no I don't like it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0083">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> I thought you'd improved</u>
<u n="12" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0083">well clearly not</u>
<u n="14" who="S0084">no no no no no</u>
<u n="15" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and how are you?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0084">I'm exhausted</u>
<u n="17" who="S0083">are you?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0084">ah I've just had the supplier coming around to <pause dur="short"/> well when I say we I had to do a review meeting</u>
<u n="19" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0084">and my brain aches <pause dur="short"/> I've been dreading it for about a month</u>
<u n="21" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="22" who="S0084">I woke up with like a sick feeling butterflies</u>
<u n="23" who="S0083" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="24" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah I've been really dreading it because I had to lead the meeting</u>
<u n="25" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0083">my daughter the manager</u>
<u n="28" who="S0084">mm hardly but</u>
<u n="29" who="S0083">you're so capable and</u>
<u n="30" who="S0084">I'm not I want to cry</u>
<u n="31" who="S0083">oh I think this is excellent</u>
<u n="32" who="S0084">it's horrible</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="33" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> horri-bubble <pause dur="short"/> but it was good it was erm because we've reached the end of two of our projects that they've been project managing for us</u>
<u n="34" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0084">and we're replacing the typesetter the typesetting work with Indian suppliers</u>
<u n="36" who="S0083">oh excellent</u>
<u n="37" who="S0084">yup because they're five pounds a page rather than twenty-five pounds a page which UK suppliers are</u>
<u n="38" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">but they're rubbish so it's a completely</u>
<u n="40" who="S0083">well yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0084">false economy</u>
<u n="42" who="S0083"><trunc>E</trunc> exactly</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084">erm so we're looking at ways of making it a bit easier for them looking at ways looking at how they've really let us down and</u>
<u n="44" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084">because it was the first time we've used this project management company and the guy the MD used to work in-house</u>
<u n="46" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="47" who="S0084">A really nice guy</u>
<u n="48" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084">he used to work in like our academic division so he knows <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my old boss because she worked in academic</u>
<u n="50" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">and another one of the erm one of my er colleagues who is on maternity leave at the moment <pause dur="short"/> there's another production controller so it was good for him to come in and</u>
<u n="52" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">for us to say like we're all a bit concerned about these issues <pause dur="short"/> how have you found it because he's essentially the buffer between us and the typesetter so he deals with a lot of their queries <pause dur="short"/> but I think actually in reality the biggest problem is they don't query stuff so when it comes in it's not it's substandard and they haven't raised</u>
<u n="54" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084">any concerns <pause dur="short"/> so erm we've done two of the six titles so far erm so it was a good point to just take stock and hold a review <pause dur="short"/> so my boss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> called in from the States which she had to leave after half an hour because of training <pause dur="short"/> but she's dealing with the same one of the same suppliers in New York and for some reason that I don't understand in New York they erm they've placed all their work with one supplier <pause dur="short"/> which is they did it before with a company called Adventure House and they went bust</u>
<u n="56" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084">which is not what you want really because they've got all your files all your formats all your covers</u>
<u n="58" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">all your body files <pause dur="short"/> and they have it and now they've asked erm and obviously you don't you can't by spreading yourself around by spreading the work around you force competition so you get better rates <pause dur="short"/> so if you're thinking with your business head on</u>
<u n="60" who="S0083" trans="overlap">has erm yeah yeah I mean that is obviously what you're supposed to do</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084">obviously you want to build relationships with people because then you understand each other you know each other you rely on each other and they understand your product</u>
<u n="62" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0084">but you know we have  we have  about four or five different suppliers in the UK</u>
<u n="64" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0084">we have about three or four Indian suppliers that we're starting to place work with <pause dur="short"/> erm so</u>
<u n="66" who="S0083">are they improving though?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0083">not really? No</u>
<u n="69" who="S0084">one of them is rubbish</u>
<u n="70" who="S0083" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to erm complain about doing that cos they're you know all companies do it <pause dur="short"/> she said the paper is poor quality the ink is <trunc>b</trunc> of poor quality</u>
<u n="71" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well luckily they don't erm control that</u>
<u n="72" who="S0083">alright</u>
<u n="73" who="S0084">I mean they literally do the design</u>
<u n="74" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="75" who="S0084">erm and the products that we have and working on should in theory be extremely straightforward because they've practise tests in Cambridge ESOL <pause dur="short"/> so Cambridge ESOL</u>
<u n="76" who="S0083">oh I see</u>
<u n="77" who="S0084">supply us with the exams</u>
<u n="78" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0084">we copy edit it erm we'll put our copyright line in <trunc>w</trunc> you know we jazz it up a bit we lay it out <pause dur="short"/> erm and that's it it should be a relatively straightforward piece of work <pause dur="short"/> for some reason they're getting it wrong you know we've found today with the set of proofs that they're copying and pasting from one</u>
<u n="80" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0084">set of proofs to another and so you've got half of one exam and half of another <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's just awful it's really basic</u>
<u n="82" who="S0083">but that's really bad</u>
<u n="83" who="S0084">bog standard stuff</u>
<u n="84" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0084">particularly because we're we're we're moving into a digital age where if we supply a Word document it's already styled so that they can flow it straight into their template in their design template</u>
<u n="86" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0084">they're not doing that even though it's that would be the easiest thing to do <pause dur="short"/> sorry am I boring you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0083">no I'm I am listening</u>
<u n="89" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what are you doing? You're not listening you're playing <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I am</u>
<u n="91" who="S0084">put the TV on then</u>
<u n="92" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I am listening</u>
<u n="93" who="S0084">er anyway so yeah so they came in and we had a chat</u>
<u n="94" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0084">end of story <pause dur="short"/> it was long it started at two</u>
<u n="96" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0084">and gradually everyone had to go to another meeting so there was just me and Joe <pause dur="short"/> it was fine <pause dur="short"/> I'm glad it's over but it was really useful</u>
<u n="98" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0084">cos it was a I think he's taken stuff away and we've taken stuff away so</u>
<u n="100" who="S0083">Good</u>
<u n="101" who="S0084">it was good</u>
<u n="102" who="S0083">are you going to be doing more with these now? Is this this is gonna be part of your life now doing meetings like this</u>
<u n="103" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hate it</u>
<u n="104" who="S0083">oh you don't hate it it's just  it's just</u>
<u n="105" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I do hate it it makes me feel sick</u>
<u n="106" who="S0083">it makes you a bit nervous that's all but</u>
<u n="107" who="S0084">that's why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is insisting I go on this presentation skills workshop which is awful <pause dur="short"/> you have to give a presentation in the morning and she said when they'd confirmed my place and she sent me an email to say now you must remember that I did my presentation on Ladybird books and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did hers on baking so you've got a really high standard to maintain here <pause dur="short"/> but a talk for about five minutes on whatever you fancy erm and then you do the workshop and then you have to give a presentation on your job at the end of the day <pause dur="short"/> but you should come prepared with some material and then you hone it during the day <pause dur="short"/> so so she said it was really useful I mean I'm dreading that <pause dur="short"/> there's gonna be role-play and</u>
<u n="108" who="S0083">yes <pause dur="short"/> oh this is your business</u>
<u n="109" who="S0084">all that horrendous stuff</u>
<u n="110" who="S0083">life now</u>
<u n="111" who="S0084">I hate it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="113" who="S0084">but while those courses are available and they're not free</u>
<u n="114" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0084">but you know they could be <pause dur="short"/> they're free for me</u>
<u n="116" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0084">the department pays</u>
<u n="118" who="S0083">exactly <pause dur="short"/> we'll take them up on it</u>
<u n="119" who="S0084">but you might as well</u>
<u n="120" who="S0083">just think of erm <pause dur="short"/> I always think this is so funny and <trunc>w</trunc> I can't <pause dur="short"/> I think her name was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't it? In <anon type="place"/> when she works in the office</u>
<u n="121" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0083">and she has to give that presentation and she has the circle</u>
<u n="123" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0083">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0084">did she say what are we doing?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0083">yes <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember when it was  it was  <trunc>j</trunc> it was ridiculous</u>
<u n="127" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> and they all applauded</u>
<u n="128" who="S0083">and and they all applauded yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was so funny</u>
<u n="129" who="S0084">and she asked everybody what are  what are  we doing here?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0084">what what is this job? And no no one tells her no one can answer her</u>
<u n="132" who="S0083">but it's all just  it's all just  words and they don't mean anything and the idea is they don't mean anything and erm names for things that don't mean anything is actually all of it is just meaningless</u>
<u n="133" who="S0084" trans="overlap">erm and they just business-speak is so stupid the</u>
<u n="134" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0084">the things that they say like I was in a meeting with erm it was when I was being a PA for Geoff and I was taking minutes and he was talking about something or other and he said we'll take this offline <pause dur="short"/> which just means we'll talk about it later</u>
<u n="136" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">why not just say that?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0083">I know</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">or or going forward or what</u>
<u n="140" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">you know?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0083">it's all just jargon and</u>
<u n="143" who="S0084">all management-speak it's just</u>
<u n="144" who="S0083">business-speak and</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084">you just sound like an idiot</u>
<u n="146" who="S0083">it's it's all horrible <pause dur="short"/> I hate it</u>
<u n="147" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> we've got to you've got to embrace it though if you want to get ahead</u>
<u n="148" who="S0083">I suppose you do</u>
<u n="149" who="S0084">and maybe it just happens one night you just wake up and you speak like an idiot</u>
<u n="150" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0084">that's what I'm worried about</u>
<u n="152" who="S0083">I think  I think  it's if you're in that environment you just it's you just become like that</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0083">and you start speaking like them</u>
<u n="155" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0083">so watch it <pause dur="short"/> we'll pull you up on it if we <trunc>s</trunc> if we</u>
<u n="157" who="S0084">well I already told you that I felt sick the the other week when I had to erm knock down one of our UK suppliers</u>
<u n="158" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0084">on their price <pause dur="short"/> they'd quoted fifteen pounds a page which actually is <trunc>incredib</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> no actually thirty pounds a page for a for quite a difficult complex book</u>
<u n="160" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0084">and I <trunc>n</trunc> I had to knock them down to twenty-five</u>
<u n="162" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0084">and they are <pause dur="short"/> we went to see them and they're really nice have got a really nice set up but they're struggling for work like they keep emailing saying if you've got any projects you know we could handle anything any size shape whatever <pause dur="short"/> and you know that actually they've got a lot of overheads in the they expanded I don't know if it was last year or the <trunc>y</trunc> year before at a time when we are looking to</u>
<u n="164" who="S0083">but they they're obviously struggling now</u>
<u n="165" who="S0084">offshore <pause dur="short"/> and they're struggling and so but you saying well I would pay thirty pounds but I know that because you're struggling you'll take twenty-five</u>
<u n="166" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0084">and you're not  you're not  cutting off</u>
<u n="168" who="S0083">it's horrible isn't it?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0084">their hands but it just makes you feel sick</u>
<u n="170" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0084">and you think well that's <trunc>w</trunc> basically what you have to do</u>
<u n="172" who="S0083">it is horrible mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0084">I mean it's not  it's not  erm it's not it wouldn't be a problem to pay thirty pounds a page because that's what you would expect to pay</u>
<u n="174" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0084">but we did say to them when we went to meet them that erm you know we are being asked to <pause dur="short"/> the dictat from on high is</u>
<u n="176" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0084">offshore where possible</u>
<u n="178" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0084">erm and if and our argument is it's a false economy because</u>
<u n="180" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0084">the amount of time we've spent in man hours liaising with them and answering the most basic of queries and sending stuff back when it's wrong</u>
<u n="182" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0084">you know to pay a production controller's salary you might as well freelance it out to a get</u>
<u n="184" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0084">UK supplier and get it right first time someone who knows you</u>
<u n="186" who="S0083">well yes</u>
<u n="187" who="S0084">it's just</u>
<u n="188" who="S0083">sometimes it is just a false economy</u>
<u n="189" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> we were saying that they'd have to come and come down on their prices</u>
<u n="190" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0084">if they wanted to keep the work and it's probably what they're gonna have to do</u>
<u n="192" who="S0083">it's very hard though cos you know small companies er will really struggle in this kind of climate</u>
<u n="193" who="S0084">and really at this time you want to be placing work</u>
<u n="194" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0084">with suppliers you trust and</u>
<u n="196" who="S0083">you would think so but it</u>
<u n="197" who="S0084">suppliers in the UK</u>
<u n="198" who="S0083"><trunc>c</trunc> but every company when it comes to it will will it's just the bottom line is the only thing that matters</u>
<u n="199" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0083">their own profits are the only things that erm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0083">really matter</u>
<u n="203" who="S0084">and we're not</u>
<u n="204" who="S0083">so</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084">we're not  making any money</u>
<u n="206" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">we're really not</u>
<u n="208" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and that's what that's what'll happen</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084">mm it's a problem</u>
<u n="212" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0084">Oscar <pause dur="short"/> I know you can hear me you just twitched your ear <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0083">he looks even funnier from the other side</u>
<u n="215" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0083">he looks hilarious</u>
<u n="217" who="S0084">half a head</u>
<u n="218" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't even see his ears you can just  you can just  see this much</u>
<u n="219" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> do they do it when it's raining?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0083">yes and I mean it's not raining at the moment so maybe he's just being cautious because he thinks it will any minute now</u>
<u n="221" who="S0084">because he got very wet today</u>
<u n="222" who="S0083">he always gets wet</u>
<u n="223" who="S0084">your bedroom doors are open though</u>
<u n="224" who="S0083">yes <pause dur="short"/> well my duvet cover is covered in muddy footprints so I don't see the point in washing it until it stops raining and he stops jumping on it</u>
<u n="225" who="S0084">it's been raining for about three weeks</u>
<u n="226" who="S0083">I know</u>
<u n="227" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0083">it's just so difficult to keep him out you know I don't it's a small flat and he's my cat erm I don't like chasing him out of places</u>
<u n="229" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0083">but I do get fed up with paw prints everywhere</u>
<u n="231" who="S0084">like here</u>
<u n="232" who="S0083">oh yeah and all up and down here <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's just</u>
<u n="233" who="S0084">tend to wipe his feet when he comes in</u>
<u n="234" who="S0083">yeah I would do</u>
<u n="235" who="S0084">the paws</u>
<u n="236" who="S0083">he's also moulting so there's fur everywhere I've just hoovered <pause dur="short"/> big clumps of hair everywhere or fur I should say</u>
<u n="237" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0083">anyway</u>
<u n="239" who="S0084">so how has your day been?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0083">quiet <pause dur="short"/> I've had a quiet one</u>
<u n="241" who="S0084">oh that sounds nice</u>
<u n="242" who="S0083">yes <pause dur="short"/> well I seem to need it</u>
<u n="243" who="S0084">you've had quite a busy week from the sounds of it? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="244" who="S0083">I know <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's it is ridiculous it's erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it's just just me <pause dur="short"/> erm and when I only went to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s for a couple of hours so I mean it's not</u>
<u n="245" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0083">not onerous it's not erm <pause dur="short"/> it's just the the having to go there and I suppose I mean I did go from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s to his yesterday but the day before I didn't I just went straight there <pause dur="short"/> erm but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I I just  I just  have this feeling that I've taken on too much <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's <trunc>n</trunc> by any stretch it's really not but it it's beginning to feel like it to me and I I'm trying not to let it <pause dur="short"/> erm also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s erm erm he's he's starting a project</u>
<u n="247" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0083">that erm he'd like me to be involved with and it sounds really good and it shouldn't be too much <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'll you know I just said it's on a proviso that you know if I feel I can do it I'll do it and if I feel I can't then you know? He's fine about that <pause dur="short"/> erm it just feels a bit much I suppose because it's not none of it is is just <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously this is a good thing but it's also a bad thing from my point of view</u>
<u n="249" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0083">none of it is just turn up do it and go home <pause dur="short"/> I mean with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know I'm emotionally involved now</u>
<u n="251" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0083">erm she was quite down <pause dur="short"/> erm the the scan was I mean it wasn't  it wasn't  terrible but they are growing again and she's started she's she will be starting the next kind of treatment <pause dur="short"/> which which <trunc>i</trunc> is a it's an unusual thing it's it's quite new it's <trunc>o</trunc> only received erm erm a a sort of license or approval or some <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whatever whatever you have to do to to get erm medication or a treatment passed in this country</u>
<u n="253" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0083">erm I think two years ago maybe less erm so it's quite new <pause dur="short"/> it's a form of chemotherapy but it's erm it's a tablet and it works in a different way</u>
<u n="255" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="256" who="S0083">so you just take tablets but there are quite a few side-effects and she's obviously worried that the side-effects are going to be something she can't cope with <pause dur="short"/> there are quite a lot</u>
<u n="257" who="S0084">really? Will it make her lose her hair?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0083">no I mean it the thing that will bother her most I think is erm is nausea and sickness</u>
<u n="259" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0083">it also can affect your blood pressure your iron levels your thyroid levels <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's quite a few things it can interfere with so</u>
<u n="261" who="S0084">blimey <pause dur="short"/> because that was a problem last time</u>
<u n="262" who="S0083">but they do</u>
<u n="263" who="S0084">wasn't it all the nausea?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0083">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> and she does have it all the time and she has <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc> there's there are quite a few <trunc>anti</trunc> anti-nausea erm drugs but only one of them is <trunc>v</trunc> is effective for her and it's it's fairly expensive <pause dur="short"/> and they are so stingy with it they only ever give her ten at a time or something and she has to take one every day <pause dur="short"/> if she doesn't then she ends up you know being sick or just feeling so sick that she can't do anything <pause dur="short"/> they are so stingy with them and I think if she's got cancer you know come on give her the bloody tablets</u>
<u n="265" who="S0084">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="266" who="S0083">I just  I just  think it's so bad</u>
<u n="267" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0083">anyway</u>
<u n="269" who="S0084">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="270" who="S0083">so I think she's worried about that <pause dur="short"/> erm so she was not herself yesterday erm and I can understand that <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>th</trunc> <trunc>th</trunc> there are two  there are two  types of this they've got different names and I suppose they will try one or then the other and see how she is with either of them <pause dur="short"/> but actually erm this is the last you know there are no other options</u>
<u n="271" who="S0084" trans="overlap">last options</u>
<u n="272" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that so either of these hopefully they will <pause dur="short"/> and people do I mean I was reading on one of the blogs you know people take them for fifteen years or something you know?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0084">oh God</u>
<u n="274" who="S0083">so you know you can</u>
<u n="275" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0083">so long as it agrees with you and so long as it works</u>
<u n="277" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0083">but it is effective for this kind of cancer so</u>
<u n="279" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0084">well that's good news cos this <unclear/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0083" trans="overlap">so they've got everything crossed and I suppose Alex is running around like a crazy person following up <pause dur="short"/> you know he's made some very good connections now with these with this virotherapy but</u>
<u n="283" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0083">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how close he is to getting anything organised <pause dur="short"/> I've emailed him but I haven't heard back so I don't know</u>
<u n="285" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0083">sometimes he's just incredibly busy speaking to er <pause dur="short"/> I think he's very good you know he doesn't <pause dur="short"/> I mean he goes straight to the person you know he'll read about the the research at this clinic in this hospital in this place and this is the consultant who is doing it or this is the scientist who is doing it and he just rings them up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="288" who="S0083">and and the thing is that they're brilliant they say oh yeah yeah what do you want to know about it? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> no this really interests <pause dur="short"/> and they talk away for hours to him so</u>
<u n="289" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0083">it's fantastic <pause dur="short"/> he's got such a good attitude erm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0083">and such a good way about him and they're they seem very happy and and keen to talk about it and to discuss what they've done and you know possibilities and</u>
<u n="293" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0083">you know? So that's what he's done he goes straight to the top <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0084">fabulous <pause dur="short"/> well that's what he needs</u>
<u n="296" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it seems like a very good  a very good  way of doing things</u>
<u n="297" who="S0084">A good friend to have</u>
<u n="298" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="299" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0083">whether anything will come from the <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="301" who="S0084">you'll just <trunc>h</trunc> have to be positive</u>
<u n="302" who="S0083">hopefully one day I mean it does sound incredibly promising</u>
<u n="303" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0083">but erm I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="305" who="S0084">you've just got to keep at it</u>
<u n="306" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> you're recording this</u>
<u n="307" who="S0084">well no one's gonna listen to it</u>
<u n="308" who="S0083">okay <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="309" who="S0084">Oscar</u>
<u n="310" who="S0083">you should remind me not to say names</u>
<u n="311" who="S0084">they anonymise it</u>
<u n="312" who="S0083">okay</u>
<u n="313" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I told you that didn't I?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="315" who="S0084">they anonymise it yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0083">okay</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="317" who="S0083">okay <pause dur="short"/> yup here comes the rain</u>
<u n="318" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm bored with the rain</u>
<u n="319" who="S0083">yeah me too and the wind it's very windy today</u>
<u n="320" who="S0084">have you spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0083">I haven't erm I meant to phone him this afternoon and I haven't got around to it <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0084">are you going to see him at the weekend?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0083">is it Thursday?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0084">it's Thursday yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it is isn't it? Erm I'm hoping he'll come over erm but he hasn't said</u>
<u n="326" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0083">erm and you're going to dad's this afternoon so you'll see him there won't you?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0084">I'll see him there yeah <pause dur="short"/> he texted me yesterday saying he'll give me the money next week</u>
<u n="329" who="S0083">yeah?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0084">they've screwed up his benefits I think</u>
<u n="331" who="S0083">really?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0084">he sent me a message last night but I just didn't really read it properly I just said it's fine <pause dur="short"/> something about some paperwork or something I don't know <pause dur="short"/> so they've messed his benefits up so he won't get paid until next week <pause dur="short"/> I mean it doesn't bother me</u>
<u n="333" who="S0083">no okay so long as he's not spinning you a line</u>
<u n="334" who="S0084">well I'm gonna go around there tonight and just speak to him about it in front of dad</u>
<u n="335" who="S0083" trans="overlap">what and and dad  and dad  would know cos obviously he has to go with him</u>
<u n="336" who="S0084">exactly</u>
<u n="337" who="S0083">so that's  so that's  good <pause dur="short"/> erm it might be because</u>
<u n="338" who="S0084">well he's been filling all his paperwork in to say</u>
<u n="339" who="S0083">we still  we still  haven't  we still haven't  you know agreed all of this so</u>
<u n="340" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0083">we need to do this <pause dur="short"/> erm dad was gonna get him to do it today <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> anyway there's the letter</u>
<u n="342" who="S0084" trans="overlap">is this your letter?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0083">yes do you want to read it?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0084">do you want me to?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0083" trans="overlap">of course</u>
<u n="346" who="S0084" trans="overlap">do you mind?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0083">of course</u>
<u n="348" who="S0084">oh my God <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Hah wow</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="349" who="S0084">oh lovely names</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="350" who="S0084">causes me some query <pause dur="short"/> the name Imogen causes causes causes me</u>
<u n="351" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0084">some query?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0083">he's not sure if it's a boy's name or girl's name <pause dur="short"/> now the funny thing is when I wrote that first letter I wrote in great detail about all three of you</u>
<u n="354" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0083">about who you were when you were born and what you do erm but he's obviously forgotten <pause dur="short"/> I mean maybe he didn't read the letter or didn't take it in or you know and they've  and they've  <trunc>thr</trunc> they haven't kept it and he can't remember what I said whether it was a girl's name or a boy's so</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="356" who="S0084">nice that he's written by hand</u>
<u n="357" who="S0083">it is and it's  and it's  from him</u>
<u n="358" who="S0084">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="359" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well I mean he says it's from both of them but you know what I mean</u>
<u n="360" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="361" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> We would love to see you whenever you can make it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0084">I mean why can't he come here firstly? I strongly suggest you travel business class <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0083">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="365" who="S0084">well I've just got to get my spare three grand out of my savings</u>
<u n="366" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0084">and to use British Airways we have found them the best <pause dur="short"/> Well does that mean that he comes back to the UK?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0083">well they've travelled a lot in their lives and they have been back to the UK erm a few times I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> and they actually lived here for a while in the eighties erm for about five years or maybe longer</u>
<u n="369" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="370" who="S0083">but they've travelled a lot</u>
<u n="371" who="S0084">hope to see you this year <pause dur="short"/> Ah <pause dur="short"/> Even better than flying will definitely be a cruise <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0083" trans="overlap">cruise</u>
<u n="373" who="S0084">I don't know the cost <pause dur="short"/> What planet does this guy live on?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0083">I know</u>
<u n="375" who="S0084">the two but two of you would be ideal for but is that better? Four berth</u>
<u n="376" who="S0083">berth</u>
<u n="377" who="S0084">a four-berth cabin with bathroom toilet and shower and friendly Friday?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0083">what's the next word?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0084">end of the sentence</u>
<u n="380" who="S0083">friendly I think it says yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0084">we have done some great cruises our first being on Love Boat <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> broke for what?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0083">broke her ankle</u>
<u n="383" who="S0084">her ankle and a short time ago plus elbow <pause dur="short"/> very painful and can you imagine wheelchair at the airport et cetera <pause dur="short"/> recovering gradually but will never dance again <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0084">very sad for a trained ballet dancer <pause dur="short"/> bye for now and hope all is well with your family love <unclear/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> That's weird that he's signed it twice then?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0083">well I think he he obviously had more to say <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0083">you know just just carried on</u>
<u n="389" who="S0084">I I say business class perhaps if you come on your own and if the boys could help financially <pause dur="short"/> A there's only one boy</u>
<u n="390" who="S0083">I know but</u>
<u n="391" who="S0084">and B why would it only be boys who could support you financially?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0083">I know</u>
<u n="393" who="S0084">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well you've got to  you've got to  think of it as age</u>
<u n="395" who="S0084">luggage comfortable seats et cetera <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0083">you've got to think of his age and you know he is thinking</u>
<u n="397" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a boy</u>
<u n="398" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> she she was a bit</u>
<u n="399" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0083">I mean she hates her name as it is and it's <trunc>aw</trunc> it's awful and I think it's a lovely name <pause dur="short"/> she texted me last night</u>
<u n="401" who="S0084">was she out?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0083">no she was  she was  at home and I was on my way and I'd just  I'd just  left <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and I was <trunc>g</trunc> waiting for the bus</u>
<u n="403" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0083">and I noticed I'd had a text from her and she said I'm watching Pointless and there are two sisters on there called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> she said What cruel parents</u>
<u n="405" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0083">and I I texted back Well I think that's really nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0084">what on earth is Pointless? Ah the TV show</u>
<u n="408" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know the?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> wowzers</u>
<u n="410" who="S0083">I mean that is a bit much perhaps for the two of them but</u>
<u n="411" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="412" who="S0083">it's nice to have</u>
<u n="413" who="S0084">they sound like witches</u>
<u n="414" who="S0083">a name that stands out you know? I don't know</u>
<u n="415" who="S0084">it's nice to have a name that's quite different</u>
<u n="416" who="S0083">I mean</u>
<u n="417" who="S0084">not that it is anymore</u>
<u n="418" who="S0083" trans="overlap">so your name we wanted something traditional and we thought it would be unusual in those days</u>
<u n="419" who="S0084">not that it was</u>
<u n="420" who="S0083">to have you know everyone was called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or</u>
<u n="421" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0083">you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and we thought well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is is a much more traditional and beautiful name so we went with that <pause dur="short"/> and of course everyone was you know it was  it was  still the most popular girl's name that year</u>
<u n="423" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0083">which we we didn't we hadn't banked on that at all <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="425" who="S0084">yeah good work</u>
<u n="426" who="S0083">well you don't know these things do you? I mean I'm <trunc>gl</trunc> would you rather have been <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0084">no obviously not</u>
<u n="428" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well there you go <pause dur="short"/> you would have been one of millions</u>
<u n="429" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0083"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is actually a lovely name</u>
<u n="431" who="S0084">I really like the name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I did at the time but I do now I think it's a really nice name</u>
<u n="433" who="S0084">mm I like that as well</u>
<u n="434" who="S0083">because it also means star</u>
<u n="435" who="S0084">that's what I mean yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I wouldn't spell it with an A ER <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0083">no it's it's with an A</u>
<u n="437" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> other than star <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> well that's pretty exciting news though I mean for him to have actually</u>
<u n="438" who="S0083">I know <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="439" who="S0084">and he's been the one to write it himself though</u>
<u n="440" who="S0083">I think it's interesting <pause dur="short"/> I think the the broken ankle is actually quite erm crucial <pause dur="short"/> I think what that's done is that erm they've obviously not been performing and I think he's had some time</u>
<u n="441" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="442" who="S0083">and I think he's had some space to actually you know go off on his own</u>
<u n="443" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="444" who="S0083">and write the letter</u>
<u n="445" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0083">and I think she probably is very domineering</u>
<u n="447" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0083">and not that he <pause dur="short"/> you know I mean he obviously enjoys that and is <trunc>ha</trunc> happy about it</u>
<u n="449" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0083">but</u>
<u n="451" who="S0084">it doesn't leave much room for anybody else</u>
<u n="452" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> and I think this has given him some some space to do it</u>
<u n="453" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> er forgive me I can't remember are you his only child?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0083">erm no he has he had a a daughter <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is his second wife and he married erm er a woman called June and they had a little girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who is about I think  I think  she was born ten years after me <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't sure whether it was sixty-seven sixty-eight or sixty-nine but</u>
<u n="455" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0083">it's around that</u>
<u n="457" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0083">that sort of time <pause dur="short"/> erm erm and then they got divorced and he married <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so erm but one of the things that that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said when she wrote cos she did write <pause dur="short"/> I mean she said</u>
<u n="459" who="S0084">oh and there was</u>
<u n="460" who="S0083">that it was from the both of them</u>
<u n="461" who="S0084" trans="overlap">both but it was her and not him</u>
<u n="462" who="S0083">but it was you know she said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has asked me to do this erm but it was  it was  clearly from her</u>
<u n="463" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0083">I mean he might well have done he might have <pause dur="short"/> I mean I presume it was a a shock</u>
<u n="465" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0083">but anyway erm I mean she knew about me but</u>
<u n="467" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0083">anyway <pause dur="short"/> and so she's I think she's  I think she's  quite difficult and I think you know that's where there's going to be a problem</u>
<u n="469" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0083">erm she didn't get on with her and erm I think her name is Samantha <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it is yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't get on with her <pause dur="short"/> now what she said was that Samantha never accepted her but basically they've cut her out of their lives</u>
<u n="471" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh I didn't know this</u>
<u n="472" who="S0083">she said oh it's very sad and it's very you know all the rest of it <pause dur="short"/> but that you know that's what she wants to do and we have to live with that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> and I'm thinking mm it sounds like it's probably the other way around</u>
<u n="473" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="474" who="S0083">erm and I was quite shocked that you know that he would be okay with that but</u>
<u n="475" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0083">maybe he's one of these men anything for a quiet life</u>
<u n="477" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0083">I get the feeling he probably is</u>
<u n="479" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0083">erm so she wouldn't er she wouldn't say anything about her <pause dur="short"/> now what I would like to do is is actually ask him you know in a very sort of gentle way I know you know things are <trunc>diffi</trunc> difficult between them</u>
<u n="481" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0083">but would he be okay could he give me her you know an address or or something so that I could contact her? Would he be okay with that? You know I don't  I don't  I'm not gonna force the issue with them</u>
<u n="483" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0083">but would he mind if I did because I would like to contact my sister <pause dur="short"/> so and I as you <trunc>sa</trunc> as you say I mean this came totally out of the blue and I'd really just resigned myself to the fact that they didn't want to know and that was that there's nothing I could do about it</u>
<u n="485" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="486" who="S0083">I mean I suppose if I did have the money I could have gone out there and and it might have been awkward <pause dur="short"/> it's a long way to go if you're not sure of your welcome <pause dur="short"/> erm it would have forced the issue wouldn't it? But but anyway erm but I had kind of got used to the idea and that was that you know so but this does open up all kinds of things again which is nice</u>
<u n="487" who="S0084" trans="overlap">very exciting</u>
<u n="488" who="S0083">which is nice <pause dur="short"/> I I mean I'm really pleased</u>
<u n="489" who="S0084">it's really good</u>
<u n="490" who="S0083">I was very touched <pause dur="short"/> very touched especially you know when he  when he  addressed it and I thought oh you know that's</u>
<u n="491" who="S0084">yeah of course</u>
<u n="492" who="S0083">I was quite emotional about that</u>
<u n="493" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0083">very emotional about it so</u>
<u n="495" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah it's a really nice way to open the letter</u>
<u n="496" who="S0083">it is <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know the rest of it is a bit odd but anyway</u>
<u n="497" who="S0084">well I mean how old is he</u>
<u n="498" who="S0083">it's it's really nice</u>
<u n="499" who="S0084">anyway?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0083">he's eighty-one</u>
<u n="501" who="S0084">well there you go</u>
<u n="502" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0084">he probably is a bit bananas</u>
<u n="504" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0084">he lives out in Australia</u>
<u n="506" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0084">it is in Queensland and they're all <trunc>b</trunc> bananas</u>
<u n="508" who="S0083">yeah well maybe <pause dur="short"/> well I certainly think erm if you go out there next year you should go you know</u>
<u n="509" who="S0084">well only if you think that that's okay</u>
<u n="510" who="S0083">have a  have a  weekend <pause dur="short"/> oh I <trunc>d</trunc> I absolutely do I think I mean presumably there might have been a couple more letters by that stage</u>
<u n="511" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0083">erm and you know you should do that <pause dur="short"/> whether I'll ever have the money to do it is another matter entirely so</u>
<u n="513" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0083">because I can't imagine how much the flight might be?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0084">it depends when you want to go <pause dur="short"/> I mean the good thing is</u>
<u n="516" who="S0083">well I'd go when it wasn't hot so</u>
<u n="517" who="S0084">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> well yeah I mean Queensland would be okay because it's halfway down on the east</u>
<u n="518" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0084">like if you were if it was the north</u>
<u n="520" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0084">then it would always be hot because it's the tropics <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I mean if you went on standby if you just went on the hope that you might be able to get a seat obviously you can buy them at the airport and they're cheaper because they just want to fill up the the flight</u>
<u n="522" who="S0083">really?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> remember when Will and Emma were living in Melbourne and were saying you can get like you know just come out on standby because obviously I was a student then <pause dur="short"/> and they just oh just wait</u>
<u n="524" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0084">you know to come out and go on a day when you know if you think like mid-week and it's not going to be very busy and they're gonna have empty seats on the plane</u>
<u n="526" who="S0083">but you'd have to be prepared to go there every day you know on the off-chance of</u>
<u n="527" who="S0084">on the off-chance</u>
<u n="528" who="S0083">of getting</u>
<u n="529" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0083">I mean that's that's quite a risk</u>
<u n="531" who="S0084">it is quite a risk <pause dur="short"/> that's why people don't do it if you work obviously because if they've</u>
<u n="532" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0084">only got two weeks and you need to guarantee you've got a holiday</u>
<u n="534" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> but if if I mean is it better to book way ahead or</u>
<u n="535" who="S0084">I still don't know</u>
<u n="536" who="S0083">nearer the time?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0084">erm I mean they do often do deals</u>
<u n="538" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0084">I mean I'm gonna try and keep an eye out for British Airways <pause dur="short"/> but my colleague Steve flew to Cuba recently</u>
<u n="540" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0084">on a holiday there and I was so jealous <pause dur="short"/> erm and he booked with what he thought were British Airways and I said</u>
<u n="542" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0084">british Airways I don't think fly to Cuba but he said yeah yeah it's British Airways <pause dur="short"/> okay fine</u>
<u n="544" who="S0083">I didn't think you could go straight there isn't that what you found?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0084">no you can't go from America</u>
<u n="546" who="S0084">oh from oh okay</u>
<u n="547" who="S0084" trans="overlap">you can go from here but it's Virgin</u>
<u n="548" who="S0083">right <pause dur="short"/> oh I see</u>
<u n="549" who="S0084">which is who I flew with erm or like a tin can</u>
<u n="550" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="551" who="S0084">but you don't want to be doing that</u>
<u n="552" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="553" who="S0084">it turned out British Airways put their name erm to other airlines and you think you're flying with British Airways but you're not</u>
<u n="554" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="555" who="S0084">so Steve ended up flying with some bucket shop erm tin can</u>
<u n="556" who="S0083">surely that's illegal?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0084">which must be illegal so he's following it up with the airline because there's no way they would have gone <pause dur="short"/> because they got really good deals and they thought this is brilliant British Airways fantastic <pause dur="short"/> get to the airport and they find out they're on some sort of</u>
<u n="558" who="S0083">how can they do that?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0084">little tin can</u>
<u n="560" who="S0083">that's so unethical</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">so one screen for the whole cabin it's really bad <pause dur="short"/> it's it's er basically it's erm trade descriptions act isn't it?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0083">that's outrageous</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084" trans="overlap">because they're saying you're getting your British Airways flight and you're not</u>
<u n="564" who="S0083">that is outrageous</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084">so he's gonna follow up with that because that's just absolutely shocking</u>
<u n="566" who="S0083">he'll write to er Anne bloody Robinson</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084">yeah she'll take it up she loves a good cause <pause dur="short"/> so erm with er well when I flew to Australia obviously I got a cheap deal <pause dur="short"/> in fact it wasn't cheap I just flew with someone who I was the cheapest of the lot but really I flew at a peak time so I'm just</u>
<u n="568" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084">wondering if you flew in the middle of the year</u>
<u n="570" who="S0083" trans="overlap">you did you thought erm you knew you'd paid quite a lot because you went out on Boxing Day didn't you?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah my flight was a thousand pounds and that was with an airline who only had one screen in the whole cabin and</u>
<u n="572" who="S0083">oh my God</u>
<u n="573" who="S0084">that was like budget <pause dur="short"/> but when I flew to New Zealand it was about I think it was about six hundred pounds return</u>
<u n="574" who="S0083">that's just <trunc>t</trunc> I can't imagine spending all that money on that <pause dur="short"/> cos you need  you need  money when you're out there</u>
<u n="575" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="576" who="S0083">my God</u>
<u n="577" who="S0084">but if you went during the year but yeah it probably would be about a thousand pounds by the time you <pause dur="short"/> I I mean if you depending on how you feel about it and how they feel about it whether you can stay with them you're gonna have to get accommodation</u>
<u n="578" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0084">and spending money <pause dur="short"/> so it'll be yeah a thousand pounds fifteen hundred pounds</u>
<u n="580" who="S0083">oh God</u>
<u n="581" who="S0084">so yeah I mean maybe in the letter you would write back and say yeah I'll I'll certainly be saving some money so I'm not quite sure when blah blah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0084">erm oh are they coming to the UK any time soon? And then <unclear/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I think she would say if he was I think they're probably not</u>
<u n="585" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean if he's saying that he still owes as much of his mortgage</u>
<u n="586" who="S0083">I mean he's got</u>
<u n="587" who="S0084">as he did when he was twenty</u>
<u n="588" who="S0083">I think it's you see I think she immediately thought</u>
<u n="589" who="S0084">you were after his money</u>
<u n="590" who="S0083">I was after an inheritance which is ridiculous</u>
<u n="591" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0083">but she immediately thought that because she made several comments <pause dur="short"/> not directly</u>
<u n="593" who="S0084">directly yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0083">but you know obliquely</u>
<u n="595" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0083">erm erm and I think he that that might be a way of him saying you know I couldn't help you you know?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0083">could you know because otherwise he he might have suggested but now anyway</u>
<u n="599" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="600" who="S0083">so yeah erm I don't think he realises how tough you know economically it is living here so</u>
<u n="601" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0083">excuse me <pause dur="short"/> erm so yeah oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I might win on the premium bonds but I rather doubt it <pause dur="short"/> but I mean <trunc>y</trunc> you know he hasn't got any family here now you know? Obviously his parents have <trunc>di</trunc> they died some time ago</u>
<u n="603" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0083">his his brother er died I think  I think  I'm sure he said he died well quite a while ago in the early two thousands I think</u>
<u n="605" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0083">erm I can't remember exactly <pause dur="short"/> erm so he's got like nieces and nephews and me and basically that's it <pause dur="short"/> so I mean I think before they had reason to come over and and visit family</u>
<u n="607" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0083">but now no</u>
<u n="609" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah there's no reason to come all this way</u>
<u n="610" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no exactly so</u>
<u n="611" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> so far away why does he have to live in Australia for goodness sake? Why did they move to Australia?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I think he liked it <pause dur="short"/> I think  I think  he liked it there <pause dur="short"/> I don't I mean I don't know  I don't know  I think he went out there because <trunc>h</trunc> he played with various bands and orchestras and things like that and they travelled a lot</u>
<u n="613" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0083">and I'm pretty sure that's what he was referring to you know he the bands on these big cruises I think he used to do that for a while <pause dur="short"/> erm so I think there was a lot of that and I don't know maybe he just enjoyed it there</u>
<u n="615" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0083">I don't know</u>
<u n="617" who="S0084">well I mean in terms of land you get a lot more for your money</u>
<u n="618" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0084">you know if if he does <unclear/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well it looks like they've got quite a nice big place</u>
<u n="621" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="622" who="S0083">you know it's it's er it's a very posh kind of area</u>
<u n="623" who="S0084">oh right okay</u>
<u n="624" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="625" who="S0084">I mean Australia is expensive but it</u>
<u n="626" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I looked  I looked  at it on the erm on Google Maps I looked it up</u>
<u n="627" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0083">well it's it's the Gold Coast so it</u>
<u n="629" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0083">it is an expensive area yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0084">it's a nice nice area</u>
<u n="634" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0084">A nice area to live</u>
<u n="636" who="S0083">so you know they've done quite well for themselves I think</u>
<u n="637" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="639" who="S0084">so does she have kids?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0083">erm didn't I tell you? She had a daughter and er she was murdered <pause dur="short"/> I told you this didn't I?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah you probably did tell me that I don't know why that didn't stick in my mind</u>
<u n="642" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="643" who="S0084">God</u>
<u n="644" who="S0083">I think she was her only child and she was incredibly close to her <pause dur="short"/> I think this is probably where some of the tension arose</u>
<u n="645" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0083">you know that she was so <pause dur="short"/> and it made me think of erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and erm what's her daughter's name? You know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0084">oh erm</u>
<u n="648" who="S0083">what's her <trunc>d</trunc> her name?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0083"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> it made me think of that <pause dur="short"/> she absolutely she was fixated on her</u>
<u n="651" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0083">and I think there was just no space for anyone else</u>
<u n="653" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0083">and she became jealous of her and the way that you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was jealous of erm well</u>
<u n="655" who="S0084">overprotective?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0083">yeah and and had no time for erm Lauren</u>
<u n="657" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it made life very difficult for her and I think it would have been a similar situation I</u>
<u n="659" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0083">that's what I'm reading into it</u>
<u n="661" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0083">that it seems likely that that's what happened <pause dur="short"/> erm no and she she went off and met this erm Egyptian guy married him and er he he murdered her</u>
<u n="663" who="S0084">bloody hell</u>
<u n="664" who="S0083" trans="overlap">there was a big trial and everything yeah <pause dur="short"/> and er she's never got over it obviously so</u>
<u n="665" who="S0084">well no</u>
<u n="666" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and it really is a terrible thing to happen of course it is</u>
<u n="667" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I don't think you ever could could you?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0083">no <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="669" who="S0084" trans="overlap">bloody hell</u>
<u n="670" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0084">right so there's just the two of them then?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="673" who="S0084">and does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> live in Australia?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0083">yes but I don't know where and it's a big place</u>
<u n="675" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0083">erm so I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but if I you know if I had some way of finding her I'd I'd you know it'd be just nice to</u>
<u n="677" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0083">well it would be nice but anyway</u>
<u n="679" who="S0084">baby steps</u>
<u n="680" who="S0083">yes</u>
<u n="681" who="S0084">this is really encouraging it's really positive</u>
<u n="682" who="S0083">it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0084">it's nice to think</u>
<u n="684" who="S0083">it is</u>
<u n="685" who="S0084">that that's not going to be your lasting memory of them</u>
<u n="686" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0084">you know?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="689" who="S0084"><trunc>Th</trunc> that he couldn't actually bring himself to write the letter</u>
<u n="690" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0084">personally</u>
<u n="692" who="S0083">but maybe it was a shock to the system at the time</u>
<u n="693" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0083">and they've both kind of forgotten about it erm but obviously I think it's been kind of</u>
<u n="695" who="S0084">yeah it's been in the background</u>
<u n="696" who="S0083">yeah in the back of his mind and and suddenly he's had a little bit of space to do it and he's actually sat down and done it</u>
<u n="697" who="S0084">he's probably wanted to for a while</u>
<u n="698" who="S0083">I think may be mm</u>
<u n="699" who="S0084">you know he wasn't sure what reaction she would have if she was a bit <pause dur="short"/> if he had picked up on the fact that she was</u>
<u n="700" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0084">a bit unsure about the whole thing <pause dur="short"/> as you say he might have <unclear/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I think he's just used to letting her make decisions and you know that was that really</u>
<u n="703" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well yeah it sounds like it's like that <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling me she hates it when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s parents come and visit because they always say when are you going to get married and when are you going to have kids? <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and saying <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad is very much the same whatever meal they go out for he has exactly what his wife has without fail <pause dur="short"/> whatever she orders he will order</u>
<u n="704" who="S0083"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes mental she goes absolutely spare <pause dur="short"/> as you would because what kind of a life is that? You know even to the point where your wife dictates every meal you have <pause dur="short"/> awful</u>
<u n="706" who="S0083">I think some men just were like that you know whatever the woman said went</u>
<u n="707" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0083">I mean erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like that <pause dur="short"/> you know she organised and booked and did every holiday every house move every you know weekend that they went to see auntie this or uncle that you know she organised it and granddad was happy about it <pause dur="short"/> I mean men just well that's what the women do</u>
<u n="709" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="710" who="S0083">they make you know they do all the domestic stuff I go to work <pause dur="short"/> that's a very clear division</u>
<u n="711" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0083">and it saves them from having to think about it</u>
<u n="713" who="S0084">the precious dears <pause dur="short"/> it was my housemate <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday yesterday and er you know she wants to join the Navy?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="715" who="S0084">and I'd found online a seller who deals in vintage Ladybird books</u>
<u n="716" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0084">and you know sort of collectable</u>
<u n="718" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="719" who="S0084">books erm and there was one called The Sailor which obviously as the name suggests is about the Navy</u>
<u n="720" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="721" who="S0084">and obviously it's got a picture of a male sailor on the front</u>
<u n="722" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="723" who="S0084">and he's <pause dur="short"/> I've so I got it for her and gave it to her yesterday and she opened it and there was completely this moment where she thought what the hell is this? But you know it's only gonna accrue in value like</u>
<u n="724" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="725" who="S0084">they are  they are  worth something and it's you know it is er it is appropriate <pause dur="short"/> but you know when you see something and you think that's perfect and then the closer it gets to</u>
<u n="726" who="S0083">then you think yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0084">the time you think oh I don't know is it?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0083">yes exactly</u>
<u n="729" who="S0084" trans="overlap">but she really did like it</u>
<u n="730" who="S0083">Good</u>
<u n="731" who="S0084">but it's very I think it's from nineteen fifty-seven</u>
<u n="732" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0084">so it's obviously very much of its time</u>
<u n="734" who="S0083">wow that's that's an early one</u>
<u n="735" who="S0084">yeah really early erm so</u>
<u n="736" who="S0083" trans="overlap">God</u>
<u n="737" who="S0084">yeah it's just really hilarious <pause dur="short"/> yeah the men do this <pause dur="short"/> there's a whole series of them people at work so there's a sailor there's a nurse</u>
<u n="738" who="S0083">mm that's right</u>
<u n="739" who="S0084">which is</u>
<u n="740" who="S0083">I remember those yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0084">obviously a a female nurse</u>
<u n="742" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I remember those</u>
<u n="743" who="S0084" trans="overlap">A schoolteacher</u>
<u n="744" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="745" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0083">how funny</u>
<u n="747" who="S0084">absolutely hilarious <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> God I could sleep for about eight days <pause dur="short"/> I'm just not getting eight hours sleep that's the problem and I need</u>
<u n="748" who="S0083">why not?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0084">eight hours sleep <pause dur="short"/> because I'm waking up <trunc>ev</trunc> every night <pause dur="short"/> and in order to get eight hours sleep I have to be in bed asleep by ten pm which is</u>
<u n="750" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="751" who="S0084">just not feasible really</u>
<u n="752" who="S0083">oh well you're gonna have to do it <pause dur="short"/> you used to do it here you were like right bedtime</u>
<u n="753" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0084">well yeah I mean I might turn in but you know it's sort of pottering around and</u>
<u n="755" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="756" who="S0084">and when I've done a few emails or watch a bit of TV and I have to yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0083">no no no</u>
<u n="758" who="S0084">I'll have to be a bit strict I'm tired</u>
<u n="759" who="S0083">yeah you you just have to learn to switch off and er</u>
<u n="760" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="761" who="S0083">try and get your sleep</u>
<u n="762" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yup <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="764" who="S0084">I know</u>
<u n="765" who="S0083">so what are you doing this weekend?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0084">erm drinks after work tomorrow but not a late one</u>
<u n="767" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0084">and then it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday drinks at the weekend</u>
<u n="769" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0084">so I thought I might make a cake Saturday and then get ready and she wants to go for cocktails but luckily because she works at the hotel we can get half price cocktails</u>
<u n="771" who="S0083">oh good</u>
<u n="772" who="S0084">I'll probably go there and then I might try and persuade her by <anon type="place"/> with <anon type="place"/> or the <anon type="place"/> or something <pause dur="short"/> because she was talking about going to <anon type="place"/> which I couldn't imagine anything worse</u>
<u n="773" who="S0083">God I think that would be awful on a Saturday night</u>
<u n="774" who="S0084">absolutely horrendous and it's all just gonna be <trunc>ei</trunc> eighteen-year-olds</u>
<u n="775" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0084">so she's not gonna want to go I mean she's younger than me she's twenty-five but still</u>
<u n="777" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="778" who="S0084">erm I've been trying to persuade her</u>
<u n="779" who="S0083">yeah quite</u>
<u n="780" who="S0084">with not going there <pause dur="short"/> and you have to pay to go in</u>
<u n="781" who="S0083">which is such a cheat honestly</u>
<u n="782" who="S0084">such a rip-off</u>
<u n="783" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="784" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> cheeky</u>
<u n="785" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="786" who="S0084">yup and then sleep Sunday</u>
<u n="787" who="S0083">fair enough</u>
<u n="788" who="S0084">I think</u>
<u n="789" who="S0083">that's what I need to do <pause dur="short"/> what are you sitting there for?</u>
<u n="790" who="S0084">my dates?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="792" who="S0084">okay so the first date <pause dur="short"/> oh do you wanna just go by weekends?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0084">well this weekend I'm around but not really</u>
<u n="795" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0084">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding is the fifth of May so that's and that's next Saturday <pause dur="short"/> so I'm going down to Brighton Saturday morning and I'm staying in a B and B overnight and then I'm seeing <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and co on Sunday</u>
<u n="797" who="S0083" trans="overlap">on the Sunday mm</u>
<u n="798" who="S0084">obviously then it's the bank holiday which is nice so</u>
<u n="799" who="S0083">oh right</u>
<u n="800" who="S0084">I'm off on the Monday</u>
<u n="801" who="S0083">okay so we might see you on the Monday?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0084">er possibly yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0083">okay</u>
<u n="804" who="S0084">and the following weekend I'm where? I was gonna be going to <anon type="place"/> but I'm not going now so we've rearranged it somewhere around <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding is the eighteenth which is erm the Friday</u>
<u n="805" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="806" who="S0084">so I'm around on the Thursday night if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to go out for a meal or if she wants me to come around sort of blahdy-blah whatever <pause dur="short"/> whatever she wants to do so I'm around in the evening but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I are leaving first thing erm Friday morning <pause dur="short"/> and then we're staying overnight and then back on the Saturday which is the nineteenth <pause dur="short"/> erm and so yes I'll be</u>
<u n="807" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="808" who="S0084">here on the Sunday <pause dur="short"/> and then the following weekend I'm in <anon type="place"/> because <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is doing this ten k run <pause dur="short"/> well actually I'm in <anon type="place"/> on the twenty-<trunc>s</trunc> what's the following weekend then? The eighteenth nineteenth twenty-sixth twenty-fourth or twenty-fifth I'm on a course which is the Thursday and Friday in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then I'll probably stay at <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s on the Friday night and then she's doing this run somewhere on the Saturday then I might come back Saturday evening</u>
<u n="809" who="S0083">so is that the twenty-sixth then?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0084">well what's the Saturday then? Yeah the twenty-sixth yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0083" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="812" who="S0084">back on the twenty-sixth from London <pause dur="short"/> and then the following weekend it's the Jubilee weekend and we're going to Sheffield for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday see meet her dad and see some school friends</u>
<u n="813" who="S0083">so what's that?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0084">that's the fourth of June is it? Is that the Monday? So there's so the Saturday is the second of June</u>
<u n="815" who="S0083">alright</u>
<u n="816" who="S0084">and then I'm off all of that week</u>
<u n="817" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and then you're back?</u>
<u n="818" who="S0084">I'm back I don't know Sunday Monday I'm not sure</u>
<u n="819" who="S0083">oh okay</u>
<u n="820" who="S0084">I'm off all that week <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s off all that week the Jubilee week <pause dur="short"/> because obviously the bank holiday is Monday and Tuesday so everyone so we'll probably end up staying in Sheffield on the Monday <pause dur="short"/> on at least on the Sunday night because everyone will be going out on</u>
<u n="821" who="S0083">fair enough</u>
<u n="822" who="S0084">Sunday Monday and Tuesday so</u>
<u n="823" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0084">erm and then I'm around the rest of the week</u>
<u n="825" who="S0083">mm mm and when's <pause dur="short"/> oh so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is erm?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0084">eighteenth</u>
<u n="827" who="S0083">the eighteenth</u>
<u n="828" who="S0084">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>s is the fifth</u>
<u n="829" who="S0083">and is that?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0084">that's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0083">that's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="834" who="S0084">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is in Brighton <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then I've booked the time off but I haven't booked the flights yet to go to <anon type="place"/> on the <trunc>t</trunc> eleventh of July for a long weekend which is a Wednesday evening <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got all of that week off <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen the new house <unclear/> and I won't get to see it obviously at the wedding so</u>
<u n="835" who="S0083">so and you're going for a week then?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0084">er no I'm going Wednesday to probably Saturday</u>
<u n="837" who="S0083">okay</u>
<u n="838" who="S0084">and that's it</u>
<u n="839" who="S0083">okay that's well that's quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> blimey</u>
<u n="840" who="S0084">that's quite a lot yeah</u>
<u n="841" who="S0083">bl-imey</u>
<u n="842" who="S0084">I know that's why I had to say no to all the hen parties <pause dur="short"/> the <unclear/> and hen party was last weekend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s hen party is this weekend and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding is next weekend</u>
<u n="843" who="S0083">wow</u>
<u n="844" who="S0084">so you just can't I mean</u>
<u n="845" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="846" who="S0084"><unclear/> and a wedding a hen party would have been hundreds of pounds so</u>
<u n="847" who="S0083">yeah it would have been fun but anyway</u>
<u n="848" who="S0084">it would have been really fun yeah <pause dur="short"/> just you know you've got to see the light at the end of the tunnel</u>
<u n="849" who="S0083">exactly</u>
<u n="850" who="S0084">like I saw <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> on Tuesday and she was saying oh I haven't got nearly as much money saved as I need and I said well can't your folks lend you? And she said her mum obviously is a bit of a cow bag just said categorically before she'd even got the words out no there's no way I'm lending you any money which is really charming <pause dur="short"/> but to get into the country you need to have five thousand Australian dollars in your bank account to prove that you can sustain yourself <pause dur="short"/> and they haven't just plucked this number out the year that's how much you need</u>
<u n="851" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0084">but she doesn't have that so she's <trunc>a</trunc> arranged for her parents to give her two of the thousand dollars erm like a thousand dollars each the day before she flies <pause dur="short"/> so it's in the account and then when she goes through it'll look like she has the money and then take it out again</u>
<u n="853" who="S0083">right okay</u>
<u n="854" who="S0084">but the thing is then she won't have any money</u>
<u n="855" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well she's <pause dur="short"/> no quite</u>
<u n="856" who="S0084">so her dad said I can lend you some money but he he's not flush by any means so</u>
<u n="857" who="S0083">no I mean it's it's hard for</u>
<u n="858" who="S0084">you can't and you can't rely on your parents to do that</u>
<u n="859" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="860" who="S0084">it's not really very fair that they fund your trip</u>
<u n="861" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I mean if they're wealthy then that's another matter but most you know ordinary people are</u>
<u n="862" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> you're generally just surviving aren't you?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0083">yeah pretty much</u>
<u n="864" who="S0084">so and plus it's her <pause dur="short"/> she is an adult and she wants to go on this trip then</u>
<u n="865" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="866" who="S0084">she has to pay for it</u>
<u n="867" who="S0083" trans="overlap">she's gonna have to work for another year and save up the same as you</u>
<u n="868" who="S0084">well she's paid for her flight she's off she doesn't have a job <pause dur="short"/> you know she's booked the flights for the fourteenth of June or the tenth of June or something I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> she's going erm but she hasn't got money saved <pause dur="short"/> she'll just come back</u>
<u n="869" who="S0083">well what <pause dur="short"/> oh I see</u>
<u n="870" who="S0084">because her flight's now is June</u>
<u n="871" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I mean what happens if you go there on on holiday and stay there?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0084">they'll kick you out</u>
<u n="873" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="874" who="S0084">I mean you can't use any kind of <trunc>id</trunc> identification because they'll know that you're not meant to be there</u>
<u n="875" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0084">so you have to apply for a working visa which she's been granted</u>
<u n="877" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="878" who="S0084">erm which is why you need to have the five thousand dollars</u>
<u n="879" who="S0083" trans="overlap">but if she doesn't hasn't got the money there then</u>
<u n="880" who="S0084">they won't let you in</u>
<u n="881" who="S0083">she's <pause dur="short"/> they won't let her no</u>
<u n="882" who="S0084">yeah they'll just send you back which is in absolute waste</u>
<u n="883" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and what's she gonna do?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0084">well she says to start work straightaway I mean she wanted to go all around</u>
<u n="885" who="S0083" trans="overlap">is she gonna  is she gonna  take a loan out or something?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0084">well I don't know she's only just cleared herself of debt</u>
<u n="887" who="S0083">well she can take a loan out so the money was there but how would she pay it back from there?</u>
<u n="888" who="S0084" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> well basically she's fine for getting the money in</u>
<u n="889" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="890" who="S0084">she's just not gonna have any money when she's there</u>
<u n="891" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="892" who="S0084">because her mum at least will take her side of the share of the money back <pause dur="short"/> so she'll have to her plan at the moment is to bum around in Brisbane of all places and some other random cities just having a nice time and then she'll think about work <pause dur="short"/> and I said to her she'll need to work almost straightaway because the cost of living is so high you need to be earning their salary <pause dur="short"/> but obviously she wants to have a rest and a break and</u>
<u n="893" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0084">erm it's gonna be fairly hard <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously unless she teaches summer school</u>
<u n="895" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="896" who="S0084">what is she really gonna be doing?</u>
<u n="897" who="S0083">yeah quite</u>
<u n="898" who="S0084">until the schools go back in September or whenever they start back <pause dur="short"/> I mean luckily the curriculum doesn't sound like it's that different to ours</u>
<u n="899" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="900" who="S0084">so she would erm the PGCE is recognised globally so</u>
<u n="901" who="S0083" trans="overlap">right so she shouldn't have much of a problem</u>
<u n="902" who="S0084">she wouldn't</u>
<u n="903" who="S0083">it's just I mean how many jobs are there for primary school teachers?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well this is it I mean certainly in the UK if you don't have a job by the spring the summer term</u>
<u n="905" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="906" who="S0084">you won't have a job for September</u>
<u n="907" who="S0083">Oscar in or out <pause dur="short"/> oh thank you <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="908" who="S0084">so I don't know I mean she's booked the flight the return flight for February</u>
<u n="909" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="910" who="S0084">but you can  you can  change it</u>
<u n="911" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="912" who="S0084">it's you pay a premium but you can change it</u>
<u n="913" who="S0083">hello</u>
<u n="914" who="S0084">but you need to be <unclear/> really because I mean you don't want to tie yourself in</u>
<u n="915" who="S0083">well it gives her some time to to sort things</u>
<u n="916" who="S0084">well it might mean that if she can't get a job and all she's got is the money that in her pocket which might only be a couple of thousand <pause dur="short"/> that's great for a really nice holiday but she'll be back after three months because the money will have run out</u>
<u n="917" who="S0083" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0084">but it does mean <pause dur="short"/> I mean she must have something she must have like a couple of grand at least <pause dur="short"/> she's booked all her flights and everything so that's fine</u>
<u n="919" who="S0083">yeah it just depends how er</u>
<u n="920" who="S0084">but if she's got a couple of grand</u>
<u n="921" who="S0083">how expensive it is to live there</u>
<u n="922" who="S0084">very expensive</u>
<u n="923" who="S0083">well where where is she gonna stay?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0084">she's gonna have to stay in hostels which is expensive and annoying you know you don't want to stay in a hostel when you're thirty</u>
<u n="925" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="926" who="S0084">that's why people do it when they're you know eighteen or twenty-one</u>
<u n="927" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah and they don't  they don't  care</u>
<u n="928" who="S0084">and rest</u>
<u n="929" who="S0083">he does like it up there it's really funny <pause dur="short"/> cos I forget he's there and I turn around and oh</u>
<u n="930" who="S0084">cat face</u>
<u n="931" who="S0083">it's your favourite person over there <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0084">hiya <pause dur="short"/> Funny article <pause dur="short"/> yeah so she'll be off before you know it</u>
<u n="933" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="S0084">she said I saw her on Tuesday and we went to the cinema erm</u>
<u n="935" who="S0083">yeah what did you go and see?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0084">oh it was some stupid horror film it was pretty funny actually <pause dur="short"/> there was one girl who was getting really into it you know these stupid teen horror films and it was  it was  sending itself up and it was quite funny</u>
<u n="937" who="S0083" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="938" who="S0084">and erm but one girl was taking it very seriously and they were in the cabin and you know like just don't go upstairs <pause dur="short"/> she was shouting Don't stand by the window don't do it <pause dur="short"/> you know she was really really scared and then obviously something happens to the kid and she was screaming</u>
<u n="939" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="940" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I mean normally you don't like it when people talk through movies but she <trunc>wa</trunc> was pretty funny <pause dur="short"/> especially because erm it is a bit of it's it's a sort of a spoof in a way and er Bradley Whitford or whatever his name is from</u>
<u n="941" who="S0083">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="942" who="S0084">West Wing Kay was in it and he was so funny <pause dur="short"/> there's a scene where they do a little dance routine and it was pretty hilarious</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="943" who="S0084">ho-hum Dominoes have sent me a text message Domino's Pizza any size pizza seven ninety-nine <pause dur="short"/> delivery every day</u>
<u n="944" who="S0083">any size? Can we have one that's this big?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0084">well yeah basically that's what I think that's what they're saying <pause dur="short"/> terms and conditions apply</u>
<u n="946" who="S0083">oh that'll be alright <pause dur="short"/> I just fancy a pizza you shouldn't have said that</u>
<u n="947" who="S0084">Pisa <pause dur="short"/> that's not what dad's got on the menu for this evening <pause dur="short"/> probably not Pisa</u>
<u n="948" who="S0083">erm what's oh he's working isn't he?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0084">yup that's what I mean he's not gonna be home until half six <pause dur="short"/> that's why I can go around and see erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="950" who="S0083">that might be nice actually rather than leave him on his own <pause dur="short"/> erm and you can tell him about this <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="951" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="952" who="S0083">I haven't spoken to him so erm although I did tell dad and he was quite he was very pleased to hear it so er erm</u>
<u n="953" who="S0084">you told dad?</u>
<u n="954" who="S0083">yeah he phoned just to say oh that he'd he'd got a new fridge yesterday he was waiting for that and erm</u>
<u n="955" who="S0084" trans="overlap">he'd called just to tell you he'd got a new fridge?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0083">well no there was that and also we need to fill some forms in and he'd found a phone number <trunc>s</trunc> so he was hoping to be able to get through to this person <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know if they have or not but they were gonna try again so</u>
<u n="957" who="S0084">what happened to the woman who came around and did the assessment?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0083">well we haven't heard from her so</u>
<u n="959" who="S0084">so that's who he's trying to call or just the fact <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no this is about the other form so yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know</u>
<u n="961" who="S0084">I'll have to get him to follow up with that woman</u>
<u n="962" who="S0083">yes I mean he did phone her once I think</u>
<u n="963" who="S0084">yeah he did yeah</u>
<u n="964" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0084">so if that means that there is funding available for Richard for September</u>
<u n="966" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well exactly</u>
<u n="967" who="S0084">I mean you need to get on that because</u>
<u n="968" who="S0083">I know we do I know</u>
<u n="969" who="S0084">you need to apply</u>
<u n="970" who="S0083">I know</u>
<u n="971" who="S0084">important</u>
<u n="972" who="S0083">definitely yeah</u>
<u n="973" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="975" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm so tired <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> but tomorrow is Friday <unclear/> to the Friday a day of work but</u>
<u n="976" who="S0083">Don't you?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0084">my Mac exploded or imploded</u>
<u n="978" who="S0083">what?</u>
<u n="979" who="S0084">yesterday it just went ah goodnight and just wouldn't start and wouldn't run programmes and</u>
<u n="980" who="S0083">oh my God</u>
<u n="981" who="S0084">yeah apparently it's quite new it's only it's less than a year old and it was just really unhappy so the IT</u>
<u n="982" who="S0083" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>y</trunc> you mean your one at work?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0084">yeah not mine</u>
<u n="984" who="S0083">oh I thought you meant yours</u>
<u n="985" who="S0084">no no at work</u>
<u n="986" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="987" who="S0084">sorry at work <pause dur="short"/> so the IT help desk unhelpful desk has given me a little laptop to use but it's so pathetic it's really small and I can't get it to do what I want it to do <pause dur="short"/> but they've found an old Mac and they've taken everything off the hard drive on mine and put it on there so hopefully I'll be able to use that <pause dur="short"/> fingers crossed</u>
<u n="988" who="S0083">Good</u>
<u n="989" who="S0084">tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> it's just so frustrating</u>
<u n="990" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="991" who="S0084">but that's my breakfast sausage cup <pause dur="short"/> I need to really sort of knock that on the head cos I do go every week but it just wouldn't be Friday without</u>
<u n="992" who="S0083">no apparently not</u>
<u n="993" who="S0084">sausage cup <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="994" who="S0083">oh dear never mind</u>
<u n="995" who="S0084">and we move into our new office in <trunc>t</trunc> two weeks' time</u>
<u n="996" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="997" who="S0084">next week I'm volunteering I'm using my seven hours to volunteer at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="998" who="S0083">are you? Oh</u>
<u n="999" who="S0084" trans="overlap">for the charity shop erm tidying and selling and I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="1000" who="S0083">well good luck with that it's just an absolute jumble sale in there</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0084">I'm so excited <pause dur="short"/> you know how I like it tidy?</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0083">you do</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0084">I'm getting my Marigolds on</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0083">it won't look like that for long</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0084">Kim and Aggie style <pause dur="short"/> I can't wait <pause dur="short"/> and there might be some hidden gems in the back room you know but I doubt it</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I I doubt it</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they do</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0083">yeah right</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0084">actually have a sale there</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0083">oh that's nice though</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0084">so that's yeah that's where we're doing it <pause dur="short"/> because the other bit of volunteering stuff is go and build a bird's nest or something and you know?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0083">that would be cute</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0084">it would be  it would be  nice but they were doing it this week in the rain</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0084">on the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm a bird hide or something</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well I don't know you you'd quite like that wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0084">I would if it wasn't persisting it down then yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0084">but</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0083">oh well</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0084">yeah it's good that they do it and they give you the option to volunteer</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0084">a day a year so it's good</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0084">yup it is good <pause dur="short"/> so that's Monday then I'm in the office in my current office Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0084">and then they're moving us over the weekend</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0083" trans="overlap">over the weekend yeah</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0084">so it's power down pack everything up next week <pause dur="short"/> it's quite good actually everyone's have to shed</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0084">all the crap that you accumulate <pause dur="short"/> so that's good so I've been having a sort out</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0083" trans="overlap">so and where is it then?</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0084">it's the <anon type="place"/> it's the other building</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0083">really?</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0084">yup so over time what everyone's speculating is that they'll move us all over over there</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0084">and sell our building <pause dur="short"/> which is a nice building sort of the brown brick</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0084">building and sell it on to the property developers <pause dur="short"/> because all of that that's now flats was <anon type="place"/> land and bit by bit they've sold it off and it's it's basically been keeping the <anon type="place"/> afloat</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0083">selling things off?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0084">selling things off <pause dur="short"/> so but the thing is you've only got one access road</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0083">well what happens when they when they've er ran out of things to sell?</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0084">well I think that's when the redundancies come</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0083">so what what have they done to the printing er?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0084">well this where we are now</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know they sold it off but but I mean</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0084">yeah they've sold the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1048" who="S0083" trans="overlap">they're not offices are they?</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0084">no they're it was a hangar</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0084">so they've brought in a company to put in a low ceiling and better flooring</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0084">and lights and all the rest of it <pause dur="short"/> the reported cost is two million pounds now I don't know if that's true</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0083">well why would <trunc>th</trunc> why bother why not just sell that bit off and leave you where you were?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0084">well there's er there's more  there's more  space to move everybody into that building rather than move everybody from there into ours and ours is older</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0083">oh I see okay</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0084">and so they've moved us all into that but I think ELT's grown erm at an unsustainable rate</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0084">very quickly where we actually now er are no more than two hundred and then education they downsized and they had redundancies and they offshore all of their page makeup and all of their costs and they're turning a a really good budget now they're they're making quite a a healthy profit <pause dur="short"/> eLT is not making a profit this is the first year that I've been there that we won't get a bonus</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0084">we won't meet budget this year which is really worrying</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0084">it's mainly and mainly because we sell <pause dur="short"/> I mean the education team don't sell internationally in the same that we do our markets our international markets <pause dur="short"/> and because of what's happening to the global market at the moment that's affecting our sales</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0084">so our <anon type="place"/> office closed recently you know the Arab Spring probably</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0083">right</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0084">didn't help the <anon type="place"/> office closed <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/> office closed</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0084">erm yeah I don't know what's gonna happen? I mean if if you have two hundred people <pause dur="short"/> basically we don't have enough people to publish the number of products that we have so they're hiring but at the same time we've got too many people <pause dur="short"/> so I think they're really gonna have to look at</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0083">oh it's strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0084">what we can actually manage to publish and that was the whole thing behind this new restructure in the ELT</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0083">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0084">even though I've been there two years and we've had three restructures <pause dur="short"/> hopefully this is it for the restructure but they've decided that they're not gonna publish more products than we already have they're just going to look at respeccing what we already have in theory <pause dur="short"/> which should be less work but boost sales and look at obviously digitising everything that we have</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0084">but I don't know</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0084">but we have a hell of a lot of work on at the moment just and that our digital capacity just isn't isn't there</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0084">you know that we've had to put on hold two of our global learning courses so creating something that's completely online</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0083">mm mm</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0084">and no books <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0083">wow</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0084">which American institutions and <anon type="place"/> institutions love</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0084">they want to be completely paperless <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> erm but I don't think we have the functionality and the capability there because it's just we've had to put them on hold and it's embarrassing</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0084">I don't know I think the Press is <unclear/></u>
<u n="1088" who="S0083">well I suppose you've got to decide if that's definitely the way you you've got to go</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0084">well certainly that's if that's what the markets are telling you they want that's what you have to do you have to respond</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0084">so I don't know I mean it's in terms of what we have at the moment I don't think our jobs are in danger because we have too much work <pause dur="short"/> but there's certainly our department isn't gonna hire to the point where <trunc>s</trunc> one of the lads in my department is doing maternity cover and what normally <trunc>ha</trunc> what's happened in the last two instances is they've given the person doing maternity cover a permanent job</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0084">because there's money in the budget to do so and we need help <pause dur="short"/> that won't happen this time</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0084">and it is really unfair because there's two people in this department who were hired <trunc>a</trunc> after maternity leave but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't be <pause dur="short"/> and he gave up a full-time job to do this one on the  on the  hope that it would lead to turn permanent</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0083">yeah I mean  I mean  you <trunc>d</trunc> because you you know</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0084">but you can't ever go guarantee</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0083">it's  you know it's  only for <trunc>matern</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I mean usually maternity cover that's it isn't it? So</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0084">well yeah but not it doesn't seem to be at the <anon type="place"/> and then then you get hired that's</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0083">well I think that they've been lucky</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0084">that's not</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0083">in the past because that wouldn't normally happen</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> well I think a lot of the time it sort of happens from within</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0084">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> certainly <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was hired who's another production controller but for education and he was hired as maternity cover but from erm internally</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0084">he was working in finance <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was working in the content services department and then came across because he wanted a job in our department and thought risk it for a biscuit <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's gonna pay off though there's no money <pause dur="short"/> but it does make you wonder like if they're gonna manage to promote people when the time comes</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0083">yeah <trunc>e</trunc> exactly <pause dur="short"/> well I mean this you know <pause dur="short"/> in the long-term that's not gonna worry you too much is it?</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0084">no but I'd like to leave as a production controller and not a trainee</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0084">and I don't know how long it'll take</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0083">to get to that</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0084">to get there</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0083">okay <pause dur="short"/> well you'll have to wait and see won't you?</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0084">yeah but I mean I'm already worrying you know it's the end of April which I can't really believe</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0083">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0084">I'm not quite sure how that happened</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0083">no I'm not</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0084">erm but we are</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0083">I wish it was a bit nicer I I really enjoy the light evenings now <pause dur="short"/> it's always a huge relief to me when it's lighter in the evenings</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0084">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0083">but I mean the weather you just wouldn't think <pause dur="short"/> everything's growing like crazy out there</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0084">yeah isn't it?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0083">and you know including the weeds and and I can't get out there to do anything so</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0084">yeah we need it though</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0083">as soon as  as soon as  the rain stops we're gonna have to have a blitz out there</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0083">we did need it <pause dur="short"/> yes definitely <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0084">that's fine</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0083">it has encouraged</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0083">all kinds of growth everywhere</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0084">I can see the honeysuckle oh that looks nice <pause dur="short"/> in the corner <pause dur="short"/> is that a honeysuckle the yellow?</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0083">no it's</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0083">erm er forsythia I think it's called</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0083">I mean it's it's very cheerful erm and it's bright yellow in the spring yeah</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0084">I mean really we need to cut down the honeysuckle on the</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0083">we do</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0084">trellis</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0083">I know we do</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0084">sooner rather than later no matter what the weather <pause dur="short"/> because as soon as that starts blooming</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know I'm just not going I'm not going out there in the pouring rain and pulling out plants</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well no but I mean on a day like this I know it's it stop starts stop</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0084">starts because of the wind</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0083">it is yeah</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0084">but actually if you were to run out now and not that any of us are going to for an hour</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0084">and hack it down while it's cold and windy but actually not raining that's what we need to do</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0083">I'll see  I'll see  how how I feel on the next few <trunc>d</trunc> you know and if it's <pause dur="short"/> I mean we haven't had that much rain today yesterday was horrible</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0084">yeah it's been horrible all week</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0083" trans="overlap">but it's but today has been better it's just incredibly windy</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0083">erm I mean it wouldn't be pleasant going out there in all this wind <pause dur="short"/> erm but I'll see how the weather is cos I mean I I am aware of you know things really need to be done <pause dur="short"/> I mean look how much the grass has grown?</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah you can't <unclear/></u>
<u n="1158" who="S0083">but you can't cut it</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0084">no I know</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0083">Cos it's just too wet</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0083">so we're gonna have to wait until it's all finished</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0083">I mean I don't know I might have to risk it you know on a  on a  bright afternoon you know and cut it <pause dur="short"/> cos if we can it's if it's gonna rain for another two weeks solidly then what are you supposed to do?</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0084">well there's <trunc>no</trunc> nothing you can do <pause dur="short"/> but yes I mean the the grass will just have to grow</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0084">but the rest of it we can <unclear/></u>
<u n="1168" who="S0083">well we'll we'll have to <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to give it a try yeah <pause dur="short"/> I do  I do  need to do it I know</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0084">it's <trunc>m</trunc> my only concern is that big bracken because if we let it bloom it's gonna be a total nightmare</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah really hard to do <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0084">we need to do it the next week</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0084">because really</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0083">yeah I should do</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0084">it was horrible chopping it down last year</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know  I know  it was I know</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0084">but that's the only thing the rest of it we can dig it up as we <trunc>g</trunc> you know when the weather is</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0083">as we go yeah</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0084">a bit nicer</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0083">I should go out there and do that at least</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0084">well <trunc>d</trunc> don't do it on your own cos it's a nightmare but certainly when</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0083">I could have a go at it yeah</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0084">the next time I'm here if it's like this we can go out</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0084">and do it <pause dur="short"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if he's here</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0083">even if I make a start yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll see how it is over the next couple of days</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1188" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I <trunc>d</trunc> I haven't got anything planned so I'm at Dido's on Monday</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0083">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s on Tuesday</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0084">and you said you emailed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1192" who="S0083">I did yes</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0084">about when he was next round?</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0084">yeah cos now that you've put the idea in my head</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0083">I know</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0084">I just really</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0083">I know <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0084">I need to get out</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0083">I just need him to reply <pause dur="short"/> I mean if he says that it's a bit awkward then fine at least we know erm</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0083">but it's annoying when he <trunc>d</trunc> he does this though <pause dur="short"/> I mean sometimes he replies straightaway and other times it just goes on <pause dur="short"/> I have kind of picked up a couple of times and actually erm if there's something he feels he can't answer he just doesn't answer</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0083">you know some people are like that?</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0084">yeah <trunc>absolu</trunc> they don't wanna hurt your feelings</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0084">they just ignore you as if that's not gonna hurt your feelings</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and I think no just say</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's a bloke thing though</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0083">I think it is <pause dur="short"/> I think it is</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0084">he's not addressing the problem</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0084">but that's fine I mean if you emailed him like a week ago and he hasn't replied then I think that's a bit of a tell-tale</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0083">no erm erm what's today?</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0084">Thursday</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0083">I think I did it on Tuesday</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0084">okay so he'll just be rushing around</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0083">ooh I don't know</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0084">you're hungry</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0083">it's rumbly</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0084">rumbly in your tumbly?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0083">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've had some another cup of tea I don't know</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0084">gosh Gromit</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0083">and I don't know what to do for dinner <pause dur="short"/> oh I hate</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0084">egg and chips?</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0083">oh I think we've only got one egg left</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0084">oh no</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0083">mm we had  we had  eggs the other day</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0084">yum in my tum</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0083">there's lots of stuff in the freezer cos I I got stuff in cos she wanted me to so</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0084">waffles?</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0083">yeah there's lots of waffles there's also erm you know like these vegetable burger things</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0083">cos she likes those and they're very easy</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0083">and kind of vegetable fish fingers and things and I'm thinking really? Fish <trunc>fing</trunc> and it's just cos it's the shape that's all</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0083" trans="overlap">so it's it's all a bit strange but anyway that's fine</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0083">erm because I because she just doesn't cook <vocal desc="laugh"/> She heats something up and she just doesn't <pause dur="short"/> I mean she did the other day but that's the first time for weeks that she's cooked anything and er she always says oh you don't have to do it for me but I  but I  do it cos I'm gonna do it anyway <pause dur="short"/> but sometimes I really just don't want to so we have pizza or scrambled eggs</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0084">yum</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0083">so for whatever's in the freezer and that's that</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0084">pizza and scrambled eggs together</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0083">well no</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0084">yum</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0083">dear</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0084">there's a pizza with an egg in it isn't there?</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0083" trans="overlap">is there?</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0084" trans="overlap">florentine or something? Yeah they crack an egg in it</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0083">oh my God</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0084">florentine I think is the one with spinach</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0083">spinach yeah it's spinach and egg</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0084">there you go</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0083">that's what it is Florentine it's it's usually you know it's it's a bed of spinach that's been nicely cooked and flavoured and and you poach an egg on the top of it</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh well that's the name of the pizza Florentine yeah</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0083">well I've never seen that on a pizza</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0083">which seems a bit strange</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0084" trans="overlap">pizza Express do one I think</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0083">it seems a bit odd</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0084">yum yum yum in my tum</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0083">no I'm sure that's not right <vocal desc="laugh"/> it doesn't seem right to me <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0084">well no cos it's just egg on bread isn't it? With tomato and cheese</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah it's just you know I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> you know pizza is</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0084">Pisa</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0083">you know a real Italian pizza is is as it is it's not meant to have all these strange and weird and wonderful things on them so <pause dur="short"/> oh anyway <pause dur="short"/> oh I really fancy a pizza now I wish you hadn't said that and you keep on about it</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0084">put a pizza in the  a pizza in the  oven</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0083">I might do</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0084">have you got one of your garlic mushroom ones?</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0083">I don't know what's left actually cos she's been hitting them quite hard erm and and whatever's left</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0084">I had one for dinner last night</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0083">did you?</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0084">for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0083">oh you might be having another one tonight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1275" who="S0084">well if dad has got a pizza that'd be find by me but I don't think he's probably cooking what he cooks every time I go around which is chicken potato and veg <pause dur="short"/> which is fine because I never have</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0083">no and you like that yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0084">meat in the house so <pause dur="short"/> well I'd rather he didn't cook the potato <pause dur="short"/> well I'd rather he mashes old potatoes if I was to put in a request but it's fine <pause dur="short"/> it's him cooking not me so</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0083">well you could always like peel potatoes when you get there and sort of so that when he comes in it's that's ready and you know?</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0084">yeah I could do <pause dur="short"/> I could do <pause dur="short"/> I mean I I just let him do what he's thinking of doing</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0084">because if you start messing with the the way he does things he doesn't like it <pause dur="short"/> no he doesn't like he doesn't know what's happening <pause dur="short"/> he's got a very straight idea of what's gonna happen</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0083">oh dear</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0084">I don't want to mess with that cos it might confuse the poor boy</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0083">you see I think that's I think he has taken a retrograde step</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0084">well no just that he <trunc>rea</trunc> his reactions all a lot slower when we were driving to wherever we went on the walk</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0083">I don't  I don't  mean in age I mean because he hasn't had me to nag him to to to think in a different way you know?</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0084">well possibly <pause dur="short"/> I mean but I don't think that's a problem to him and it's</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0084">certainly not a problem for a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>I mean</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0083">no it's not</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0084">they <pause dur="short"/> but in in a way he's doing things that he would never have done before</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah and that's that's a very good thing</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0084">which is fine <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously the things he does now are things that you suggested that he do rambling</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0084">volunteering <pause dur="short"/> but they're things that he enjoys so fine</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0083" trans="overlap">well if if he enjoys it that's absolutely fine</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean certainly he gets involved to quite a degree</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0083">yeah he does yeah</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0084">you know he's he's treasurer and <trunc>s</trunc> something else and</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0083">I know</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0084">what have you so</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0083">no it's all good</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0084">it's it's good that he gets out and you know</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0083">no it is it's very good</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0084">and meets people <pause dur="short"/> but yeah certainly when he was driving I noticed that his reactions are quite slow but then that's probably only because I'm I drive now and I compare his driving to my driving <pause dur="short"/> and he's I've always thought he was a very safe driver which he is</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> well as you get older your reactions do slow down</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> but probably you know just sort of hypersensitive to it because</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0083">mm you're you're</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0084">I know what I'm looking out for now</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yes exactly yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0084">you know without realising I'm not judging him deliberately I don't mean that I'm judging him at all <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1312" who="S0083">oh</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0084">where's my dinner?</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0083">yes where's my dinner? Who's going to cook me dinner?</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0084">your dinner's in the freezer</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0083">well it might be</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0084">has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> eaten all her Easter eggs yet?</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0083">no she's not eating er very much at all <pause dur="short"/> she seems to be really off chocolate and I don't know why</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0084">weirdo</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0083">well she eats about three packets of crisps a day</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> you know I I only finished my chocolate bunny at the weekend so that was quite restrained</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0083">that was actually for you yeah</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> so that was a good two weeks after Easter finished</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0083" trans="overlap">she's nearly finished her bunny but she's got another thing on the side</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0084" trans="overlap">has she?</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0084">well let's go and liberate it</u>
<u n="1328" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1329" who="S0084">which means you lose quite frankly <pause dur="short"/> has she heard anything from the Boleyn University application?</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0083">erm no er I mean she won't will she or do they send like a?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0084">well they should at least acknowledge the application I mean if they have</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0083" trans="overlap">an an acknowledgement that's the word I was thinking of yeah</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0083">erm I don't know</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0084">do you know she hadn't even told dad? She's useless she doesn't tell him anything <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know their their relationship is a bit weird but still when I was around there the weekend that she was</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0083" trans="overlap">what do you mean she hasn't told him?</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0084">she hadn't told him he didn't know anything about it <pause dur="short"/> she's shocking <pause dur="short"/> I was there <trunc>Eas</trunc> whenever it was the Sunday that she was applying because I'd been here on the Saturday night</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0083">yeah that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0084">hadn't I or at some point? And I made a passing comment to dad about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> potentially not being here in September and he said why where is she going? And I said well you know I know she doesn't want us talking about it that much but you know the Boleyn application and he said What? <pause dur="short"/> he knew nothing about it she'd not mentioned it at all <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't do anything to <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know he's equally as bad but neither of them make a</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0083">she</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0084">particular effort to see each other</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0083">you see he she doesn't</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0084">if he doesn't</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0083">she doesn't feel <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0084">then she's obviously she doesn't need to either</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0083">she doesn't feel that she should have to make the first move and I I tend to agree</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0084">well that's fine</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0083">but that is after all how he is <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'm but <trunc>th</trunc> you know he shouldn't be like that but he is</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0083">and I I I <trunc>f</trunc> feel that I was wrong to say to you a long time a long long time ago when you were having all kinds of problems with him that's just how he is you have to accept it and I think you</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0084">I remember that conversation</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0083">and I think you  did <pause dur="short"/> and you've always</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0084">but I think I was always more <unclear/> him</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0083">you've always  made the effort <pause dur="short"/> no but you've always made  you've always made  people you know if you wanted</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0084">yeah but that's because I'm selfish and like I I</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0083">it's not a selfish thing</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0084"><unclear/> on him because I that's what I need from him</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0083">yeah but that's</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0084">so I make him do that</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no but but there's <trunc>no</trunc></u>
<u n="1361" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I don't know whether that's because he should be doing that</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0083" trans="overlap">but that's a perfectly natural thing for you need that</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0083">it's not a selfish thing it's perfectly natural and you prompt him and he then responds because he will he won't do it himself but he will respond</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then he doesn't</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0083" trans="overlap">and if she did the same he would respond to her but she doesn't see why she should have to</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0084">agreed <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0083">that's the difference between you two</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0084">I agree but the more you do it the more he it enters his head to do it with you</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0084">then because he thinks right I should call Michael and he might not do it but he</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0084">the feel the thought is there which is probably what it is with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I should call her and I should arrange to see her</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0084">but he doesn't actually follow through all of the time and he will call</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0083" trans="overlap">he does  he does  phone her sometimes not very often but he does do it</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0084">and he'll call me and say oh are you gonna come around for</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0084">dinner this week or whatever?</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0084">which is nice and he'll call me at the weekend</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0084">erm but I don't know whether that's because you know I do go around and see him which <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't and the thought is already in his mind</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0084">because I have done in the past <pause dur="short"/> whereas if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just <pause dur="short"/> you know when I was living here I would go I would cycle over and see him</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0084">you know spend the night there on a Friday night or whatever</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0084">she doesn't do that</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0084">and fine that's their that's up to them</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0083" trans="overlap">but then she doesn't you see she she's <pause dur="short"/> but also don't forget she doesn't know if <trunc>sh</trunc> if he wants her to do that she this is what she feels</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0084">is that  is that  true?</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no she feels <pause dur="short"/> that is absolutely true she doesn't know</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0084" trans="overlap">what the <pause dur="short"/> the thing is with dad the the thing that I've always the reason I've always been able to get over the fact that he can't communicate through words is because I've always been assured of how I feel just through his actions <pause dur="short"/> obviously I I feel it's true when I say actions speak louder than words and I think he shows his affection through the things that he does for us <pause dur="short"/> but that I also can see that he doesn't necessarily pick up the phone when he should and</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0084">suggest things when he should <pause dur="short"/> but generally speaking</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0083">you make allowances</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0084">it goes above and beyond what I think is required but I can't I would never question how he feels about any of us and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I don't think she questions it I think she  I think she  just questions what she should do and why and what she feels he wants from her erm</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0084">that's so funny</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0083">mm there's just a different way of looking at things</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0084">yeah I would have never have thought that I didn't realise</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no she does <pause dur="short"/> because he's the parent</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0084">well yes yes</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0083" trans="overlap">it should be up to him you know? I mean I do  I do  feel that</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely he should drive the <trunc>r</trunc> the relationship ultimately</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0083">yes but he's not  he's not  a good driver</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0084">but then I think you know it was easier when they were living together because obviously they were there and</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0084">now that they're not living together <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think maybe he made more of an effort when she was at uni because she wasn't in the same city</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0083">yes</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0084">so I think he thinks oh she's here</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0083">that's right</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0084">now why wouldn't she come and see me?</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0084">so he's not</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0084">being the one saying well come over because he thinks oh she must be really busy <pause dur="short"/> when in actual fact she's just here every night waiting for him to pick up the phone <pause dur="short"/> so they're probably both guilty of</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0084">not making the effort that they should but as to who should start it</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0083">exactly</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0084">who can say? I mean yeah there's an argument that it should be dad</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0084">I would say it should be dad but I suppose my relationship with him is is different</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0083">it is different</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0084">because I</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0083">and you are a different character to her so</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0084">yeah but she's</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0083">the way you respond to him is different to the way she does</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0084">that's probably because I'm a bull in a china shop when I just charge in there and she's more of a retiring violet or whatever the phrase is</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0083" trans="overlap">yeah but that's you know you you you get results through doing that</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0084">yeah but you also annoy everybody because ultimately</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0083">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0084">you just you're you're not as <pause dur="short"/> even though you try to be thoughtful and considerate you</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0083">you are</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0084">you try <pause dur="short"/> but yeah but I do feel like you sort of you put yourself out there and you put yourself first and that's all I need</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0083" trans="overlap">that's it's always a risk <pause dur="short"/> it's not  it's not  putting yourself first you're you're just putting yourself out there and that is always a risk but I think it I still think you're right to do it <pause dur="short"/> erm and I can understand her reluctance to do that as well so</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0083">erm but don't beat yourself up for for any of this</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> well no I just accept that that's  that that's  my character and that's hers <pause dur="short"/> but I did find it strange that she hadn't even mentioned it to him but then you know if he's he's not very <unclear/> I mean they were meeting for lunch and things like that weren't they you know occasionally? They'd meet in town or spend a day together</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0083" trans="overlap">very occasionally <pause dur="short"/> I think that was before she even started work erm</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0083">I mean <trunc>sh</trunc> because I mean like like</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0084">that's the thing she is quite tired</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0083">like it used to you all went over for Sunday lunch there</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0083">so she did that and then  and then  you see what happened was that he came over and he's done that a couple of times <pause dur="short"/> you know he will come over with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when she's here to spend time with her</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0083">but I find that difficult</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0084">yeah of course</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0083">so because you know he'll be here for two or three hours and I think oh God just go home</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0083">erm and that's fine so they get to see each other and that's good but you know it's</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0083">a bit more awkward for me</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0083">and I'm not gonna make a big song and dance about it but you know</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0084">well but the thing is she should know that do you know what I mean? Like she should think it's not fair on you</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I know but she's also she's you know she's tired and</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0084">this is her home</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0083">yeah it is her home</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0084">but</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0083">and when when she's not working I mean she does just kind of sleep and read and that's it</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0084">yeah but you know that's that's not really an excuse</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0083" trans="overlap">I mean I might suggest  I might suggest</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0084">yeah but you shouldn't have to suggest</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0083">no you see she's working  she's working  Saturday but I don't think she's working Sunday <pause dur="short"/> I might suggest she goes over and has lunch with him on Sunday</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0084">I think they should just spend the day or some time just the two of them or if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s there then fine</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0083">mm <pause dur="short"/> I might</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0084">but they never do that</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0083">I might I might  prompt her to do that because she doesn't do it enough really and I might  I might  prompt her to go over on Sunday maybe because I don't think she's working</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> but she isn't that sort of person she isn't the sort of person to say what are you up to I'll come over?</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0083">no she's not</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0084" trans="overlap">she would always wait for the invitation whereas I'm not like that at all</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0083">no</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0084">because I think oh I'd quite like to pop down to <anon type="place"/> and see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I would just say right how do you <trunc>f</trunc> how how are you fixed next weekend I thought I'd come down? And I would expect other people to be the same</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0083">yeah</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0084">but I suppose it's more polite to wait for an invitation but then in some instances when either either if it's family or if it's close friends</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0083">well no but they they</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0084">they're not gonna judge you if they want to see you</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0083" trans="overlap">no and then and they're very happy to to do that</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0083">I mean I'm probably very pleased that you do do that so</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0084">I don't know</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0083">I'm sure they would be <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they would be</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0084">yeah it's just different characters isn't it?</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0083">it is <pause dur="short"/> it is</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0084">she's a funny one</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0083">oh well I think she is a little bit but I think you all are and that's because probably I am so I don't think that's going anywhere that conversation</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0084">you and dad</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0084">well everyone's a bit peculiar</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0083">yeah we are</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0084"><unclear/> qualities</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0083">I think we're quite normal when I see some people though</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0084">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean but what is normal?</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0083">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes quite <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm tired <pause dur="short"/> I think I might put some dinner in the oven</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0084">Pisa</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0083">Pisa <pause dur="short"/> put some Pisa in the oven</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0084">yup <unclear/></u>
<u n="1502" who="S0083">I don't know</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> when I was in the cinema the other day and there was a trailer for a new Ridley Scott film that looks exactly like Alien <pause dur="short"/> in fact it's about Alien</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0083" trans="overlap">surely all his films are exactly the same aren't they?</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0084">well Gladiator wasn't like Alien but this is actually about aliens</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0083">oh is it?</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0084">yes</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0083" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0084">and it's shot like Alien dark and a bit creepy <pause dur="short"/> michael Fassbender's in it who I love</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0083">mm</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0084">so I will be going</u>
</body>
</text>
