<text id="SVBJ">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:19:49</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0093</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A gym café, Birmingham </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Film, celebrities TV &amp; radio, music, conspiracy theories, marriage, work, education</topics>
		<activity>Friends catching up over a coffee at the gym.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0093">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Company director</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_1</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">so what what was the first film about?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0093">well the first well I've got two there's two films <pause dur="short"/> the one that was very nearly made in back in two thousand and and eight was erm er My Brum Rom Com</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0093">which was as would suggest a Birmingham based romantic comedy</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0093">called Lip Sync</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="8" who="S0093">cos it was part partly musical well the characters burst into song for no reason every so often <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">it wasn't about erm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0093">danced down New Street</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">it wasn't about two bloke friends cos then it could've been a Brum  a Brum</u>
<u n="12" who="S0093" trans="overlap">A brum a brom a broman</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">A brum bromoman <pause dur="short"/> rom brum brom com <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0093">well actually the two it is a male female leads you know the <trunc>th</trunc> a typical romance but the there are two best friends</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh</u>
<u n="16" who="S0093">one's a Blues fan <pause dur="short"/> one's a Villa fan</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="18" who="S0093">so there's a romance there</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018" trans="overlap">it's like Romeo and Juliet <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0093">you've got to have a romance in every film these days you know <pause dur="short"/> and erm the second one which is being well like very well procrastinated over by Hammer</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">mm mm?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0093">do you remember the Hammer House Of Horror?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="24" who="S0093">they've reformed and they did Woman In Black recently</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="26" who="S0093">with Daniel Radcliffe <pause dur="short"/> and they really like my vampire film called Crimson Moon</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">ooh</u>
<u n="28" who="S0093">crimson Moon <unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0018" trans="overlap">vampires are all the rage nowadays aren't they</u>
<u n="30" who="S0093">they have never had <pause dur="short"/> they've never been away really</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0093">they've always been popular but it's a bit of overkill possibly at the moment so we'll see what happens</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0093">the thing with these though is they can always be changed into another creature quite easily you know</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0093">erm and that's er er yes so subsequently I was I've been interviewed a lot by Nick Owen at the Bedwood Mill</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0093">er er I met him today <pause dur="short"/> erm Evening Mail I've been on <pause dur="short"/> tom Ross interviewed me on BRMB</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">ooh</u>
<u n="40" who="S0093">and er and so on and so forth <pause dur="short"/> and er and it's been quite an interesting experience cos usually I'm doing the interviewing</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0093">being in television you know</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0093">so <pause dur="short"/> actually we could talk about that for a while <pause dur="short"/> I I've cos I work mostly in documentary and film now</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="46" who="S0093">er documentary and current affairs now</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but have you got your own? Are you freelancing? And you've got your own company?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0093" trans="overlap">yeah I've got a small production company now</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="50" who="S0093">which we sort of dip into every so often but a lot of the work recently has been freelance away from my my business partner</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0093">and er so I've interviewed some interesting people <pause dur="short"/> you know and it's always quite fascinating sitting in front of somebody</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0093">asking the questions <pause dur="short"/> cos you're always thinking ahead <pause dur="short"/> you're always thinking of the next question</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="56" who="S0093">and then to be the person being interviewed and you're you're trying to work out what they're gonna ask you next and all this sort of thing</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0093">and it's quite an interesting <pause dur="short"/> but I've interview quite a few famous people <pause dur="short"/> and it's difficult not to name drop but um but from from Indiana Jones you know from Harrison Ford to</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0093">Katy Price I've interviewed a couple of times now <pause dur="short"/> she's a nightmare</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0093">and er</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018">luckily yes I don't actually know these <trunc>peop</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I imagine that she's a famous a really famous type person is she?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0093">jordon <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="66" who="S0093" trans="overlap">you know Jordon <pause dur="short"/> yeah Katy Price yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018">orange</u>
<u n="68" who="S0093">yes</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">er hair yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0093">yes very orange</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0093">and these were in the days <pause dur="short"/> this was for a programme called Girl's Girl's Night Out</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="74" who="S0093">and it was round the early early early to yeah it was probably early er two thousands <pause dur="short"/> when the girl the ladish ladette</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0093">culture was all about <pause dur="short"/> and she was sort of spokesperson for that</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0093">and she was awful <pause dur="short"/> a dreadful person <pause dur="short"/> actually she turned up as Katy Price</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0093">and she was really nice <pause dur="short"/> very pretty <pause dur="short"/> really pretty face <pause dur="short"/> she was lovely</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0093">she was all covered up</u>
<u n="83" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="84" who="S0093">and then <pause dur="short"/> she was two hours late <pause dur="short"/> and then she said right I've just gotta go and get ready <pause dur="short"/> cos we're we're on on camera <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="85" who="S0018">stepped into a telephone box and came out</u>
<u n="86" who="S0093" trans="overlap">I'll be another hour <pause dur="short"/> no no big telephone box</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0093">it took her an hour to walk round it <pause dur="short"/> but she erm and then she <trunc>d</trunc> she came out as Jordan and it was all low cut this</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0093">er the tan looked very orange and erm and the make-up was just dreadful</u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0093">and she just became this other person <pause dur="short"/> this Chav almost <pause dur="short"/> from being a really pretty a very pretty girl she is</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="94" who="S0093">to suddenly morphing into this caricature <pause dur="short"/> and it was just awful you know I hated it</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">did her personality change as well?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0093">er er well I didn't speak to her enough as Katy Price to</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0093">to know that to be honest but yeah that was an interesting experience <pause dur="short"/> and then I worked on Rugby Special for many years but it's back in London I I did um I was based in London for thirteen years and I mostly did sport then</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">ah-huh</u>
<u n="100" who="S0093">light entertainment and sport</u>
<u n="101" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="102" who="S0093">so the sport took me to Rugby Special and Football Italia</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="104" who="S0093">and things like that <pause dur="short"/> which are probably of no interest for to you at all <vocal desc="laugh"/> But for me it was</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0093">great because er because er I was interviewing Martin Johnson you might have heard of the England er former England captain</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="108" who="S0093">er Lawrence Dallaglio <pause dur="short"/> big rugby players <pause dur="short"/> all my heroes really</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0093">and then footballers as well <pause dur="short"/> gazza I interviewed and people like that</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0093">it was a fascinating world you know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0093">so I'm very lucky to be able to name drop cos otherwise</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">super</u>
<u n="116" who="S0093">so heavily and er <vocal desc="laugh"/> no um get paid for something that's quite enjoyable</u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="118" who="S0093">much like yourself</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018">er a <trunc>coup</trunc> a few of my friends work at er BBC and erm they love that <pause dur="short"/> they get to do stuff that they'd probably be doing anyway er anyway in their free time</u>
<u n="120" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">manny's at Wembley this weekend filming</u>
<u n="122" who="S0093">oh right</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018">something and he put it up on his Facebook page yesterday saying look what I'm doing</u>
<u n="124" who="S0093"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">I'm recording this dedelededede sound check and oh I'm just standing here and thinking</u>
<u n="126" who="S0093">oh it's a band is it? <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they they work for the Asian network so it's all kind of erm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0093">I wonder what's on the <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0018">asian <trunc>Kalil</trunc> <trunc>kallilkahl</trunc>? Kalil</u>
<u n="130" who="S0093">yeah Kalil</u>
<u n="131" who="S0018"><trunc>Kal</trunc></u>
<u n="132" who="S0093"><trunc>Kal</trunc> <trunc>kal</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> we erm that's something I've never done <pause dur="short"/> there are two areas I would have really loved to have worked in</u>
<u n="133" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0093">even just for a year or something</u>
<u n="135" who="S0018" trans="overlap">music</u>
<u n="136" who="S0093">one is music <pause dur="short"/> the other is nature</u>
<u n="137" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0093">I would have liked to have done some David Attenborough type of things</u>
<u n="139" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0093">although it's incredibly boring apparently</u>
<u n="141" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0093">on the real edge <pause dur="short"/> there's a  there's a  camera lady</u>
<u n="143" who="S0018">get David Bellamy and get right in there</u>
<u n="144" who="S0093" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0093">so so it's what I was saying before I I I've actually been interviewed a lot recently</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0093">even on  today and you you know I'm sort of God what do I</u>
<u n="149" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0093">I really <trunc>fre</trunc> you know it's really quite bizarre <pause dur="short"/> but by the <trunc>s</trunc> the radio Fox stuff I'm absolutely fine <pause dur="short"/> I'll just chat and make jokes and</u>
<u n="151" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="152" who="S0093">I was on Tom Ross' show which is BR and B <pause dur="short"/> he's a big Birmingham personality</u>
<u n="153" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0093">and he erm and the first thing I said was he said so you're a Birmingham City fan <pause dur="short"/> and I went yeah hence the hence no hair <pause dur="short"/> and then I went yeah that's a great joke for radio isn't it</u>
<u n="155" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0093">and and and and he laughed <pause dur="short"/> er er and I sort of  sort of  sank into it quite easily and I really enjoyed that</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-huh</u>
<u n="158" who="S0093">but when you've got a camera <trunc>st</trunc> in your face</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0093">which I've done to people all my life</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0093">it's a really different experience</u>
<u n="163" who="S0018">why is it cos it's daunting?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018">the fact that you're visually?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0093">no it's not daunting <pause dur="short"/> it's more of a ego <trunc>thi</trunc> no er well ego is a bit strong <pause dur="short"/> it's more of a it's more I suppose</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018">is it my best side? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0093">yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah how do I look? What do I? You know <pause dur="short"/> not that I'm that narcissistic <pause dur="short"/> now please don't get me wrong</u>
<u n="169" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0093">er you know I haven't got much to work with but erm <pause dur="short"/> but you do worry you know how's my <trunc>teet</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you know I've <trunc>had</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> did I have spinach? Er er you know <pause dur="short"/> or did I?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0093">what did I eat before? Wait have I done this? Have I? And then you're conscious of what you're doing as well</u>
<u n="173" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0093">are you waving your hands and</u>
<u n="175" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0093">and are you <trunc>shif</trunc> shuffling around and and whenever <trunc>I've</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> the worst is when you're standing doing an interview</u>
<u n="177" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0093">being interviewed standing and suddenly <pause dur="short"/> yeah what do you do with your hands? Cos usually it's just a you know a relative close up</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="180" who="S0093">on your face and possibly shoulders <pause dur="short"/> erm and er hands you still you know I do er this a lot anyway</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0093">and this for the microphone is me waving my hands around gesticulating <pause dur="short"/> but erm when you're on camera so I've learned to just put my hands in my pocket and try and stay still but you know just er er be yourself</u>
<u n="183" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0093">that's that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> so it's an interesting experience</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">it is very</u>
<u n="186" who="S0093">when the tables are turned</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> well the tables have now have turned but don't worry I'm only recording you your voice</u>
<u n="188" who="S0093">yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">there's no hidden camera anywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0093">it's erm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">I was reading an interesting article the other day</u>
<u n="192" who="S0093">yep?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">about how the the lines between radio and TV are being blurred because like in a lot of radio stations they'll be erm webcasting</u>
<u n="194" who="S0093">yes that's right yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">a visual of the programme being made</u>
<u n="196" who="S0093">yeah I can think of nothing more tedious</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">ha <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="198" who="S0093">why would people want to go onto a website and watch people sitting across a table talking</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="200" who="S0093">you know it's it's not the most visual of of <trunc>well</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">it's not</u>
<u n="202" who="S0093">erm er but you know it's part of the interactive thing I suppose</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0093">which is all the the you know which is the future I guess of television radio whatever</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0093">but television has been dumbed down an awful lot <pause dur="short"/> I work in documentary and current affairs</u>
<u n="207" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0093">I do I've done a lot of tonight programmes on ITV which</u>
<u n="209" who="S0018">mm that's</u>
<u n="210" who="S0093">for ITV is is still they're still well made</u>
<u n="211" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0093">erm <pause dur="short"/> I've done a lot of stuff for the BBC but even within the BBC within Channel Four <pause dur="short"/> erm forget the cable cos that's really dumbed down but er everything is</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0093">is just cheaper now</u>
<u n="215" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="216" who="S0093">you've got to get to the story quickly <pause dur="short"/> you can't let the audience work it out for themselves you know and I</u>
<u n="217" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0093">blame the X Factor and programmes like that <pause dur="short"/> I'm sad to say but um I hate the X Factor er with a vengeance <pause dur="short"/> erm and er and that type of thing <pause dur="short"/> it's just got too</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">I agree</u>
<u n="220" who="S0093">well it's almost dictating culture now</u>
<u n="221" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0093">and it's so I find it wrong because the X Factor for example I know  I know  I've met a lot of musicians <pause dur="short"/> I know a lot of musicians who have worked and slaved away and done all this sort of stuff <pause dur="short"/> and then X Factor it's it seems to be able yes you've got the overnight success for some people</u>
<u n="223" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0093">but obviously a lot of them have been struggling for years and it is a great way for them to get onto telly onto television where they wouldn't be able to usually</u>
<u n="225" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0093">but there's a lot of there there it seems to encourage the fact that all you have to do is get up and sing a song in tune</u>
<u n="227" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0093">all be it <pause dur="short"/> well actually thinking about it there's been a lot of  a lot of  accusations that they don't sing in tune <pause dur="short"/> and they've been retuning it</u>
<u n="229" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0093">in the edit process and even live they've been actually <trunc>s</trunc> you know so they've picked the face already that's gonna fit</u>
<u n="231" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0093">whether they can sing or not <pause dur="short"/> and that's dreadful <pause dur="short"/> but also it's erm it's not encouraging people to actually write songs as well <pause dur="short"/> the creative process of writing</u>
<u n="233" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0093">songs albums you know and actually creating fans</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0093">through your own voice <pause dur="short"/> literally going you your your own voice but also what you want what you have to say has been heavily dissipated I think <pause dur="short"/> we've always had those girl <trunc>ban</trunc> boy bands <pause dur="short"/> back to the Bay City Rollers and whatever else</u>
<u n="237" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0093">but whereas someone like Take That who Gary Barlow ironically was on X Factor</u>
<u n="239" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0093">it was a manufactured band but God they were talented er within their</u>
<u n="241" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0093">you know collectively and er individually</u>
<u n="243" who="S0018">also the whole thing about celebrity er nowadays isn't it than as in you're not  you're not  revered if you've got talent <pause dur="short"/> it's just anything that will sell whether they've got a talent or not</u>
<u n="244" who="S0093" trans="overlap">you don't have to have a talent to be revered and that's that's exactly it yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">that's er I think that's the problem with nowadays like celebrity and music and</u>
<u n="246" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">the whole media agenda</u>
<u n="248" who="S0093">well what I find</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">but obviously it's being that it's been dictated by policies coming down from above by fat cats at the top who want</u>
<u n="250" who="S0093">well it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">to control what people are</u>
<u n="252" who="S0093">Simon Cowell makes a very very good living from from all this</u>
<u n="253" who="S0018">oh he makes me cringe</u>
<u n="254" who="S0093">well it's all about <pause dur="short"/> that's what it's all about</u>
<u n="255" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0093">he sizes people up and bang they're gone within three months after that</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0093">some <pause dur="short"/> some have made it a bit bigger but not many</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0093">Will Young of course has done very well <pause dur="short"/> not through X Factor but by through Pop Idol or whatever it was</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0093">um Alexandra Alexander Berk <pause dur="short"/> alexandra Berk <pause dur="short"/> um what was the <trunc>boy</trunc>? Was the boy band er <trunc>J</trunc>? Not JLS <pause dur="short"/> one One Direction or something</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018">I don't know I was er <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether I should be thankful but I've kind of missed all of this</u>
<u n="264" who="S0093">yeah you are</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018">I've missed the past fourteen years of</u>
<u n="266" who="S0093">be very thankful <pause dur="short"/> be afraid <pause dur="short"/> be very afraid</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">culture <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0093">er but I yeah I I really despair at the fact that also the the audience have become almost Americanised as well</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0093">so whether you they get up and so somebody stands up and sings a dreadful song <pause dur="short"/> a a cover version or whatever <pause dur="short"/> it's never their own song and um and does it really badly <pause dur="short"/> still you get this whooping</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0093">screaming from all the  all the  fans as it were</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0093">whether it's good bad or indifferent so it's just the fact that if you get on stand up and you're on television you're a celebrity <pause dur="short"/> you're big <pause dur="short"/> you're huge <pause dur="short"/> you're er talented</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018">yep yep</u>
<u n="276" who="S0093">oh my God you must be wonderful <pause dur="short"/> and it's not the case you know</u>
<u n="277" who="S0018">but do you not think that there's that in a way there's you know a positive effect from that? In that the backlash against well the backlash that's taken place because of the manufactured</u>
<u n="278" who="S0093">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0018">the easiness of manufacturing</u>
<u n="280" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0018">hits and profits as opposed to actually er promoting real talent</u>
<u n="282" who="S0093">well it it's</u>
<u n="283" who="S0018">Cos that's that came about in the er er the the time where er social networking was really taking off and lots of people actually made their</u>
<u n="284" who="S0093" trans="overlap">yeah the famous one was erm Rage Against The Machine</u>
<u n="285" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0093">and there was this big Facebook I think er campaign</u>
<u n="287" who="S0018">oh that's right abouts yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0093">to get this one song <pause dur="short"/> it's no it was Chris the Christmas number one and and they've succeeded and it was brilliant</u>
<u n="289" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0093">this song which it must have been about fifteen years old and it was I can't remember what the song was called now but it was something very appropriate to the situation</u>
<u n="291" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0093">and er you know Don't Feed The Machine or or er er I don't know what it was <pause dur="short"/> something like something about along that line</u>
<u n="293" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0093">and it was <pause dur="short"/> that was brilliant yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0093">but that was just a small individual you know</u>
<u n="297" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="298" who="S0093">unfortunately what I worry about is my are my nieces and the like all my kid's <trunc>frien</trunc> <trunc>g</trunc> er children who are growing up</u>
<u n="299" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0093">thinking this is normal <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> as they are growing up with iPads and er you know this is all normal to them</u>
<u n="301" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0093">so what you grow up with is normal <pause dur="short"/> I mean to me it was Scalelectrics and and Lego</u>
<u n="303" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0093">to my parents it was huh Scalelectrics? How does that work? Er whereas you know now there are iPads and whatever but also that celebrity is just being on television</u>
<u n="305" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0093">it doesn't matter what you can do or can't do</u>
<u n="307" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then music being churned into their poor little heads</u>
<u n="308" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0018">it's like even the pop music from from my day it was er <trunc>m</trunc> <trunc>m</trunc> basically Michael Jackson and Madonna <pause dur="short"/> but if you actually listen to the songs <trunc>they're</trunc> there's still quite a lot of musical</u>
<u n="310" who="S0093">oh yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0018">genius in them that but nowadays</u>
<u n="312" who="S0093" trans="overlap">but there's still musical genius around</u>
<u n="313" who="S0018">yeah but it's not getting pumped through the airways</u>
<u n="314" who="S0093" trans="overlap">there's lots of it <pause dur="short"/> no with the death of Top Of The Pops and er and I suppose the birth of of downloading</u>
<u n="315" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0093">and and and that you don't get the bands that are actually writing songs <pause dur="short"/> that are creating things <pause dur="short"/> that probably</u>
<u n="317" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0093">probably would be creating new movements as well</u>
<u n="319" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0093">which is what how music always generates</u>
<u n="321" who="S0018">yep yep</u>
<u n="322" who="S0093">you know punk came about because of</u>
<u n="323" who="S0018">yeah that's true actually <pause dur="short"/> there hasn't been</u>
<u n="324" who="S0093">progressive rock and all that</u>
<u n="325" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0093">and then from punk came scar and</u>
<u n="327" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0093">two-toned and er the new wave and then as a rebellion to that came er new romanticism <pause dur="short"/> and then a rebellion to that became</u>
<u n="329" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0093">came er house er well erm garage and and acid</u>
<u n="331" who="S0018">hmm mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0093">and so on and so forth</u>
<u n="333" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0093">and it was <trunc>k</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> er but at the moment it's just</u>
<u n="335" who="S0018">evolution</u>
<u n="336" who="S0093">now we're stuck at cover versions</u>
<u n="337" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0093">by X Factor people <pause dur="short"/> and that's what it is</u>
<u n="339" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0093">or you've got the jangly Brit pop bands which came about and there are too many of those as well <pause dur="short"/> and what they haven't had in the last five six seven years are is the the next movement</u>
<u n="341" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0093">which maybe is just waiting to happen as a as I say as a</u>
<u n="343" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0093">backlash to to the Cowell era</u>
<u n="345" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0093">and I hope it does you know cos there's always you know even when we were growing up there were boy bands girl bands manufactured music and and culture generally <pause dur="short"/> but erm but it's just got too but that's taken over now and that's I</u>
<u n="347" who="S0018">yeah yep</u>
<u n="348" who="S0093">I find it really sad <pause dur="short"/> it maybe makes me a a Victor Meldrew and</u>
<u n="349" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0093">and I'm proud of that</u>
<u n="351" who="S0018">Don't worry <pause dur="short"/> I'm a complete conspiracy theorist <pause dur="short"/> I think it's being done for a reason <pause dur="short"/> people are being dumbed down</u>
<u n="352" who="S0093">really?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0018">in one sense while above <trunc>every</trunc> you know all the fat cats</u>
<u n="354" who="S0093">wow</u>
<u n="355" who="S0018">there in their little playgrounds</u>
<u n="356" who="S0093">yeah well</u>
<u n="357" who="S0018">and they're er trying to orchestrate</u>
<u n="358" who="S0093">there's a classic example of say I I I I totally agree in one respect cos I what I've noticed is er well Blair I suppose Blair and Brown's children</u>
<u n="359" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0093">are now the people who are you know they're the thirteen fourteen year-olds whatever <pause dur="short"/> and I just had a load of letters and as I do every year <pause dur="short"/> er thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen year-olds all trying to in fact er yeah and to eighteen er all trying who basically who are educated over the last fifteen years</u>
<u n="361" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0093">who erm want work experience all of that type of thing <pause dur="short"/> and they cannot put a letter together <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="363" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0093">whereas over the Labour years <pause dur="short"/> the New Labour years I should say er one of the reasons why I I was in favour of the change back in ninety-seven er I soon came out of favour of that</u>
<u n="365" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0093">erm was that oh my God you know cos education education education <pause dur="short"/> and suddenly all the A Level results were all As</u>
<u n="367" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0093">oh yeah and of cause they were just bringing down the levels</u>
<u n="369" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0093">they were stopping the great the the the high flyers as if well in terms of education <pause dur="short"/> bringing er those down to a level</u>
<u n="371" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0093">and that's what I find now with Britain is that there is this level <pause dur="short"/> and it seems to have come from the top</u>
<u n="373" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0093">where whether it be erm the press or erm or what could be told in the press <pause dur="short"/> what er can be actually told to the public <pause dur="short"/> or whether it be culture</u>
<u n="375" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0093">television <pause dur="short"/> erm education <pause dur="short"/> it's all a bland middle ground at the moment</u>
<u n="377" who="S0018">yep definitely</u>
<u n="378" who="S0093">everything er reflects the weather here</u>
<u n="379" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0093">and it seems to have been a deliberate thing because when I grew up there was distinctly an upper class middle class lower class</u>
<u n="381" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0093">working class <pause dur="short"/> and there was also <trunc>high</trunc> er at school whatever school you went to whether it be public private comprehensive there was the <trunc>achiev</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="383" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0093">the the the people with photographic memories <pause dur="short"/> the people who were genuinely fantastically <trunc>edu</trunc> you know intelligent</u>
<u n="385" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0093">and geniuses <pause dur="short"/> then there was the middle ground <pause dur="short"/> and then there was the lower ground <pause dur="short"/> and you know they were split</u>
<u n="387" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0093">that way <pause dur="short"/> and it was almost like everybody knew their place</u>
<u n="389" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0093">not not in a you know erm Nazi sort of way <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="391" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0093">there's this there's one word <unclear/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0018">but no yeah I can see what you mean</u>
<u n="394" who="S0093" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="395" who="S0018">I mean you have aspirations</u>
<u n="396" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0018">that are set out according to your not your station in life but your</u>
<u n="398" who="S0093">not cos you <trunc>asp</trunc> no and then there are ways to achieve you know</u>
<u n="399" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0093">and when I was there there wasn't university didn't cost so much <pause dur="short"/> there were more grants cos there were less people going</u>
<u n="401" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="402" who="S0093">so whether you came from a working-class background a middle-class upper class you still had pretty much the same opportunities</u>
<u n="403" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0093">let's be honest it wasn't as clear cut as that but you you you could aspire and you could get you know the American dream almost</u>
<u n="405" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0093">you know that's what we all <trunc>m</trunc> that's what we had more of <pause dur="short"/> now I think it's just sort of okay everybody goes to university therefore we'll bring we we'll just generate</u>
<u n="407" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0093">this entire <trunc>gen</trunc> er two or three generations <pause dur="short"/> we'll generate generations <pause dur="short"/> what a terrible phrase</u>
<u n="409" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0093">you can tell I'm a writer</u>
<u n="411" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0093">er ha erm <pause dur="short"/> I've really I find dumbed down very unaspirational and</u>
<u n="413" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0093">erm quite simple people to be honest</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0093">it's an awful thing to say <pause dur="short"/> very sad <pause dur="short"/> it's very snobbish and elitist <pause dur="short"/> snobbish and elitist but er I don't  I don't  mean it to be <pause dur="short"/> I I will just worry for the future <pause dur="short"/> and I think part of that has definitely come from higher <pause dur="short"/> certainly not you know er Simon Cowell has his own <trunc>mo</trunc> motives</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0093">and the British public being sheep for the most part have just bought into it</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="420" who="S0093">er er isn't it great watching someone do a cover version very badly <pause dur="short"/> er not it's not actually <pause dur="short"/> it's not that great</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">yeah but it gets more sinister than that when you find out that Michael Gove used to be erm the henchman of er Rupert Murdock</u>
<u n="422" who="S0093">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0018">and that they are in cahoots what I think <trunc>ju</trunc> just before the whole shit hit the fan with the the the Leveson Report</u>
<u n="424" who="S0093">leveson Inquiry and that yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018">and everything that erm preceded that <pause dur="short"/> they were in cahoots trying to get a lot of what was being taught in the classroom done virtually</u>
<u n="426" who="S0093">oh</u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">using erm the the whole archive of The Daily Mail and all the</u>
<u n="428" who="S0093">oh my God</u>
<u n="429" who="S0018">those kind of erm papers that obviously Rupert Murdock</u>
<u n="430" who="S0093">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0018">was gonna charge a pretty penny for <pause dur="short"/> they'd actually bought in an education tsar who was er part of Newsgroup International</u>
<u n="432" who="S0093">oh my word <pause dur="short"/> who was this? Er was it Cameron or <unclear/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0018" trans="overlap">Michael Gove <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>go</trunc> well <trunc>G</trunc> under Cameron yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0093">under Cameron of course yes <pause dur="short"/> oh that's interesting</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018">since Gove has been education secretary <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="436" who="S0093">of course yes <pause dur="short"/> erm I wonder yeah I wonder</u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">it's dodgy as  dodgy as  hell though really isn't it</u>
<u n="438" who="S0093" trans="overlap">I've always I I've there's one or two conspiracy good old-fashioned conspiracy theories that I love</u>
<u n="439" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0093">the moon landings for example</u>
<u n="441" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0093">I'm <unclear/> Man has not been on the moon <pause dur="short"/> they couldn't have done been there in nineteen sixty-nine in a tin can</u>
<u n="443" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0093">no way <pause dur="short"/> and I love all that <pause dur="short"/> but then it gets ooh too much</u>
<u n="445" who="S0018">it does</u>
<u n="446" who="S0093">sometimes <pause dur="short"/> there's er there's some great ones yeah <pause dur="short"/> some great conspiracy theories</u>
<u n="447" who="S0018">the yeah Bush engineered nine eleven <pause dur="short"/> that's um</u>
<u n="448" who="S0093">that's a good one yeah <pause dur="short"/> well he knew knew the Obamas <pause dur="short"/> not the Obamas the erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> Obamas</u>
<u n="449" who="S0018">oh Bin Ladens?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0093">oh Bin Ladens sorry</u>
<u n="451" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0018">Osama Obama</u>
<u n="453" who="S0093">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly er yes he knew the he knew them <pause dur="short"/> the families know each other very well</u>
<u n="454" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0093">and erm actually there are a lot of echoes though between the moon landings and whatever you know <pause dur="short"/> bush wasn't having a good time politically at the time</u>
<u n="456" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0093">back in sixty-nine of course a losing  a losing  war in Vietnam</u>
<u n="458" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="459" who="S0093">everyone was completely against that <pause dur="short"/> jFK the one of the still the one of the <trunc>h</trunc> the all American heroes</u>
<u n="460" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0093">that had been assassinated a few years <pause dur="short"/> and one of the last things he said is we'll put a man on the moon before the end of the decade <pause dur="short"/> so part of his legacy was to you know we've gotta get  we've gotta get  up there</u>
<u n="462" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0093">of course there was the Cold War and everything else and the Russians were beating them</u>
<u n="464" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="465" who="S0093">and then suddenly these three men went into <trunc>space</trunc></u>
<u n="466" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0093">went through space <pause dur="short"/> apparently er I forget what they're called now <pause dur="short"/> is it the Van  the Van  something rays that occurs from the  from the  sun</u>
<u n="468" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0093">ha er it's not Van Demon but it's something like that Van something rays <pause dur="short"/> it was the er which which are basically a hundred per cent radiation</u>
<u n="470" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="471" who="S0093">that come out of <trunc>sh</trunc> you know solar flares from the sun <pause dur="short"/> and it was the highest it's ever been during the time they did erm they got through space</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0093">in a tin can</u>
<u n="474" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0093">er and none of them had any radiation poisoning <pause dur="short"/> basically the experts said they would have they should have died <pause dur="short"/> all three of them</u>
<u n="476" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="477" who="S0093">and they didn't even er they weren't even sick</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="479" who="S0093">er and then there's the faking</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018" trans="overlap">there's a film about that isn't that the film about the</u>
<u n="481" who="S0093" trans="overlap">there's lots actually <pause dur="short"/> capricorn Thirteen</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018">that's it <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0093">Capricorn Twelve <pause dur="short"/> capricorn Thirteen <pause dur="short"/> one of those two</u>
<u n="484" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0093">and erm and then there's there's a lot of proven erm a lot of the photographs were proven to be fake</u>
<u n="486" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="487" who="S0093">there's too many light sources <pause dur="short"/> iE they <trunc>s</trunc> they were shot in a studio</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="489" who="S0093">now that you know opens up questions of why why were they faked? A if the <pause dur="short"/> the surface of the moon apparently goes from in the shade it goes er er out of the sun it's minus a hundred and twenty degrees</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0093">it's something incredible <pause dur="short"/> to in the sun cos there's no atmosphere at er plus a hundred and twenty degrees <pause dur="short"/> man cannot survive on that</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0093">on its own <pause dur="short"/> nor can film</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="495" who="S0093">film would either melt or or or disintegrate</u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="497" who="S0093">in the intense cold</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="499" who="S0093">so and then I think it was Hasselblad supplied the cameras which were basically on just</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0093">attached to the chest of the space suits <pause dur="short"/> and yet if you watch <pause dur="short"/> you look at the moon shots they are fantastic</u>
<u n="502" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0093">beautifully posed <pause dur="short"/> they're <trunc>every</trunc>everything's done</u>
<u n="504" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="505" who="S0093">the er light readings are just perfect <pause dur="short"/> amazing <pause dur="short"/> erm and they had this camera attached which were just they would just basically point their chest in the vague direction of whatever they were looking at</u>
<u n="506" who="S0018">smile <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0093">yeah and they all came out brilliantly <pause dur="short"/> but there are er there are  there are  <trunc>n</trunc> a lot of anomalies within them <pause dur="short"/> but also <trunc>Hassel</trunc> I think it's Hasselblad have never used in all their publicity</u>
<u n="508" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="509" who="S0093">in all the marketing and any anything they put out to the public you know share erm share issues or whatever it is they don't mention the moon</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0093">which is just the most astonishing thing <pause dur="short"/> if you  if you  had been the</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0093">I think Kodak had a bit of that as well <pause dur="short"/> they didn't really push it <pause dur="short"/> who supplied the film itself</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0093">you know Hasselblad <pause dur="short"/> I think it was Hasselblad supplied the cameras <pause dur="short"/> so why on earth?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">well on the moon?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Why on the moon?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0093">we were the  we were the  we took the pictures on the moon</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0093">we were the <pause dur="short"/> and they don't</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018" trans="overlap">especially in that era because it was all about</u>
<u n="523" who="S0093">well ever since</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">advertising <pause dur="short"/> it was becoming huge wasn't it</u>
<u n="525" who="S0093" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they haven't said a thing <pause dur="short"/> well it's they have in in the past but</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0093">they don't go overboard with it which you just think you'd be shouting from the roof tops then</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0093">so er and the the anomalies the the whistle blowing which is supposed to have happened is fascinating to me <pause dur="short"/> er and that's where I really started believing that it was something else going on <pause dur="short"/> so anyway coming back to what I was saying erm <pause dur="short"/> why were they faked? If they were faked photographs</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0093">which most <trunc>ex</trunc> a lot of experts say they are faked <pause dur="short"/> some of them are faked <pause dur="short"/> erm why were they? You know if <trunc>th</trunc> if they just went to the moon and they the cameras didn't work <pause dur="short"/> the film melted or snapped or whatever</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="533" who="S0093">you know just that's tough <pause dur="short"/> and then try and lie about it and pretend that they were</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="535" who="S0093">so you know they might have landed on the moon but they faked the photographs</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="537" who="S0093">but I do believe they didn't do any of that</u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">was there moving film footage as well?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0093">yes of later <pause dur="short"/> well there was a camera attached to erm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="541" who="S0093">the side of the er or the <trunc>moon</trunc> er of the landing buggy</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0093">er landing craft <pause dur="short"/> er but that could you know <unclear/> it could you could shoot any of that in a studio</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0093">there's no question about that <pause dur="short"/> erm and there was so many in the within the photographs there's one famous one where there's a if you can imagine cross hatch</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0093">where you get the cross on on a lens</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="549" who="S0093">and in those days for some reason they're not on the moon landing shots had that <pause dur="short"/> and of course the lens is right there at the front of the  front of the  picture <pause dur="short"/> er sorry the hatch is at the <trunc>fr</trunc> front of the big cross hatch <pause dur="short"/> and yet there's one particular picture where there's a flag in the background something in the background <pause dur="short"/> and yet the cross goes behind the object</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="551" who="S0093">that's supposedly two hundred yards in front <pause dur="short"/> so you can't <pause dur="short"/> it can't be <pause dur="short"/> and that's thought to have been er somebody who has just sort of placed a</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="553" who="S0093">little cos</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">wasn't there something random in a something very strange in a reflection of the helmet visor or something?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0093">yeah well there's endless ones yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">is it?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0093">light <pause dur="short"/> there's lots of light sources as well though cos it's you know they were all wearing white</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0093">and it's so reflective <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>it</trunc> <trunc>It</trunc> there are light sources <pause dur="short"/> there's only one light source <pause dur="short"/> it's the sun</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0093">that's what it should be but unfortunately it's got two or three light sources <pause dur="short"/> iE studio lights</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="565" who="S0093">and also shadows as well don't make sense <pause dur="short"/> there's a shadow going <pause dur="short"/> you know one sun you get one shadow in a direct straight line <pause dur="short"/> and yet on some pictures there's shadows at different angles <pause dur="short"/> and er and it's it all points to <pause dur="short"/> and I love this</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="567" who="S0093">I love it <pause dur="short"/> I think erm and if you look at the you know the political side of things like that</u>
<u n="568" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0093">and rather like the twenty er the the two thousand and one conspiracies <pause dur="short"/> I suppose you might have Diana as well might be in there as well <pause dur="short"/> but there are definite question marks</u>
<u n="570" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0093">the American government have been known to lire in the past <pause dur="short"/> and for  and for</u>
<u n="572" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="573" who="S0093">for political gain</u>
<u n="574" who="S0018">was that like in the race against Russia to be the best at everything?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0093">that was all part of it as well</u>
<u n="576" who="S0018" trans="overlap">and yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0093">yeah they beat Russia supposedly <pause dur="short"/> and there are er we've got telescopes that can see light years ahead <pause dur="short"/> they can see other planets <pause dur="short"/> they can see other solar systems</u>
<u n="578" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0093">the moon is the nearest thing to us and yet they <trunc>can</trunc> nobody has been able to see any of the space</u>
<u n="580" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0093">er any of the crafts that landed</u>
<u n="582" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0093">they're all in sight <pause dur="short"/> cos they landed on this side of the moon <pause dur="short"/> er nobody can see anything</u>
<u n="584" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0093">you know which is just the most bizarre thing <pause dur="short"/> you know they left a huge craft which is you know half the size of this room</u>
<u n="586" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="587" who="S0093">if they can see er  if they can see er  er a a crater on the moon</u>
<u n="588" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="589" who="S0093">that's the size of this building they can see the craft within it <pause dur="short"/> but nothing <pause dur="short"/> and man and of course they haven't been back to <trunc>sp</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> and if you look at Apollo 13 with the famous Tom Hanks film</u>
<u n="590" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="591" who="S0093">how well scripted that was you know <pause dur="short"/> so nobody can tell if that actually happened or not</u>
<u n="592" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0093">but the American public were really losing interest in um and and subsequently the government</u>
<u n="594" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="595" who="S0093">were losing interest in erm well the finances behind the <trunc>gov</trunc> er were losing interest in the space race</u>
<u n="596" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0093">Cos they you know they supposedly wanted <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>Am</trunc> Apollo 13 came about you know where they</u>
<u n="598" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="599" who="S0093">slung sling shot round and came back</u>
<u n="600" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0093">and that won the public back onto the side of the space race <pause dur="short"/> the space <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="602" who="S0018" trans="overlap">politically motivated yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0093">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that was brilliantly done <pause dur="short"/> now this could all be absolute rubbish of course you know</u>
<u n="604" who="S0018">it could be but</u>
<u n="605" who="S0093">for me <pause dur="short"/> er this is for saying it but I've read this one book called Dark Moon</u>
<u n="606" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh</u>
<u n="607" who="S0093">and that's what convinced me <pause dur="short"/> before that I was like I really can't imagine they didn't</u>
<u n="608" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="609" who="S0093">you know what a lie that would be <pause dur="short"/> and erm and then I read and went they didn't</u>
<u n="610" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0093">they did not land <pause dur="short"/> no chance</u>
<u n="612" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="613" who="S0093">and I'm convinced to this day so when you mentioned conspiracy theories it's you've got mine</u>
<u n="614" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0018">relief</u>
<u n="616" who="S0093">but they but there are <trunc>com</trunc> er you know there are</u>
<u n="617" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0093">there's gotta be truth in some conspiracy <trunc>theor</trunc></u>
<u n="619" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="620" who="S0093">you know people have conspiracy theories about everything <pause dur="short"/> but erm but when it comes to anything politically</u>
<u n="621" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="622" who="S0093">you know with a political agenda <pause dur="short"/> fabulous you know</u>
<u n="623" who="S0018">you could believe anything though</u>
<u n="624" who="S0093">oh yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0018">that happens <pause dur="short"/> especially with the American government <pause dur="short"/> I just wouldn't trust them</u>
<u n="626" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0018">as far as I could throw them</u>
<u n="628" who="S0093">well we know that the you know a lot of er er <trunc>pad</trunc> er you know dictators have lied in the past and</u>
<u n="629" who="S0018">what I find interesting is it Hugo Chávez <pause dur="short"/> the erm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0093">Hugo Chávez</u>
<u n="631" who="S0018">is it the Venezuelan president?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0093">okay</u>
<u n="633" who="S0018">he's saying that isn't it funny how all the Latin American presidents over the past twenty years have died of cancer</u>
<u n="634" who="S0093">mm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0018">or are dying of cancer <pause dur="short"/> and he's he has actually said it's the CIA</u>
<u n="636" who="S0093">uh-huh</u>
<u n="637" who="S0018">who have er managed to manufacture some kind of</u>
<u n="638" who="S0093">really?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0018">cancer inducing substance</u>
<u n="640" who="S0093"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0018">and that obviously they have given to all of us</u>
<u n="642" who="S0093">blimey</u>
<u n="643" who="S0018">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0093">er I'm <trunc>st</trunc> I'm staggered there isn't a cure for <trunc>c</trunc> cancer yet</u>
<u n="645" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0093">and of the course the the the there are just to many people on this planet now <pause dur="short"/> and because we don't have the World Wars that we used to do where there was a natural selection process as it were</u>
<u n="647" who="S0018">Culling <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0093">yeah there was yeah <pause dur="short"/> men and women <pause dur="short"/> mostly men sadly but erm and we don't have those wars now</u>
<u n="649" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="650" who="S0093">so all the governments about <pause dur="short"/> everybody in this room <pause dur="short"/> everybody could do more to help the starvation problems and AIDs problems around Africa and various other places</u>
<u n="651" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0093">er and that isn't being eliminated either <pause dur="short"/> and yet erm Gaddafi er Mugabe all sorts of people have been given huge amounts of money <pause dur="short"/> iran have been given huge amounts of money</u>
<u n="653" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0093">Korea by by the west</u>
<u n="655" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> to nuke a few countries</u>
<u n="656" who="S0093">erm Afghanistan who have been at war with us annoyingly and America for the last ten years</u>
<u n="657" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0093">twelve or eleven years have er that was mostly er they were funded by American and by us you know</u>
<u n="659" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah the er the Taliban were trained by the CIA weren't they</u>
<u n="660" who="S0093">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's a very odd situation yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah so your your end game there is that you reckon that they're trying to get rid of a lot of people so then there's not gonna be so much war for resources</u>
<u n="662" who="S0093">for cancer <pause dur="short"/> yeah through cancer <pause dur="short"/> it's a killer</u>
<u n="663" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="664" who="S0093">well isn't it we we we manage to cure everything else pretty much but not cancer which is <pause dur="short"/> well we got near to it of course but</u>
<u n="665" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0093">er yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0018">they didn't Steve Jobs though <pause dur="short"/> do you not think they would have saved Steve Jobs if they found a cure for cancer and they were just keeping it secret cos they didn't want</u>
<u n="668" who="S0093">yeah possibly</u>
<u n="669" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0093">but no I  but no I  think I I'm agreeing with you <pause dur="short"/> I think there is something</u>
<u n="671" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0093">out there that they er there is something that they er there's just something to it because they do  they do  protect the <trunc>r</trunc> the sort of people they wanna protect</u>
<u n="673" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0093">but I think like with the possibility of UFOs and all that <pause dur="short"/> er yeah I don't know about that stuff <pause dur="short"/> but there's gotta be life out there</u>
<u n="675" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="676" who="S0093">because we are <pause dur="short"/> there's life here</u>
<u n="677" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="678" who="S0093">end of</u>
<u n="679" who="S0018">I agree</u>
<u n="680" who="S0093">you know so there has to be another planet ninety-two million miles from its sun that can sustain life</u>
<u n="681" who="S0018">I agree <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you think about the fact that you know the whole gestation of a child</u>
<u n="682" who="S0093">mm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0018">and the creation</u>
<u n="684" who="S0093">yes</u>
<u n="685" who="S0018">thing <pause dur="short"/> that's miraculous isn't it <pause dur="short"/> so you're thinking you're telling me that</u>
<u n="686" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0018">life can't exist on another planet but that can happen?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0093" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0018">it just doesn't seem</u>
<u n="690" who="S0093">no</u>
<u n="691" who="S0018">no I agree <pause dur="short"/> I agree</u>
<u n="692" who="S0093">it's just ridiculous really when you <trunc>look</trunc> think about it <pause dur="short"/> and er fortunately it doesn't get to the whole God question</u>
<u n="693" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0093">if you do believe in aliens <pause dur="short"/> and I don't believe in aliens necessarily</u>
<u n="695" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0093">I think there's something <pause dur="short"/> there's gotta be life out there</u>
<u n="697" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0093">whether it er whether they can fly here and buzz people and never actually make contact to the people that really matter <pause dur="short"/> it always seems to be some hillbilly that they make contact with</u>
<u n="699" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0093">and and anally probe and then you know I go out I I I I go out <pause dur="short"/> I've had a third <trunc>encount</trunc> a close encounter of the third kind</u>
<u n="701" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0093">er why didn't they come and speak to er to Cameron or to Obama or somebody like that or you know get a news conference going?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0093">if they really want to make contact</u>
<u n="705" who="S0018">maybe cos they're intelligent <pause dur="short"/> a very intelligent life form</u>
<u n="706" who="S0093" trans="overlap">maybe they don't want to know at this <pause dur="short"/> look <pause dur="short"/> they look at us and go what the hell do we want with these people</u>
<u n="707" who="S0018" trans="overlap">they're like what <pause dur="short"/> stay away from them</u>
<u n="708" who="S0093">they'll just er kill themselves off in a few minutes <pause dur="short"/> we'll just keep checking on the planet <pause dur="short"/> and we can move in when they  when they  have destroyed us <pause dur="short"/> but there is there's some great theories <pause dur="short"/> the er conspiracy theories out there <pause dur="short"/> and there's gotta be <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> you know there is some truth in some things but a lot of  a lot of  them will be just there's a question mark over something <pause dur="short"/> and they think ooh</u>
<u n="709" who="S0018">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="710" who="S0093">but there are major ones</u>
<u n="711" who="S0018">A lot  a lot  of the the purveyors of conspiracy theories I think they do grasp at straws <pause dur="short"/> at very tenuous links and tenuous evidence to support some certain things</u>
<u n="712" who="S0093" trans="overlap">well I've seen documentaries</u>
<u n="713" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="714" who="S0093">and you get that <pause dur="short"/> you get the sort of</u>
<u n="715" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0093">the same type of person talking about these conspiracies</u>
<u n="717" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="718" who="S0093">and that's what shocked me about the moon landing one and the Dark Moon book</u>
<u n="719" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="720" who="S0093">Cos it was so well researched and</u>
<u n="721" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="722" who="S0093">and they spoke the it it it was all it all makes sense <pause dur="short"/> you know questions I have about Diana for example</u>
<u n="723" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="724" who="S0093">well that could have happened you know</u>
<u n="725" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="726" who="S0093">yeah so <trunc>appe</trunc> you know the queen <trunc>d</trunc> wanted her to be killed off <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> you know that's just ridiculous</u>
<u n="727" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0093">but there are question marks over what happened and why it happened and</u>
<u n="729" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="730" who="S0093">you know <trunc>res</trunc> certain people and erm organisations responses that don't add up you know</u>
<u n="731" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="732" who="S0093">that it's human nature that comes into it <pause dur="short"/> but er one one thing again was that sorry to bore you with the going around with this moon thing</u>
<u n="733" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no no no no <pause dur="short"/> not boring at all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="734" who="S0093">was that there was er that when they were building the crafts</u>
<u n="735" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="736" who="S0093">to start with and going through all the research process not one company had it <pause dur="short"/> now that could make economic sense so the <trunc>split</trunc> spread the spread it around so <pause dur="short"/> but when it came to actually making the erm the the landing crafts and the rockets and everything else two or three thousand companies sort of <pause dur="short"/> so one company would manufacture a screw</u>
<u n="737" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="738" who="S0093">another <trunc>com</trunc> <unclear/> would manufacture the hole that it goes in <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> well they <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean</u>
<u n="739" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="740" who="S0093">the bracket that it goes into and all that sort of stuff <pause dur="short"/> so no one company could say put it all together and go ah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0093">it doesn't work</u>
<u n="743" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0093">erm <pause dur="short"/> and there are a number of people at NASA who were sceptical about the whole thing</u>
<u n="745" who="S0018">yeah didn't you say there were some whistle-blowers as well?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0093" trans="overlap">and they disappeared <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then a lot of people disappeared <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean you just reminded me when you said people died of cancer who were you know</u>
<u n="747" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0093">the er you know the dictators</u>
<u n="749" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="750" who="S0093">erm and sure enough there were a number of people who died on a lonely road in the desert</u>
<u n="751" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="752" who="S0093">car crash <pause dur="short"/> spun out of control <pause dur="short"/> bang <pause dur="short"/> dead</u>
<u n="753" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="754" who="S0093">who were high top scientists <unclear/> working with NASA who might have known er one or two things <pause dur="short"/> and it just became after the <trunc>af</trunc> after sixty-nine when it all happened there just there was a spate of them <pause dur="short"/> and it was just so coincidental</u>
<u n="755" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="756" who="S0093">it was just too much <pause dur="short"/> again it was picked up in this book you know <pause dur="short"/> and you think well why don't they go and interview the top people at NASA and say come on what happened <pause dur="short"/> and the other thing is that the erm the er astronauts as well don't really or didn't until these conspiracies came out <pause dur="short"/> er probably about ten years ago that it this book hit the shops and everyone went oh my God they might be right on that</u>
<u n="757" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0093">erm but the the astronauts themselves both Aldrin and Neil Armstrong were there but they didn't really talk about it that much</u>
<u n="759" who="S0018">no?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0093">and it ended up with somebody accusing I think it was Buzz Aldrin <pause dur="short"/> it might have been Neil Armstrong actually <pause dur="short"/> erm er with a camera saying you didn't land on the moon did you <pause dur="short"/> you didn't <unclear/> And Neil Armstrong punched this guy in the face er like on camera <pause dur="short"/> it was fantastic</u>
<u n="761" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0093">but he just said I've had enough of this you know <pause dur="short"/> of course we did <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> er but before that they didn't they had never really talked about it <pause dur="short"/> and again if I was an astronaut</u>
<u n="763" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="764" who="S0093">who walked on the moon</u>
<u n="765" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0093">I'd be I'd be telling everybody <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> never mind what you've got to talk about</u>
<u n="767" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Look at my pictures <pause dur="short"/> this</u>
<u n="768" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0093">you know and I just thought actually yeah there's all these interesting links that that maybe just fantastically educated people have put together and go huh <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="770" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="771" who="S0093">Cos it is well argued <pause dur="short"/> the whole thing <pause dur="short"/> particularly the science side of it where the <trunc>man</trunc> three men could not have got across space without even vomiting once you know</u>
<u n="772" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="773" who="S0093">through radiation <pause dur="short"/> this radiation is a killer <pause dur="short"/> erm the space stations er Mia and all those sort of things they're not in space <pause dur="short"/> they're in within the earth's atmosphere</u>
<u n="774" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="775" who="S0093">the furthest point <pause dur="short"/> er but if you go into space you're gonna die basically <pause dur="short"/> so subsequently no apparently nobody has gone into space cos we just can't survive <pause dur="short"/> now we probably could now with the</u>
<u n="776" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="777" who="S0093">technology we've got to actually you know <pause dur="short"/> but in nineteen sixty-nine</u>
<u n="778" who="S0018">you wouldn't be able to</u>
<u n="779" who="S0093">no chance <pause dur="short"/> no chance at all no</u>
<u n="780" who="S0018">was there a Russian space exploration around that time? A bit later</u>
<u n="781" who="S0093">mm there were loads yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0018">was that?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0093">er Yuri Gagarin and people like that</u>
<u n="784" who="S0018">yeah that's right <pause dur="short"/> and was that proved? Proven to have been faked?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0093">no there's no question marks about that because they didn't actually make it get it to the moon <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="786" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="787" who="S0093">but it according to this book if I remember correctly they they were genuine</u>
<u n="788" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="789" who="S0093">you know the Russians were actually winning the space race by miles</u>
<u n="790" who="S0018" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="791" who="S0093">and then suddenly the Americans were like ooh hello we've got one <pause dur="short"/> ooh we've landed <pause dur="short"/> ooh we've come back again safely</u>
<u n="792" who="S0018">yeah right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0093">oh right okay <pause dur="short"/> we've won <pause dur="short"/> we won <pause dur="short"/> ha ha ha</u>
<u n="794" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="795" who="S0093">any more flights to the moon now <pause dur="short"/> no sorry</u>
<u n="796" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0093">no we've been there done that <pause dur="short"/> and they haven't been since <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="798" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0093">and er there's so many <trunc>thin</trunc></u>
<u n="800" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="801" who="S0093">I I read that book well as I say <trunc>prob</trunc> in fact I remember reading it on the on a flight to New York in two thousand and one</u>
<u n="802" who="S0018">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> ooh</u>
<u n="803" who="S0093" trans="overlap">bizarrely yes <pause dur="short"/> about well a few months only a few months before nine eleven and er and I remember flying into New York <pause dur="short"/> and yeah reading this and going Gawd blimey I'd love to have a chat with a few Americans about this and see what they think you know</u>
<u n="804" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="805" who="S0093">and I did <pause dur="short"/> and they were all like they were you can't say that <pause dur="short"/> we didn't you know <pause dur="short"/> one guy got really aggressive</u>
<u n="806" who="S0018">it is <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's a national pride issue for them isn't it</u>
<u n="807" who="S0093">well it is yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0018">it was such a</u>
<u n="809" who="S0093">but one another guy I spoke to an American</u>
<u n="810" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="811" who="S0093">I just said you know I can believe that <pause dur="short"/> the American government lie to us about everything and anything <pause dur="short"/> and they always have done</u>
<u n="812" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="813" who="S0093">and they create all these things like you know the commie thing you know the <unclear/> the Russians you know</u>
<u n="814" who="S0018">create Al-Qaeda</u>
<u n="815" who="S0093">race</u>
<u n="816" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="817" who="S0093">Al-Qaeda of course yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean who</u>
<u n="818" who="S0018">that's another conspiracy theory that Al-Qaeda don't actually exist</u>
<u n="819" who="S0093" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> that'll be the next  the next  big one because oh well it's just too much <pause dur="short"/> it's just too much you know that</u>
<u n="820" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0093">the er er we got you know Blaire stupidly got involved as well <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="822" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="823" who="S0093">the Americans looked er er you know <pause dur="short"/> and er they had this great <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what programme it was now <pause dur="short"/> I was watching something the other day and somebody was slagging off the <trunc>Fr</trunc> American programme and er it was a chat show or something <pause dur="short"/> and they I think it was Craig Ferguson actually Craig Ferguson who is a Scottish guy</u>
<u n="824" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="825" who="S0093">but now very big in America <pause dur="short"/> he's got his own chat show <pause dur="short"/> and he was  he was  talking to somebody erm and it might have been Susan Sarandon who's quite right on usually but she said something</u>
<u n="826" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="827" who="S0093">quite anti French <pause dur="short"/> and he went ooh you can't say that and she said oh well you know they didn't get er behind us with the in the war <pause dur="short"/> and er Craig Ferguson said what the war that we went to against</u>
<u n="828" who="S0018">the illegal war</u>
<u n="829" who="S0093"><trunc>Ira</trunc> Iraq who had nothing to do with nine eleven <pause dur="short"/> erm and might have been about oil only</u>
<u n="830" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0093">and we were lied to about in the <trunc>mat</trunc> er you know <pause dur="short"/> yeah they had it yeah they would have been right not to go to war with us <pause dur="short"/> you know and er er the audience actually clapped and it was quite good</u>
<u n="832" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0018">american audience?</u>
<u n="835" who="S0093">an American audience actually clapped</u>
<u n="836" who="S0018" trans="overlap">and what was er Susan's response?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0093">er she went well yeah okay</u>
<u n="838" who="S0018">was she?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0093">not the best war <pause dur="short"/> that type of thing</u>
<u n="840" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0093">erm so she</u>
<u n="842" who="S0018">she's quite a vocal supporter of is it democrats?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0093" trans="overlap">well she is very <pause dur="short"/> yeah she's been very good at the  It was more of a slip of the tongue <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't anti French</u>
<u n="844" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="845" who="S0093">you know a sort of</u>
<u n="846" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="847" who="S0093">political point</u>
<u n="848" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0093">it was just something about the food or something</u>
<u n="850" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="851" who="S0093">something silly</u>
<u n="852" who="S0018">freedom Fries <pause dur="short"/> not French fries</u>
<u n="853" who="S0093" trans="overlap">freedom fries <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="854" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="855" who="S0093">but our special relationship dragged us into a war <pause dur="short"/> well David Kelly you know <pause dur="short"/> er Dr David Kelly is another conspiracy theory yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> what happened to him? Well it's that one's pretty obvious really isn't it</u>
<u n="857" who="S0093">well it would be to most people <pause dur="short"/> most educated people</u>
<u n="858" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0093">er but it's been you know proven by erm by a jury that was picked by Blair erm that that that it nothing untoward happened you know so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm surprised Cameron hasn't opened it up again actually</u>
<u n="860" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="861" who="S0093">I think he's got enough problems of his own though really but er</u>
<u n="862" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="863" who="S0093">yeah just as maybe it was done and dusted <pause dur="short"/> he can't do anything about it now but <pause dur="short"/> cos that was there's too many questions on it <pause dur="short"/> and again blimey really?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="865" who="S0093">and here's this guy saying no no there's nothing wrong <pause dur="short"/> there's no reason for us to go to war <pause dur="short"/> ooh I'm dead <pause dur="short"/> suicide is a massive <pause dur="short"/> apparently he wasn't that type of person you know</u>
<u n="866" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="867" who="S0093">it was a bit out of left field as the <unclear/> was saying</u>
<u n="868" who="S0018" trans="overlap">it was the timing of it though wasn't it really it's</u>
<u n="869" who="S0093">it was perfect for er some people</u>
<u n="870" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> but that's why you imagine that it was some kind of oh the two things are coarsely related <pause dur="short"/> must be</u>
<u n="871" who="S0093">er it's just too</u>
<u n="872" who="S0018">who done it?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0093">coincidental <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's the er coincidence can can become a great theory</u>
<u n="874" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="875" who="S0093">A conspiracy</u>
<u n="876" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="877" who="S0093">and there's so many coincidences in life <pause dur="short"/> we have them all the time</u>
<u n="878" who="S0018">that's true</u>
<u n="879" who="S0093">you know just me bumping into someone on the street <pause dur="short"/> serendipity and</u>
<u n="880" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="881" who="S0093">you know <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>c</trunc> just plain coincidences is it it can really er cloud the the mind you know</u>
<u n="882" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="883" who="S0093">but when it comes to massive political and international</u>
<u n="884" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="885" who="S0093">decisions made by politicians or or declarations of innocence or whatever else</u>
<u n="886" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="887" who="S0093">and you think well hold on a minute <pause dur="short"/> there's something else in this</u>
<u n="888" who="S0018">something smells fishy here</u>
<u n="889" who="S0093">there's no smoke without fire <pause dur="short"/> your turn</u>
<u n="890" who="S0018">true <pause dur="short"/> ooh ooh</u>
<u n="891" who="S0093">let's keep that going <pause dur="short"/> oh we've got a cliché time <pause dur="short"/> come on</u>
<u n="892" who="S0018" trans="overlap">we need another one <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="893" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0093">something smells fishy <pause dur="short"/> I had er no smoke without fire <pause dur="short"/> and we've gotta have a last one <pause dur="short"/> I can't think of another one no</u>
<u n="895" who="S0018">let's think of another one quickly er</u>
<u n="896" who="S0093">um <pause dur="short"/> all the <pause dur="short"/> no everything <unclear/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0018" trans="overlap">you can take a politician to water but you can't make him tell the truth <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0093">you can take a a horse to the to the water but a pencil must be lead</u>
<u n="899" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="900" who="S0093">that's Laurel and Hardy</u>
<u n="901" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0093">see he had a joke from nine</u>
<u n="903" who="S0018">oh the comedy</u>
<u n="904" who="S0093">nineteen twenty probably is still <pause dur="short"/> I still find funny <pause dur="short"/> and um that's the best you're gonna get from me</u>
<u n="905" who="S0018">do your you could  you could  film your own conspiracy comedy act</u>
<u n="906" who="S0093">well there has been there have been two films that I know of that have actually said hold on a minute <pause dur="short"/> let's just throw something in here <pause dur="short"/> one was Capricorn</u>
<u n="907" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0093">was it Capricorn Thirteen? Anyway it was er OJ I think was in it actually <pause dur="short"/> erm Another conspiracy there</u>
<u n="909" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="910" who="S0093">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0018">with his glove <unclear/></u>
<u n="912" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="913" who="S0093">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no he did it <pause dur="short"/> end of <pause dur="short"/> erm and er and that was all about you know a fake moon landing and then it got out in public and the government were trying to kill the astronauts who knew nothing about it</u>
<u n="914" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="915" who="S0093">they were just the innocent victims <pause dur="short"/> they were told to tell to say that they landed on the moon <unclear/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0018" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="917" who="S0093">and it's a <trunc>gr</trunc> it's an interesting film <pause dur="short"/> it's dated now but it's interesting</u>
<u n="918" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="919" who="S0093">and then brilliantly there was a there's erm <pause dur="short"/> now which one was it? One of the Bond films <pause dur="short"/> one of the Bond films <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it's one of the later Sean Connery's <pause dur="short"/> so IE early seventies</u>
<u n="920" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="921" who="S0093">er he's he's in a he's in the desert and then he stumbles in onto the set of a  of a  moon landing</u>
<u n="922" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0093">and it's just bizarre I think in a  in a  a studio</u>
<u n="924" who="S0018" trans="overlap">was it Moonraker? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0093">no it wasn't Moonraker</u>
<u n="926" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0093">no it was one of the early ones <pause dur="short"/> erm one one of the later</u>
<u n="928" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="929" who="S0093">Sean Connery's <pause dur="short"/> and he so he stumbles into this thing and they're filming people pretending to be on the moon and walking slowly on</u>
<u n="930" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="931" who="S0093">and he just drives through <pause dur="short"/> and this spacecraft er on this little space <trunc>mobil</trunc> and goes through <pause dur="short"/> and that was a really good little <unclear/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0018" trans="overlap">does he comment on it?</u>
<u n="933" who="S0093">no no</u>
<u n="934" who="S0018">or is it all left like?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0093">well that's the comment</u>
<u n="936" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="937" who="S0093">that's the comment <pause dur="short"/> it's er anyway yeah</u>
<u n="938" who="S0018">I I like that <pause dur="short"/> when they did it subtly before and they let you <trunc>in</trunc> infer it</u>
<u n="939" who="S0093">well I suppose</u>
<u n="940" who="S0018">now they have to point it out <pause dur="short"/> by the way that was the moon landing</u>
<u n="941" who="S0093">yes</u>
<u n="942" who="S0018">we were trying to infer that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="943" who="S0093">the dumb down the dumbing down in television and film yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it is though <pause dur="short"/> you know when you take a look at the best films <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if you saw New Year's Eve I think it was called? Er which was just out</u>
<u n="944" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="945" who="S0093">on New Year's Eve this year <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> A big American film <pause dur="short"/> it's basically an American rip off of Love Actually</u>
<u n="946" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="947" who="S0093">where they all come together at the end <pause dur="short"/> all that so lots of individual stories</u>
<u n="948" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="949" who="S0093">and they had a fantastic cast and everything but it was awful <pause dur="short"/> and it was just so <pause dur="short"/> erm what's the word I'm looking for? Morkish and very American er <pause dur="short"/> what's the word? What's the word I'm <trunc>look</trunc> I'm searching for?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="951" who="S0093">there you go <pause dur="short"/> a perfect example</u>
<u n="952" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="953" who="S0093">on tape to be stuck for a word</u>
<u n="954" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="955" who="S0093">er in this <trunc>experime</trunc> in this erm er</u>
<u n="956" who="S0018">squishy? Er</u>
<u n="957" who="S0093">no no no <pause dur="short"/> no the Americans don't do it better than anybody just</u>
<u n="958" who="S0018">back <trunc>le</trunc> <trunc>backb</trunc> <trunc>le</trunc> without a backbone?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0093">no it's the  it's the  Morkish sentimentality of the</u>
<u n="960" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="961" who="S0093">there's a word um in between that that I'm missing but <trunc>never</trunc> never mind</u>
<u n="962" who="S0018"></u>
<u n="963" who="S0093">it'll come back to me <pause dur="short"/> not  no <pause dur="short"/> it'll come back to me <pause dur="short"/> but it was just so treacle and oh</u>
<u n="964" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="965" who="S0093">and</u>
<u n="966" who="S0018">cheesy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="967" who="S0093">A lot of cheesy yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's the same word <pause dur="short"/> it's another word for cheesy basically <pause dur="short"/> erm but particularly when it comes to romance and and the</u>
<u n="968" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="969" who="S0093">the feel good end <pause dur="short"/> you know the It's A Wonderful Life type of ending <pause dur="short"/> which is a genuine ending</u>
<u n="970" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="971" who="S0093">now it's all it's a crowbar er a <trunc>ha</trunc> a sad you know a happy tearful end</u>
<u n="972" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> engineer us into having those emotions as opposed to</u>
<u n="973" who="S0093">yeah a bit like The X Factor really</u>
<u n="974" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="975" who="S0093">you know <pause dur="short"/> it's just like if everybody screams and shouts at the same whoops on the same level</u>
<u n="976" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="977" who="S0093">I mean how do you discern between what's good and bad really</u>
<u n="978" who="S0018">hmm mm</u>
<u n="979" who="S0093">er yes you've got your judges and all the acts and stuff but again it's er it's all it it's all really if you're told something's good <pause dur="short"/> if the kids are told something's good then they believe it's good <pause dur="short"/> whether it be X Factor</u>
<u n="980" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="981" who="S0093">or Big Brother or you know Ollie Mur Mores Murs whatever his name is</u>
<u n="982" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's how the the whole basis of advertising and commercialism nowadays isn't it</u>
<u n="983" who="S0093">yeah Jedward <pause dur="short"/> you know they're</u>
<u n="984" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0093">very distinctly untalented</u>
<u n="986" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="987" who="S0093">said of Jedward if you don't know they're twins</u>
<u n="988" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="989" who="S0093">and now they've just got this <pause dur="short"/> they're making fortunes from er from from er commercials yeah <pause dur="short"/> jade Goodie was another astonishing thing <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if you must have been when that happened</u>
<u n="990" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh no I did hear about Jade Goodie <pause dur="short"/> yes and she even reached er international news <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="991" who="S0093">yeah for the</u>
<u n="992" who="S0018">the whole <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="993" who="S0093">well when she became famous I actually watched cos er people were <pause dur="short"/> I think I was working for TWI at the time <pause dur="short"/> a big television company in London <pause dur="short"/> and er there were loads of people watching Big Brother and I'd watched the first series thinking this is gonna be really fun cos you know I'd like to see well how people like respond and the</u>
<u n="994" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> I watched</u>
<u n="995" who="S0093">and the first series</u>
<u n="996" who="S0018">I watched the first series of Big Brother in Spain</u>
<u n="997" who="S0093" trans="overlap">the first two series really <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="998" who="S0018">and it was super <pause dur="short"/> it was a social <trunc>ex</trunc></u>
<u n="999" who="S0093" trans="overlap">the Spanish version or the?</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was like a social experiment</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0093">it was a social experiment yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0018">and they chose lovely people as well who really <trunc>co</trunc> <trunc>corab</trunc> collaborated and cooperated</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0093" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's human nature</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0093">it er under the microscope er you know not under the microscope but it would you know in in a verified situation but but it was more real I thought <pause dur="short"/> but then they started manufacturing it and you know</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0093">getting these people who are characters on it</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0093">anyway this one this Jade Goodie was so thick that people said you've just gotta you've gotta watch it <pause dur="short"/> and I said I'm not gonna watch er Big Brother <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta watch it <pause dur="short"/> and I er started watching it and she was just car crash television really</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0093">and she said  she said  that East  that East  Angular <pause dur="short"/> east angular she used to call it is East angular is in London isn't it</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1013" who="S0093">and all this <pause dur="short"/> it was and she was just so thick <pause dur="short"/> it was unbelievable <pause dur="short"/> which is another word I hate but anyway</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0093">that's another conversation</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1017" who="S0093">the word unbelievable <pause dur="short"/> cos that must show up so many times <pause dur="short"/> and I work do a lot of work in football <pause dur="short"/> and it's the most overused</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0093">the phrase is to be fair</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0093">erm unbelievable er er word <pause dur="short"/> unbelievable <pause dur="short"/> er a couple of them <pause dur="short"/> anyway I'll come back to that</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1023" who="S0093">anyway erm and er then she became this sort of people's princess almost you know</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0018">um</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0093">certain people's princess <pause dur="short"/> and she made a fortune <pause dur="short"/> I mean a lot of money out of</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0018">didn't she have a PR? A machine behind her <pause dur="short"/> wasn't it Max</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0093">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0018">cliffard</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0093">well latterly when she had all the problems but</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0018">swinging it all for him <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0093">she had a good agent and um</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0093">and she married this bloke and just basically er since she's died has just spent all the money <pause dur="short"/> ended up back in prison and all sorts of stuff <pause dur="short"/> but she would get she would charge five thousand pounds a night <pause dur="short"/> not just the night <pause dur="short"/> per periods of a nightclub and she would go to two or three a night you know</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0093">and just wave and go ha ha <pause dur="short"/> and people would turn up and scream and say ah there's Jade Goodie <pause dur="short"/> and then  and then  she hit the racism problems</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0093">you know where she was just it was  it was  racist bleeing <pause dur="short"/> it was the worst kind of</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0093">human behaviour you could come across</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0018">but wasn't it just as you said the fact that she was thick and she didn't realise that it was?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0093">er well no</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0018">then again she was making fifteen thousand a night <pause dur="short"/> she can't have been that thick <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0093">well she was thick <pause dur="short"/> she just had a good manager</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0093">or whatever er else <pause dur="short"/> and er and unfortunately a very gullible public</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0093">who just thought around the Essex area just thought she was amazing you know</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0093">why? I didn't get it <pause dur="short"/> and then she had all that problem <pause dur="short"/> and then she had you know and then she became this martyr almost you know</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0093">and isn't she <trunc>d</trunc> isn't she amazing? Why is she amazing? She was a horrible person <pause dur="short"/> she wasn't very intelligent</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0093">she she racially bullied somebody</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0093">on live on television</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0018">but she died on reality TV and that's</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0093">she</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0018">what people like isn't it</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0018">they like to see reality</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0093">and she raised awareness of cancer</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0093">we were all aware of cancer before Jade Goodie</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0093">you know um <pause dur="short"/> she died with dignity er</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I think as you said it's car crash TV <pause dur="short"/> and it's all these people who aspire to be rich</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0093" trans="overlap">it is yeah</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0018">and have a horrendous amount of money without actually having any talent</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0018">and</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0018">and that people do like watching to see if people are going to succeed or fail and</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0093">yeah there's a gladiatorial thing isn't there now</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0093">I er you know it really is thumbs up thumbs down and you're dead almost</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0093">you know and <trunc>peo</trunc> I mean it's</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0093">it is car crash television <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately the rest of television some of which I work in of course</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0093">will always have a market I hope <pause dur="short"/> current affairs</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0093">documentary <pause dur="short"/> you know where you can actually tell a story and you can</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0093">and it might be about a celebrity <pause dur="short"/> it might be about something else</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0093">so there's always a <trunc>s</trunc> a cross over</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0093">erm you know I've done  I've done  a lot of sport and there's always a cross over there <pause dur="short"/> people are ha footballers footballers oh my God oh my God</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0093">erm but I did this documentary not so long <trunc>a</trunc> well a few years ago now and and er one at some point we we talked to a group of erm well er er all sorts of people about aspiration <pause dur="short"/> and and there were a lot of girls we talked to <pause dur="short"/> across the various different interviews <pause dur="short"/> young <pause dur="short"/> twelve thirteen fourteen year-olds</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0093">who erm almost to person wanted to marry a footballer when they grew up</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0093">that was it <pause dur="short"/> that's the only thing they wanted to do <pause dur="short"/> now possibly because that's what everybody was talking about at the time</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0093">and then they've grown up since then in terms of that <pause dur="short"/> but er I just thought oh my God you know how many footballers do you think there are to go around anyway</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1099" who="S0093">and but that's all they really wanted to do <pause dur="short"/> and there's the whole generation of</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0093">young girls</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0093">in particular post feminism you see who who you know their parents grandparents or whoever had fought for the right for a woman to earn and to be in the board room <pause dur="short"/> and to</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0093">you know to run companies and everything else <pause dur="short"/> and here's this whole generation being brought up now because of X Factor because of the the Heat magazine <pause dur="short"/> the celebrity thing</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0093">where it's all about how much money you've got <pause dur="short"/> and and I think that's really worrying <pause dur="short"/> and there's still I <trunc>so</trunc> sort of speak to girls here at David  who all they're after is the marriage <pause dur="short"/> they don't</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0093">and it doesn't matter who it's to as long as they're rich <pause dur="short"/> they don't care about the person</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0018">how shallow <pause dur="short"/> what a shame <pause dur="short"/> it's just <unclear/> isn't it really</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0093" trans="overlap">well I I know there's a few unfortunately <pause dur="short"/> there's one girl friend of mine who's actually cos she is quite a friend of mine but she's but she before I knew her I have to say she actually targeted a guy who was wealthy <pause dur="short"/> married him and divorced him in two years and took half his money</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0093">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and she did it deliberately <pause dur="short"/> she's quite open about it</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0018">does he not know a thing called the prenup? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1115" who="S0093">well no cos you know a lot of people don't</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0018">yeah well you you don't think</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0093" trans="overlap">I mean this was fifteen years ago</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0093">now you know people don't get married <pause dur="short"/> men</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0093">A lot of my my contemporaries don't want to get married</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0093">because of all this <pause dur="short"/> the last ten years have been dreadful for men</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0018" trans="overlap">fair enough</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0093">with marriages and divorce and everything</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0093">and men have been absolutely clobbered financially <pause dur="short"/> women have their own er downs as well of course</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0093">you know it's not all one sided <pause dur="short"/> you can't <pause dur="short"/> but you know financially there's been a lot of gold digging and all sorts of stuff</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0093">and I really worry for the this generation of kids who are growing up who haven't got the quite the  quite the  er erm they haven't been taught you've got to work at something</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0093">the the education system now is almost about you do the work the day before and you pass it that day <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to study</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0018">yeah definitely definitely</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0093">and really work and go over the same subject</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0018" trans="overlap">what what most surprised me when I was in school doing er the training was that kids don't have a any kind of work <trunc>eth</trunc> work ethic <pause dur="short"/> they they seem to come to school to widen their social circle</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0018">and that's it <pause dur="short"/> they're in class talking about <trunc>some</trunc> what someone posted on Facebook the night before <pause dur="short"/> and you're like er excuse me <pause dur="short"/> can you kind of like pay attention now? We're</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0018">trying to learn this <pause dur="short"/> can you tell me the answer to number whatever? Or can you perform your little role play for me?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0093" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0018">and they're like but miss we're talking about what happened last night on Facebook <pause dur="short"/> cos do you know  do you know  that this happened and this happened <pause dur="short"/> and it's so much more important than French <pause dur="short"/> and it's like</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0093">well there you go <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0018" trans="overlap">you'll always I mean you'll always get that to some extent but it just surprised me as to how all pervasive it was that they didn't value learning</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0093" trans="overlap">well the</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0018">they didn't value knowledge</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0093">no</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0018">they didn't <pause dur="short"/> to them they can get <pause dur="short"/> they don't need to store knowledge <pause dur="short"/> they can just go onto Google and get knowledge and dispose of it <pause dur="short"/> and not have to process it</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0093">I interviewed um an eighteen year-old a couple of years ago now <pause dur="short"/> she's probably twenty-one twenty-two now or something <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> for a documentary <pause dur="short"/> she wanted to be a researcher on a programme we were doing</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0093">and I just said okay so tell me how you would go about researching um and I gave her I can't remember what the subject was but I gave her an example <pause dur="short"/> how would you go about erm researching this for for our purposes for television?</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0093">an hour long programme <pause dur="short"/> she said well I'll go onto the internet and I'll look look it up <pause dur="short"/> and I said</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0018">resourceful <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1155" who="S0093">is that your answer seriously? So so basically anybody can walk in to this job and just go onto the internet and look it up? And so I said so what so er you're sure everything is correct on the internet <pause dur="short"/> she said well most of it is <pause dur="short"/> I said look I think we're going the wrong way here and I don't think you're gonna get this job</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1157" who="S0093">I was honest with her</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0093">I said can I just teach you something er for the next job <pause dur="short"/> for your next <trunc>inter</trunc> job interview</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0093">Don't ever ever say that <pause dur="short"/> whether you end up going on the internet or not</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0093">and you've gotta do a certain amount of internet</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0093">which I do it <pause dur="short"/> we all do it <pause dur="short"/> but you've gotta check your subject <pause dur="short"/> yeah checked your checked the references <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta really be sure</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0093">and you've got to back er that up with</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0018">one of the things that I teach as er academic English like how to reference things <pause dur="short"/> how to research <pause dur="short"/> and I had a group of Chinese students last year who no matter how many times I told them they had to <trunc>pr</trunc> they had to choose valid and reliable er sources to get their information from there was still Wikipedia two thousand and eleven popping up in all their essays <pause dur="short"/> so I just showed them <pause dur="short"/> I put it up on the</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0093">that's the worst</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0018">the screen and I chose the thickest student in the class which</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0093"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1172" who="S0018">obviously I didn't say okay you thickest student in the class come here but</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0018">the kind of <vocal desc="laugh"/> the black sheep of the family as it were that everybody knew <pause dur="short"/> I said okay Marina <pause dur="short"/> let's look at globalization in China <pause dur="short"/> can you see anything on Wikipedia about it? She was like yes <pause dur="short"/> I said okay right now I want you to go onto edit and I want you to write the most stupid er erroneous sentence you can imagine possible about <trunc>Ch</trunc> er globalization in China <pause dur="short"/> and so she did <pause dur="short"/> and we pressed save and er I just said okay <pause dur="short"/> so are you gonna use Wikipedia now knowing that it's been edited by people like Marina? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1175" who="S0093" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> well this girl actually did say</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0018">made the point</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0093">that her she does most you know she goes on Wikipedia and she gets all her knowledge there</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0018">mm anyway</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0093">and I tried to explain to her again exactly what you just said</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0093">it's incredible <pause dur="short"/> so you know but she that was her that was how she's been brought up</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0093">Cos it was just okay <pause dur="short"/> er I wanna work in television <pause dur="short"/> I don't <pause dur="short"/> it's almost as if she ad erm had some sort of right to just walk in and say okay I'll do that and do that</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah because she</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0093">she didn't actually research the job</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but that's the thing I think the kids kids are <trunc>gr</trunc> <trunc>gr</trunc> kids grow up in an atmosphere whereby education's not too important <pause dur="short"/> what is most</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0018">what most attracts their attention is commercial advertising campaigns that</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0018">kind of instil in them this this attitude that they have the right to</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0093">mm</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0018">these trainers that cost this amount of money</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0093">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0018">and they have a right to this car that cost this amount of money and they've got no er understanding of reality about what they're gonna have to do to get that amount of money</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0093" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0018">and so they just expect that they have this God given right to that job or to that salary</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0093" trans="overlap">oh it's shocking <pause dur="short"/> britain's terrible for that <pause dur="short"/> er coming back to what we were just saying erm when you have this the girls I've mentioned you know about</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0093">they wanna marry footballers cos they wanna have the lifestyle <pause dur="short"/> they wanna have this that and the other <pause dur="short"/> and there's a guy I was speaking to who I went to school <trunc>with</trunc></u>
<u n="1200" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0093">not so long ago <pause dur="short"/> and he er just just got divorced <pause dur="short"/> and he's forty-four <pause dur="short"/> and er he's a car salesman <pause dur="short"/> all be it Porche</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0093">so he's quite you know <pause dur="short"/> they the the commission is quite big</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0093">but it's a very basic <pause dur="short"/> and when it's bad it's bad <pause dur="short"/> and when it's good it's good <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0093">er so it's it's not a great salary <pause dur="short"/> he's not  he's not  earning a hundred  a hundred  and fifty thousand a year or something <pause dur="short"/> he's probably turning over oh I don't know anywhere between on a good year probably fifty to seventy</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0093">bad year twenty to fifty <pause dur="short"/> I don't know something like that <pause dur="short"/> and anyway she wanted the lifestyle <pause dur="short"/> so they had a six bedroom house in Dorridge which is a very affluent part of Solihull <pause dur="short"/> six bedroom house <pause dur="short"/> the two of them</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0018"><vocal desc="whistle"/></u>
<u n="1211" who="S0093">she's a a teacher by the way</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0093">she's a teacher <pause dur="short"/> he's a car salesman</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0093">and they had a six bedroom house in Dorridge and both drove Porches <pause dur="short"/> and also had a big four-by-four Mercedes four-by-four <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what it was but you're talking about a fifty grand <trunc>s</trunc> car <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1216" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0093">and you just go that doesn't add up</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0093">that just does not add up</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1221" who="S0093">you are you're going for the lifestyle without in any way paying for it</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0093">and sure enough they can't afford it <pause dur="short"/> she just buggered off basically <pause dur="short"/> and has left him <pause dur="short"/> and he has to find <pause dur="short"/> he's gonna have to sell the house so he can cut things down</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0093">the cars <pause dur="short"/> the loans they took which they can't he can't do anything about <pause dur="short"/> he's having to find five thousand pounds a month just for the bills</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0018">crikey</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0093">let alone to live on</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0093">and that that's all because of the aspiration or whatever</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0093">but it's also the the erm <pause dur="short"/> there is a word that I'm searching for again <pause dur="short"/> the second time I've done that</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1233" who="S0093">erm it's this is the British society has become this there is erm <pause dur="short"/> what's the word? What's the word? Um <pause dur="short"/> it'll come back to me <pause dur="short"/> that that people do have erm a right to be given things</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0093">and the worst thing you see it here a lot at David  There are a lot of kids <pause dur="short"/> er the last not so much now I guess <pause dur="short"/> they kind of had to cut it down <pause dur="short"/> the pre-recession where Brown you have to say was encouraging people to borrow money and the banks were encouraging to</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0093">people to <trunc>ba</trunc> to borrow money <pause dur="short"/> er sorry the Brown was encouraging the banks to borrow money <pause dur="short"/> er and so on and so forth <pause dur="short"/> and it was all a and I remember Brown saying you've never had it so good</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0093">and I even at the time about two thousand and three two thousand and four er and I was thinking no you've never owed so much <pause dur="short"/> there's a massive difference between them</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0093">right I want a new car <pause dur="short"/> I'll go get a loan <pause dur="short"/> ah I've got the car <pause dur="short"/> isn't it brilliant? Ah look at you <pause dur="short"/> aren't you successful? No you you're owing all this money</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0093">it's not you know how much do you er what are you worth? It's only what you're worth after you've paid everything off <pause dur="short"/> so people have got to <trunc>admi</trunc> you know a five hundred thousand pound er mortgage</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0093">they've got to pay that back before the value of the house actually keeps it <pause dur="short"/> and people just didn't get it <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately the kids some of the kids that were here they were <pause dur="short"/> it was Christmas <pause dur="short"/> there was a fight amongst all the parents to see how much they could spend on their children you know</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> oh no crikey</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0093" trans="overlap">I spent a thousand <pause dur="short"/> I remember er er er one conversation I overheard</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1249" who="S0093">well I was part of actually cos the er the tennis social <pause dur="short"/> there were about twenty of us sitting down to have a cup of tea after</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0093">er after this game of tennis <pause dur="short"/> er a Tuesday morning and er and and these  and these  ladies were talking <pause dur="short"/> and they just said oh I've just spent a thousand on on on Johnny <pause dur="short"/> he's two</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0018">huh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1253" who="S0093">er what what what <trunc>d</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> and then there was this whole conversation going on for ages</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0018" trans="overlap">he's not going to remember it</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0093">like oh well we'll try and limit it you know to to a thousand pounds per child or something for <pause dur="short"/> and you think Jeez you know <pause dur="short"/> and then all the stuff they get during the year as well</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0093">all er because they just say they want it</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0093">there's no earning it <pause dur="short"/> when I was when I grew up my mum was a <trunc>sec</trunc> <event desc="sound of phone"/> oh that's me <pause dur="short"/> a secretary in a family planning clinic</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0093">sorry I should have turned that off</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0018">Don't worry</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0093">erm I'll see who it is <pause dur="short"/> er I do need to take that but I'll take it later obviously <pause dur="short"/> er and er she erm er er er erm er erm <pause dur="short"/> what was I? Oh yes <pause dur="short"/> erm mum was a <trunc>fam</trunc> <trunc>fam</trunc> worked in a family planning clinic as a secretary</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0093">and my dad worked in the post office all his life <pause dur="short"/> so I came out with a fairly</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0093">you know normal upbringing <pause dur="short"/> I went to Solihull school <pause dur="short"/> and I went to Solihull school because my brother got a full scholarship so my parents</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0093">with the help of granddad could pay for me basically <pause dur="short"/> so I was very lucky with that <pause dur="short"/> you know so I came from a</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0093">quite a normal background and then you know was able to I was able to get a better education as it were</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0093">because of the circumstances you know <pause dur="short"/> um parents er kids I speak to that's right people um some parents I speak to sort of say right well I've got to get my kids into Solihull school <pause dur="short"/> so you know people there don't you? And I know the headmaster <pause dur="short"/> I play golf with him <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1274" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0093">so they say so you know if can we bung him some money and he'll get us <pause dur="short"/> no it doesn't work like that <pause dur="short"/> you have to</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0093">you know I had to sit my eleven plus and actually get it</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0093">and it was like uh God</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0018">meritocracy</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0093">and I I did pass just passed <pause dur="short"/> oh thank God for that <pause dur="short"/> and my brother who was a real high flyer you know he's now a lawyer and er very successful and all that <pause dur="short"/> he's one of those high flyers</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0093">you know always will be <pause dur="short"/> and I had to you know fight my way in there</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0093">erm now there's a lot of  a lot of  parents who think they just that their kids deserve</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0093">what they deserve <pause dur="short"/> so when I grew up I was um you know if I wanted the latest Action Man or whatever else I had to you know er earn it <pause dur="short"/> you know whether it be cleaning the car or</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0093">when I was really small <pause dur="short"/> or actually doing a paper round <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0093">er cos my granddad owned um two or three news agents around Hall Green</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0093">and and has a store in <unclear/> So of course I used to do paper rounds and things like that</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0093">you know six o'clock on a Sunday morning I was up in the snow doing all that when I was fourteen fifteen</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1297" who="S0093">and you try and get a fourteen fifteen year old to do that now you can forget it</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0018" trans="overlap">A job? What are you talking about?</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0093">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0018">A holiday job?</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0093">but again a part of that whole X Factory type of thing</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0093">I keep saying that <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's an overnight success <pause dur="short"/> it's a</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0018">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to work at it</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0093">I demand to have it</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0093">you've gotta work at these <pause dur="short"/> a lot of them do</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0093">you know and but it's also the fact that it's just you know it's almost  it's almost  because it the the bits in the X Factor I don't mind watching <pause dur="short"/> I don't sit there and watch it <pause dur="short"/> but if it's on <pause dur="short"/> if somebody else is watching it <pause dur="short"/> girlfriend or whatever it's just the it's those early rounds where</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0093">it's all about how bad people are <pause dur="short"/> and let's laugh at how bad they are</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0018">yeah but that's that's the way they choose them <pause dur="short"/> I think they have a</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0018">three different piles <pause dur="short"/> the mingers the blingers and the clingers or something like that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1315" who="S0093">yeah you're right <pause dur="short"/> that's it <pause dur="short"/> I like the phrase</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0018">just to make it</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0093">but there's all this erm</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0018">isn't it sad that that makes people watch it</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0093">well I watch <pause dur="short"/> that's the only bit I watch <pause dur="short"/> it's brilliant you know in a way <pause dur="short"/> I don't watch it really just say if it's on</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0018">you're a rubber neck</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0093">that's the only bit I'll watch</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0018">car crash TV</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0093">well you can't help watching it <pause dur="short"/> these people are awful <pause dur="short"/> but they're being laughed at and I don't like that</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0093">and the and they they <trunc>en</trunc> the the entertainment</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0093">seems to be about how bad these people are and how what a  what a  fool they make of themselves</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0093">and then they get with ooh yeah you're on stage <pause dur="short"/> aren't you brilliant <pause dur="short"/> no you're not</u>
<u n="1330" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1331" who="S0093">and then the people at the <trunc>e</trunc> the top end who are you know back to the down to the  now that's what I don't watch cos I just find it so manufactured and <trunc>s</trunc> and you know if if somebody could get through a song without crying and a speech afterwards without crying <pause dur="short"/> it's you know how about a backbone as well</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0093">you know <pause dur="short"/> yes there's emotion and there's a good time <pause dur="short"/> but not every single time you come on television don't cry</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0018">oh yeah yeah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1335" who="S0093">you sort of begin to lose a bit of sympathy with with me</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0018">it's crazy</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0093">if there's something er real <pause dur="short"/> I'm doing this</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0018">it's sensational and</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0093">well I watched The Apprentice the other night and that's the one programme I do actually quite like because</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0093">you can learn from it</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0093">I can learn from it by watching these people who are mostly idiots who are mostly chosen to be idiots or to be a bit confrontational or to be a bit erm you know a bit good at what they are supposed to be doing <pause dur="short"/> who knows <pause dur="short"/> er but they actually but I learn from it about how not to pitch</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0093">I have to do that all the time you know</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0093">so I pick up things from this programme and I think actually that's</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0093">that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> I you know if I'm gonna be doing a presentation</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0093">don't do this <pause dur="short"/> but do this</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0093">or if I'm going to buy something <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite a good negotiator anyway</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0093">I've been working for twenty odd years in television and you learn how to negotiate with Channel 4 the BBC and all that sort of stuff <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite good at that <pause dur="short"/> but you can still learn</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0093">whereas the X Factor doesn't actually teach me anything</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0093">big Brother didn't teach me anything <pause dur="short"/> erm I don't find you know even in sport there's an educational side to it I suppose <pause dur="short"/> of <trunc>cer</trunc> of most things about how to</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0018">yeah but even sport isn't really sport any more <pause dur="short"/> it's a profit making</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0093">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0018">machine</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0093">well it it yes <pause dur="short"/> er Sky of course um you know is all about that but actually their coverage is very good <pause dur="short"/> I'm bias cos I've worked in sport</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0093">you know <pause dur="short"/> what they do is very good</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0018" trans="overlap">do you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that works on the bar here?</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0018">yeah cos he I was chatting to him the other day and he said that he was a sports journalist who'd worked for Sky and since then</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0093">oh I'm thinking about another <anon type="name" nameType="m"/><pause dur="short"/> no which <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0018">oh he works on the bar here</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0093">not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the singer then? Who used to work behind the in reception</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0018">I don't know</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0093">no I don't know this other <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'll look out for him though <pause dur="short"/> he works for? How old is he?</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0018">he's about twenty-four</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0093">oh right so he's probably done a</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0018">he's done a</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0093">he's probably struggling a bit yeah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0093">hence why he's working here <pause dur="short"/> I'd say he's</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0018">struggling completely yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a shame really cos he seems so into it <pause dur="short"/> he's started up his own blog and everything to</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0093">there was erm again there's I get a lot of people <pause dur="short"/> er coming back to the dumbing down thing <pause dur="short"/> one of the  one of the  things I I'm guilty of I I I what I <trunc>sh</trunc> I don't hire people who have done media studies</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0093">by just on principle</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0018">is that's cos it's too</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0093">Cos there are so many people</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0093">who are after each job <pause dur="short"/> when I hire people you know</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0093">if I'm doing a big production or something I get a series of runners researchers juniors for some researching and obviously they're younger people and I wanna give them a  give them a  chance</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0093">most and maybe it's coming back to this dumbing down of education and it was  it was  deemed a an <trunc>eas</trunc> an easy degree</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0093">to get back in the two</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0018">right okay</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0093">back in the noughties</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0018">Micky Mouse thing</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0018">kind of yogurt studies</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0093" trans="overlap">A Micky Mouse degree yeah</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1401" who="S0093">and what I find with media studies students is they're just er you know they'd know who won Big Brother in what year cos they've <trunc>s</trunc> you know that's what they've done <pause dur="short"/> they've studied the media <pause dur="short"/> they don't really know what who Murdock is and <pause dur="short"/> they know who he is and who he owns but they don't what his politics are or</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0093">completely <trunc>im</trunc> you know important stuff</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0093">erm but they certainly don't know how to actually make a programme</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0093">which is what I need <pause dur="short"/> so I hire people who have got experience and whatever else <pause dur="short"/> and this is what Eliot must be struggling with <pause dur="short"/> that he's got</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0093">a bit of experience <pause dur="short"/> but even he can't get in</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0093">er so I er I myself have decided that I'm only gonna hire people who have actually got either a erm a an actual degree you know in er I don't know what it would be er cos you don't get degrees in researching necessarily but you know</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0018" trans="overlap">it's like broadcast journalism?</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0018">something like that</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0093">something more specific erm job-related <pause dur="short"/> it er <unclear/> you can study to be a camera person for example</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0093">you know there are degrees <pause dur="short"/> the old B-techs</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0018">vocational type things</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0093">yeah vocational degrees yeah <pause dur="short"/> and there are of course erm er excuse me actual er writing courses and that</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0093">people er who have actually studied and worked</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0093">again the X Factor thing as well <pause dur="short"/> I raised it you see <pause dur="short"/> people who have actually just gone into something <pause dur="short"/> ooh media studies <pause dur="short"/> ooh great I can then get into media and become a celebrity</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0093">ha</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0018">woo <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1427" who="S0093">no you can't <pause dur="short"/> you can't not with me anyway <pause dur="short"/> er unless you've got something to say</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0093">and you've got and you know you're a you're the next erm I don't know Alan Carr who I hate <pause dur="short"/> erm again Alan Carr is sums up to me</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0093">modern television in many ways <pause dur="short"/> he's a very funny man on stage <pause dur="short"/> really funny funny man because it's his stuff is really well written</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0093">but what having watched his show and listened to his radio show to a certain extent he's just not a funny man <pause dur="short"/> he's he's</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0093">he's a <trunc>g</trunc> he's a modern day comedian</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0093">that actually is not very funny <pause dur="short"/> and again if you watch his Channel 4 show even if he just says the most er just a straight thing or</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0093">whoop and the media American whoop and the applause and all that <pause dur="short"/> and he actually hasn't said anything funny</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> it's all about well belittling people and as you said the whole thumbs up thumbs down</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0093">but there is that as well <pause dur="short"/> but he's an awful interviewer</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0093">so when he's interviewing you know quite big celebs</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0093">he's dreadful <pause dur="short"/> erm and he comes out with the odd one liner and it makes you think well I could have done that you know but I haven't got what he's got <pause dur="short"/> you know in terms of</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0093">you know being a face and all that <pause dur="short"/> but I he just sums up to me the modern media <pause dur="short"/> and the modern culture I suppose</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0093">and er um and he's very much <trunc>s</trunc> er a result of the last ten years that we've</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0093">been talking about in this interview as it were</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0093">erm that you know that that social media has well I think the dumbing down of education was part of this the process of it</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0093">and then in the back in the nineties</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0018">do you think it was the agenda? Do you think it was er the effect?</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0093">it's cause and effect isn't it partly partly</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><trunc>Cau</trunc> but do you think that was actually a an engineered cause to bring in the effect of people being dumbed down? Or do you think it was a kind of like a secondary effect?</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0093" trans="overlap">I think  I think  it's a result of it <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a result of <pause dur="short"/> it's technology anyway isn't it</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0093">we've got this amazing technology where you can just go oh and you're talking to somebody else</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0093">the trouble is you'll sit around this room next week when it's Easter holidays and you'll see a load of teenagers here <pause dur="short"/> they're not talking to each other</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0093">but they're all on their</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0018">I hate that</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0093">all on their <unclear/></u>
<u n="1468" who="S0018" trans="overlap">my friends do it <pause dur="short"/> the girls  the girls  who work at the BBC and I'm like they're doing that thing called Draw Something</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0093">oh they're playing games <pause dur="short"/> they're not even just emailing or texting?</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0018" trans="overlap">or they're sending <pause dur="short"/> yeah but they send it to each other <pause dur="short"/> and I'm like no we're not gonna do that again tonight are we <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1471" who="S0093">no I'm I I just say no and people think of me as a bit of a</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0093">a bit of a dinosaur</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0018">well I had a a nineteen seventies brick mobile phone up until about a month ago when I had to change it cos it died <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1475" who="S0093">and I I just I have got a brick <pause dur="short"/> because I got cloned <pause dur="short"/> I did have a Blackberry</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0093">and now I have a erm er well I I got cloned so I I had to lose my old phone and then they're gonna give me one back again</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0093">so in the meantime I've just got a pay as you go <pause dur="short"/> that just sends messages</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0018">and they're so but they</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0093">texts <pause dur="short"/> it hasn't even got a camera <pause dur="short"/> and actually I'm thinking</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0018" trans="overlap">but that's all you need</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0093">do you know what?</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0018">exactly</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0093">I quite like it</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0018">I agree <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1487" who="S0093">but Alison my girlfriend has got a er iPhone and they're fantastic <pause dur="short"/> I've got a</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0018">really? Do you like them?</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0093">and actually I've got this <pause dur="short"/> yeah well I've got um I mean I I've got an Apple myself</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0093">and I've got er in fact one of the <pause dur="short"/> I'll send you my CV</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0093">I'll send you my CV <pause dur="short"/> cos you might be able to <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's relevant but you might wanna</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0018">no but I'm sending out my CV to lots of places at the moment so it would actually be quite interesting to see how other people lay theirs out and</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0093">oh well there there you go <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> erm I think I have to re-join this erm</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0018">talking about researchers <pause dur="short"/> cos I've I've</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0093">let me send you that yeah</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0018">A quite close friend of mine at the moment is doing the research for a film they're gonna make about an American company is gonna make about the roots of reggae music <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0093">er what a documentary or a?</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no a film <pause dur="short"/> so he's been in the British library for the past couple of months every every week researching</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0093" trans="overlap">oh that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> there was erm there must have been a BBC4 programme</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0093">not so long ago on the er <pause dur="short"/> er he or she must know about that <pause dur="short"/> erm definitely worth checking out because it's on the roots of well it no it's not <pause dur="short"/> it was about British reggae</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0093">there's also one about British blues as well which actually there's a massive tie <pause dur="short"/> I would be interested to er hear about that</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if you ever need</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0093">I don't know if <unclear/></u>
<u n="1508" who="S0018">yeah he's a PhD Oxford graduate student</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0093">well that's very good</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0018">and he's he's a I mean he's his brain is made for researching so if you ever need someone quite high up</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0093" trans="overlap">I always <pause dur="short"/> I always do yeah</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0093">um would you just forgive me one moment I I</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0093">I just can't remember if I'm supposed to be if I've saved my CV on here <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I have actually</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1517" who="S0093">but I'll send <pause dur="short"/> what I'll do though is I'll send you <pause dur="short"/> I should have done this anyway so that you could come pre-<trunc>arm</trunc> pre-armed really</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1519" who="S0093">er I'll send you a little thing on Head First media</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0093">which we've rebranded <pause dur="short"/> we've dropped the website</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0093">Cos we're gonna have it redesigned <pause dur="short"/> and we might drop the name as well <pause dur="short"/> so don't worry about Head First media but I'm it might be useful to you</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0093">because um <unclear/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> because um there's um there may be some cross overs we could do <pause dur="short"/> and what I can't <pause dur="short"/> I'm really quite interested in this you know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if you wanna pause it for a moment whilst I'm waffling</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0018">oh no waffle away <pause dur="short"/> er do you want me to pause it?</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0093">yeah cos I'm just gonna</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0018" trans="overlap">for confidential?</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0093">oh no no no no <pause dur="short"/> not cos of that <pause dur="short"/> I just thought this might be a bit boring but</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0018">no no no it's okay <pause dur="short"/> it's it's speech</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0093">it is speech <pause dur="short"/> you're right</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0018">but if you want me to pause it because you</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0093">no no no no</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0018">would prefer</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0093">it's I'm just saying it might be <trunc>wor</trunc> this</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0093">this quite kind of thing has been done a lot on Radio 4 of course</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0093">speech <pause dur="short"/> speech patterns <pause dur="short"/> there was a great</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0018">ah yeah</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0093">erm Stephen Fry series on BBC 4</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0093">er Radio 4</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0093">er I can't remember what it was called now but it was about three four part series on</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0018">oh no it was on TV as well wasn't it <pause dur="short"/> the Stephen Fry one about <trunc>ling</trunc></u>
<u n="1547" who="S0093">yes there was one about words actually</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0093"><unclear/> about the technology</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0018" trans="overlap">language and</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0093">well etymology <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>indemoler</trunc> <trunc>indemoler</trunc> <trunc>eti</trunc></u>
<u n="1552" who="S0018"><trunc>Eta</trunc> etymology</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0093">it is etymology isn't it</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0093">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm it's a really fascinating thing <pause dur="short"/> but he did this whole documentary on the history of puns really <pause dur="short"/> puns and</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0018">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0093">metaphors and</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0093">erm yeah he went through various clichés as well which is quite a good one <pause dur="short"/> well how do clichés come about? Where do they come from? And all that</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1561" who="S0093">and but I find I think there's a bit of a lack on television</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0093">again it's maybe part of trying to dumb up television unsuccessfully</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> what a fantastic cause</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0093">well you er there would be a lot of people who would be interested in that <pause dur="short"/> er a few years ago I started a company with a guy <pause dur="short"/> who unfortunately we fell out</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0018">ah what a shame</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0093">um er <unclear/> but we had a um an interesting idea where it was gonna we were gonna call it <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well we we were aiming television <pause dur="short"/> this was back in the early two thousands</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0093">right and it was already going a bit Big Brotherly and reality E E and I wanted to er</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0018">and now it's gone scripted reality which is even worse <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1571" who="S0093">what the hell is that about? It's just it's all appalling actors and everything as well <pause dur="short"/> the only way is Essex <pause dur="short"/> jesus</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1573" who="S0093">the only way is downhill</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1575" who="S0093">erm but yeah</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0018">so what was your company called?</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0093">er I've I've</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0018"><unclear/> educate</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0093">no</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0018">educator?</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0093">no it wasn't that anything so pompous</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1583" who="S0093">er presumptuous <pause dur="short"/> and erm ha erm Wholesome TV <pause dur="short"/> wholesome TV</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0093">I was trying to remember <pause dur="short"/> er and it was basically that <pause dur="short"/> we were trying to do we were trying to bring back sort of Sunday evenings</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0093">get the family sitting around the television with their tea <pause dur="short"/> after their tea or whatever erm and just sit down and watch some non-controversial</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0093">probably boring you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> But one of the first things we developed and the BBC was so keen and then they just went cold on it was er a silent comedy</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0093">A half hour</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0093">and then Lee Evans came up with something similar</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0093">and of course The Artist has has won everything now <pause dur="short"/> er fair enough <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought what a shame cos you know we had that idea</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0093">but it was just really <trunc>un</trunc> inoffensive</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0093">it was a comedy thing really</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0018">it wasn't the zeitgeist</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0093" trans="overlap">A bit like a Harry  Well not at the time</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0018">it wasn't right</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0093">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1604" who="S0018">before your time</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0093">did you see what I did there?</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0018" trans="overlap">you were ahead of the times <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1607" who="S0093">I'll tell you what I'm just gonna er I'll just send you this <pause dur="short"/> here's the</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0018"><unclear/> a bit uh</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0093">here's the er CV thing</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0018">all things about language are amazing <pause dur="short"/> like the relationship between language and thought <pause dur="short"/> and cross cultural studies <pause dur="short"/> the way people think because of the language that they've um learnt</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0093">yes</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0018">and yeah the the comparisons between languages like things that have <trunc>e</trunc> evolved that represent the way that humans think</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0018">because how could something</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0093">right yeah</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0018">er <trunc>t</trunc> evolve very similarly in two different languages that have had no contact and</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0093">and yet have got this connection yeah</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like erm <trunc>mo</trunc> I think the babies become aware <pause dur="short"/> the first part of the body they become aware of is their lips <pause dur="short"/> and so that's why most of the words for mother</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0093" trans="overlap">yes that was that was on QI or something <pause dur="short"/> that was mentioned on QI I think</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0093">well it's coincidental</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0018">so that's though the first</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0018">most of the words for mother begin with mm bilabial sounds</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0093"></u>
<u n="1628" who="S0018">Bilabial</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0093"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1630" who="S0018">get your lips together to make them</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0093">oh <pause dur="short"/> I've just worked out where another word comes from <pause dur="short"/> erm my apologies <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1632" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1633" who="S0093">I never realised that <pause dur="short"/> anyway erm yes it was erm <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a really good idea to bring back that idea of</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0093">you know it doesn't things don't have to be offensive <pause dur="short"/> and things don't have to be gladiatorial or</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0093">or erm or</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0018">and I think it's sad that if</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0093">offensive really</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0018">if dumb down TV you don't necessarily have to be dumb to become dumbed down by it <pause dur="short"/> I think there because there's a lack of an alternative <pause dur="short"/> a lot  a lot  of people</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0093">yeah</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0018">I know I you see I don't usually watch TV <pause dur="short"/> I didn't watch TV at all in Spain <pause dur="short"/> I just used to watch DVD box sets and stuff <pause dur="short"/> so when I came back to England I was quite surprised at what some of my very intelligent friends are watching</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0093">oh er yeah</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0018">come Dine With Me <pause dur="short"/> sex Sun And A and E <pause dur="short"/> um Supersize Versus Superskinny and just ooh</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0093">it's just so bland to me</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0018">it's <trunc>stu</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> exactly it's stuff that</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0093">I've got no interest</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0018">is just</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0093">but is it the lack of alternatives? Is that?</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0018">it's like fast food for the mind <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0093">just because it's the water cooler thing <pause dur="short"/> if you don't watch it you're not part of the <pause dur="short"/> no? Or is it just?</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no I think they're past that kind of mentality <pause dur="short"/> but I <trunc>ju</trunc> I think it is because there's a lack of alternatives</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0093">there is that <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> that's why I always fight for you know current affairs and all the stuff I try and do and</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0093">you know you I I I er cos Come Dine With Me again everything starts with a with fairly good intentions</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0093">you know The Apprentice has gone that way as well <pause dur="short"/> and say that I actually learnt things <pause dur="short"/> and I take the good with the bad on that one <pause dur="short"/> and I  and I  don't like Alan Sugar at all <pause dur="short"/> I met him a few times at the football</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0018">hmm mm</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0093">erm cos I'm connected with Birmingham City and all that</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0093">so I mean I'm in the board room and and I managed to meet a lot of these very selective people <pause dur="short"/> roy Hattersley I met not so long ago</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0093">he's very much a part of Sheffield Wednesday and</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0093">I had a long chat with him <pause dur="short"/> erm Alastair Campbell is er</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0093">part of er Burnley</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0093">erm and I get to meet with these people</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0018" trans="overlap">did you have to pay him for the questions?</u>
<u n="1671" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1672" who="S0093">no but he told me how to answer it which was good</u>
<u n="1673" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1674" who="S0093">he asked me a question and then said this is how you answer it</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1676" who="S0093">it was just yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> just write it out yeah <pause dur="short"/> thank you for asking Alastair <pause dur="short"/> I firmly believe that I'm guilty of er</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1678" who="S0093">I just said how are you <pause dur="short"/> and he said erm and it but oh er er er and I meet all these very interesting people <pause dur="short"/> and they all say the same <pause dur="short"/> all the people who are at the top of the game</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0093">they all say that television's rubbish you know <pause dur="short"/> now a lot of the er James Corden er I had a long chat with <pause dur="short"/> is it James Corden from Gavin And Stacey <pause dur="short"/> you know quite chunky guy</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0093">who is very much all the rage <pause dur="short"/> and he um and he's the same <pause dur="short"/> he said well I made Gavin And Stacey because I hated what was on television you know <pause dur="short"/> and I was like blimey you know <pause dur="short"/> and now he's part of the <trunc>zeit</trunc> you know part of the</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0093">the culture the the in crowd</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0093">and he erm and he hates being part of it <pause dur="short"/> it's a really interesting thing but <pause dur="short"/> the Apprentice started as a genuine you know he's looking for an apprentice</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0093">and he's still looking for to a as a  as a  he's looking for a business</u>
</body>
</text>
