<text id="SVCS">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:29:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Music, Twitter, taxation</topics>
		<activity>Talking while watching TV</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">do you remember this song?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">oh yeah I know this song <pause dur="short"/> but I don't really uh <pause dur="short"/> it's it's the eighties isn't it so um <pause dur="short"/> oh there's Paul McCartney in the audience</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is it? Oh he's so annoying</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">is that uh Top Of The Pops isn't it um?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is it Bananarama?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um so I <trunc>r</trunc> I didn't really know much about pop music back in the uh eighties and I mean I was pretty I was born in nineteen eighty so</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but not many people do when they're like five and stuff though</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean I was like uh <pause dur="short"/> so when this came out would've been what like eighty-seven or something?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I missed the bit  I missed the bit  where they said</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> so I <trunc>j</trunc> I just I didn't know them at the time but uh <pause dur="short"/> I know that song that's quite a well-known song</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115">um so uh is <trunc>T</trunc> Top Of The Pops Two isn't it but it's that thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's no it's about yeah this one's about girl groups <pause dur="short"/> I'll turn it over</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's it's yeah cos I think no no no this is alright</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah she looks so chavvy</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">no this is alright <pause dur="short"/> um that's uh Girls Aloud uh Cheryl Cole and uh</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037">shall I turn it over?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">no no no no this is fine <pause dur="short"/> let's follow this</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> no no no it's fine</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037">she's a proper chav though Cheryl Cole</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115" trans="overlap">unless unless there's something you wanted to watch was there something?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">um it is sorry is this something I wanted to watch or is there something?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">unless that you you said you did you want to turn it over to watch something else? Is that?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">oh no no I just um <pause dur="short"/> I could put the radio on something like if this is</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> no this is okay <pause dur="short"/> I dunno how long it would uh go on for I mean it's it's a fairly short uh</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037">yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">like a short one isn't it so there's uh <pause dur="short"/> dunno what happened to the other uh Girls Aloud cos obviously</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037">what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">Cheryl Cole's really famous I know but I dunno  I dunno  what what happened to the others</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037" trans="overlap">um well so Kimberley the one that's like the most normal out of all of them</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">is that the one with the ginger hair?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037" trans="overlap">was she from like Warrington? No so there's the gingery one <pause dur="short"/> there's the Irish one <pause dur="short"/> there's um Cheryl Cole</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">I can see there's a blonde one there</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037">and then there's the blonde one Sarah Harding and then there's the other one called Kimberley</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037">I sound like I'm a massive fan <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no no no you don't you just know like pop trivia</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and then <pause dur="short"/> and then um she's anyway now she's Princess Fiona in Shrek The Musical</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">kimberley?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">which one's that one?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037">that's the Irish one</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> so she's uh an actress then?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037" trans="overlap">this was like quite early on I think they all look quite young</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="47" who="S0115">all I remember is that Cheryl Cole was</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's the</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">she sort of stood out as being very defensive and like quite sort of boisterous but like defensive like if you  if you</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">in interviews you mean?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">if you tried to <pause dur="short"/> if you <trunc>sai</trunc> like she would just be very very like</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Don't mess with her? She's just well hard isn't she you know? <trunc>N</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> girl and</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">she is pretty from uh you know quite a rough background isn't she so?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037">yeah she is</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">I remember this song like</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so it's like</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037">look at them in their combats <vocal desc="laugh"/> You would never get them in that sort of thing now like</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's quite sort of  quite sort of  like The Gap that those outfits there</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">like</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">the old nineties The Gap and the the uh <trunc>j</trunc> what d'you call them? Khaki trousers and pastel pastel uh shades</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah it's like</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="63" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">it was really ninety like nineties styles like combats and stuff like the</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that is this is Goldie and the something Gingerbreads</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037">I don't know if I know this one <pause dur="short"/> slightly before my time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0115" trans="overlap">with a sixties look <pause dur="short"/> uh it's an old girls group <pause dur="short"/> never heard of them and um</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037">but she's playing the guitar that's quite unusual isn't it like it didn't really get like women musicians like on the telly</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's that's unusual for the sixties to have <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>th</trunc> you had Motown didn't you?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">yeah but that's singing mainly we didn't you didn't really get like women guitarists for a long time</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah no no no that was when there there are there haven't been that many sort of female like guitar rock stars with guitars have there?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">I mean <pause dur="short"/> big <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean you could say like Cheryl Crow or something</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037">yeah but I don't know if she's in the same sort of <pause dur="short"/> some Country ones yeah <pause dur="short"/> a lot of the</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I was <unclear/> In Alternative you have like uh uh <trunc>J</trunc> um P J Harvey and uh</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037" trans="overlap">everyone loves a bit of Dolly Parton <pause dur="short"/> p J Harvey yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">uh the majority of female singers seem to just be tend to not have guitars like that I mean</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">uh <unclear/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0037">got trousers on and everything <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">they have like proper sixties uh haircuts though</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">I like that <pause dur="short"/> I think I could uh <trunc>re</trunc> revive that one <pause dur="short"/> that nice sort of curly one</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">um is that like?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">actually the I like sort of  I like the sort of  shorter ones that are bigger</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what d'you call that? It's like a <pause dur="short"/> what d'you call that haircut there?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">um I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but I quite like it <pause dur="short"/> maybe I should get one <pause dur="short"/> I'm sick of my long hair anyway</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's kind of round and like big at the top so like a beehive like</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's a bit like a  a bit like a  beehive yeah but it's also like ur um like a Lego man's haircut a bit</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> these <pause dur="short"/> the Saturdays</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">kind of heard of them but</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">these were on uh ones that were on like a talent show one</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115">oh did they?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">I still don't understand what was happening on The Voice last night like what was that? I don't understand the <trunc>pre</trunc> like the premise <pause dur="short"/> did you <trunc>rea</trunc> did you hear anything about it in the <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">all all I know is that it's is like you choose based on the sound not the performer</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but how pardon me but how do they get on there anyway because none of them were like terrible so they must've been like</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">must presumably they just apply and then maybe they get filtered down but I don't know</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115">um I could have a little look on the</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">no it's alright</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">smartphone to to to uh <trunc>cla</trunc> clarify that but uh <pause dur="short"/> no I don't</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037" trans="overlap">are the is the window open?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean it's it's a good idea but also they started Britain's Got uh Talent as well but I don't really like that very much so I didn't watch it</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037">is it Simon Cowell that you don't like though?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115">partly</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">Cos David Walliams is on it now and he was like</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the Simon Cowell element <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think David Walliams is I find a lot funnier than Simon Cowell</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but he's a bit <pause dur="short"/> I just watched a bit of it before this morning when you were still in bed and um he was like David Walliams was saying things like that's the most exciting thing I've ever heard in my life and loads of <trunc>stup</trunc> and I'm like is he taking the mickey?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah but it's it's from the comedian's irony isn't it? Comedian comedians <trunc>i</trunc> you know if you're a popular comedian you can just talk as much crap as you want and people will just say oh he's being ironic or whatever</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> I suppose</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115">uh it's a bit like Ricky Gervais doing  Ricky Gervais doing  bad jokes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was a bit annoying <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's like <pause dur="short"/> this is a bad joke <pause dur="short"/> I'm Ricky Gervais and I can tell bad jokes</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">oh he's terrible Ricky Gervais I really don't like him</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">no I don't like him</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">oh I really don't like him</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">like um um</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">it's like he's made not funny like loads of money out of not being funny</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">there there is an element of like maybe overratedness maybe going on there but uh he's popular so</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">he's stupid</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">yeah you can  you can  make you know you you can achieve a lot by uh by kind of not being that talented I think or</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037" trans="overlap">nah <pause dur="short"/> I really don't think he is <pause dur="short"/> I mean I can see like why people like the um The Office and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I can understand why they like it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah but there's there's also Extras isn't there?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037">and Extras yeah that is quite funny <pause dur="short"/> but I think I saw that what's it called? What was that about? <trunc>Sci</trunc> was it about science? Like he did a stand-up thing</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">oh yeah he's terrible as a stand-up isn't he? That's his worst thing that's his worst skill</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was just like <pause dur="short"/> it was just so painful to watch</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115">he's very popular though but just can't stand</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh excuse me <pause dur="short"/> I didn't find anything funny about it at all like</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">yeah Science was pretty bad actually but his stand-up is really bad and</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">but why do people go and see it like?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> he's he's on Twitter isn't he uh?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">is he I haven't <pause dur="short"/> I dunno if I've got him</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but I don't think you'd find it very funny yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">well I don't</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">I think there's like loads of like random like world leaders and stuff like like Mahmood Ahmedinejad is on Twitter or something</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037">is he? Is it him though or is it a spoof one cos the spoof ones are my favourite</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">well I probably think he he has  he has  like a  like a  main official one maybe</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's like a <pause dur="short"/> well I know I've got like President Obama on Twitter but it's obviously not him it's like</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is there  is there  like Steven Hawking?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">uh I don't know</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">oh yeah like the official one <pause dur="short"/> I I imagine that he he has one you know run by  you know run by  his his government runs uh like an official government <unclear/> tweet</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've got like um Arnold Schwarzenegger just cos I thought it was funny</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like Kim Jong Kim Il  Kim Il  Sung</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but then <trunc>ma</trunc> <trunc>ma</trunc> my favourite thing is like the ones where you get like um a spoof one <pause dur="short"/> so like you know when Harry Redknapp was involved in all of that scandal and then there was all the like um what was I gonna say all of that uh or whether he's gonna get the England job and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and he obviously he speaks with a like a really strong sort of East End accent doesn't he?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">and like there was loads of like  loads of like  you having a laugh?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah it's good yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037">like loads of like really <vocal desc="cough"/> excuse me loads of really funny tweets like from someone who's pretending to be Harry Redknapp</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">yeah and there's a lot of like anything in football you're gonna get lots of spoofs</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">um so it might be <trunc>he</trunc> like um and on Facebook it might be actually hard to tell whether it's a real celebrity or if it's a spoof I mean</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">I think it would be fair that everybody should have the right to their own uh name you know to their own</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">well you can get it validated I think</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but of course some people have</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">on Twitter like you can get it like um you can write like accredited like Stephen Fry's one is like got like a little badge <pause dur="short"/> the ones that are like they've got like a little badge in the corner to show that it really is them</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">oh yeah I see</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">so you can get it like especially if you</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">the best thing I saw about Twitter is you um</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so there's the that's one I've got like from Cheryl Cole <pause dur="short"/> it's called Cheryl Kerl K E R L</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Chery Kerl <pause dur="short"/> so it's done by someone from the Northeast who knows like who knows the uh Newcastle accent</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there you can read it</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">uh April Fool's Day  <pause dur="short"/> oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> April Fool's Day but nobody got us uh cos I just sat inside the joke proof tent that Simon sent us till twelve o'clock <pause dur="short"/> simples pet <pause dur="short"/> okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> Uh</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">it's stupid</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">that's crazy I watched this last week</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what's this? What is it?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">um it's about Sandhurst so it's about like</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">oh oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll <trunc>j</trunc> probably put some uh put some music on</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I'll find something else but it was quite interesting but I don't understand why people would wanna go in the army and just be like shouted at in the face</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> hopefully kick it over</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">oh yeah there was a girl there wasn't there and?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">yeah and there she was like you're not up to standard <pause dur="short"/> and she was like ugh like trying not to cry <pause dur="short"/> pop power lists celebrity splurges</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">fair enough</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037"><unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">yeah what d'you think about celebrities? D'you think it's moral or like a bit dodgy to have like prying cameras in celebrities' lives and everybody getting <trunc>in</trunc> really interested about things that have gone wrong with celebrities you know or d'you think that's a bit like unethical maybe?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">I think like it <trunc>dep</trunc> I well I don't think anyone should be like spying on people</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">yeah obviously like within the law and uh</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't think like if you're inside your own house</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's a bit of a gray area for the law isn't it because um <pause dur="short"/> because like if if you uh you know if you're  if you're if you're  sitting outside someone's house every single day but I mean it is very gray with area with that sort of thing and also private detectives like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">how much monitoring are they allowed to legally do like can they stand opposite your house in on the road where it's a public road <pause dur="short"/> they could just stand there and basically just stand there and basically just spy on you in your windows and every time you ever come out in your gardens that they'll they'll be there to take a photo of you</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it must be horrible <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> or like you know when you go on holiday they just  they just  go on holiday with you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">personally I think like um they should ban uh <trunc>s</trunc> paparazzi from certain <trunc>ar</trunc> distance</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but but then also like people do things on purpose don't they? People encourage you know</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">yeah and that's bad as well like <pause dur="short"/> but if you wanna have an interview and a press conference in your <trunc>b</trunc> in your bedroom when you've got up in the morning then that's up to you but I mean</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">I mean if that's <pause dur="short"/> if they  if they  want to use it like</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is the problem not though people</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">I would ban I would definitely ban paparazzis from going within a certain distance of people's houses</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is the <trunc>prob</trunc> is the problem not though like well you can get long lenses though that doesn't matter does it?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115">well I'd ban any like any taking of photos of um</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is it not the people who buy the pictures and therefore the people who read the magazines and that? That's the problem really</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> You know you can ban I mean <trunc>s</trunc> I would basically ban any paparazzi photographs in the house that weren't authorised basically</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">I think I would probably do that if I ruled the world <pause dur="short"/> is that still going? Cos it would be rather <trunc>ir</trunc> a bit irritating if it uh</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no no it's fine</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">no cos usually it's like like me and I just press the wrong button</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">no no no no uh like it sometimes just it just dies doesn't it?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">well I just put new things in so</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">what it should do is it should make like a bleep like when it's died</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> like bee bee dee dee like if it was closing down</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">um a charge my alarm but uh <pause dur="short"/> it um doesn't does it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh there's I have got Ricky Gervais on Twitter look <pause dur="short"/> he's tweeted a picture of his cat</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">genius <pause dur="short"/> comedy genius <pause dur="short"/> he he does look a bit like your uh your friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't he actually particularly in that photo?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">oh I suppose he does a bit round the eyes</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">he was actually quite a good looking guy in his  in his  younger days though</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would be very flattered with that uh comparison so perhaps don't point that</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I dunno no Ricky Gervais had a was quite good looking in the old days wasn't he?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">when when he had that Bowie</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the David Bowie thing? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">he's always had a David Bowie obsession hasn't he? Uh I think he may be going a bit thin on top</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">think so?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> that's a <trunc>g</trunc> that's a nice looking cat <pause dur="short"/> looks a bit like a Persian one cos it's like white and black</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">I wonder what your <trunc>m</trunc> your mam's new dog's like <pause dur="short"/> is she gonna send you a picture?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">is that sort of Siamese is it what's the type of cat that's got like white with like a</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> a black face? I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I'm not very <pause dur="short"/> I don't really like cats so</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">so we're definitely not getting a cat then</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">well I'm allergic to cats</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115" trans="overlap">unless you stop being allergic <pause dur="short"/> we could get one at first and if you get allergic then we'll take it back</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">that's not very nice on the cat though <pause dur="short"/> it like gets rejected</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">no just we'll just um <pause dur="short"/> yeah but but there'd be  there'd be  lots of good owners wouldn't there?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">so but you don't wanna get a dog you wanna get a Jack Russell don't you?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> I haven't necessarily fully decided but I think dogs are better than cats because dogs do things like cats just like do</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>d</trunc> cats do stuff as well</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">cats just turn their nose up at you and just like scratch things and</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no no no they don't always turn their nose up at you they <trunc>sor</trunc> they can be friendly you know like they were talking on that programme yesterday or whatever it was uh</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">uh they come in you know they come on your bed and like they share like they <trunc>i</trunc> you can share stuff share food with them and they sleep on your bed and</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's not nice that's not a nice idea if I've made some food I wanna eat it</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">well it's like a fluffy like mobile cushion isn't it?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">well I like cushions</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">you don't have to really do much to take care of it apart from feed it</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">yeah but why have a pet if you don't have to do anything to it? Like you may as well just get <trunc>y</trunc> sort of like a plant</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's it's a mobile cushion</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">yeah but</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">that heats <trunc>its</trunc> self-heating cushion</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">if you could eat it at the end that might be better</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">if you could eat it? Well you can eat it but um</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">most people view it as a friend and like they wouldn't like eat a friend if a friend died</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> I wonder</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if I died would you eat me?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">well it depends how hungry I was</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">is that legal? I don't think it is</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">eating another person?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is that legal?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> I had a horrible dream</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">Cos um if I donate my organs to um <pause dur="short"/> so I could donate my  could donate my  muscles to uh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">to my dinner</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">to to your <trunc>di</trunc> to your dinner</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">I wouldn't eat you <pause dur="short"/> that's horrible</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">might be tasty</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">mind you I'd be a bit old <pause dur="short"/> bit old and uh</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037" trans="overlap">let's hope so</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">old and uh you know</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037">grizzly?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">nasty <pause dur="short"/> um no but perhaps uh it hopefully soon you know in terms of science they will actually  they will actually  invent um</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">yeah I'll just keep your head in a jar</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">like they will  they will  be able to grow um artificial they'll be able to grow uh meat <trunc>artifiti</trunc> you know the muscles by themselves uh so you don't have to kill uh like a whole animal you can simply grow these muscles so they don't have any</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037" trans="overlap">cows? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they've done it haven't they? They've done it with cows <pause dur="short"/> it was just really expensive</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they don't have any pain <pause dur="short"/> I I think  I think  they <pause dur="short"/> I think they have done certain things like I would expect there to be some progress hopefully within the next hundred years or so yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">well I think definitely by then</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">um in the direction of like perhaps of removing the need to um to to kill animals for uh for food like by growing the muscle tissue</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037" trans="overlap">stupid interview <pause dur="short"/> put it on uh</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What show was that one on Kerrang?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">ah Adele <pause dur="short"/> it's annoying</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">lot of Adele isn't there?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">is that some sort of jibe <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> oi no no I didn't mean like there there's a lot of Adele like in a certain in terms of mass and um spatial like volume as well</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's not very nice</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115">uh several metres squared of Adele</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037" trans="overlap">although I sort of don't really like her when she was going on about like whinging about having to pay tax it's like oh poor you <pause dur="short"/> you and your ten million pounds <pause dur="short"/> probably ten billion pounds</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115" trans="overlap">metres cubed <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what do they get like fifty or forty-five or forty percent tax or something um</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">well they've just changed it haven't they recently but yeah but it was fifty <trunc>perc</trunc></u>
<u n="281" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they've slightly <trunc>low</trunc> they've <trunc>s</trunc> they've done something to lower it slightly for wealthy people</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">but it was fifty percent tax</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">but if you're gonna make like ten million pounds then it's five million pounds is much the same ten million pounds I imagine</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">ah well I don't know I mean <pause dur="short"/> I think it it does go <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not  it's not  great to to have to take that much of someone's money but uh</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but I think  I think  it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you you probably would be benefitting from you know from the tax in certain ways but uh</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037">yeah but I mean</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean ideally the the there <trunc>sh</trunc> there should be more I think that the the government should make more of a profit by itself without having to tax people although that sounds nice on paper but I don't know the extent that uh we would be taking about state capitalism <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know what they it's like</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't have a problem with taxing people who've got millions of pounds half of it</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">uh well yeah it's it's controversial isn't it because obviously they're gonna  they're gonna  say well I uh I've got if I earn um a million pounds a year and you're taking half of that that then</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">yeah but that's more than enough to live on</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they would feel they're not  they're not  getting as much back as like as other people are I suppose <pause dur="short"/> I mean it is controversial but I guess they of course they're free to leave though they're free to leave the country and if they don't  if they don't  approve of it then they uh</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037" trans="overlap">does it not work <pause dur="short"/> does it not work that like you get taxed normally up to a certain rate and then whatever you earn over that you get half of?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">um I'm not I don't know much that much about it</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it is man <pause dur="short"/> like so I remember like if if you're earning under something you don't get taxed <pause dur="short"/> if you're earning like the majority of the population earning between I think</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well <trunc>the</trunc> they have different rates d'you mean different rates for different income?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the progressive taxation increases <pause dur="short"/> the percentage increases as you get more yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah so like <pause dur="short"/> most people are taxed whatever it is twenty-five percent or twenty percent or I can't even remember</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean the problem is it's like  it's like  a big system isn't it the the government and you know the people are sort of a bit confused sometimes as to where the money's going and how efficiently it's being used</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037" trans="overlap">thirty percent <pause dur="short"/> yeah but a <trunc>hun</trunc> but for most people like a hundred thousand pounds a year is more than enough to live on</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">I've heard comments coming from your direction that you you believe that you pay uh rather a large amount of tax</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">I do <pause dur="short"/> I hate it</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and you you only pay like uh you know the the sort of the more the lower rate isn't about twenty-five for you I guess</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know it's annoying <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is and I hate it I hate seeing like I've got like eight hundred pounds out of me</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> so if <trunc>s</trunc> if you can see their point of view you're like obviously you're only paying twenty-five but Adele you know poor old Sean Connery is is paying like you know fifty percent on his  on his  uh income and stuff but uh</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I can <pause dur="short"/> I can but <pause dur="short"/> yeah but that's probably <trunc>en</trunc> like but it's probably enough to live on isn't it?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115">I think some people just don't seem to mind and others really hate it they think tax is theft so</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">but</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">that's what you hear from the you know sort of you know sort of centre right or libertarian type of people</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you know I was a student for a long time and I've got grandparents who get pensions and stuff so I suppose we've just got to live with it everyone</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115" trans="overlap">all the the sort of the the main strategy of government is to sort of keep things more or less the same unless unless you have to change something um <pause dur="short"/> you generally keep don't mess with something you know if it ain't broke don't fix it sort of thing but</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">they wouldn't make too many changes but they do they have made some changes they have lowered slightly the like some they have lowered tax for wealthy people <pause dur="short"/> uh that's that's that's sort of the the the uh the the the doctrine that uh you know that um</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's just Tories isn't it? It's just their  it's just their  like</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">yeah the like the sort of uh of the  of the of the  economic liberal people who who would obviously they believe that if you lower tax then you encourage uh global business and that view is espoused by you know like the Economist magazine</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's unsurprising that they should do that</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">so the latest magazine uh the Economist's front cover that I saw was um</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">uh Cameron's budget for global uh for what was it? Cameron's budget for <trunc>bus</trunc> you know global business or something like that</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">and there was a picture of like basically complimenting and</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037" trans="overlap">his big yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">actually it was actually Osborne and you know <trunc>com</trunc> complimenting Osborne and Cameron and sort of <trunc>ma</trunc> mocking the Vince Cable um but uh they the the suggestion on the cover was that uh Osborne and Cameron were welcoming foreign investment basically into the country using the incentive of lower tax but <trunc>obv</trunc> but obviously it's not <trunc>a</trunc> it's not just about tax is it I mean that's <pause dur="short"/> it's it's in fact <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well of course I mean <pause dur="short"/> I I'm not <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> but I'm not suggesting that I've got a like a massive global standpoint on it all I'm saying is like in my opinion we should tax them because</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">the best thing  the best thing  with this is</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I was trying to say ten million pounds is as much as saying five million pounds like</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">well that's clearly not the same is it?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">no but if you're just a person like the salary that I get</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well that is a hundred million pounds the same as fifty million um well does it? Is it are you doing like a  like a  linear relationship?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well yes <pause dur="short"/> in terms of what you need <pause dur="short"/> no but like it's just extra stuff isn't it after that <trunc>l</trunc> really? You need a house to live in <pause dur="short"/> you need some food <pause dur="short"/> You know like it's just <trunc>ec</trunc> it does <trunc>all</trunc> they don't need ten million pounds for that you need like I dunno</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah no I mean I kind of see I kind of know what I kind of see that point of view uh but obviously if you're an investor that you know they these guys like <pause dur="short"/> the there's a lot of there are a lot of injustices in the world that's for sure but I mean <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's a lot of</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">the problem with <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot of problems with money I mean cos like if you you know you can get money from from not doing anything so I mean that was the whole like if you're talking like the sort of Marxist idea which was to sort of you you want to connect uh money with with labour</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">uh so therefore I suppose that uh that that that a Marxist view would criticise uh having you know the <trunc>a</trunc> the ability to sort of invest money and then to receive money back</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115">uh for an individual without actually doing any labour</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">um but the reality is that the individuals and investors do tend to <pause dur="short"/> they will choose lower tax over high tax a lot of them <pause dur="short"/> but it's more complicated though because</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I mean</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115">it's a bit like uh you know if you wanna <pause dur="short"/> britain and America that the so-called Anglo-Saxon system was to be more liberal and like lower the tax and like um allow the <trunc>f</trunc> the free business whereas European models who are like Germany and France would do uh more supposedly more like statey</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115">and more like regulatory <pause dur="short"/> and I think a another example is the banking um regulations cos there was a big fight over this there was a big bust-up within the EU in between you know it was when Cameron vetoed it and um</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115">and then for example you know Mr Wetherspoon put like pro-Cameron like in stuff in in Wetherspoon's <pause dur="short"/> so Mr Wetherspoon is an example of these types of people who want like <pause dur="short"/> he's not called Mr Wetherspoon he's called  he's called  Tim he's called Tim Martin and uh and he is an example of the sort of person who wants the Anglo-Saxon model and they want lower tax you know lower they want less red tape they want less state interference</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know he's not <pause dur="short"/> I like I liked his name</u>
<u n="349" who="S0115">I mean he's it's not a coincidence that he's that his pubs are based on George Orwell's idea of a good pub and you know he he will have read George Orwell presumably because he dislikes state interference</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but one of the best things <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> one of the best policies that I read though is about like in Norway I think it's Norway one of the Scandinavian countries where like it's they set it so that it's not possible for people at the top to earn</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115">yeah this is the redistributive redistributative <pause dur="short"/> um <vocal desc="laugh"/> redistributional uh model</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037">okay well it's not</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115" trans="overlap">in the  in the  Scandinavian countries yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037">yeah so it's like they set it so that wages at the top can't be I can't remember how many times like</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037">eight times or five times or something more than <trunc>wa</trunc> the minimum wage like</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean that's kind of <pause dur="short"/> yeah that that's sort of point that I was <trunc>tr</trunc> that I was gonna mention before</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that means every uh that drags everyone up like that seems like a better idea</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well yeah I mean like those kind of countries are what might be called socialist by American um like Americans</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that seems a bit more Marxist</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115">but yeah that was the point I was gonna make it's like I was talking about the European bust-up and like UK was like Germany was gonna was trying to force and like EU was trying to force England to to to <trunc>re</trunc> you know reel in ringing</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037">to what?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115">reel reel in its bankers a bit like to to restrict its its banking</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah reign in?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was trying to come out with some words there uh yeah the EU wanted to impose like certain restrictions on banking and you know on trading but Britain was getting all like classical liberal you know Adam Smith about it and saying you know you can't interfere with the banker cos you'll scare them off and they'll all go to America and you know London blah blah blah is the world's one of the three so-called financial hubs or whatever they're called financial centres of the world along with Tokyo and New York like if you  if you  start to you know putting red tape in now like you're gonna drive all them they're gonna go out of London and you know leave the Gherkin and leave the Canary Wharf</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> capital yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah empty Gherkin <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0115">you know that's what we but they're gonna leave the Gherkin leave the <trunc>n</trunc> leave the Canary Wharf leave the Citigroup</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115">whatever they're all gonna  they're all gonna  go uh to gonna go to America and Shanghai and they're gonna make us look like a right bunch of losers uh compared to Germany but the yeah the point I was gonna make is that <trunc>German</trunc> Germany has a quite a big banking and company and capitalism industries itself</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">even though it has more tight regulations so like it's not uh <trunc>re</trunc> always as simple as like just saying</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115">if like there has to be a kind of national pride amongst businesses within countries like in like if you want good investment a lot of it's gotta be <trunc>na</trunc> there's a <trunc>s</trunc> an element of nationalism about a lot you you've got uh like German bankers that are staying in Germany rather than going to London perhaps</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think that's more loose here like did you see that? Did you see that Mary Portas programme?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's it's companies cos they they're proud of their country you know what I mean? I don't know who that is</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you do man <pause dur="short"/> she's she's a lesbian <pause dur="short"/> she's got ginger hair</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115">ginger lesbian?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I know one ginger lesbian <pause dur="short"/> I know the <trunc>gir</trunc> the woman from uh Sex And The City</u>
<u n="379" who="S0037">no not her</u>
<u n="380" who="S0115">she's uh uh a ginger haired lesbian to to put it rather bluntly</u>
<u n="381" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no not her she's um she's got like a very distinctive haircut <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ve</trunc> very gingery <pause dur="short"/> she's quite tall sort of slim <pause dur="short"/> she goes round and like tells people who've got shops what they're doing wrong</u>
<u n="382" who="S0115">oh right is she um? I didn't realise?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0037">is she what?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0115">oh yeah I know her she has one of those those harsh uh</u>
<u n="385" who="S0037">oh my phone's ringing it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0115">okay um</u>
<u n="387" who="S0037">D'you wanna?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0115">I'll just pause this then</u>
<u n="389" who="S0037">hello? Hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how are you? Yeah fine thanks  fine thanks  nice to hear from you <pause dur="short"/> ah it's no problem <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="390" who="S0037">yeah yeah</u>
</body>
</text>
