<text id="SVDM">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:56:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0290 S0291</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At the Cox family house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Travel and recent holiday to Thailand, college in Germany</topics>
		<activity>Two siblings talk about their summer holidays</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring,  anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T13</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0290">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>19</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0291">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Surrey</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0290">so is this what am I allowed to talk about this recording whilst it's on?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0290">is it is it being analysed by a computer sort of or by a person going through it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0282">I don't know probably people</u>
<u n="5" who="S0290">oh</u>
<u n="6" who="S0282">might be people I don't know</u>
<u n="7" who="S0290">fair enough okay so I'll explain my trip</u>
<u n="8" who="S0282">to Thailand</u>
<u n="9" who="S0290">to Thailand I suppose <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0290">erm so erm took the bus to Gatwick I think the airport</u>
<u n="12" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0282">did your mum not drive you?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0290">no she doesn't drive</u>
<u n="15" who="S0282">why? <unclear/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0290">anyway erm it's just not the trains aren't working <unclear/> it's actually actually not <unclear/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0282">why don't you just get the train together?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0290">erm well I think it was Heathrow and you can't get a train to Heathrow</u>
<u n="19" who="S0282">oh Heathrow how long did it take you to get to Heathrow?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0290">erm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0282">by bus</u>
<u n="22" who="S0290">no it's like <unclear/> it's really slick well I thought it was a little bit more but I thought it was easier to get the train</u>
<u n="23" who="S0282">how much did the bus cost?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0290">it cost about the same and then we went up erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0290">and then I had a seven hour flight to <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0290">and that was that was really good because it was really I never went <unclear/> before and it's so like dry and deserty and desolate and looks very <unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0282">is that where you were staying?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0290">no no no we just stopped over there and it was like it was unimaginable it made Turkey look cool it was just it was like it was like a desert with houses in it and stuff</u>
<u n="31" who="S0282">erm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0290">I think in <unclear/> and countries like that <unclear/> it was so hot</u>
<u n="33" who="S0282">so how do you get around?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0290">well like stay inside in the hot hours of the day and if you need to get anywhere you have to get a taxi <unclear/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0282">fridge</u>
<u n="36" who="S0290">no yeah lack of air conditioning in these countries is not good</u>
<u n="37" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0290">erm anyways we stayed there for like an hour turnover and then got back on our eight hour flight to Thailand so by this point for the sake of <unclear/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0282">so what will you do at the airport?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0290">well it is just an hour change over</u>
<u n="41" who="S0282">so just eat</u>
<u n="42" who="S0290">so I just ate a burger and got back on the plane <unclear/> oh now we'd had the <unclear/> as you're changing time zones you need to try and sleep but I was wrong</u>
<u n="43" who="S0282">was it better than the flight to America?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0290">erm yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0282">was it a patch flight?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0290">it was it was an evening flight to America</u>
<u n="47" who="S0282">and it was only seven hours?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0290">it was kind of no I think it was fourteen hours</u>
<u n="49" who="S0282">oh I see but at least you had a stop over</u>
<u n="50" who="S0290">erm yeah but it's almost like it's almost nicer to get it all out of the way at once like when we flew to America I don't know it was a bit half and half but erm anyway so we arrived in Thailand in the evening time</u>
<u n="51" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0290">having left <unclear/> and like after a great deal of trauma</u>
<u n="53" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0290">like how on earth do we get from the airport to where we were meant to be staying</u>
<u n="55" who="S0291">well did you not work that out before?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0290">erm no obviously not</u>
<u n="57" who="S0291">how much of it had you planned?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0290">what?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0291">but you did book a hotel?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0290">we had a conversation about the <unclear/> but it's it's so cheap you don't need to book those you don't book stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0290">because obviously it's a bit more impoverished erm so we like spent about an hour at the airport to work out how exactly to get into where we were going <unclear/> so then we got the train and then had to get a taxi from the train station because it was too far to walk then it was really really coming into coming into the train station into just the hustle and bustle cos it's like so different to England's quite a erm erm what's the word I'm looking for? it's just so much more chaotic in Thailand it's it's so much more ordered and like purposeful whereas it's just</u>
<u n="63" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0290">with cars all over and <unclear/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0282">and people are there for a purpose</u>
<u n="66" who="S0290">there's tooting and there's it's very smelly <unclear/> it's a much more dangerous city</u>
<u n="67" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="68" who="S0290">um sort of really really it's just like so crazy and then we had to try and call a taxi and erm this is we realized we couldn't get a taxi because erm he was like yeah yeah man you want two two of these fingers and <unclear/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0290">and erm we're like oh <unclear/> cos you're meant to like make sure they use the meter</u>
<u n="71" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0290">because otherwise they wouldn't be <unclear/> and it ends up we get there and it's sort of like sixty something <unclear/> which is like one pound something <unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0290">and so we handed him over a thousand cos that's all you can get out of the ATMs</u>
<u n="75" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0290">and we only gave seven hundred on the way back <unclear/> try to like engage with him well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't getting out of the taxi and I was arguing with this guy he was like I said two hundred and it turned out being two hundred even though he's not gonna use the meter they do that it's like a thing but I was like man you said you would keep the meter running and as I was arguing with him the door was open and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had taken the stuff out and he started trying to drive off with me like half in the taxi which was a bit of a nightmare erm so eventually we jumped out it was only couple of quid but I was just a bit annoyed about it</u>
<u n="77" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0290">from then on you have to be quite careful it's weird though because of it's like the only place we've been where you know I think in England I think it's a law that they have to use the meter or something</u>
<u n="79" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0290">no but in erm in Thailand you get all the taxis that were going in certain touristy areas and they'll put a cloth over the meter they call it the <unclear/> top taxi meter so you think oh that's fine but they won't they refuse to use a meter and if you say to them <unclear/> can use the meter they'll just drive off</u>
<u n="81" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0290">they'll only do a pre-negotiated bumped up fare so <unclear/> but then <unclear/> are a lot cheaper but you risk death in them</u>
<u n="83" who="S0282">oh it's like in <unclear/> like taxis you have to ask how much it would be to go somewhere <unclear/> ridiculous</u>
<u n="84" who="S0290">yeah no you have to like pre-negotiate a fee and yeah what we found is a couple of times we have to be like how much <unclear/> cos they'll be like eight times the price</u>
<u n="85" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0290">and then eventually with a bit of haggling it will be just like <unclear/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0290"><unclear/> erm yes so anyway we stayed in <unclear/> for like a couple of days which isn't like a really touristy district and</u>
<u n="89" who="S0282">what did you do when you got to the hotel?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0290">we just <unclear/> for a few days but that's like that's like erm western night life sort of district it's basically</u>
<u n="91" who="S0282">did you go out?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0290">it's like an epicentre for yeah it's like an epicentre for groups of like various Westerners crossing paths erm all coming into like very erm western culture to</u>
<u n="93" who="S0282">really</u>
<u n="94" who="S0290">so that like <unclear/> for a couple of days <unclear/> which is up in the north which is <unclear/> rural area of Thailand but <unclear/> was the biggest city up there</u>
<u n="95" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0290">erm so we went <unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0290">because you know in <unclear/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0290">and we just didn't want to <unclear/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0282">I'm <unclear/> didn't get much sleep</u>
<u n="102" who="S0290">no cos they're so like stuffed for space on a plane but whereas on a train there's plenty of room</u>
<u n="103" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0290">but erm <unclear/> you get like a proper bed and <unclear/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0290">erm and then we arrived in Shanghai in about seven hours and when we off the train and there was a tourist information centre and so we go up there to ask where to stay and this man was really nice <unclear/> erm <unclear/> explaining you know <unclear/> and he kind of whisked us off around the back and put us in a back of a pickup truck that <unclear/> seats in the back of a pickup truck</u>
<u n="107" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0290">and erm erm he said we'll just grab some more people and then we'll take you for free to your hotel</u>
<u n="109" who="S0282">oh dodge</u>
<u n="110" who="S0290">and then basically it all unfolded and we got there and we weren't like forced into staying there but it turns out all the people at the tourist information booths were various different owners of the different hotels so where you stayed depended on who you spoke to at the tourist information booth and which hotel they owned so he just whisked us off to his hotel it was really nice though and that was actually probably the nicest place we stayed by far <unclear/> but he actually provided good customer service whereas a lot of those places were rude</u>
<u n="111" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0290">but erm it was just really weird cos I the tourism is so corrupt in these small areas that there's no like official</u>
<u n="113" who="S0282">yeah but it's like <unclear/> it's like in <unclear/> if you ask for directions they expect you to pay them</u>
<u n="114" who="S0290">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0282"><unclear/> together</u>
<u n="116" who="S0290">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I know that is very weird erm but you know he was but he was really quite nice cos whereas he was like friends spoke very good English made sure people were looked after although it wasn't the nicest hotel he was a good sort of man and we went to like other places like when we were trying to book some snorkel and we walked in and erm we were looking and we were like what snorkelling trip have you got available to the <unclear/> and he points at the thing like at a poster thing and goes back to playing his computer game and we're trying to talk to him and he didn't really want to talk to us because he was trying to do his computer game or something so it was</u>
<u n="117" who="S0282">why didn't you just go to the maps?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0290">yeah we did but erm the point is we got a lot of that in some places</u>
<u n="119" who="S0282">but yeah why are people like that?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0290">I don't know but you got that in places like that and then you've got <unclear/> but erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0290">but erm <unclear/> I always thought when you always see the TV programs and people <unclear/> looks awesome so humid and sweaty hot very hot <unclear/> not at all like cos it's like</u>
<u n="123" who="S0282">why</u>
<u n="124" who="S0290">because like it's very beautiful but like you see it on TV and it looks amazing but it's very sticky and insects attacking you but you can put on whatever Deet you want but you get attacked by mosquitoes so you have to wear as much clothes as you can to try and put off the mosquitoes</u>
<u n="125" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0290">at the same time as trying to take off as many clothes as possible because it's so hot</u>
<u n="127" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0290">and erm yeah that was a bit so you end up covering like over a period of a day you would like <unclear/> like really <unclear/> but erm very <unclear/> and erm we stayed</u>
<u n="129" who="S0282">how many days <unclear/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0290">two days so we tracked it up to some small village stayed in like a bamboo hut and then erm we tracked <unclear/> back over the next day but we went to a waterfall which was pretty awesome</u>
<u n="131" who="S0282">it was</u>
<u n="132" who="S0290"><unclear/> but erm like we stayed in the village and we were <unclear/> cos it was like no electricity maybe running water no no no they had like very limited like running water supplies in certain places and like literally bamboo huts and they just go on to the rice fields and work so that was <unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0290">well it was me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0282">were they nice?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0290">yeah they were all quite like erm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0290">it was like Jordy <unclear/> but they were quite like erm <unclear/> no they were they were nice but</u>
<u n="141" who="S0282">a bit</u>
<u n="142" who="S0290">a bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0291">it's like when we went onto erm Safari into the desert in <unclear/> two American people and we were just amazed <unclear/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0291">they'd obviously been on like desert wear dot com</u>
<u n="148" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> and we got into like the desert site thing and um they were just like well we're going to go to bed now oh look which bedroom do we get because like me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were like gonna be in one little hut and they were gonna be in another and we're like are we gonna fight this out except for me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are obviously gonna sleep out in the stars like we weren't gonna watch like we weren't just gonna go to bed and sleep and they're like making sure <unclear/> okay we're <unclear/> we don't really care we're we're not really sleeping and they were like oh okay well can we just take one of your beds then for the other thing that we <unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0290">how old were they?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0291">they were bit older like thirty or forty</u>
<u n="154" who="S0290">so did you sleep out in the</u>
<u n="155" who="S0291">we didn't we were we were just like there was like a fire which went down and we just sat along and looked at the stars all night but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was explaining all the different stars and then they were all like yeah it's so much <unclear/> they didn't want to know any of the stuff that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying</u>
<u n="156" who="S0290">oh right cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0291"><unclear/> to get really pissed off <unclear/> but he was saying that what they were made of and stuff they were like gosh he's really like destroying the atmosphere</u>
<u n="158" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0291">yeah so we just <unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0290">how long was that visit <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0291">well I was terrified I was gonna get bitten by a snake or scorpion</u>
<u n="164" who="S0290">were you right out in the barren desert?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0291">one of them run over me like just as I went to sleep</u>
<u n="166" who="S0290">a snake?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0291">no like erm some kind of scorpion</u>
<u n="168" who="S0290">well that's a pretty scary wait how long were you out there for?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0291">we were there for like two days</u>
<u n="170" who="S0290">and was it like you were sleeping in the open desert or was it <unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0291">no it was just an open desert</u>
<u n="172" who="S0290">well that's pretty crazy the stars must have been amazing</u>
<u n="173" who="S0291">they were <unclear/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0290">okay</u>
<u n="175" who="S0291">it was actually really fun</u>
<u n="176" who="S0290">how are camels compare to horses?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0291">well <unclear/> bigged it up so much I thought I was literally gonna be killed by one of the animals they said yeah it's gonna kick you off they're really grumpy</u>
<u n="178" who="S0290">they're quite horrible</u>
<u n="179" who="S0291">no they're not they were <trunc>complete</trunc> they they're like they're not really like affectionate I would say but but they they've got a job to do and they do it and they don't like get randy about it so we all kind of like just sat and pooted along</u>
<u n="180" who="S0290">how many hours?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0291">erm two</u>
<u n="182" who="S0290">so you sat between the humps?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0290">that's cool</u>
<u n="185" who="S0291">the one in front was like really greedy and would keep stopping to eat and obviously all the others were like attached to the guy in front so whatever that one stopped everyone else would have to stop</u>
<u n="186" who="S0290">what would it stop to eat then?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0291">like erm well it looked like twigs but it's like a twiggy <unclear/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0290">oh</u>
<u n="189" who="S0291"><unclear/> but yeah it was quite fun</u>
<u n="190" who="S0290">what else did you do there?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0291">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0291">uh yeah we went for about ten days</u>
<u n="194" who="S0290">stay in a five star hotel the whole time?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0291">no no no it was like <unclear/> we went in the first we stayed <unclear/> which was like I think we were there for erm and it took us like an hour and a half to walk to the hotel suitcase and it's like dead of night in Morocco and it's so dodge and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was convinced she'd got the right way and she often <unclear/> hotel</u>
<u n="196" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0291"><unclear/> hotel <unclear/> it was so <unclear/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0290">do you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0291">it was such a nightmare</u>
<u n="200" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0291">and especially since you don't have like Google map or that we didn't even have a map</u>
<u n="202" who="S0290">oh yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0291">well we had a we had a map <unclear/> but all the roads were wrong like all the road names were like swapped around oh it was such a nightmare</u>
<u n="204" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0291">that was not the biggest problem it was finding hotels I think</u>
<u n="206" who="S0290"><unclear/> and they had this massive <unclear/> so <unclear/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0290">you could try and find a nice one and then you have to <unclear/> it's just getting somewhere with a bed and so we looked and had some pretty dodgy accommodations</u>
<u n="211" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0290">cos like all these places are <unclear/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0290">and when we actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0290">and like <unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0291">oh my god see we got lucky but <unclear/> well when I say we <unclear/> but um</u>
<u n="220" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0291">yeah <unclear/> like the last day because trains were like seven pounds <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0291">so <unclear/> reservations</u>
<u n="224" who="S0290">yeah so that I think if you don't know the place <unclear/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0291">yeah but it's a lot less hassle knowing that you're going to stay with them</u>
<u n="226" who="S0290">yeah well me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were only planning on staying a week <unclear/> and then we ended up staying two weeks</u>
<u n="227" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0291">I think it depends where you're going because <unclear/> like people's absolute <unclear/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0290">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0291">you know I would not have wanted to like <unclear/> from the hotel because it was <unclear/> got all the printouts so everything was completely settled so they couldn't like add any extra prices to it and <unclear/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0290">how much <unclear/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0291">about ten pounds four pence</u>
<u n="234" who="S0290">that's not too bad</u>
<u n="235" who="S0291">no</u>
<u n="236" who="S0290">it's weird <unclear/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0291">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0290">so what else did you do for ten days? just shopping?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0282">we went <unclear/> for one day we went down to the beach and went swimming which was like <unclear/> because none of the girls would go swimming or to the beach <unclear/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0290">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0291">so we so we kind of went down there</u>
<u n="242" who="S0290">so they would like follow</u>
<u n="243" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0291">so <unclear/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0291">only went to the beach once</u>
<u n="248" who="S0290">so the Moroccan sea</u>
<u n="249" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0290">was it warm?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0291">yeah it was warm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0290">I'm sure it's got quite a lot of exotic creatures in</u>
<u n="253" who="S0291">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0290"><unclear/> even know what was in it</u>
<u n="255" who="S0291"><unclear/> so it was a nice long <unclear/> and there were little carriages for people <unclear/> speak French and</u>
<u n="256" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0290">now wait you were with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0291">oh yeah she was there for the first couple of days</u>
<u n="260" who="S0290">oh okay</u>
<u n="261" who="S0291">but um because that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like fiftieth birthday to her</u>
<u n="262" who="S0290">oh well what did she go off on her own and then?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0291">erm no and then she went home cos she was teaching next weekend she just came out for that weekend but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> managed to get some unbelievable deals like <unclear/> pounds</u>
<u n="264" who="S0290">blimey</u>
<u n="265" who="S0291">for hotel</u>
<u n="266" who="S0290">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0291">erm but yeah and then we got the train to <unclear/> and we had an absolutely <unclear/> hotel <unclear/> like really poor area <unclear/> suitcases like all like English clothes <unclear/> which is like so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I feel like a tourist</u>
<u n="268" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0291">so then the next day it was like you know trousers and a full long sleeve shirt and head scarves and we were still getting <unclear/> even after like even though we were completely covered up <unclear/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0290">some of my friends were there for <unclear/> erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0291">if you're with a girl I think maybe it's easier</u>
<u n="274" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0291">but actually cos it was me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos they could tell that she was like <unclear/> whatever they're not <unclear/> say but like someone knew and then just completely <unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0290">wow</u>
<u n="277" who="S0291"><unclear/> the same</u>
<u n="278" who="S0290">yeah we have manners in the same way</u>
<u n="279" who="S0291">nobody they they just get all their English off like English like off American movies stars and the stuff they come out with is like so inappropriate and doesn't make any sense</u>
<u n="280" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0291">but they think oh see we understand and it was just like oh after like I just got so bored after a while but you just couldn't go you just had to continue <unclear/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0290">oh me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just stopped like I think at first you try and communicate</u>
<u n="283" who="S0291">and then you just stop acknowledging people but it's not even really <unclear/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0290">well we just got to the point when you walk down the street and <unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0291">but it it just turned into where you just don't trust anyone and we had such an awkward situation did I tell you about this café we went to? we were outside a library there and we were looking to go into the library and we were oh god someone is going to try and sell us stuff and we were like no like go away <unclear/> café here if you want to and then we saw oh there's a café here if you want to come have some tea <unclear/> and we were no we're not going to a bugger old café just leave us alone cos we were getting really pissed off because they were getting pushy and then finally we were we're just like oh fine we'll just go into this café so we went into the café and got a coffee but we waited for ten minutes we pretended we didn't speak English <vocal desc="laugh"/> because like that's the only way to leave anyone alone so she was pretending she was Greek and I was pretending I was German and so like we to this point we were just talking about jibbery gook to him but just using <unclear/> so he thought well everyone spoke English but then he was like oh so you're from Greek oh okay what about you and I was like and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes oh yeah she's from Greece as well and I was like oh my god no but he turns around and said he can speak Greek erm and I was like oh no but I study in Germany and then he was like oh perfect I speak German and I was like oh bullocks I've really put my foot in it now</u>
<u n="286" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0291">so then he started to like say say stuff to me in German and then he was like translate it to her in Greek <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh so what he spoke Greek and German</u>
<u n="289" who="S0291">no no no he didn't speak Greek he spoke German but he spoke to me in German and obviously I and he was like no can you translate now Greek to her so that she's a part of the conversation? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0291">and then I was just like oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/> like so he'd say something to me and I kind of turned to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and would be like blah blah blah blah <vocal desc="laugh"/> just so bad and then it lasted a bit and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just like started talking like a bit of broken English and you know when you speak broken English it's really difficult to speak like bad English so we were both trying to be like <unclear/> oh it was so bad and then after a while we just left we were just like screw off this guy but</u>
<u n="292" who="S0290">erm we got a guy we were trying to get into the palace and it was huge</u>
<u n="293" who="S0282">which palace?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0290">one of the big palaces <unclear/> of the king's palace erm and it is really huge there's no indication of where the entrance is</u>
<u n="295" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0290">and it's probably like a couple of miles long and obviously <unclear/> so we were walking around it for ages and then erm some guy came up to us and was like where are you trying to <unclear/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0291">oh no that's always the way when <unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0290">yeah I mean and then he was like erm it's erm it's closed for lunch but erm and then he was like but we can show you some other stuff to do and yeah he was like I'll show you some other stuff to do but it reopens in a couple of hours and he was like no no I'll tell you what <unclear/> and then you can erm you can go off and tell him to take you back here <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0290">that means it's a scam because any arrangement between <unclear/> drivers and like <unclear/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0290">erm so we walked away and then we <unclear/> palace and they have tons erm <unclear/> don't talk to anyone in the palace we don't close for lunch and <unclear/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0291">oh good</u>
<u n="304" who="S0290">so it was a big disheartening <unclear/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0291">but you got in?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0290">yeah then it was like thirty quid <unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0291">that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="308" who="S0290">mm so we didn't bother with that</u>
<u n="309" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0290">er</u>
<u n="311" who="S0291">it is funny how different countries work</u>
<u n="312" who="S0290">yeah but they do all speak quite good English considering the state of their education in Thailand though but I suppose it's cos it's like their whole industry</u>
<u n="313" who="S0291">tourist</u>
<u n="314" who="S0290">it's it's <trunc>tw</trunc> it's like something like ten ten percent or twenty percent of their national income is tourism which is huge</u>
<u n="315" who="S0291">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0290">compared to other countries</u>
<u n="317" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0290">but I'd quite like to be in Vietnam or somewhere I think that's like I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0291">really?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0290">like what was it? <anon type="place"/> or something? somewhere like less tourist-based</u>
<u n="321" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0290">cos like it's become more of a like holiday like lots of big holiday resorts and stuff</u>
<u n="323" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0290">like very like you know like the Greek islands and stuff? it's become a bit like that so I don't know it's not really my thing</u>
<u n="325" who="S0291">I hate touristy areas</u>
<u n="326" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0291">like I'd much rather go somewhere where like when I went to Spain it was so good cos all of my friends were like Spanish and knew exactly where to take me and exactly <trunc>w</trunc>what to do and like</u>
<u n="328" who="S0290">yeah like when we were in Turkey <unclear/> took us everywhere <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0291"><unclear/> oh god yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0290">I think that was the other end of the stick where it's the opposite</u>
<u n="331" who="S0291">well they didn't take us anywhere</u>
<u n="332" who="S0290">oh yeah they took us to that to a river</u>
<u n="333" who="S0291">what river?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0290">I swear we went on a river <unclear/> we went on a river thing</u>
<u n="335" who="S0291">no that was at a lake wasn't it?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0290">that was quite <unclear/> er yeah we went down a river at the end of the lake to the sea</u>
<u n="337" who="S0291">oh yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0290">that was quite good</u>
<u n="339" who="S0291">that was nice</u>
<u n="340" who="S0290">and that was like</u>
<u n="341" who="S0291">until we got back</u>
<u n="342" who="S0290">oh</u>
<u n="343" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0290">there's that day and the day when mum had a migraine and we all went away</u>
<u n="345" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0290">the two best days weren't they?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0291">yeah those were the two best days that <unclear>dodgy old burger off?</unclear> the beach and the rabies dog</u>
<u n="348" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0290">that was the day when mum like passed out wasn't it?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0291">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0290">oh <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0291">mm but erm yeah Spain was good er you you've never been have you?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0290">no</u>
<u n="355" who="S0291">we went to like the mountains</u>
<u n="356" who="S0290">how hot are they?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0291">oh my god you would love it you would love it</u>
<u n="358" who="S0290">why?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0291">it's like the mountains above Madrid and it was like not that hot but like er nice hot so it wasn't humid or dry it was just like perfect temperature and you could climb up into the mountains and like there'd just be these waterfalls all the way through and you could like the plunge pools were huge so you could jump in and swim in them like go under waterfalls</u>
<u n="360" who="S0290">in countries like this water is so like</u>
<u n="361" who="S0291">and then climb up into the mountains like the views were like incredible like <trunc>s</trunc> oh it was so nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0290">like the views in America?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0290">but but without the rocks it's all all like trees it's like a big valley <unclear/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0290">and is it more densely?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0291">mm more like yeah unbelievably dense like just densely treed bits of the</u>
<u n="366" who="S0290">treed <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0291">technical term but we'd like I I this was on like the second day obviously I hadn't driven in about a year and they're so chilled about driving lets like like here's there's so much like safety caution and everything and apparently I was insured to drive the car like <unclear/> insurance <unclear/> but whatever and we were like yeah like we should drive up to the forest and just go there and I was like well I haven't driven in a long time and they're like oh you'll be fine you'll be fine so I like got into the car and started driving obviously it's on</u>
<u n="368" who="S0290">what car?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0291">it's on like the other side of the road it was er it was <unclear/> it was like er I dunno Golf or something but obviously I was driving on the other side of the road then we got up to the forest and it's just all of these trials trying to get into a car park on like a vertical hill and their their like gear stick didn't really work you had to like push it in to like get into another gear and into reverse and I didn't realize this like that you had to push to get into reverse and so we're on this hill and then we'd stopped and then I was trying to get like back into a car park like this and then I was like trying to go up and I well I was like reversing into this car behind and I was like oh my god I like can't get up this hill I'm so bad at hill starts and then finally we got into this car park and then on the way back from like the walk I fell over and like massively cut my knee and then had to drive back with like just blood everywhere</u>
<u n="370" who="S0290"><unclear/> so none of your friends drive?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0291">er no well they're like learning to drive they haven't passed the test no</u>
<u n="372" who="S0290">how old are your friends then?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0291">mm oh same age as me</u>
<u n="374" who="S0290">bit late to start driving isn't it? <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0291">well they're probably not home very much to learn or they're just too chilled</u>
<u n="376" who="S0290">so wait how many people from Germany were there? was it just one friend?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0291">no no no no</u>
<u n="378" who="S0290"><unclear/> other people <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0291">it was like loads it was about this was so weird like from <anon type="place"/> there was about <trunc>tw</trunc> mm twenty maybe like fifteen people who live in in <trunc>s</trunc> these mountains and they all went to the same school and they've all ended up in <anon type="place"/> just completely coincidentally</u>
<u n="380" who="S0290">oh right okay</u>
<u n="381" who="S0291">like it's so weird so like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's the friend's house I went to and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's he was at <anon type="place"/> and he's gone to <anon type="place"/> and I knew him at <anon type="place"/> when I was there and then when I went to <anon type="place"/> for Erasmus he was like oh my best friend's in <anon type="place"/> and that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0290">oh okay</u>
<u n="383" who="S0291">so like it's so it's like such a small world so when I went to Spain he was there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there and then like loads of other friends and loads of friends had gone out to Spain for summer because like their parents live really far away like one of my friends is from Serbia and his parents have just moved to South Africa so he went to Spain for the whole of the summer</u>
<u n="384" who="S0290">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0291">so like a lot of people if they live outside Europe they'll just go to Spain for summer and then go back home for Christmas or something maybe but I dunno it's all very different</u>
<u n="386" who="S0290">where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> live then?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0291">he currently lives in</u>
<u n="388" who="S0290">I thought <unclear/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0291">but he has a flat in <unclear/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0290">I thought <unclear/> America</u>
<u n="391" who="S0291">yeah but he couldn't travel because of his heart</u>
<u n="392" who="S0290">yeah but <unclear/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0291">his family he's he's half American</u>
<u n="394" who="S0290">oh</u>
<u n="395" who="S0291">his his aunt lives in in fact where <unclear/> lives</u>
<u n="396" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0290">that's good yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0291">erm well it's in <unclear/> but you know</u>
<u n="400" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0291">well his he left home at like sixteen so his grandparents bought him and his sister a flat <unclear/> anyway so he's like basically lived there since he was sixteen but now his sister is living there so like it's half his I guess and half hers</u>
<u n="402" who="S0290">how is his heart?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0291">erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0290">so is he waiting for a transplant?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0291">he's on the list yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0290">but far from</u>
<u n="407" who="S0291">well he isn't like I don't know he keeps going on emergency going further up the list and then obviously going back down so and like it doesn't really work in that it's like someone it's like who whoever needs a heart most urgently will get it so he's on the list but it doesn't mean that he'll necessarily get one within the next couple of years</u>
<u n="408" who="S0290">about how well is <unclear/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0291">erm I don't know</u>
<u n="410" who="S0290">so he couldn't go to <unclear/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0291">erm I think well the thing is he was meant to go in erm when was it last February or no no like May June but he keeps on having panic attacks so <unclear/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0290">what cos he's scared of flying?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0291">oh no no no it's like his family is like a complete mess <unclear/> have to have like a <unclear/> or something it can be triggered by anything so it just <unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0290">oh gosh</u>
<u n="415" who="S0291">it like just triggers itself</u>
<u n="416" who="S0290"><unclear/> is it?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0291">no it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0290">how horrible</u>
<u n="419" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0290">what's his <unclear/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0291">his wife is from <unclear/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0290">that's awful</u>
<u n="423" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0290">do they really trust him up there?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0290">there's always <unclear/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0290">yes but do you see him <unclear/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0291">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0290">but do you see him?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0291">well he's coming out for <unclear/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0290">so is he studying at home?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0291">well he's doing like a post grad so that's not really like if you imagine <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s heart that's what <unclear/> it's like you get one hour or something and then everything else is up to you <unclear/> close to his heart</u>
<u n="434" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0290">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0291">no he's in <unclear/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0291">he missed the audition to <unclear/> because he had a had a panic attack on the flight so they <unclear/> place</u>
<u n="440" who="S0290">okay</u>
<u n="441" who="S0291">yeah but anyway it's not so bad because they didn't have a VHS <unclear/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0290">yeah he wouldn't be able to get drunk <unclear/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0291">well no and like he he'd be leaving <unclear/> would be a bit difficult and it would be in Germany of course <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0291">but his teacher is like the <unclear/> English person you ever met it just makes me laugh every time he's taking such a liking to <unclear/> and like every time we get in a lift together he sort of wants <unclear/> basically got kicked out of just because of <unclear/> because he will just outright say he's the best <unclear/> or he's the best <unclear/> and best at this in the world but he erm always seems and he will just tell tell people how it is like he'll say just you <unclear/> kind of thing but not in like a mean way but just in like I'm not gonna lie to your face <unclear/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0290">so what does he teach you?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0291">he doesn't teach me but he</u>
<u n="450" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0291">yeah <unclear/> he's done <unclear/> at <unclear/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0290">how is <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0290">how how <unclear/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0290">how far <unclear/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0291">like I can hold a conversation understand lessons get by but it's definite <unclear/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0290">do you just speak English or German</u>
<u n="459" who="S0291">well most of my friends prefer to speak English but in the general class we all speak German to each other and if I want to speak German I can just speak German because it's just like <unclear/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0290">so do you think that you do you not think that it might be easier to learn if your friends speak German to you? you're forced into learning?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0291">yeah but everybody speaks English at school</u>
<u n="462" who="S0290">isn't but it's Germany surely I mean I know they choose to but surely generally speaking they have to speak German</u>
<u n="463" who="S0291">yeah they do but they also want to speak English like people who want to speak English <unclear/> so like if there's an option to speaking English to an English speaker or speaking German to an English speaker it's going to be English isn't it?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0290">are they always really good at it?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0291">yeah but it's so funny because this this guy who moved there this year he learnt English from watching <unclear/> accent and he'd come up with all these cockney phrases <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0291">and I would just be like sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0291">it was so funny he would say you little plonker and I was like okay this is so funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0290"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0290">does he wait does he have like the accent?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0291">yeah yeah he does well he's a bit of a bad boy anyway but he just like bigs it up a little more but he <unclear/> and then the other guy is Dutch and his accent he comes up with the most ridiculous things but it's interesting <unclear/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0291">the worse are the French though for sure</u>
<u n="476" who="S0290">they're bad?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0291">oh my god their accent but they don't even they don't even pretend</u>
<u n="478" who="S0290">oh they have very heavy French accents as well</u>
<u n="479" who="S0291">yeah it's really funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0290">but their French accent's quite nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0291">oh it's <unclear/> but I think they're quite <unclear/> like one of my friends <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> speaks like fluent German and I think her German accent is really good well all Germans <unclear/> she's definitely doing better than me</u>
<u n="482" who="S0290">oh</u>
<u n="483" who="S0282">so when are you going back?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0291">Tuesday</u>
<u n="485" who="S0282">for Christmas</u>
<u n="486" who="S0291">yeah I might come back some time later but we'll have to see <unclear/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0282">so how does that work? would you come back that far?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0282">well no but for practices and for concerts and how do you how do you be in concerts if you can't</u>
<u n="492" who="S0291">oh it's not for a concert it's like an interview for orchestra so you just come back</u>
<u n="493" who="S0282">oh for when you're finished</u>
<u n="494" who="S0291">not even well for when I finish this experience like apart from <unclear/> doing audition and maybe do but you have to start early and just keep doing hundreds and hundreds of <unclear/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0282">well that's exciting</u>
<u n="496" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0282">so if you succeed would they would they wait for you or would they want you to</u>
<u n="498" who="S0291">well if I got through they would want me to do a trial and a trial period so like they'd ask you to do like certain concerts during the year and the concerts will have probably have a week of rehearsals so maybe they're doing a concert in Birmingham and concert in Cornwall and somewhere else in London and they like give the dates and you know you can say oh yeah I can do this one and this one and this one and go and do those and then gradually they'll stop asking you about four concerts like if you do one concert and completely fuck it up they'll be like okay and just won't ask you for another concert and if you do well they'll ask you for another one and then after a year or something they would say <unclear/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0282">oh I see</u>
<u n="500" who="S0291">so it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0282">so it's kind of an extended interview?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0291">yeah <unclear/> but I mean I've got a friend who's she left she finished her degree like two years ago maybe and she's now on trials for about six orchestras so <unclear/> Philharmonic and stuff and she does concerts here and there but like it could be a year before she years like it could be four years before one of them will offer her an official <unclear/> you know and there are a lot of auditions at the moment anyway because of the Scottish thing</u>
<u n="503" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="504" who="S0291">so</u>
<u n="505" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0291">I don't know but like they they won't offer a post until they know because a lot of them have connections so they won't offer any place <unclear/> Scottish <unclear/> so it's a little bit hard</u>
<u n="507" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0290"><unclear/> audition the other day then?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0290">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0291">because they said it's erm the next one is in early October and I <unclear/> the week before October so it was <unclear/> and <unclear/> and anyway the person on the interviews is a guy from Wales so</u>
<u n="513" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0290">erm October the third or fourth I think so all my mates are leaving at the moment they started going off they started very late compared to everybody else</u>
<u n="519" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="520" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0282">are you gonna live in?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0290">sorry</u>
<u n="523" who="S0282">are you going to live in?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0290">oh yeah I've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0291">what are you gonna do <unclear/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0291">do you like it?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0282">yeah I loved it I got off the bus I did all my interviews and I got off the bus and I thought oh this one this one</u>
<u n="529" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0282">erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0291"><unclear/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0282">uhu well it was if you wanted to erm in our day erm you had to have two languages to study history and you had to do an entrance exam and you had to pass the entrance exam and they are much less erm there was an awful lot of competition by professors</u>
<u n="535" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0282">I mean it's still like that but</u>
<u n="537" who="S0291">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0290">now why don't you <unclear/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think he's always</u>
<u n="539" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0290">always gonna be a regret for him <unclear/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0291">that's only because <unclear/> parents and <unclear/> I think</u>
<u n="542" who="S0290"><unclear/> him he just <unclear/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0282">he used to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0290">one of my friends who erm <unclear/> we we took it <unclear/> last year but he won't make it this year</u>
<u n="545" who="S0282">no no</u>
<u n="546" who="S0290">perhaps because his grades went down</u>
<u n="547" who="S0282">no no</u>
<u n="548" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0282">biggest regret in his life</u>
<u n="550" who="S0290"><unclear/> his life planned <unclear/> and couldn't really see the future he was considering taking out another year to <unclear/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0282">um</u>
<u n="552" who="S0290">I think like no he still talks about it <unclear/> and he thinks because he applied to <anon type="place"/> for the first time really bad he said something he shouldn't have</u>
<u n="553" who="S0282">oh what does he say?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0290">um they were talking <unclear/> or something and erm talking about whether countries should offer charitable support to others and erm he what's it called erm <pause dur="short"/> the uhu interview <unclear/> to parallel it with <unclear/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="556" who="S0290">erm a situation like a similar like Animal Farms you know that book?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0290">well that's <unclear/> expression so it's like a small situation</u>
<u n="559" who="S0282">an example</u>
<u n="560" who="S0290">with the same principals of the</u>
<u n="561" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0290">um anyway he tried to describe it in terms of if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was walking to work and he saw a child well first I should point out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in his original working with the countries was like erm we shouldn't help other countries <unclear/> toward its citizens that's their problem and then the argument was erm was walking to work and he sees a small child drowning or something and should he save the child but he'll it will ruin his clothes forever I can't remember quite how it was described but he'd never have nice clothes again sort of thing or pretending he didn't see it and walk on and in in the sense of being stubborn he erm said that he'd leave the child and walk <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0290">because he wanted to stick to his original argument</u>
<u n="565" who="S0282">oh but but was he studying economics?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0290">it was economics and history I think</u>
<u n="567" who="S0282">economists there are loads of economists who take that view</u>
<u n="568" who="S0290">no but he's but it like he's interviewer really didn't obviously his interviewer was quite socialist or whatever and didn't like him at all</u>
<u n="569" who="S0291"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0290">especially that comment and the fact that he was being so stubborn about it that he'd say he let a child drown but um his <unclear/> when the results came back it said <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> so he was like <unclear/> interview that he didn't get in for that was the reason he didn't get in so he then applied to <anon type="place"/> with me this year but <anon type="place"/> based their selection more heavily on your available grades and he what a story which is <unclear/> as in for <anon type="place"/> it's like the bare minimum so I think they <unclear/> so he had been competing against <unclear/> bad grades so I think he would have been really well interviewed to get a place but he said his interviewer seemed to be falling asleep in his interview <vocal desc="laugh"/> and stuff so he was pretty upset about that</u>
<u n="571" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="572" who="S0290">but he thought it had gotten in as well thought he had and then he got the letter that said no</u>
<u n="573" who="S0282">oh that would take him a while to get over it</u>
<u n="574" who="S0290"><unclear/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0282">it depends I mean you might have really good <unclear/> and you might end up where's he gonna go?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0290"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0282">oh he'll love it at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0282">I'm surprised that they gave him a place if you'd let a child drown they really are supposed to be um</u>
<u n="580" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0282">pretty much erm left wing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0290"><unclear/> are they left wing?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0282">well they used to be I don't know if they are these days</u>
<u n="584" who="S0290">that's interesting</u>
<u n="585" who="S0282">well my grandma when I was when I my grandma was worried about me going to <unclear/> and my grandma was like you can't go to <anon type="place"/> they have riots there <vocal desc="laugh"/> they get in trouble with the police <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0291">police</u>
<u n="587" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0290">mm</u>
<u n="589" who="S0282">so anyway we're just coming up to the end of the tape so I think fifty-five fifty-nine fifty-six minutes so we can stop now if you wanted</u>
<u n="590" who="S0290">alright lovely</u>
<u n="591" who="S0282">good I just need you to fill in some forms</u>
<u n="592" who="S0290">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0282">so that's good here's the forms here's one for you <unclear/> that's <unclear/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
