<text id="SVET">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:35:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-02-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A pub, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>TV, friends, pintrest, birthdays</topics>
		<activity>TV, friends, pintrest, birthdays</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling, buying/selling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">yeah so it was funny when you said</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">bit weird</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">um let's try it over here <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> alright okay that's fine</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah so it's it was funny when you said uh like like you don't  like you don't  wanna sit <trunc>any</trunc> anywhere</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">I didn't</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">it's like <pause dur="short"/> how about here? There there must be about <trunc>hun</trunc> hundred free seats here</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">I know but I don't really like them like</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and you like turned your nose up at every <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">I know but I don't like ones that are like <pause dur="short"/> I like ones where the tables are higher than the chair</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> where you can sort of sit back and like</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think those where the <pause dur="short"/> those ones are alright those little like what are they called them cup chairs or <pause dur="short"/> that's not the name <pause dur="short"/> You know those little ones?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">yeah uh they've sort of got a curvy arm and um</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">can't think of the name</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115">like a soft <pause dur="short"/> they're sort of soft and like curved arms and like slightly curved top of them with like four legs but I've never really</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">haven't been here for</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115">Don't really <trunc>th</trunc> don't think really think about um <pause dur="short"/> don't really think about chairs very much but uh</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Room for some uh</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037">I'm sick of those those signs</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115">you what?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037">those signs <pause dur="short"/> the Keep Calm And X I'll call them</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115">ah right</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037">like Keep Calm And Carry On was the original one</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">I didn't really notice it that much</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but like I I read an article by Charlie Brooker that he was like really vitriolic about <trunc>p</trunc> these Keep Calm And Have A Cigar or Keep Calm And Make Cakes or Keep Calm And Drink Wine</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">vitriolic? He's he's vitriolic about all uh things isn't he?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">well of course but</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">what exactly is it that annoys him about keeping calm?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037">no no it's just that it's just like</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115" trans="overlap">why should we keep calm? I mean for God's sake <pause dur="short"/> keep calm? Like what next though?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no it's not about keeping calm it's about those posters <pause dur="short"/> it's about how like everyone's making like amusing posters</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115">everyone's making amusing posters are they?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037" trans="overlap">those like Keep Calm And you know like play sports or if you're into sports or Keep Calm And Knit if you're a knitter say</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> still don't get what's annoying about them though</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037">they've just become quite ubiquitous I think</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he was on the TV last night wasn't he with his uh with his <unclear/> programme</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was a better episode though</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">although I fell asleep a bit</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">it was funny when you woke us up when I was on the sofa <pause dur="short"/> I woke with a real <trunc>star</trunc></u>
<u n="43" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the um Something Show <pause dur="short"/> the Something Show?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">ten o'clock</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">live at? Not Live From Studio Five that's something else</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">no Ten o'clock <pause dur="short"/> ten o'clock Live?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037">but I woke with a real start like when you woke  when you woke  us up <pause dur="short"/> I was like <vocal desc="gasp"/> like</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">yeah think that's cos I sort of tripped and sort of fell on you a bit</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">did you?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">rather than</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">that's naughty</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">sort of like</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037">waking us up gently</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">gently <pause dur="short"/> I you know fell fell you awake</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">so um <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was good <pause dur="short"/> wednesday's good for TV isn't it because you've got uh</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> masterchef</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115">uh there's usually a football on isn't there? What although actually</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">there's some final on on Sunday like some somebody's cup final</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037">there's that many cups</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115">would it be?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">it's Liverpool versus Swansea City or something</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">it's not the the um <pause dur="short"/> like the the old league cup is it?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037">maybe yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037">milk Cup <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> The Milk Cup <pause dur="short"/> me granda calls it that I don't know why?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115">yeah you wouldn't call it that if you'd won it though</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">eh? You wouldn't call it that if you've won it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115">no <pause dur="short"/> I mean like</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You might do</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">isn't it like cos <pause dur="short"/> like the the sort of league cup you know the the second  the second  cup of England <pause dur="short"/> You know winning that is a  is a  good achievement cos you you have gotta beat sort of</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">quite a lot of people <pause dur="short"/> You know um</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">got an email from Tosh today</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">yeah?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">just the usual rubbish</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">he's always <pause dur="short"/> he's he's very talkative isn't he?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037" trans="overlap">saying that he'd <pause dur="short"/> he was saying that he'd been chatting up some girl in a shop by telling her about my thesis <pause dur="short"/> I was like Oh well I'm glad those eight those like ten years of study <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">that's funny cos he doesn't actually know anything about your thesis does he?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">well he knows what it was on doesn't he? And um <pause dur="short"/> he's something about <pause dur="short"/> he said something to her and she <trunc>s</trunc> like he got talking to her and then she said that she was doing like Lancashire Lancashire dialect stuff</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">where's that then? In Australia?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">in Huddersfield</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">ah Huddersfield? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">and um said she was doing like Yorkshire stuff</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> Australia</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037">and then he said Ah me friend did a PhD on whatever <pause dur="short"/> And um <pause dur="short"/> and he <trunc>w</trunc> and I so I replied and said like Ah it's good to know that my like ten years in my eight years at university didn't go away didn't go to waste then for that two minute conversation <pause dur="short"/> But uh</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115">no well <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">but uh <pause dur="short"/> but then I was telling him about <pause dur="short"/> then he said something about Are you up to much? And I said Ah um not very much <pause dur="short"/> And then I was telling him about about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and about um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saying to her like You haven't got a real job <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">and he was like Have you told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this? Tell him <pause dur="short"/> Like in capital letters I was like I think he can see both sides though <pause dur="short"/> And then I told him the story about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> going D'you want the money or is it alright? like when I went to the bar</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> there's some funny <pause dur="short"/> we just don't seem to be able to <trunc>th</trunc> find people who haven't got like certain certain you know idiosyncrasies and and stuff</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">well everyone has that's why like</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">if I had friends who were normal then they would be boring wouldn't they? Nobody you know</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">I mean no one is normal that's that's my point you see <pause dur="short"/> who's normal I mean like</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">no I know <pause dur="short"/> I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> but like if they were really like</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115">trying to think you know like who's the most normal <trunc>per</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I suppose maybe there's some people who were more normal than others</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">it depends what you mean by normal like do you mean like sort of calm and like rational? Or do you mean like stereotypical or do you mean?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> that's quite like it's one of them sorts of discussions where you're talking about something but you're <pause dur="short"/> You know because of the the sort semantics you could be talking about absolutely anything you just don't know what it is you're talking about cos like</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">Cos I've got friends who are rational and sort of sensible</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115">I guess yeah certainly like part of it you'd have to have like you couldn't be um couldn't be stupid</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115">but um <pause dur="short"/> they couldn't be <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it's it's what you're  what you're  not isn't it <trunc>p</trunc> partly <pause dur="short"/> uh it's like they they wouldn't wanna be like what you might say I dunno eccentric or something <pause dur="short"/> that would be by definition not normal um</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115">but then that's very broad as well um <pause dur="short"/> they they couldn't be like like for example criminals I I'd imagine um</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think any of my friends are criminals</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115">to to be normal um <pause dur="short"/> you say like something typical about being you know in a family perhaps</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> the old two point four children or <pause dur="short"/> so if you're  if you're  at some stage of being in a family then that helps to make you more normal</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> lots of families that are very not normal <pause dur="short"/> none of my family are very normal</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115">no I mean just the fact that you're in a family makes you more normal maybe</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">think so?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">normal</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">I don't know if I agree</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">might do</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">Cos everyone's in a family everyone's got a family</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I guess there's more  there's more  like more than one type of normal that you are in like</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">stereotypes <pause dur="short"/> You know sort of standard standard types of people you know like a normal uh <trunc>f</trunc> um banker or a normal banker or a normal</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">uh uh</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037">student yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">scientist or something <pause dur="short"/> normal <pause dur="short"/> uh then you could have a normal criminal I suppose couldn't you? Like a people</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">ooh I found this website today</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is it like I think there's nothing much that you can say really about about</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">oh that's true yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh hang on <pause dur="short"/> nobody is normal <pause dur="short"/> I found this website today called Pinterest have you been on it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">no never heard of it</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">it's really good like you'll probably not like it it but it's it's where like you can put like <trunc>ha</trunc> have pictures of things that you like</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">and you create your own little pin board <pause dur="short"/> but you can also look at other people's <pause dur="short"/> and so on the front page they showed like loads of different photos</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">and like of all different things like so people might've done their hair nice and then taken a photo of it or <pause dur="short"/> it might be of a</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115" trans="overlap">shall I go on the pin board then?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037">and you can like you can put things on your own pin board <pause dur="short"/> and and you can find people</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so it's basically it's kinda like a  like a  blog <pause dur="short"/> almost</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">yeah but it's just pictures <pause dur="short"/> or you can find things that other people have put on their pin board and put it on yours</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I see <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">and like you can use it to like if you were creating <pause dur="short"/> You know did you ever do it design like at school where you were creating mood boards and stuff?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">uh yeah I think I've used uh whether you can use it like a wiki you mean work with other people?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so if you were like looking for inspiration for <pause dur="short"/> well it's more like <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> it's more like a place where you can group like um pictures together and stuff</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I see so you don't use it like wiki pin board or something?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so if you were having a thing <pause dur="short"/> no you can <pause dur="short"/> I think you can</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> but people can comment on all like think you pin and you can comment on other things some other people have pinned and stuff and</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037">you can pinch theirs and pin it on yours as well <pause dur="short"/> you could have themed ones like there were some people there who were like <trunc>do</trunc> redecorating some <trunc>s</trunc> things they were like looking for inspiration</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">like if you're <trunc>d</trunc> redecorating your living room you might wanna like put theme you know pictures that you like and get ideas of colours and <trunc>s</trunc> like also of like things to put in it like lamps and stuff <pause dur="short"/> there's also a lot of like food things on there <pause dur="short"/> really nice food people have made</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">yeah?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">lots of like hair things lots of really good clothes and <pause dur="short"/> all different pictures from everywhere so</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so it's like my my pictures</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">it's kind of yeah but it's it looks really nice and snazzy</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">it's uh <pause dur="short"/> you should have a look <pause dur="short"/> I mean for me literally every single thing I was like Ooh look at that ooh look at that ooh look at that like times a hundred but I maybe it's more of a girls' thing</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so it could <trunc>s</trunc> could have like a purpose as being <pause dur="short"/> you could find someone else's idea and copy that basically</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">I think so but like you can also add your own things and like if you were collaborating on like a project or something like <pause dur="short"/> have you seen it on that that Blackberry advert though when it's like What about this? And then he takes a picture of like a some colours and then the other one goes Is this what you mean? and takes another picture</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">oh yeah I think so yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">I think that you can do things like that on there</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">so you you sort of put notes on? Yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">yeah you put notes under the things</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah it seems  it seems  good although yeah haven't some</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it can also link it to something else like if you took a picture of like a</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we we did we not already have this sort of before but not maybe with the ability to put them all on next to each other or something?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">oh right yeah of course you can save a folder of photos but it's you can sort of display them nicely and like</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">I haven't explored it fully but it looks good <pause dur="short"/> but I think it might be more of a girl thing <pause dur="short"/> it was like shoes and cakes and um interiors and um food and oh I've said that and like holidays and</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah I mean I dunno what would be a male version of that</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037" trans="overlap">baby hedgehogs and stuff <pause dur="short"/> no I think there is like men's stuff on there <pause dur="short"/> I think men are interested in like that sort of thing but <pause dur="short"/> maybe the bits I looked at <pause dur="short"/> sorry I've got a bit of a cough <pause dur="short"/> hope I'm not getting that like Liz's horrible ming</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you could go to a specialist site and like if you've seen a good hedgehog or made a good cake then you could go to a specialist hedgehog or cake site that you can  you can  sort of compete and put your own cake and your own hedgehog <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah of course <pause dur="short"/> but I think you can like <pause dur="short"/> I think you can tag things so that you can search for other hedgehogs say</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">yeah? Yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">so like you can search on their site for <trunc>hair</trunc> hairdos or</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">I see</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">you know um <pause dur="short"/> wedding dresses or</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I can kind of see it although I think probably myself I would go to a specific hedgehog site <pause dur="short"/> so you know like We've Got Hedgehogs Dot Com</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh no I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> but I think as well one of the good thing <trunc>i</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Find Me A Hedgehog <pause dur="short"/> but I think one of the good things is like that you get inspiration like if you just wanna see different things <pause dur="short"/> it's like a blast of new things like if you once you open the page there might be like a cocktail on like a um I don't know like a car <pause dur="short"/> and then like some a <trunc>g</trunc> somebody's garden</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it has a <pause dur="short"/> it's like a magazine yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">you know just all different things like <pause dur="short"/> suppose it just gives uh gives you ideas and like sometimes like when I'm at work and I've got a few spare minutes and I wanna do a bit of web surfing like sometimes I'm like Okay what should I do like what should I go to?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">yeah yeah okay yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">I struggle with like things to do like to read and <pause dur="short"/> I know there's Wikipedia I know you like it but</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah you need suggestions yeah like you mean <pause dur="short"/> what people are doing well that's something I was thinking about Wikipedia was that it is a bit more sort of um uh well it it's very broad but it tends not to write like methods</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">like if you were looking on cooking you know it would  it would  tend not to really have a proper recipe for something if you were looking on</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">to be honest if you were looking on anything</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">ultimately in any profession or any field of science</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">you're ultimately gonna get to the point where you would be wanting to do something</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> find out how to do it <pause dur="short"/> well this one was good Pinterest was good I looked at</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> wouldn't it doesn't really <pause dur="short"/> there's a site called Wikihow that that does have something <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well Pinterest was because I it was like there was ones where it showed you how to like put your hair up nice</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">and they'd like they had one picture on the front but then when you clicked it it had like ten different pictures and showed you all the different steps</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right yeah I see</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">you know so like</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">but obviously like if you went to the create Wikipedia page on like updos or whatever <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know if there is a page for updos if that's just what I call them but you know hair hairdressing or something</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115"><trunc>Perha</trunc> perhaps Wikipedia is not very well represented in like</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">hairdos</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">like cosmetics as well like there wasn't a page for um</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">soap And Glory</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">soap And Glory that I knew about for example</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">uh so but but you don't you use Wikipedia for for finding methods you use it for um</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">just general like broad sort of knowledge <pause dur="short"/> but it is <trunc>pr</trunc> it is really good in its breadth but</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">but <trunc>l</trunc> but yeah I suppose it's more like scientific <pause dur="short"/> maybe like you could find uh you could find most chemicals I imagine almost like</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I bet there's a side to that I mean I've only really like I only really found Pinterest today so I was just like <pause dur="short"/> having a little look but <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">should uh should d'you reckon I should have another or d'you wanna</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">if you'd like one yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">balance it out or?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">have you got any cash or d'you wanna borrow some? I think I've got some I went to the cashpoint and risked me life <pause dur="short"/> in that traffic jam</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I might actually <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> uh yeah I think I <pause dur="short"/> think I have actually how much is a pint?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037" trans="overlap">have you? I've I dunno <pause dur="short"/> that those were six six eighty so</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">three forty <pause dur="short"/> I reckon I've got three forty</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there's a pound just in you can give us it</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">hold on <pause dur="short"/> uh yeah I think I'm okay actually</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">sure? Well take that just in case</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">okay</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">then you can give us it back</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> uh <trunc>j</trunc> uh just another of these please</u>
<u n="226" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">D'you want a new glass</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">uh no thanks</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="228" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">here you go it's three pounds please</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="229" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">thank you very much</u>
<u n="230" who="S0115">cheers</u>
<u n="231" who="S0037">must've been my drink that was really expensive</u>
<u n="232" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah we've just uh found uh</u>
<u n="233" who="S0037">typical <pause dur="short"/> it's normally the other way around though that's normally really expensive</u>
<u n="234" who="S0115">well I mean it it it can both be like cider can  cider can  get you sometimes like if you go in um like to the Wetherspoon's and and ask and get Strongbow it'd probably be a bit more than like than like if you went for a an Abbot and</u>
<u n="235" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0115">uh like they don't really have a a <trunc>ci</trunc> a cider as cheap as an  as an  Abbot</u>
<u n="237" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0115">um unless you wanna go into the the sort of dangerous ciders like sort of cloudy <pause dur="short"/> if you wanna go cloudy</u>
<u n="239" who="S0037" trans="overlap">them are horrible</u>
<u n="240" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>S</trunc> some of the perries I think you could probably get from a</u>
<u n="241" who="S0037">but they're not that cheap <pause dur="short"/> not even in</u>
<u n="242" who="S0115" trans="overlap">for like two pounds or something <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then this your Kronenbourg is Kronenbourg can be quite expensive can't it?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0037">yeah it's nice though</u>
<u n="244" who="S0115">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> it is it's got quite a <pause dur="short"/> it's quite um a strong flavour actually</u>
<u n="245" who="S0037">Kronenbourg?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0037">ah I quite like it</u>
<u n="248" who="S0115">it's um <pause dur="short"/> I like Grolsch as well</u>
<u n="249" who="S0037">I like Grolsch <pause dur="short"/> I like the sort of European ones better than like the</u>
<u n="250" who="S0115">so the strong lagers then?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hopefully there'll be some nice ones in the Czech Republic but uh <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I was saying to Tosh I was like I'm going to Brno on the twenty-first and he was like Yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I've got a conference here here actually</u>
<u n="253" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he was like Send me a  send me a  postcard and he was like It's my birthday <pause dur="short"/> And then he put then he sent me an email straight after saying I'm just saying that in case you wanted to buy us a Czech beer <pause dur="short"/> And I was like Tosh I know it's your birthday and I'll buy you a beer next time I see you Czech or otherwise <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> When's his birthday exactly?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0037">twenty-first of March and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s is the eighteenth of April</u>
<u n="256" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> why?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0037">I keep I got them the wrong way round I couldn't remember which <trunc>w</trunc> whose was the eighteenth and whose was the twenty-first</u>
<u n="258" who="S0115">nah I was pretty sure that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s was the April one cos I remember</u>
<u n="259" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> when's your mum's?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0115">the nineteenth of April <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so his is just then <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was I thought it was the uh</u>
<u n="262" who="S0115">yeah it's uh <pause dur="short"/> but I'm very bad at remembering um birthday dates actually uh I think some people have got some kind of talent for it or or they just they focus on that or you know they memorize it so</u>
<u n="263" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know I'm terrible <pause dur="short"/> it's sort of like</u>
<u n="264" who="S0115">I can I probably only know about at most ten birthday dates</u>
<u n="265" who="S0037">go on then let's have a test</u>
<u n="266" who="S0115">oh right  oh right  um let's I'll have to prove it now won't I?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0115">I think I know  I know  mine my parents</u>
<u n="269" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0115">I think I know your <pause dur="short"/> no I don't <pause dur="short"/> I think I know your brother's actually</u>
<u n="271" who="S0037">okay when's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="272" who="S0115">I know yours so that's four</u>
<u n="273" who="S0037">okay that's mine that's four</u>
<u n="274" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="275" who="S0037">when's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0115"><trunc>H</trunc> hold on uh <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> well obviously I knew <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s cos we've just just done them</u>
<u n="277" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no they don't count</u>
<u n="278" who="S0115">uh I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="279" who="S0037" trans="overlap">although you might've known <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> when's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0115">um he's a <trunc>Tau</trunc> he's a Taurus <trunc>i</trunc> it's May the twenty-fourth</u>
<u n="281" who="S0037">well I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so I can't prove that</u>
<u n="282" who="S0115">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> yeah so uh</u>
<u n="283" who="S0037">you could just tell me anything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0115">me and my parents you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0037" trans="overlap">me</u>
<u n="286" who="S0115">that's definitely five down</u>
<u n="287" who="S0037">no that's four</u>
<u n="288" who="S0115">I mean me my parents you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0037" trans="overlap">your own doesn't count <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0115">oh <pause dur="short"/> uh no I said I knew at most like ten birthdays I didn't say</u>
<u n="291" who="S0037">alright then</u>
<u n="292" who="S0115">apart from mine like</u>
<u n="293" who="S0037" trans="overlap">nine others</u>
<u n="294" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I know uh uh <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="295" who="S0037">well that's not very good</u>
<u n="296" who="S0115">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> but that's that's like two more so that's like six</u>
<u n="297" who="S0037">no cos you wouldn't have known them unless I just told you</u>
<u n="298" who="S0115">yeah but uh I only had to name ten I didn't didn't have to make all these conditions and</u>
<u n="299" who="S0037">should have been a barrister</u>
<u n="300" who="S0115">no I shouldn't I'm not not ruthless enough <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="301" who="S0037">anyway</u>
<u n="302" who="S0115">not not good <trunc>en</trunc> not good enough</u>
<u n="303" who="S0037">okay I'll let you have those two <pause dur="short"/> you've <trunc>on</trunc> you've got four more to get</u>
<u n="304" who="S0115">I'm not really  not really  a barrister <pause dur="short"/> like a</u>
<u n="305" who="S0037">four more</u>
<u n="306" who="S0115">okay um <pause dur="short"/> excluding you know famous celebrities from the past</u>
<u n="307" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you can't guess famous celebrities from the past <pause dur="short"/> I know who you're thinking of <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if you can class him as a celebrity anyway</u>
<u n="308" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> someone's is March the third isn't it?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0037">might be might not be</u>
<u n="310" who="S0115">that's is that your dad's?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0037">yes that is me dad's</u>
<u n="312" who="S0115">oh is it? Okay <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="313" who="S0115">this is um <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah um my cousin Phil's is on Valentine's Day <pause dur="short"/> easy to remember</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">okay two more then <pause dur="short"/> to prove that you know ten birthdays</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">oh god um <pause dur="short"/> I mean let me think like <pause dur="short"/> when was my  when was my  nan's? I mean</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">dunno I didn't meet your nan</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">she's not uh she's not alive any more but <pause dur="short"/> does it count if the person is dead? Uh um</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think so yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="319" who="S0115">uh to to be honest I uh can't remember that either</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">ah well so you don't know ten <pause dur="short"/> you know about eight</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>H</trunc> hold on um who someone's January the twenty-ninth?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> no but nearly</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">the twenty-seventh?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">uh twenty-eighth?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">ah dammit</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">Tom's is on January the thirtieth</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">I know a few</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">Anth's is on January the twenty-third</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">me Auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is on June the eleventh <pause dur="short"/> me Uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s is on July the third <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> me mam's is on June the second <pause dur="short"/> me nana's was on July the twenty-fourth <pause dur="short"/> the other nana's is on</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115" trans="overlap">have you  have you  done <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is on <trunc>O</trunc> twenty-seventh of October <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I was just about to get that one</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">I remember like some friends' birthdays as well like I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> I know that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is on the first of July <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is on the first of December <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is on the fourth of December</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s is on Burns Night <pause dur="short"/> twenty-fifth of January</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">oh <pause dur="short"/> hold on <pause dur="short"/> there's a few people I know whose birthdays are really close to mine <pause dur="short"/> and um this could push me  this could push me  up to ten actually</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> you should have got those <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is one of them</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115">hold on <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>lu</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> uh</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">I've just told you these <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's like and uh</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">I just told you these a second ago</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh did you? Was was they on the list?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0115"><trunc>W</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> okay um</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037">I did I just <trunc>to</trunc> I just told you them I was like <trunc>L</trunc></u>
<u n="351" who="S0115" trans="overlap">when was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s then?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037">the fourth</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">okay <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is on the first <pause dur="short"/> or was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on the second?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115">there's a lot  there's a lot  who have birthdays at the end of November anyway</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037" trans="overlap">actually I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> well there's your dad <pause dur="short"/> and you <pause dur="short"/> liz</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037">I know like a few people I used to be friends with</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037"><trunc>Sagi</trunc> all Sagittarians you see <pause dur="short"/> best way to be <pause dur="short"/> and then it's obviously me <pause dur="short"/> and uh Jamie Theakston <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0115">it's a good one to you know like man on a horse <pause dur="short"/> ay? Jamie Theakston yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I said uh</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115">there must be  there must be  someone more more famous than Jamie Theakston</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037">I dunno he's just one that sticks in me mind <pause dur="short"/> as having the same birthday as me</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115">there's a guy who had a birthday um <pause dur="short"/> yesterday it was on Google <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> lots of people had a birthday yesterday</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah um it was uh it was like a sine wave</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh Hertz</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hertz's birthday yesterday so that's uh <pause dur="short"/> that's another one</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I saw that <pause dur="short"/> it was a good Google thing wasn't it?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037">did you ever see that one that was to celebrate um the graphic novelist what's he called? It was really long and you had to like press buttons and do things</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115">is that the one that went <pause dur="short"/> there was one</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was like a machine?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115">I think there was one with Jules Verne</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it wasn't Jules Verne</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115" trans="overlap">where he went down  he went down  to the bottom of the sea or something and then uh there was like a</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that's pretty good <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember his name</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">there was like a full-on <trunc>ani</trunc> animation and stuff</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037">can't remember his name <pause dur="short"/> it was really good though <pause dur="short"/> well I was like it took like ten minutes to go through the whole thing <pause dur="short"/> you had to like press stuff and do things <pause dur="short"/> I had one of them these days at work today like when you <pause dur="short"/> you know when <trunc>y</trunc> like I've got obviously got things to do I've always got like things to do but like I just couldn't get settled into anything</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115">oh right yeah just not not can't think positively or?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like some days I get to work and I'm like do this do this do this</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037">and like it's and I just like <trunc>kn</trunc> knock things out and get things done really fast and type really loads of emails and do all my work and do my research and everything <pause dur="short"/> and then other days like today when <pause dur="short"/> I just got to work and I spent the whole morning doing something that would normally take us about an hour like <pause dur="short"/> just wasn't in the right mood and like</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">like I was reading somewhere that in like um in Norway like okay you get your annual holiday allowance and stuff but you get three days like three duvet days when you can just ring up and say d'you know what I just  I just  don't wanna come to work today</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Three duvet days?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037">so you can use them as holiday if you want <pause dur="short"/> but apparently people use them for those days when they feel like unproductive</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">okay <pause dur="short"/> but you don't always know though before you've gone in do you?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but you can ring on the morning <pause dur="short"/> no you don't always know</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037">yeah but you could go home at lunchtime and use half of your duvet day <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115">um yeah yeah I do yeah yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you could like be like I haven't done anything any more today I can't do this afternoon I'm just gonna home like</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">guess it you can learn a lot by</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037" trans="overlap">obviously you can't have duvet days if you're like a nurse but like</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0037">like a brain surgeon but you've just got like an office job</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you can learn a lot by by reading reading about um the practices of other countries like</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I just like that idea like</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh the Scandinavian ones are pretty</u>
<u n="402" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I just like that idea like cos you know some days when you wake up and you just don't feel like it <pause dur="short"/> and you drag your bones there and you put yourself through it and you go through the motions but you're not really feeling like it <pause dur="short"/> and just like one you know a day off would just rejuvenate you</u>
<u n="403" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's that was it I mean  I mean  you get bad days when although you may not always know that it's gonna be one but</u>
<u n="404" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115">you get a bad and things that it you get in a negative frame of mind and things seem to <pause dur="short"/> things seem to go wrong like</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's bad <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't really that today it was more like I just couldn't get like there wasn't anything was really like really interested us to do</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it was more like a bored day?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0037">like everything was okay but I just <pause dur="short"/> You know when you go around doing like little tiny bits of one thing and then a little tiny bit of another thing so you don't achieve anything?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well um you should have things like in place that you can do when when you feel like that you should have like little little side side plans and stuff that you can do</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I have got some side projects <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> I sort of have but even those weren't taking me fancy <pause dur="short"/> nothing was <pause dur="short"/> I cleaned the keyboard for a while</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Did you take the keys off?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037">no but I got one of those special wipes</u>
<u n="413" who="S0115">that's <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah a sprayer?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0037">no it was a wipe</u>
<u n="415" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0037">I emptied the crumbs off it though</u>
<u n="417" who="S0115">fair enough <pause dur="short"/> yeah you just you <trunc>ti</trunc> sort of shook it?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> tipped it out yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0115">yeah I mine's uh <pause dur="short"/> my laptop's pretty you know</u>
<u n="420" who="S0037" trans="overlap">cleaned all the ming under my <pause dur="short"/> cos I've got a wooden desk and I don't have like a mouse mat</u>
<u n="421" who="S0115">you don't have a mouse mat?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> I don't really like them</u>
<u n="423" who="S0115">oh you don't mouse <trunc>m</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> how can you not like mouse mats?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it's crazy <pause dur="short"/> but uh <pause dur="short"/> so consequently my mouse picks up all of my like cake crumbs and bits of eraser and <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah they they you have to clean them don't you have to open them and uh get the ball out and like pull all the dust out</u>
<u n="426" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I just <pause dur="short"/> it was just collects underneath so I just</u>
<u n="427" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0037">got rid of all that</u>
<u n="429" who="S0115">is it uh quarter to seven already?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="431" who="S0115">thought it was earlier cos it's quite late actually</u>
<u n="432" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it is quite late <pause dur="short"/> I know the shop closes in like an hour yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0115" trans="overlap">at eight eight or maybe nine no eight</u>
<u n="434" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no eight I think</u>
<u n="435" who="S0115">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> might be nice and quiet</u>
<u n="436" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is it eight or just some? Yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0115">think it's eight yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0037">yeah it was probably better off coming for a drink first because like sometimes it just gets totally rammed</u>
<u n="439" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> hopefully they've uh they'll have had a chance to restock some stuff cos</u>
<u n="440" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0115">sometimes you if you go late you get um</u>
<u n="442" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0115">totally empty but probably wouldn't happen  probably wouldn't happen  today though Thursday</u>
<u n="444" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="445" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="446" who="S0037">I think there's</u>
<u n="447" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah it was nice and you get the whole place to yourself you know</u>
<u n="448" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0115">at this time you sort go round and uh</u>
<u n="450" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I used to like going shopping like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> cos you know only recently isn't it I mean I don't mean like very recently but within the past five years that like shops have started opening all through the night <pause dur="short"/> big supermarkets</u>
<u n="451" who="S0115">have they?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0037">certainly in Sunderland like I remember <pause dur="short"/> About five years ago</u>
<u n="453" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I think it's a good idea</u>
<u n="454" who="S0037">like shops are open at all like there's a few in Sunderland like a big Asda that's open all night <pause dur="short"/> and sometimes like um</u>
<u n="455" who="S0115">actually there was in Lancaster wasn't there?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0037">was there?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0115">yeah I think so yeah the Asda in Lancaster I think it was</u>
<u n="458" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah yeah it was yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0115">and <trunc>ov</trunc> we drove there at like ten or something once <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I remember going shopping with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in Sunderland once at like half ten and it was so nice <pause dur="short"/> there wasn't like any kids in there no like <pause dur="short"/> not even really very many staff</u>
<u n="461" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="462" who="S0037">it was so peaceful</u>
<u n="463" who="S0115">supermarkets that are crowded really really are quite annoying in fact well <trunc>ev</trunc> everything is annoying when it's crowded like I think I usually prefer like peace you know</u>
<u n="464" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it's horrible <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> sometimes when I go to Aldi like I just feel like there's just a person just in the way like I'm just trying to get like something off the shelf and there's just a person there</u>
<u n="465" who="S0115">yeah I mean I think sometimes you you you do sort of get a bit frustrated in in smaller shops when when they're full and you're like</u>
<u n="466" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> I hate it</u>
<u n="467" who="S0115">you can't sort of browse or you feel like you can't browse but but I know I like browsing so um <pause dur="short"/> but sometimes you go sometimes I go there and I think just gotta get through it really fast like</u>
<u n="468" who="S0037" trans="overlap">gets right on me nerves <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0115">um it's gonna <pause dur="short"/> and then when when you head in and trying to grab everything really fast then then you think that someone's in the way and someone's deliberately trying to stop you from uh you know getting to the  getting to the  pastrami or whatever it is</u>
<u n="470" who="S0037" trans="overlap">stop you yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> sprouts <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="471" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0115">it's um about couple of years since we've been in here</u>
<u n="473" who="S0037">I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> has it changed?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0115">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>w</trunc> I don't think <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I remember us going to the orange part of it</u>
<u n="475" who="S0037">is it still open? Oh yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0115">and sitting there <pause dur="short"/> we went for like a long walk or something through loads of parks and nearly got lost</u>
<u n="477" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that's right</u>
<u n="478" who="S0115">then we sort of turned up here</u>
<u n="479" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0115">and went you know</u>
<u n="481" who="S0037" trans="overlap">we came out like the um what's it called? The recreation ground there <pause dur="short"/> and then came in here</u>
<u n="482" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah we we we totally surprised ourselves with like took a short cut</u>
<u n="483" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="484" who="S0115">and <trunc>a</trunc> and at the end of the short cut we were like This is right next to our house I mean</u>
<u n="485" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'd like it if it was more ranch-like if it had more of a Texan theme</u>
<u n="486" who="S0115">well part of it is orange <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="487" who="S0037">and there's some pictures of horses on the wall</u>
<u n="488" who="S0115">there's the orangeness sort of <unclear/> up</u>
<u n="489" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'd like it if the barmen wore like cowboy hats and there was like straw on the floor</u>
<u n="490" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="491" who="S0037">D'you not think? D'you not think?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0115">yeah I mean um</u>
<u n="493" who="S0037" trans="overlap">bit like a proper ranch</u>
<u n="494" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="495" who="S0037">with like lassos and like ironmonger and</u>
<u n="496" who="S0115">dunno do do they have ironmongers in in ranches?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0037">I don't know I was just thinking about like <trunc>h</trunc> horseshoes and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I think it would be good</u>
<u n="498" who="S0115">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> actually I saw a thing on uh you know the one of the things on with uh <trunc>docu</trunc> like one of those programmes where someone like um um <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what's his name uh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes um</u>
<u n="499" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0115">around the world</u>
<u n="501" who="S0037">travelling</u>
<u n="502" who="S0115">the one when he <trunc>go</trunc> went round the world <trunc>t</trunc> drinking in different place and uh</u>
<u n="503" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0115">uh when he went in Australia there was the one of like a big massive like</u>
<u n="505" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like a cattle ranch?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0115">yeah it was just a big pub and it had like masses of uh tables and that you could just bring like <trunc>the</trunc> there was like horses and</u>
<u n="507" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0115">cattle going around <trunc>ins</trunc> inside the pub and stuff</u>
<u n="509" who="S0037" trans="overlap">really? Oh that sounds good <pause dur="short"/> like Calamity Jane?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0115">uh I guess a bit like that <pause dur="short"/> perhaps more more like a almost like a sort of a hangar or a warehouse or something</u>
<u n="511" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aha <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="512" who="S0115">and more like sort of <trunc>o</trunc> a bit very open so it was out and</u>
<u n="513" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0115">but um if it was in that out in the middle of nowhere then I don't know how people got back home after uh after they'd been drinking there perhaps they took the horses and the cattle cows</u>
<u n="515" who="S0037" trans="overlap">dunno <pause dur="short"/> probably took the horse yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Like home boy you know just</u>
<u n="516" who="S0115">I guess you can ride a  ride a  cow</u>
<u n="517" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> well I don't suppose they go very fast do they?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0115">no well or indeed anywhere uh</u>
<u n="519" who="S0037">I don't think cows do <pause dur="short"/> horses probably do <pause dur="short"/> a horse could take you home</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="520" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah um <pause dur="short"/> and there's no penalty for drunken horse riding I believe</u>
<u n="521" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no don't suppose there is</u>
<u n="522" who="S0115">uh I'm just guessing I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't actually know</u>
<u n="523" who="S0037">might maybe there is <pause dur="short"/> probably like a bylaw somewhere <pause dur="short"/> You know like those stupid ones like if you're a citizen of York you can still whip your wife within the confines of the city walls and all that</u>
<u n="524" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Is that a real one?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and shoot her</u>
<u n="526" who="S0115">no no I'm <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't</u>
<u n="527" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no you can <pause dur="short"/> you have to take them down <pause dur="short"/> there's a stupid place <trunc>call</trunc> I think it's like Whipma Whoppagate in in some stupid name in York and you can take your wife there and beat her <pause dur="short"/> if you want to <pause dur="short"/> as a bylaw <pause dur="short"/> and there's also that like if you're <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>bor</trunc> if you're born within the city walls of York you can like fire a bow and arrow at a Scotsman if you want to</u>
<u n="528" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What? Anywhere or just</u>
<u n="529" who="S0037">within the city yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0115">within the city? No I didn't know about those <pause dur="short"/> those sound uh</u>
<u n="531" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I only know those cos I read something</u>
<u n="532" who="S0115">but um perhaps have been overwritten by like</u>
<u n="533" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> perhaps like <pause dur="short"/> don't yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0115">Cos I guess our law is is based on precedents isn't it rather than <pause dur="short"/> it's not  it's not  explicitly written down is it or? I mean</u>
<u n="535" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>I</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0115">parts of it are not  are not  written down as laws but merely as precedents</u>
<u n="537" who="S0037">I don't really know</u>
<u n="538" who="S0115">as common law I mean like I've not <trunc>j</trunc> certain</u>
</body>
</text>
