<text id="SVFD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:52</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-05-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0411 S0417</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home Cork</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Friends, Relationships, Step Parenting, Independence</topics>
		<activity>Evening chat about relationships with close friend</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0411">
				<exactage>46</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Brighton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>all my life</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0417">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cork</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Ireland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>not currently working, caring for toddler</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>some French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0411"><unclear/> just in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0417" trans="overlap">oh she's very near there isn't she?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah erm she is cos she could sort of show me where she lived she's like up on the cliff</u>
<u n="4" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0411">erm but it was lovely it was really nice to see her and we so we met in the car park</u>
<u n="6" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0411">and it was really really windy it had been really really windy the night before and it was still quite windy</u>
<u n="8" who="S0417">cos it's right near the coast as well</u>
<u n="9" who="S0411" trans="overlap">so yeah exactly so we walked down to the beach with the kids and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got on really well with the boys erm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0417">oh her boys are really sweet aren't they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0411" trans="overlap">they're so nice</u>
<u n="12" who="S0417">I know they're really kind of cheeky as well and they're very</u>
<u n="13" who="S0411" trans="overlap">oh they're just lovely</u>
<u n="14" who="S0417">yeah and they've got this gorgeous hair haven't they? with kind of <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0411" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah they're just beautiful yeah and she had the dog with her and then after we went for a walk we went to the café and the kids had like burger and chips and we had a coffee</u>
<u n="16" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0411">and then she had to go and do I can't remember what she had to do some work or the kids were going to an art class and she had to go and do some work or something like that</u>
<u n="18" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0411">and erm so she went off and me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went back to <unclear>work</unclear> but it was lovely it was a really nice sort of</u>
<u n="20" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0411">I think about three hours or something like that</u>
<u n="22" who="S0417">she's good company isn't she? when you</u>
<u n="23" who="S0411">she's just really easy company and</u>
<u n="24" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0411">it was just nice to catch up and we just talked about the kids and</u>
<u n="26" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0411">you know sort of work and schools and you know that sort of thing</u>
<u n="28" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah because she's she's thinking of er changing from cos she I mean she's had to stop her work because of her back</u>
<u n="29" who="S0411">yeah but she's doing bits and pieces</u>
<u n="30" who="S0417" trans="overlap">and erm is she?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0417">cos she was thinking of going into teaching</u>
<u n="33" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah was she? she didn't mention that actually</u>
<u n="34" who="S0417" trans="overlap">oh okay alright</u>
<u n="35" who="S0411">yeah but she <trunc>m</trunc> I mean she may still be but we were just sort of talking about you know gardening and you know things like that but no she'd be good at that actually</u>
<u n="36" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0411">erm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0417">she's</u>
<u n="39" who="S0411">but I think she has er the I mean obviously nobody ever truly knows from the outside</u>
<u n="40" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0411">but she seems to have quite a good balance with what's his name? is it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0417"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0411" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is that his name?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he's a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think yes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0411">no she's <vocal desc="yawn"/> from what she was saying I've really liked what she said you know she was she sort of said I'm really independent you know I <trunc>d</trunc>I do what I want when I want</u>
<u n="48" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0411">he works really hard he does work at home sometimes but that's fine we just sort of work around each other</u>
<u n="50" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0411">and erm you know she said when his kids are down that's that seems to be a successful kind of stepmum thing from what she says</u>
<u n="52" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0411">it does sound quite</u>
<u n="54" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0411">good but</u>
<u n="56" who="S0417">one of the girls wanted to move in</u>
<u n="57" who="S0411">really?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0417">for a while cos she was erm having problems with her mum</u>
<u n="59" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0417">but I think well er I think she she was kind of kicking back as her mum's a bit more structured than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0417">I think she was kind of maybe looking for an easier life <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0411">yeah exactly but erm I yeah I just got the sense that she was really quite happy actually not in that kind of I'm fucking happy kind of way</u>
<u n="64" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0411">you know but in a yeah life's good and I like life and it's not without its hitches and you know she did say it is bloody knackering</u>
<u n="66" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0411">and especially when the stepchildren are there</u>
<u n="68" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0411">but she said it is hard work because I've got two young active boys and you know the older kids do go oh can't you keep them quiet? and she's a bit like well no cos they're two young boys and this is their home</u>
<u n="70" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0411">you know?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0411">and that's how it is you know and but I did sort of get that sense that she's she's alright actually</u>
<u n="74" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0411">you know?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0417">I think you're right er <trunc>w</trunc> I haven't seen them for a while but I</u>
<u n="77" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0417">I just flew over a few years ago I think it was three years ago</u>
<u n="79" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0417">and just thought I've not seen her for so long so I actually got a flight just went to see her and just went back just</u>
<u n="81" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0417">did that and nothing else and they were so sweet</u>
<u n="83" who="S0411"><vocal desc="yawn"/> yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0417"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and her they both cooked me my favourite meal</u>
<u n="85" who="S0411">oh</u>
<u n="86" who="S0417" trans="overlap">I was so touched I didn't even know that they knew it was like a roast <unclear/> oh my god <unclear/></u>
<u n="87" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0417">and that's when erm things were going erm like funny with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and that kind of thing and er</u>
<u n="89" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0417">so I asked their advice which was like really funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0417">they were very</u>
<u n="93" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0417">we were all we'd had a few glasses of wine and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s kind of quite chirpy anyway and they were just look we just take one day at a time</u>
<u n="95" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0417">we don't worry too much about things and</u>
<u n="97" who="S0411">mm mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0417"><unclear>I mean I know there's kind of things like</unclear> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has never met the mother</u>
<u n="99" who="S0411">I know</u>
<u n="100" who="S0417">has never</u>
<u n="101" who="S0411">I know that's fucking weird</u>
<u n="102" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0411">she didn't talk about that but I do know that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0417" trans="overlap">she doesn't like her <vocal desc="laugh"/> even though she's never met her <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0411">but she's never met her how can she?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear>I know</unclear> she doesn't like her <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think there's a there's <pause dur="short"/> I suppose they took a er they they live with it in their own way I think for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0417">it's better that she hasn't met she doesn't want to meet her she doesn't really</u>
<u n="109" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0417">like any demands that she puts on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0417">sometimes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> talks <unclear>to her</unclear> on the phone and sometimes like</u>
<u n="113" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0417">you know she says she can hear him saying oh you know don't worry about things and <trunc>sh</trunc> it makes her really cross <vocal desc="laugh"/> she just doesn't want that any kind of erm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0417">you know any tenderness going there or that kind of thing</u>
<u n="117" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0417">but but they've kind of got some kind of</u>
<u n="119" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0417">they they've got something that works haven't they?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0411">yeah absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0417">and he spends a few days every week up in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0417">and sometimes she says you know it's not easy and sometimes she wonders whether</u>
<u n="125" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0417">he's being completely faithful</u>
<u n="127" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0417">I know she's said that to me</u>
<u n="129" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0417">she doesn't know but she's she hardly sort of</u>
<u n="131" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0417">it was only when I I kind of brought it up with her but she'll</u>
<u n="133" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0417">and really she just said look</u>
<u n="135" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0417">may've been but you know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0417">erm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0417">I don't know possibly but he provides for me and erm he's</u>
<u n="141" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0417">you know I know that he's er I'm the one that he wants <unclear/> maybe he you know he's had the odd slip</u>
<u n="143" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0417">I don't know but erm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0411">mm yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0417">maybe he hasn't I don't know</u>
<u n="147" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0417">but she doesn't want to she wouldn't want to go there she wouldn't want to know she wouldn't want to</u>
<u n="149" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0417">but they but they do quite a lot of fun things together as well don't they? they said they</u>
<u n="151" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm yes they have lots of holidays and they go skiing</u>
<u n="152" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0411">and it sounds great</u>
<u n="154" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0417">they went to erm <unclear>just</unclear> decided to spontaneously go to erm <anon type="place"/> to the erm moustache and beard convention</u>
<u n="157" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0411">excellent mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0417">I think that's the kind of thing that keeps them ticking over</u>
<u n="160" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0417">it's nice to see something <unclear/> cos you can you know that</u>
<u n="162" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0417">that maybe they're not always the the erm er the easiest couple either and then you can see that that works</u>
<u n="164" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0417">that's that's quite heartening isn't it?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0417">you know they have their trials and he works very long hours</u>
<u n="168" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah which is completely normal that's what I'd want to see in a relationship you know my my friends <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0411">you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they're they're really they've been together since they were teenagers</u>
<u n="171" who="S0417">really?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0411">you know yeah yeah yeah and erm you know it's definitely have er had its rough patches but they're both really up front about when it has been tough</u>
<u n="173" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0411">they've got loads of friends they've got it's open house round at theirs</u>
<u n="175" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0411">you know they're real party people but they're very boundaried as well <trunc>s</trunc> you know they've got two really lovely boys</u>
<u n="177" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0411">and the good thing about those two is they're really up front about tough times you know if you go out for a drink with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0411">she will sit there and go bloody <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and bloody pig he is and bloody this and bloody that you know and she will say that but I know that she really loves <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he's really got her back and she's really got his and</u>
<u n="181" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0411">you know that is a real relationship</u>
<u n="183" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0411">you know it does have its up and downs they have really worked through stuff</u>
<u n="185" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0411">and they've you know come out the other side</u>
<u n="187" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0411">and that's what it's all about isn't it? really</u>
<u n="189" who="S0417">yeah cos I mean I I I don't know if I've ever really made a successful partnership I think maybe this is the closest and even <unclear>that's not totally</unclear></u>
<u n="190" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0417">how do you feel about that kind of partnership? would you ever want one again? or? <unclear/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0411">if I did it would be very unconventional that's why it was very refreshing to hear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> say what she said</u>
<u n="194" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0411">you know she said I do what I wanna do you know I do my thing</u>
<u n="196" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0411">I don't answer to anyone and</u>
<u n="198" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0411">you know he does his thing I do my thing and that's exactly the kind of thing I would want to do</u>
<u n="200" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0411">I couldn't imagine having I I couldn't I know that I couldn't have a conventional relationship</u>
<u n="202" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0411">where I was in somebody's pocket all the time where</u>
<u n="204" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0411">you did everything socially with them where</u>
<u n="206" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0411"><vocal desc="sigh"/> you know coming here there's no way I'd wanna drag some bloke around</u>
<u n="208" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0411">to come and see you do you know what I mean? it's just like fuck off are you still here?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah I know what you mean <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0411">fuck off go and do something you know I couldn't I couldn't do that</u>
<u n="212" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0411">and I know a lot of people do do it and it would drive me insane</u>
<u n="214" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0411">it would drive me mad I would just say to someone just go and get a life just fuck off</u>
<u n="216" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0411">and really get a life and I'll see you next week maybe if I've got time</u>
<u n="218" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0411">you know so if er you know that's it's no coincidence that the longest relationship I've ever had was with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="220" who="S0417">yes</u>
<u n="221" who="S0411"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> worked silly hours upside down you know</u>
<u n="222" who="S0417">yes</u>
<u n="223" who="S0411">working in clubs running the <anon type="place"/> arts club running <trunc>i</trunc> working in pubs</u>
<u n="224" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0411">and it worked well because I'd <trunc>d</trunc> I could do my thing I was at my most hedonistic at that time probably</u>
<u n="226" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0411">just doing loads of pills</u>
<u n="228" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0411">with all the gay guys</u>
<u n="230" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0411">really out partying</u>
<u n="232" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0411">you know oh I'm gonna go to <anon type="place"/> for six weeks <unclear/> see you</u>
<u n="234" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0411" trans="overlap">you know that's that's what works for me</u>
<u n="236" who="S0417">also can you imagine looking back on your life and having something like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did in a way thinking I was only with that person? I think that would make me feel</u>
<u n="237" who="S0411" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0417">kind of like oh god what was?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0411" trans="overlap">suicidal <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0417">yeah what was my life? <unclear>was my life</unclear></u>
<u n="241" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0417">only about sort of one person? <unclear/> about all sorts <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0411" trans="overlap">and I think there's so much rhetoric to make you believe that that's the right thing to do there's so much media there's so much bullshit out there to make you believe that that's what you should aim for</u>
<u n="244" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0411">to only be with one person</u>
<u n="246" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0411">you know talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is one of the most interesting and enlightening things about</u>
<u n="248" who="S0417" trans="overlap">oh yeah? what does he kind of say?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0411">well he's nearly fifty</u>
<u n="250" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0411">and he firmly believes he's definitely been er by his own admission in his own words you know in his twenties he was a bit of a ladies' man you know he had a child in his teens</u>
<u n="252" who="S0417" trans="overlap">was he? did he?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0411"><trunc>wi</trunc>with yeah he when he was eighteen I think his daughter was born and the mother was just seventeen</u>
<u n="254" who="S0417">god</u>
<u n="255" who="S0411">you know so he's definitely you know he's been around the block</u>
<u n="256" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0411">and he <trunc>f</trunc>he firmly believes from experience not just bullshit but from experience that</u>
<u n="258" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0411">you that you should be not should be but it's more normal for most humans and he fully understands that some people like to be with one person for their whole life and that's fantastic but he thinks that you go through so many phases in your life that it's very very difficult for one person to weather those phases with you</u>
<u n="260" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0411">and he feels that he's a vastly different person in his for example twenties to what he was in his thirties to his forties</u>
<u n="262" who="S0417">mm yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0411">because he feels that he's really grown and developed and changed and not necessarily become a better or a worse person but is a completely different person and he feels that he really needs different things</u>
<u n="264" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0411">not necessarily women</u>
<u n="266" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0411">but he's talking about women as well he er like he him seeing me he that that's a sort of particular phase in his life or whatever and he</u>
<u n="268" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0411">at some point wants to retire probably to the south coast and so therefore you know sort of</u>
<u n="270" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0411">seeing me and the south coast and that kind of thing but not it's not just about women but he he does think and also he's sort of saying you know <trunc>m</trunc> the whole original rhetoric of marriage being with one person was when people were dying in their fifties and sixties and that made sense you know</u>
<u n="272" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0411">you sort of got married when you were twenty</u>
<u n="274" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0411">and then you're gonna be dead by the time you're fifty but he's sort of saying look</u>
<u n="276" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0411">I'm probably gonna live hopefully until I'm like eighty or something like that</u>
<u n="278" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0411">there is no way <vocal desc="laugh"/> that I will be the same person in my twenties to what I am in my eighties</u>
<u n="280" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0411" trans="overlap">you know he wants to do different things he's never really travelled because he's spent so much time working and building up a property portfolio and doing all his craft stuff that he does all his furniture upholstering and</u>
<u n="282" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh does he do that?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0411">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0417"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0411">he's really interesting he's a really amazing guy actually you know he's done</u>
<u n="286" who="S0417" trans="overlap">he does sound quite he's very nice to you isn't he?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0411">he's yeah he is he's but he's very unassuming</u>
<u n="288" who="S0417">texting all the time isn't he?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0411">yeah constantly</u>
<u n="290" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0411">but not in a kind of <vocal desc="misc"/> kind of way but it's just a constant dialogue</u>
<u n="292" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0411">all the time erm he's er he's a very interesting person and he's got lots of ideas he hasn't really travelled and he really wants to travel</u>
<u n="294" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0411">and that's another thing he likes being around me because I've done a lot of travelling and that really fits with with where his head is at at the moment and you know</u>
<u n="296" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0411">I have a perspective on life that fits with his perspective on life at the moment in his current phase of his life</u>
<u n="298" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0411">and he and it is so interesting because he said oh you know some people might look at me from the outside and say oh you're just having a mid-life crisis and it's like and he said well if that's what a mid-life crisis is then bring it on cos I'm really enjoying it <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0411">and erm and I I just really like that because he talks through how he feels and you know he has actually thought about what he's doing he hasn't just sort of gone oh yeah my wife is a bitch and so I <unclear>yeah just fucking left</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0411">do you know what I mean? he really talks about it and he will say that you know he still has an excellent relationship with his wife ex-wife</u>
<u n="304" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0411">and you know er she was a hugely important person in his life and still is</u>
<u n="306" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0411">I mean his his best friend is her brother</u>
<u n="308" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0411">you know because they've know each other for such a long time</u>
<u n="310" who="S0417" trans="overlap">oh really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0417">god</u>
<u n="313" who="S0411">they're a very very tight-knit <trunc>k</trunc>kind of family you know so er I I couldn't be with someone that was really awful</u>
<u n="314" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0411">about their ex about the mother of their children I couldn't be with someone that was</u>
<u n="316" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0411">you know talked about a woman on that level</u>
<u n="318" who="S0417">yeah I know what you mean <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0411" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? he's had three children with them <unclear/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0417">I know</u>
<u n="321" who="S0411">no I need I need to be around someone that shows respect to their ex</u>
<u n="322" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0411">and talks about them and <unclear/> he he he will mention sometimes that you know she did exasperate him sometimes around money there was lots of issues around money</u>
<u n="324" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0411">and that's fine you know that's okay for him to mention that because I certainly have mentioned numerous times about my frustrations with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0411">but I talk respectfully about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he talks respectfully about her</u>
<u n="328" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0411">you know but I couldn't I couldn't imagine erm <pause dur="short"/> you know I it we do have a relationship we know we have a relationship and we've acknowledged that</u>
<u n="330" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0411">but we don't talk about</u>
<u n="332" who="S0417" trans="overlap">it does sound like you've got something very you know he cares about you doesn't he?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0411">yeah yeah and I care about him but</u>
<u n="334" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0411">at the same time I don't have to have him here like I I did feel <trunc>re</trunc> you know I did feel really really bad and I did really give myself a hard time about it actually er cos a couple of months ago he was going for quite a senior job cos he's quite senior at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0417">oh is he?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0411">and yeah and he was going for <pause dur="short"/> erm a sort of more senior role</u>
<u n="338" who="S0417"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="339" who="S0411">and he's been doing this particular role for about fifteen years and has just kind of been coasting in it</u>
<u n="340" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0411">and he did talk to me quite a lot about it and because it's got quite big implications <unclear>it's</unclear> shift work as well cos it's doing night staff and things like that</u>
<u n="342" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0411">it's like managing a night team and things like that erm and I did a couple of mock interviews with him I looked over some things and did some mock interviews and stuff and he got the job and he does he does sort of say</u>
<u n="344" who="S0417" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0411">oh you know a lot of that was down to you and I sort of go oh not really</u>
<u n="346" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0411">but he he firmly believes</u>
<u n="348" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear>no it probably was actually <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="349" who="S0411"><unclear/> cos he hadn't had an interview for fifteen years</u>
<u n="350" who="S0417">oh really?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0411">you know cos he'd just been in the one job</u>
<u n="352" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0411">so he really needed and I really helped him because I'd recently had an interview and</u>
<u n="354" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0411">you know and I really changed cos he wasn't he was really self-deprecating and it was just like you you can't you can't</u>
<u n="356" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah you can't can you? in that kind of situation <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0411" trans="overlap">you know so it's not like you know he just sat down and talked and I went yeah that was great it was a really big sort of process</u>
<u n="358" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0411">erm but <vocal desc="yawn"/> <unclear>what was I gonna say</unclear>? yes that's right but the day of his interview and it was a really big deal for him I forgot it was his interview just forgot</u>
<u n="360" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="361" who="S0411">I completely forgot it was <unclear>his interview</unclear></u>
<u n="362" who="S0417">and usually you're actually you're usually very good at remembering <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0411">I did feel bad but <trunc>anoth</trunc>another bit of me was thinking this is why I don't have a boyfriend</u>
<u n="364" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0411">because I can't put a man here</u>
<u n="366" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0411">because I've got so many other things so I was at work</u>
<u n="368" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0411">and he was going oh is it nice and sunny in <anon type="place"/>? or something like that and I was like yeah it's alright why?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0411">and he said oh it's quite it's it's nice in <anon type="place"/> it was nice in <anon type="place"/> earlier but now I'm back home</u>
<u n="372" who="S0417" trans="overlap">oh god he should've just said <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0411">and I just went oh right okay cool you know I was at work</u>
<u n="374" who="S0417">but you're only human <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0411">and I well I did think <anon type="place"/>? er but er for about an nth of a second</u>
<u n="376" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah is it? why? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0411">and then he texted me again in the evening</u>
<u n="378" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0411">saying something else and said oh I'm exhausted after a heavy day or <trunc>b</trunc>or busy day or something like that and then the penny dropped and then because by that time I was at home I was relaxed</u>
<u n="380" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0411"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was in bed so this is now like god knows how many hours later and then</u>
<u n="382" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0411">I just texted back saying I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="384" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0411">I felt awful really awful I was thinking a good girlfriend would've sent a text in the morning</u>
<u n="386" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0411">or the night before the thing is it had gone into my head the night before and I did nothing about it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0417"><unclear>cos this is</unclear> the thing that you probably all built up separately very <trunc>bu</trunc>busy lives</u>
<u n="389" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0417">and that is <trunc>a</trunc>actually is quite hard to kind of then just</u>
<u n="391" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0417">it's not like <unclear>if</unclear> people <unclear>being like</unclear> my my brother's been with his wife since they were you know twenty-nineteen or whatever</u>
<u n="393" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0417">and it's their er their first girlfriend and boyfriend and</u>
<u n="395" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0417"><unclear>you know</unclear> they live in each other's pockets and things but</u>
<u n="397" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0417">it's not like that is it?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0417">you have separate busy lives</u>
<u n="401" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0417">which are which fill your head enough <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0411">yeah completely yeah and he gets it he gets like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> never used to get it he he just didn't get it because he would drop everything</u>
<u n="404" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0411">and everyone and he had the kind of job where he could just not turn up in the office for god knows how long as long as he <trunc>w</trunc>was making all this money somehow and he didn't understand</u>
<u n="406" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0411">that I couldn't meet him for lunch</u>
<u n="408" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0411">he didn't get it but I couldn't</u>
<u n="410" who="S0417">yeah <unclear>he was a bit demanding that way</unclear> it seems like he wanted a mistress who was just on call for him</u>
<u n="411" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="412" who="S0417">and didn't have a life</u>
<u n="413" who="S0411">I know</u>
<u n="414" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0411">and it was just a bit like and he was like oh I'll have to break you of er this habit of being so diligent and it's like it's not being diligent it's called working <unclear>you fuckwit</unclear></u>
<u n="416" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it's my life I have to keep that roof over my head I've got dependents <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0411" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? it's like he's got no concept of you know and I'd be like oh I'm really tired he's like oh come on let's go out <unclear/> no I'm really tired</u>
<u n="418" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0411">oh <vocal desc="misc"/> no I'm really tired</u>
<u n="420" who="S0417"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0411">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0417">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0411">but with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you don't have to do any of that because he gets it he understands</u>
<u n="424" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0411">you know and we're trying to make a plan at the moment but he's always got a bloody family thing or a funeral or <vocal desc="yawn"/> there's always always something you know?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0411">but I like that</u>
<u n="428" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0411">you know even though it is a little bit like <vocal desc="sigh"/> a little bit</u>
<u n="430" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0411">I really really like it because it it is normal life that is normal life to prioritise your children</u>
<u n="432" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0411">prioritise your family have to get stuff done around the house</u>
<u n="434" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0411">have to like go on holiday with your kids or whatever good</u>
<u n="436" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0411">I'm glad you're doing that stuff</u>
<u n="438" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0411">that's what you're supposed to do you know?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0417">but do you think in the future? well I suppose you won't you don't know but that'll probably become a bit less for him and maybe a bit less for you and you might</u>
<u n="441" who="S0411" trans="overlap">might be but he's a grandad now</u>
<u n="442" who="S0417"><unclear/> oh right <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0411" trans="overlap">yeah so yeah so we'll see</u>
<u n="444" who="S0417" trans="overlap">god how how old's his grandchild?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0411">er he was born in January</u>
<u n="446" who="S0417">oh right so it's very new</u>
<u n="447" who="S0411">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0417">does that make you feel weird at all or anything?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0411">no not at all no I made lots of jokes about shagging a grandad</u>
<u n="450" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0411">you know and er things like</u>
<u n="452" who="S0417">and living with a grandad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0411">very occasionally if I'm texting him on a Sunday morning he'll get back to me Sunday afternoon and go I'm sorry I was having a nap or something like that</u>
<u n="454" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0417"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0411"><unclear/> grandads grandads need their naps you know?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0417">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0411">erm yeah like <unclear/> that's his life you know that's</u>
<u n="459" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0411">that's what he does you know?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0411">yeah it might become less it might not but I think because our entire relationship has been based on us being very very <trunc>sep</trunc> sometimes I don't see him for four or five weeks</u>
<u n="463" who="S0417">really?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0411">yeah yeah and it that's where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> steps in</u>
<u n="465" who="S0417" trans="overlap">do you miss him then? oh yeah how's things with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0411">sometimes I mean I don't see very much of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because he's now a personal trainer and you know so it's very hard to juggle them</u>
<u n="467" who="S0417" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0411">sometimes because they both are busy people</u>
<u n="469" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0411">but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I do miss him a little bit but <vocal desc="misc"/> that's alright you know that's okay</u>
<u n="471" who="S0417" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0411">that's the you know we have a conversation every single day it's highly highly unusual for us to go a day</u>
<u n="473" who="S0417" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0411">without a <trunc>conversa</trunc> if <unclear>we'd like <trunc>li</trunc></unclear> if we're gonna go a day if we're gonna go twenty-four hours without any kind of contact it's invariably</u>
<u n="475" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><unclear/> speaking on the phone?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0411">no no no always WhatsApp always WhatsApp</u>
<u n="477" who="S0417" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc>not just texting? okay</u>
<u n="478" who="S0411">there's er always a conversation going on</u>
<u n="479" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0411">always yeah cos I haven't got time if I'm with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the evenings</u>
<u n="481" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0411">I prioritise <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0411">I'm not gonna be on the phone you know <trunc>w</trunc>we'll text</u>
<u n="485" who="S0417">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0411">but it means er it can wait you know</u>
<u n="487" who="S0417">god you must be good on the old kind of do you do it all on your phone?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0411">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0417" trans="overlap">or on the computer? right</u>
<u n="490" who="S0411">yeah yeah no it's just a long-running backwards and forwards all the time always</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
