<text id="SVH7">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:32:24</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-02-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Dancing lessons, holidays, Old English, university work, TV shows, ageism, celebrities, friends, charities, the route for the journey, football, medicine, cars, LoveFilm, metric and imperial, song lyrics.</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0058"><pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> that's better</u>
<u n="2" who="S0179">what's better?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0058">some food</u>
<u n="4" who="S0179">oh good</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="5" who="S0058">I bet you anything my dad'll have that sandwich when we get there</u>
<u n="6" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0058">I bet you anything my dad'll have that sandwich when we get there</u>
<u n="8" who="S0179">why would he have that sandwich?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0058">well <pause dur="short"/> as in I assume we're not gonna use it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0179">eat it tomorrow as a snack</u>
<u n="11" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> fair enough <pause dur="short"/> if we want it he won't eat it</u>
<u n="12" who="S0179">why would he eat it?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0058">I really imagine him being like oo <pause dur="short"/> he's got something for well-travelled sandwiches</u>
<u n="14" who="S0179">why?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0058">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> when we used to do dancing shows you know he obviously used to take he had to take food for the whole day <pause dur="short"/> so loads of sandwiches basically <pause dur="short"/> and um</u>
<u n="16" who="S0179">the whole day?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um so when when I used to do shows we used to um you went in the morning on the day of the show <pause dur="short"/> and you rehearsed all day <pause dur="short"/> and then did the show on the night <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> it was actually quite good preparation for a sort of professional thing <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> far more so than just going along on the evening <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="18" who="S0179">why?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0058">Cos that's more what their days are like <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="20" who="S0179">so it's nothing like say in athletics where you don't wanna train before you</u>
<u n="21" who="S0058">well yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0179">compete</u>
<u n="23" who="S0058">I'm as I said it I was just thinking that <pause dur="short"/> like it seems like an odd thing to do <pause dur="short"/> but she <trunc>w</trunc> obviously found it worked <pause dur="short"/> but I mean</u>
<u n="24" who="S0179">perhaps she presumably got to charge for this?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0058">presumably got to?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0179">charge for the fact you were receiving instruction for all the way through the day</u>
<u n="27" who="S0058">no no</u>
<u n="28" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="29" who="S0058">um we were well <unclear/> we were er there was kind of the rehearsals up to that point had been so expensive that I think that the day of the show was sort of free <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="30" who="S0179">expensive? How much do dance lessons oh God cost per session?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember exactly <pause dur="short"/> I think when I left it was about six pounds an hour <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> which isn't bad</u>
<u n="32" who="S0179">how many in a class?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0058">it varied from upper <trunc>classe</trunc> upper level classes sort of it could be as few as sort of three or four <pause dur="short"/> lower level classes thirty <pause dur="short"/> and so for yeah for the show rehearsals you'd have to pay say for a fiver an hour for three hours a night four or five times a week <pause dur="short"/> and there'd be a hundred people there <pause dur="short"/> so that's not an insignificant amount of money <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um and you had to buy all your costumes and and stuff <pause dur="short"/> so I think it was sort of taken as reasonable <pause dur="short"/> but like yeah I had to get a day off school every time I did a show</u>
<u n="34" who="S0179">really?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0179">how on <trunc>ear</trunc> you earth were you allowed to do that?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0058">I think it was argued to be a sort of enriching experience</u>
<u n="38" who="S0179">oh I figured it was only going to be a recreational activity</u>
<u n="39" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0179">you shouldn't be allowed time off school</u>
<u n="41" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="42" who="S0179">like if I'd been a head teacher I wouldn't have allowed that</u>
<u n="43" who="S0058">but I mean sort of er like obviously</u>
<u n="44" who="S0179">why should you be allowed to do that but the</u>
<u n="45" who="S0058">no I'm not  I'm not  saying</u>
<u n="46" who="S0179">parents not be allowed to take kids on holiday?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0058">I'm not saying that was right <pause dur="short"/> I mean  I mean  I guess it was one day rather than</u>
<u n="48" who="S0179">yeah but it's one day repeatedly over the year</u>
<u n="49" who="S0058">not that many a year <pause dur="short"/> a couple of times a year <pause dur="short"/> wasn't like these were every month</u>
<u n="50" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> so you er miss five days of school in two years versus one one week holiday in two years</u>
<u n="51" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> you're probably right <pause dur="short"/> in all fairness <trunc>paren</trunc> in all fairness parents can take their kids out of school for holidays if they want to</u>
<u n="52" who="S0179">oo there's an interesting legal grey area</u>
<u n="53" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think if they just keep er</u>
<u n="54" who="S0179">Cos they are legally obliged to provide <unclear/> for a full education or at least access to a full education <pause dur="short"/> I think you could be arguing that's breaching their duty of care <pause dur="short"/> the school can't legally stop them</u>
<u n="55" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0179">but social services probably could</u>
<u n="57" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it would be a case of if you're doing it and it you know and it's not being it's not enough to be brought to the attention of anyone who has any power to do anything about it then <pause dur="short"/> whereas if it was every you know two weeks every term they'd probably say something <pause dur="short"/> but you can do it <pause dur="short"/> it's just the school doesn't like it <pause dur="long"/> Do you find at work that there's er that the office is a lot quieter during school holidays? mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0179">not really</u>
<u n="59" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0179">Cos most people's kids are still quite young</u>
<u n="61" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's interesting just</u>
<u n="62" who="S0179">but to be honest <unclear/> sort of four or five people are out of the office in the States or in Europe for <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="63" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fair enough <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just interesting that yeah ours does get noticeably quieter <pause dur="short"/> like into er sort of half term and summer holidays and stuff</u>
<u n="64" who="S0179">it's a very different type of office</u>
<u n="65" who="S0058">it is <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And probably a bigger variety of child ages</u>
<u n="66" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> and most of our office are men <pause dur="short"/> so my team excluded</u>
<u n="67" who="S0058">well <pause dur="short"/> my your yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but I mean</u>
<u n="68" who="S0179">obviously you have a massive <unclear/> majority of women <pause dur="short"/> and we have a massive</u>
<u n="69" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0179">majority of men</u>
<u n="71" who="S0058">I'm not sure it would make much difference though <pause dur="short"/> like I cos er</u>
<u n="72" who="S0179">of course it will because</u>
<u n="73" who="S0058">if you  if you  wanna go on holiday both of you would go</u>
<u n="74" who="S0179">yeah but there's holidays for mother</u>
<u n="75" who="S0058">from from a child-care perspective</u>
<u n="76" who="S0179">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="77" who="S0058">yeah from a childcare perspective the mother might do it I guess <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> the moon's really weird tonight</u>
<u n="78" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0058">the moon's really weird <pause dur="short"/> it's one of those ones where you can see like the the shape of it but <pause dur="short"/> actually you can't see much now but earlier you could see the shape of the the moon but then just the the light bits</u>
<u n="80" who="S0179">well that's gonna be an M and S lorry there</u>
<u n="81" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> aw</u>
<u n="82" who="S0179">oh yeah wow that's low</u>
<u n="83" who="S0058">what the moon? Yeah it's funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0179">I thought is that a reflection?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0179">no that's actually just the moon</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="87" who="S0058">are you er you can understand all the kind of I like thinking about like in the past when they didn't know what the sun and the moon were and the stars <pause dur="short"/> and you know how would you  how would you  see them? What would you say they were? I just think it's interesting <pause dur="short"/> how do you explain the moon getting bigger and getting smaller again? You know <pause dur="short"/> eclipses and what are stars and these lights in the sky? Like that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> so like in Old English um stars are sky-candles <pause dur="short"/> they're very keen on like compounds um sort of descriptive thing <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what they're called <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so like um a swan-road is the sea <pause dur="short"/> and yeah like they're er no sorry the sun is a sky-candle <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a nice nice image</u>
<u n="88" who="S0179">surely swan-road would be a river not</u>
<u n="89" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0179">the sea?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0058">I dunno why they call it a swan-road <pause dur="short"/> it's got and whale-road as well which er makes a bit more sense</u>
<u n="92" who="S0179">hm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0058">they're quite keen on those things <pause dur="short"/> really interesting</u>
<u n="94" who="S0179">what's the Old English word for swan?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0058">probably swan <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't remember exactly <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't be surprised if it was swan</u>
<u n="96" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0058">and road's probably rad <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Or rod <pause dur="short"/> or roden or something</u>
<u n="98" who="S0179">hm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="99" who="S0058">I was thinking the other thing I need to get while we're at <trunc>s</trunc> at my parents is my um my dissertation notes and stuff <pause dur="short"/> like um my hard notes</u>
<u n="100" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="101" who="S0058">um quite useful when I as I'm rewriting it</u>
<u n="102" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sure</u>
<u n="103" who="S0058">I'm er hoping to dig them out <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they're quite handy <pause dur="short"/> be on top of all the stuff <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0179">or they'll be hidden under something <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> There's a few things to er dig out <pause dur="short"/> I'm trying to think what er what to watch first on iPlayer <pause dur="short"/> there hasn't been anything sort of revolutionary on</u>
<u n="106" who="S0179">if there's a Top Gear on I'd like to watch some of that <unclear/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0058">there's always Top Gear on to be honest</u>
<u n="108" who="S0179">yeah but any new Top Gear <unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> true <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's always some on iPlayer but it's not necessarily new <pause dur="short"/> might be <pause dur="short"/> no er cos like things like Sherlock and you know really you wanna watch <pause dur="short"/> they're really good <pause dur="short"/> but there hasn't been anything at least nothing that I know of that's been that good <pause dur="short"/> I've been watching MasterChef at work though <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0179">masterChef?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0058">masterChef <pause dur="short"/> it's brilliant</u>
<u n="112" who="S0179">how is it brilliant?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0058">how is it brilliant?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0058">I dunno it's just really interesting and er kind of engaging in a weird way <pause dur="short"/> like so it starts off er they're the same every week <pause dur="short"/> it's really simple <pause dur="short"/> like they're er in this sort of big open kitchen thing <pause dur="short"/> and they all have a bench <pause dur="short"/> and there's some ingredients at the front of the room <pause dur="short"/> and they're told right you've got however many hours <pause dur="short"/> pick your ingredients and cook us something <pause dur="short"/> and it's just really fascinating to see what they come up with</u>
<u n="116" who="S0179">you see I like Ready Steady Cook cos it's quick and they don't know what they're gonna have to use</u>
<u n="117" who="S0058">yeah that is quite fun actually <pause dur="short"/> I do like Ready Steady Cook <pause dur="short"/> um thingy's annoying though <pause dur="short"/> what's his name?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="119" who="S0058">Ainsley Harriott</u>
<u n="120" who="S0179">I like him <pause dur="short"/> I do like him</u>
<u n="121" who="S0058">he's always er yeah he's quite fun <pause dur="short"/> he's er he's um <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0179">does he ever have holiday?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0058">sorry?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0179">just wondering if he er he ever has a holiday</u>
<u n="125" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0179">actually maybe they film more than one episode a day</u>
<u n="127" who="S0058">probably yeah <pause dur="short"/> they probably did like a block of however many <pause dur="short"/> the same audience would watch <pause dur="short"/> cos they're quite short <pause dur="short"/> you know they're only half an hour programmes or something aren't they? Cos they do the twenty minute long one and then a sort of five minute challenge</u>
<u n="128" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0058">so Ready Steady Cook there was er maybe they've had to change the format halfway through or something <pause dur="short"/> but um so there'd be like it took it was twenty minutes wasn't it that you got to do the main</u>
<u n="130" who="S0179">I thought it was half an hour</u>
<u n="131" who="S0058">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> maybe it was <pause dur="short"/> yeah maybe there was some different ones where they did it twenty minutes and five minutes</u>
<u n="132" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think the whole length of the programme's forty forty-five minutes</u>
<u n="133" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> fair enough <pause dur="short"/> yeah so they could film a few of those in a day <pause dur="short"/> most stuff they do like um quiz shows and stuff they film a few in a  in a  go <pause dur="short"/> er but the the people just change their clothes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0179">who changes their clothes?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0058">so like the presenter <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> so like Rob Brydon on Would I Lie to You? would just change his clothes</u>
<u n="136" who="S0179">ah right</u>
<u n="137" who="S0058">and you and you'd probably see um more there's er probably be more than one episode filmed with the same audience</u>
<u n="138" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="139" who="S0058">I think it probably depends on the show <pause dur="short"/> but so yeah I imagine</u>
<u n="140" who="S0179">I was gonna say Mock the Week they can't do that because it's topical</u>
<u n="141" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so like Have I Got News for You they couldn't do that <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but other stuff like QI they probably film a few in a go</u>
<u n="142" who="S0179">QI annoys me so much</u>
<u n="143" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0179">how is he thirty?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0058">what the one ahead?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0058">with cool lights</u>
<u n="148" who="S0179">do you not recognize those lights?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0058">I didn't but now you've said it I do</u>
<u n="150" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> it massively annoys me <pause dur="short"/> because Stephen Fry's smug face</u>
<u n="151" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0179">that man needs a beating</u>
<u n="153" who="S0058">I mean huh it's quite it's it's er it's I was just I was about to say it's quite interesting <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> it's alright <pause dur="short"/> it's I'm I don't enjoy it quite as much as I used to <pause dur="short"/> I think it's got a <trunc>b</trunc> a bit samey</u>
<u n="154" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> stephen Fry</u>
<u n="155" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0179">being smug <pause dur="short"/> as is the programme</u>
<u n="157" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean it was  it was  quite a fun format when it started <pause dur="short"/> but yeah they're quite a way into it now so actually it's not quite as much fun <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so MasterChef is now my quality slash rubbish somewhere in the middle TV of choice <pause dur="short"/> it's excellent</u>
<u n="158" who="S0179">did you see the thing about Rowan Atkinson? So you know that er Countryfile presenter filed a law suit against the BBC for age discrimination</u>
<u n="159" who="S0058">I was reading about this today <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0179">and that Rowan Atkinson wrote a letter to some news <trunc>r</trunc> radio chat</u>
<u n="161" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0179">show thing saying that this is disgusting and that it goes against artistic freedom</u>
<u n="163" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0179">it's like no</u>
<u n="165" who="S0058">not sure it does <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0179">because there's a difference between an employment contract and er</u>
<u n="167" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0179">she's not a performer <pause dur="short"/> she was a presenter <pause dur="short"/> there is a difference</u>
<u n="169" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0179">so she's not an actor <pause dur="short"/> she is someone whose job it is to <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit like cos er I'm trying to think  I'm trying to think  of a comparable example <pause dur="short"/> there's not many</u>
<u n="171" who="S0058">well in all fairness if he was told no you can't do any more films ever because you're too old he wouldn't like it <pause dur="short"/> he'd say that was discrimination</u>
<u n="172" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="173" who="S0058">I think he's just getting a bit</u>
<u n="174" who="S0179">no I <trunc>d</trunc> I can see his point <pause dur="short"/> but then again</u>
<u n="175" who="S0058">well</u>
<u n="176" who="S0179">this is someone who's done very well out of the industry</u>
<u n="177" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I can't er I I think he's right in the sense</u>
<u n="178" who="S0179">but it's not really the same industry <pause dur="short"/> it's er  it's er  as in a camera's pointed at him it's for a completely different context <unclear/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0058">I I think he's worried about comedy being unable to say things that are offensive</u>
<u n="180" who="S0179">no that's not what he was</u>
<u n="181" who="S0058">but</u>
<u n="182" who="S0179">going on about</u>
<u n="183" who="S0058">well er the article I read was er it was was saying that it's  it's part  part of his campaign about you can't have comedy without the right to offend <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> but that has to be</u>
<u n="185" who="S0058">so</u>
<u n="186" who="S0179">in moderation <pause dur="short"/> and that's what it's always been</u>
<u n="187" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I er yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0179">Rowan Atkinson is a bit of an interesting individual</u>
<u n="189" who="S0058">yeah er I</u>
<u n="190" who="S0179">this is a guy who totalled a McLaren F1 on dry clear roads</u>
<u n="191" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>g</trunc> the more I know about him the more I'm getting the impression that he's a bit of an interesting character</u>
<u n="192" who="S0179">as in he's <trunc>cl</trunc> he's very close friends with Jeremy Clarkson</u>
<u n="193" who="S0058">and Prince Charles</u>
<u n="194" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="195" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Interesting er dinner parties he must have</u>
<u n="196" who="S0179">well hang on <pause dur="short"/> yeah and er er cos Jeremy Clarkson's very good friends with David Cameron</u>
<u n="197" who="S0058">is he?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0058">bullingdon?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0179">so</u>
<u n="201" who="S0058">or is <trunc>J</trunc> is Clarkson Oxford or not?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="203" who="S0058">they're they're not Bullingdon are they? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can just imagine them getting together and braying loudly about the plebs <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Actually Clarkson's not particularly brayey <pause dur="short"/> he's not posh <pause dur="short"/> he's just just Clarkson <pause dur="short"/> but yeah Rowan Atkinson <pause dur="short"/> I was er</u>
<u n="204" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> as I say</u>
<u n="205" who="S0058">A bit odd</u>
<u n="206" who="S0179">I don't understand how he managed to do er <pause dur="short"/> someone who owns a McLaren F1 firstly to own it is a bit of an interesting judgement <pause dur="short"/> the car costs a million quid new</u>
<u n="207" who="S0058">fff</u>
<u n="208" who="S0179">it costs about two million now <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> alright fair enough you're a keen driver but and have the money but I do get the er it's only got one seat</u>
<u n="209" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh right</u>
<u n="210" who="S0179">Cos er the idea is you sit in the centre <pause dur="short"/> it's like a racing car</u>
<u n="211" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> hence why it's called the F1 presumably</u>
<u n="212" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> um the idea was it was as close as possible to driving a road car a racing car on the road</u>
<u n="213" who="S0058">on the road <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0179">and <unclear/> symbol from the nineties <pause dur="short"/> and there is a certain amount of well yes but</u>
<u n="215" who="S0058">hm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0179">yeah I I do just <trunc>c</trunc> like before you drive that I'd have a lot of advanced driving lessons <pause dur="short"/> and I bet he didn't <pause dur="short"/> and again it'd be very easy to drive</u>
<u n="217" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0179">fast on a track <pause dur="short"/> it's very different from being able to drive on a public road</u>
<u n="219" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe he'd had lots of Formula One style racing lessons <pause dur="short"/> hence figured it was the same</u>
<u n="220" who="S0179">but no I think he had it for years</u>
<u n="221" who="S0058">oh okay</u>
<u n="222" who="S0179">but again totalling a car like that that's quite an effort <pause dur="short"/> in the sense that although it's massively fast it's just got massively good brakes and very good steering</u>
<u n="223" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0179">traction</u>
<u n="225" who="S0058">so he'd really have to</u>
<u n="226" who="S0179">well no you'd have to be driving like a tit</u>
<u n="227" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0179">which wouldn't be difficult in a car like that</u>
<u n="229" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> more money than sense I guess</u>
<u n="230" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0058">more money than sense</u>
<u n="232" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0058">as in the people who can afford them really shouldn't be driving</u>
<u n="234" who="S0179">in a lot of cases <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I just</u>
<u n="236" who="S0179">Cos when you've got that money there's a very there's a certain lack of responsibility</u>
<u n="237" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just buy another one <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0179">well you can't really <pause dur="short"/> they don't make them</u>
<u n="239" who="S0058">well er yeah maybe <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0179">I suspect they'll try and repair it <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="241" who="S0058">but it's not it doesn't mean the same maybe <pause dur="short"/> and you don't need to worry too much about other people <pause dur="short"/> cos money <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> indeed <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and I think so that's a bit interesting <pause dur="short"/> but I felt that article was just really interesting because it was sort of <trunc>y</trunc> that's not she wasn't an artist <pause dur="short"/> she was a presenter</u>
<u n="243" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0179">that was her job <pause dur="short"/> and you</u>
<u n="245" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0179">and <trunc>emp</trunc> and that she was employed in a full-time contract and</u>
<u n="247" who="S0058">well yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0179">in that capacity you are entitled to legal protection against discrimination</u>
<u n="249" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0179">and er you <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="251" who="S0058">and it's right that you are</u>
<u n="252" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0058">I think is the key point</u>
<u n="254" who="S0179">and her age didn't compromise her ability to relay information</u>
<u n="255" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0179">to the public</u>
<u n="257" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think that's the critical thing</u>
<u n="258" who="S0179">um it made her and it didn't necessarily make her you know it it's I mean do you select employee er er presenter on accounts they're attractive to look at? Um you could argue there's a part of that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0179">but then well I think there's a difference again between selecting someone from a job and getting rid of them</u>
<u n="261" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0179">from that job</u>
<u n="263" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you've selected them and you can't really go right now you're past your best <pause dur="short"/> you just it doesn't really work like that in you know <pause dur="short"/> like you said it's er it didn't compromise her</u>
<u n="264" who="S0179">well</u>
<u n="265" who="S0058">ability to to have people tune in and watch her and convey the information and you know</u>
<u n="266" who="S0179">and let's face it who the hell watches Countryfile for the totty?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was a stupid decision anyway whatever way you look at it</u>
<u n="268" who="S0179">but she did make an interesting point <pause dur="short"/> there are very few old women in television</u>
<u n="269" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's true <pause dur="short"/> it is true <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="270" who="S0179">there's lots of er elderly men <pause dur="short"/> and I think that is a you know I'm er as a rule I think that for sort of sex discrimination cases that are well not that's not a fair comment but as a I'm massively against any sort of positive discrimination</u>
<u n="271" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="272" who="S0179">but on the other hand I think that's a situation that does perhaps need correcting <pause dur="short"/> as in  an in</u>
<u n="273" who="S0058">it needs correcting but not postively discriminated against <pause dur="short"/> but you</u>
<u n="274" who="S0179">no you <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="275" who="S0058">people who are capable and have been in the job a long time shouldn't be sacked cos they've over fifty or sixty <pause dur="short"/> it's not  It's not  right</u>
<u n="276" who="S0179">no this is  this is  probably because she was over forty in all fairness but</u>
<u n="277" who="S0058">well <pause dur="short"/> er I don't I</u>
<u n="278" who="S0179">uh</u>
<u n="279" who="S0058">to be honest I don't know who it was <pause dur="short"/> I didn't recognize the name or seen her <pause dur="short"/> I've never seen Countryfile <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> There wasn't a picture in the article I read <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="280" who="S0179">probably why <pause dur="short"/> she's too <trunc>o</trunc> unattractive to</u>
<u n="281" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0179">sell the paper</u>
<u n="283" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Too old to look at yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0179">however</u>
<u n="285" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0179">the um</u>
<u n="287" who="S0058">no I agree with you that it's it er it's <trunc>tr</trunc> it's true <pause dur="short"/> there aren't any women over a certain age <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it's you know</u>
<u n="288" who="S0179">whereas there's lots of men over a certain age</u>
<u n="289" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0179">um er Paxton <pause dur="short"/> clarkson <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="291" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0179">Parkinson <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="293" who="S0058">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0179">Jonathan Ross is pushing it a bit</u>
<u n="295" who="S0058">he's probably fifty</u>
<u n="296" who="S0179">the sooner he starts pushing daisies <unclear/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean a <trunc>l</trunc> um</u>
<u n="298" who="S0179">I do not like that man</u>
<u n="299" who="S0058">Jonathan Ross? No <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0179">I think he's very clever <pause dur="short"/> well no I think he's reasonably intelligent but</u>
<u n="301" who="S0058">I think he's done good stuff in the past <pause dur="short"/> but he's past it</u>
<u n="302" who="S0179">but that doesn't excuse</u>
<u n="303" who="S0058">no it doesn't excuse</u>
<u n="304" who="S0179">the Russell Brand incident was just on what like Russell Brand I can believe is stupid enough to have thought that was funny</u>
<u n="305" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um but then</u>
<u n="306" who="S0179">Jonathan Ross is er</u>
<u n="307" who="S0058">he did the honourable thing and went yeah that was actually really stupid <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna step down <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to be involved with the BBC anymore cos I did the wrong thing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0179">yeah oddly er yes probably because he realized his Hollywood career was just about to set off</u>
<u n="309" who="S0058">well <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="311" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="312" who="S0179">however</u>
<u n="313" who="S0058">but yeah Jonathan Ross you you can't believe he's quite that stupid</u>
<u n="314" who="S0179">no I er er he would've it with him it would've been calculated</u>
<u n="315" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="317" who="S0058">he thought it would be funnier <pause dur="short"/> that's that's a bad judgement <pause dur="short"/> that's not the kind of person I really wanna be watching</u>
<u n="318" who="S0179">no arguably it was very good judgement <pause dur="short"/> it got him a lot of notoriety</u>
<u n="319" who="S0058">well</u>
<u n="320" who="S0179">as er Jeremy Clarkson will tell you there is no such thing as bad publicity</u>
<u n="321" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well quite <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I'm not sure I wanna I er I don't have to like him even if it worked <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't respect that cleverness</u>
<u n="322" who="S0179">it's not particularly <trunc>cl</trunc> it's</u>
<u n="323" who="S0058">no but I</u>
<u n="324" who="S0179">cunning rather than clever</u>
<u n="325" who="S0058">I don't er yeah I don't respect that cunning <pause dur="short"/> if it was cunning <pause dur="short"/> whatever it was <pause dur="short"/> I just</u>
<u n="326" who="S0179">but I think Tim Minchin's attitude is just perfect</u>
<u n="327" who="S0058">he's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Have you ever seen</u>
<u n="328" who="S0179">bend over and raped with your own fist</u>
<u n="329" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah <pause dur="short"/> pretty much everything he does is genius</u>
<u n="330" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="331" who="S0058">the interview with him was really boring though <pause dur="short"/> the the Jonathan Ross interview</u>
<u n="332" who="S0179">why?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0058">well cos cos er he's just not because I think Tim Minchin is is quite a kind of</u>
<u n="334" who="S0179">reasonable normal guy</u>
<u n="335" who="S0058">a reasonable sensible normal quiet reserved quite private family man <pause dur="short"/> actually in real life</u>
<u n="336" who="S0179">despite the feet the make-up the er</u>
<u n="337" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but that's er that's very much a <trunc>pers</trunc> like a persona <pause dur="short"/> and he does appear without all of that</u>
<u n="338" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0058">but when he's performing as Tim Minchin the comedian he does it all <pause dur="short"/> which is fine <pause dur="short"/> er you know <pause dur="short"/> it's great <pause dur="short"/> but yeah er er I think</u>
<u n="340" who="S0179">so why did we lose the second lane? Jesus <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="341" who="S0058">seriously? One lane? Oh my goodness</u>
<u n="342" who="S0179">well it's light traffic and it's a fifty anyway so it's not gonna make too much difference to progress <pause dur="short"/> it's just er</u>
<u n="343" who="S0058">no no but it's just impressive <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0179">for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="345" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0179">get on and widen it already</u>
<u n="347" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0179">been like this for at least five years</u>
<u n="349" who="S0058">nice</u>
<u n="350" who="S0179">how it doesn't take that long to build a road</u>
<u n="351" who="S0058">hm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0179">or at least do it in stages</u>
<u n="353" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0179">do a <trunc>f</trunc> like ten miles of it rather than trying to do fifty miles</u>
<u n="355" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0179">thirty <pause dur="short"/> whatever it is <pause dur="short"/> I think it's about twenty-five actually</u>
<u n="357" who="S0058">hm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0179">leaving that aside</u>
<u n="359" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I did feel very sorry for um Andrew Sachs</u>
<u n="360" who="S0179">I don't understand how they weren't arrested</u>
<u n="361" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er well imagine if two guys two blokes two grown men had rung up my grandpa or your grandpa and said that about us <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0179">well it wouldn't have made wouldn't quite have worked with my grandpa</u>
<u n="363" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> but okay so somebody rung up my grandpa and said that about me or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> what would you have done? You'd have rung the police <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's not alright to do that <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> it was just beyond <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0179">and the best thing er was there was a lot of evidence cos it went out live</u>
<u n="365" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It was er it wasn't</u>
<u n="366" who="S0179">oh no it didn't</u>
<u n="367" who="S0058">live <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't</u>
<u n="368" who="S0179">that was the thing wasn't it</u>
<u n="369" who="S0058">that <trunc>w</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> somebody else um lost their job because of that <pause dur="short"/> well resigned because of that <pause dur="short"/> the person who the buck stopped with basically <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="370" who="S0179">the buck stopped with lots of people I suspect</u>
<u n="371" who="S0058">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think she was fairly high up and should've um you know she was the person who was the natural choice to sort of step down <pause dur="short"/> um but yeah that was quite bad <pause dur="short"/> you wonder which actual kind of normal employee whose job  whose job  it was to check those <pause dur="short"/> to let that go through</u>
<u n="372" who="S0179">that would've been the er the the producer of the programme</u>
<u n="373" who="S0058">but <trunc>d</trunc> er that's what I mean like</u>
<u n="374" who="S0179">whoever was in the sound booth at the time</u>
<u n="375" who="S0058">oh true <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> people let it go through</u>
<u n="376" who="S0179">though I imagine there wasn't much delay <trunc>betw</trunc> between it being made and it being broadcast <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be more than a few minutes</u>
<u n="377" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> I think it was <pause dur="short"/> it was maybe like two days <pause dur="short"/> I think it was</u>
<u n="378" who="S0179">wow</u>
<u n="379" who="S0058">yeah cos they they <trunc>ma</trunc> a lot of stuff they make a little bit early <pause dur="short"/> so the I think they made it on the Thursday <pause dur="short"/> and it went out on the Saturday <pause dur="short"/> that's what I mean <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't like an a sort of oh God what are we gonna do? Panic <pause dur="short"/> it was</u>
<u n="380" who="S0179">so people did actually sleep on it?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0058"><trunc>pe</trunc> yeah people heard this <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="382" who="S0179">but you'd think Andrew Sachs would've done something about it <pause dur="short"/> I mean they didn't speak to him did they? They left a message</u>
<u n="383" who="S0058">they left a message on his answerphone <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe he did <pause dur="short"/> maybe that I mean maybe he just sat back and said er I need to <trunc>s</trunc> I don't need to say anything <pause dur="short"/> er this is gonna you know and you know this is gonna go right for me <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> They're gonna get a better come-uppance if I just sit back and refuse to get you know refuse to rise to the bait <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0179">that's really annoying <pause dur="short"/> motorway signs on a</u>
<u n="385" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0179">dual <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="387" who="S0058">on this <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And I don't know much about Andrew Sachs either <pause dur="short"/> but he the impression I've got he seems like a nice fairly elderly gentleman <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I say fairly elderly <pause dur="short"/> a nice respectable Englishman <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0058">I kind of imagine him being a bit like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in real life <pause dur="short"/> slightly scandalous but nice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0179"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and who?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> um I er imagine Andrew Sachs being a bit like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0179">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0179">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Do you only hear the names together as a pair? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="397" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0179">can I have some water please?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="400" who="S0179">slow?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> How much slower?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0179">yeah we're losing a lane <pause dur="short"/> here</u>
<u n="403" who="S0058">wow</u>
<u n="404" who="S0179">that's a vehicle but it's still shutting down <pause dur="short"/> maybe not that one actually <pause dur="short"/> but even so <pause dur="short"/> christ</u>
<u n="405" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0179">go any slower we'd be dead</u>
<u n="407" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0179">well</u>
<u n="409" who="S0058">not quite <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0179"><unclear/> quite literally but still</u>
<u n="411" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> newsnight <trunc>Di</trunc> Jonathan Dimbleby the little <trunc>s</trunc> er man on TV <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos er I mean there was the Arlene Phillips thing</u>
<u n="412" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0058">on um Strictly Come Dancing <pause dur="short"/> there was a choreographer called Arlene Phillips who if you're into choreography is a bit of a legend <pause dur="short"/> like she did all kinds of stuff <pause dur="short"/> I think she did <trunc>S</trunc> the original Starlight Express <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> she's</u>
<u n="414" who="S0179">what's that?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0058">it's a musical <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> she did loads of West End musicals basically</u>
<u n="416" who="S0179">hang on <pause dur="short"/> we lose a lane? Having just gone up to a national</u>
<u n="417" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0179">that's</u>
<u n="419" who="S0058">that's interesting</u>
<u n="420" who="S0179">is that sign right? Surely not</u>
<u n="421" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> I would assume <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="422" who="S0179">Christ <pause dur="long"/> I do not believe this tortuous road work</u>
<u n="423" who="S0058">it is a bit mad</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="424" who="S0179">fine <pause dur="short"/> you've started to move</u>
<u n="425" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So was that lane sign only for that truck thing?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure the er the roadworks extended longer than this previously</u>
<u n="427" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="428" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos it was that truck that was putting the cones down</u>
<u n="429" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="430" who="S0179">Cos again we've hit the point of the evening where they're just starting to put them out</u>
<u n="431" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="432" who="S0179">you didn't text um</u>
<u n="433" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0179"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about the er <unclear/> did you?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0058">no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I forgot <pause dur="short"/> I'll I'll do that when we get back <pause dur="short"/> that's it'll take two minutes</u>
<u n="436" who="S0179">you can't reach</u>
<u n="437" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0179"><unclear/> two minutes</u>
<u n="439" who="S0058">I'll stand on a chair <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="440" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0058">I'll sit it on the bench</u>
<u n="442" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> stand on the bench</u>
<u n="443" who="S0058">stand on the bench</u>
<u n="444" who="S0179">slippage</u>
<u n="445" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Do it in bare feet</u>
<u n="446" who="S0179">lovely</u>
<u n="447" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And then anti-bac the bench <pause dur="short"/> I haven't had a text from her <pause dur="short"/> I normally have a text to say that she's been in</u>
<u n="448" who="S0179">maybe she found my gun</u>
<u n="449" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh dear <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You didn't leave it lying around?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0179">no it was in the drawer</u>
<u n="451" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0179">she's got no reason to go through those drawers</u>
<u n="453" who="S0058">no no</u>
<u n="454" who="S0179">but if she did find it then that's that's her</u>
<u n="455" who="S0058">she didn't really look <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> That does sound really bad <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0058">maybe she found the gun</u>
<u n="458" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0179">oh yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0058">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> joy <pause dur="long"/> <trunc>H</trunc> I haven't had any weird texts about keys and porters today</u>
<u n="462" who="S0179">hm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0058">I do wish I'd found out who she was <pause dur="short"/> I was kind of hoping when I texted back saying I'm sorry you've got the wrong number I was hoping she'd text me back and say oh sorry it's so and so from so and so</u>
<u n="464" who="S0179">you should have just said who are you and how do you have my number?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I should've done</u>
<u n="466" who="S0179">incidentally has it occurred to you that um I was just wondering whether we're gonna <trunc>g</trunc> get a text from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> whinging about how he's broken his arm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh I've broken my arm <pause dur="short"/> fML <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0179">what's FML?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0058">fuck my life</u>
<u n="470" who="S0179">never heard that</u>
<u n="471" who="S0058">have you not heard that before? It's like an internet thing <pause dur="short"/> so people tell sort of <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> like depressing stories <pause dur="short"/> um so like</u>
<u n="472" who="S0179">did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> invent this expression</u>
<u n="473" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0179">by any chance?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0058">no no</u>
<u n="476" who="S0179">it <trunc>d</trunc> does seem like a distinct possibility</u>
<u n="477" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0179">fourteen miles to Darlington <pause dur="short"/> six to Scotch Corner <pause dur="short"/> that's good cos there we will gain a motorway</u>
<u n="479" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> in <trunc>m</trunc> er to be honest I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will probably have a whale of a time <pause dur="short"/> he loves things like that <pause dur="short"/> he loves trips away where he doesn't have the normal responsibilities of life <pause dur="short"/> he had a great summer <pause dur="short"/> cos he went to Cameroon and then Canada <pause dur="short"/> and he you know the food is made <pause dur="short"/> the washing is done <pause dur="short"/> you don't need to worry about anything <pause dur="short"/> it's the normal routine that he worries about <pause dur="short"/> and yeah when you're on a skiing holiday you're not supposed to be doing anything else <pause dur="short"/> you're supposed to be on your skiing holiday <pause dur="short"/> there's no sort of other obligations to worry about <pause dur="short"/> so I think he'll have a whale of a time</u>
<u n="480" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> well and now he's joining an orchestra as well as a boat club and</u>
<u n="481" who="S0058">well I mean</u>
<u n="482" who="S0179">it's like for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="483" who="S0058">the thing is</u>
<u n="484" who="S0179">and a gym <pause dur="short"/> and a</u>
<u n="485" who="S0058">I mean the thing is I think they are things he wants to do <pause dur="short"/> I think he wants to be in an orchestra and and a boat club <pause dur="short"/> that's fine <pause dur="short"/> but you probably don't have time to do that and the EWB like er and er I don't think he wants to do EWB</u>
<u n="486" who="S0179">isn't it a bit creepy? Shouldn't he leave it to his undergraduates? The student <unclear/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0058">well he's he's he's got a  a he's  he's the professional network coordinator <pause dur="short"/> um yeah shall I um</u>
<u n="488" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0058">do you want number one?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0179">er yes please <pause dur="short"/> what's that job?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0058">um he he kind of er sends out information to the um the people who were interested as you know so kind of graduates who are interested if you like</u>
<u n="492" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="493" who="S0058">so er well no people who are in industry now</u>
<u n="494" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0058">working as engineers who still wanna be without borders <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0179">of course</u>
<u n="497" who="S0058">um do you wanna turn it on or shall I?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> er the thing that amuses me a little bit I dunno why <unclear/> is the the fact that they take themselves really seriously and act as if it's sort of M<trunc>de</trunc> Mdecins Sans Frontires except they're not <pause dur="short"/> they don't do anything like that <pause dur="short"/> they piss about and</u>
<u n="499" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0179">generally again they spend a lot of time training</u>
<u n="501" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0179">for things that are never <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="503" who="S0058">there seems to be a big focus on training and meetings and organization and hierarchy</u>
<u n="504" who="S0179">if they <trunc>s</trunc> if they spent a fraction of that time and energy earning extra got a part-time job earned some more money send that to a proper aid organization or let alone the government</u>
<u n="505" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0179">who actually do this sort of work properly</u>
<u n="507" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="508" who="S0179">Cos again the point about Mdecins Mdecins Sans Frontires is they go into very iffy situations</u>
<u n="509" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0179">so they they go before the WHO does <pause dur="short"/> they go into war zones</u>
<u n="511" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="512" who="S0179">they actually go they go in ahead of armed forces in some cases</u>
<u n="513" who="S0058">hence the Sans Frontires</u>
<u n="514" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> they really put themselves in a lot of danger</u>
<u n="515" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0179">engineers Without Borders don't <pause dur="short"/> they don't go into any er they don't do any</u>
<u n="517" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> it's got an entirely different</u>
<u n="518" who="S0179">they don't do any  disaster relief work <pause dur="short"/> at least not in the immediate short-term</u>
<u n="519" who="S0058">not <trunc>imme</trunc> not short-term <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> they do</u>
<u n="520" who="S0179">they might go in six months later</u>
<u n="521" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think the point er the the their sort of their purpose is that you teach people what how to do it themselves <pause dur="short"/> and you also teach them how to get the information themselves so they can stay up to date <pause dur="short"/> so that you don't need to go back</u>
<u n="522" who="S0179">yes but the point being that <unclear/> actually it's very patronizing</u>
<u n="523" who="S0058" trans="overlap">but yeah you can pay er one person to do that</u>
<u n="524" who="S0179">no no <pause dur="short"/> it's incredibly patronizing to say there are no engineers in Cameroon</u>
<u n="525" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="526" who="S0179">of course there are engineers in Cameroon <pause dur="short"/> who will do a lot more work a lot more effectively for a lot less money <pause dur="short"/> I E for the same amount of money particularly by the time you've flown out there you get a shitload more down</u>
<u n="527" who="S0058">no well they pay yeah they pay for their own ticket so they could've donated that money</u>
<u n="528" who="S0179">exactly <pause dur="short"/> it is essentially charity tourism <pause dur="short"/> it's a whole <unclear/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean er er</u>
<u n="530" who="S0179">it's just by a slightly more high moral ground <pause dur="short"/> hey it's a  it's a  bit like you know <unclear/> I have no I make absolutely no bones about the fact that <unclear/> I do with St John Ambulance <pause dur="short"/> I'm obviously doing it because I want to have fun doing it</u>
<u n="531" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0179">um <pause dur="short"/> it will benefit people <pause dur="short"/> I'm not denying that <pause dur="short"/> but that's not</u>
<u n="533" who="S0058">that's that's not why you're doing it <pause dur="short"/> it's it's I mean</u>
<u n="534" who="S0179">that's not the main role <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0058">but you're open about that</u>
<u n="536" who="S0179">but in this situation <trunc>i</trunc> there's no alternative which will benefit people more</u>
<u n="537" who="S0058">what by driving around?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's no</u>
<u n="539" who="S0058">really quickly</u>
<u n="540" who="S0179">there's no  sort I'm not <trunc>depr</trunc> I'm not doing a job that someone else could do better <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> for</u>
<u n="541" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0179">standards et cetera</u>
<u n="543" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0179">um <pause dur="short"/> and do you see what I mean? Whereas in this case it's no actually</u>
<u n="545" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> rather than students doing it <pause dur="short"/> english students</u>
<u n="546" who="S0179">english students? What?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0058">well English</u>
<u n="548" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="549" who="S0058">students from England <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Not er yeah not not students of the English language</u>
<u n="550" who="S0179">and again</u>
<u n="551" who="S0058">that would be useless <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0179">it's fascinating how sort of oh yes Cameroon it's like poverty stricken ain't it <pause dur="short"/> there's people who are homeless in this country who you could probably build houses for</u>
<u n="553" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0179">but that wouldn't be very glamorous would it? Objectively if you went round and er you know a group of engineers <pause dur="short"/> got a bit a of council wasteland <pause dur="short"/> little bit of easing planning permission</u>
<u n="555" who="S0058">hm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0179">got and <trunc>knoc</trunc> spend a couple of weeks knocking up a essentially a scout hut that is a homeless refuge</u>
<u n="557" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0179">which would do a lot more good for a lot less money really</u>
<u n="559" who="S0058">hm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0179">wouldn't it <pause dur="short"/> but it's very funny how people choose to</u>
<u n="561" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> They choose to</u>
<u n="562" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0058">to do things in exotic <trunc>locatio</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say exotic locations <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it wasn't very exotic but</u>
<u n="564" who="S0179">it is pretty exotic</u>
<u n="565" who="S0058">er <trunc>d</trunc> different places <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="566" who="S0179">Africa is exotic as a location</u>
<u n="567" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0179">but of course it's Africa it's poverty stricken <pause dur="short"/> therefore we feel good about ourselves cos we go and work in Africa</u>
<u n="569" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0179">again er this doesn't seem to be working terribly well</u>
<u n="571" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="572" who="S0179">do you wanna take it out and put it in again?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Nice <pause dur="short"/> I'd actually <trunc>su</trunc> <trunc>sugge</trunc> selected the wrong album anyway <pause dur="short"/> so hopefully that'll work a bit better <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> can you? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> there you are <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="574" who="S0179">ha</u>
<u n="575" who="S0058">I know <pause dur="short"/> ironic <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it's what what I mean the <trunc>m</trunc> the main thing is that I think it massively stresses <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out <pause dur="short"/> and I'm not sure he actually wants to do it or gets much enjoyment from it <pause dur="short"/> and I think it's ruining his life <pause dur="short"/> so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I figure he shouldn't do it <pause dur="short"/> and yeah I think cos he feels it's a more worthy hobby than or as he doesn't see it as a hobby <pause dur="short"/> he sees it as something worthy rather than um being in the orchestra or rowing <pause dur="short"/> can you turn it down a tiny bit? I'm struggling</u>
<u n="576" who="S0179">yeah I overcompensated cos I thought it was</u>
<u n="577" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0179">too quiet</u>
<u n="579" who="S0058">so yeah cos it's</u>
<u n="580" who="S0179"><unclear/> Newcastle <unclear/> thirty minutes <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll be there before half past nine so</u>
<u n="581" who="S0058">cool</u>
<u n="582" who="S0179">four and three-quarter hours sorry four and one-quarter hours <pause dur="short"/> that's not too bad</u>
<u n="583" who="S0058">not too bad considering</u>
<u n="584" who="S0179">considering the traffic that's pretty good</u>
<u n="585" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0179">I mean we were stationary for about five or ten minutes</u>
<u n="587" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="588" who="S0179"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But anyway</u>
<u n="589" who="S0058">yeah um yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just think he's gonna kind of you know melt down <pause dur="short"/> as he has done on many occasions in the past <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0179">wow</u>
<u n="591" who="S0058">wow</u>
<u n="592" who="S0179">I'm starting to dislike roadworks</u>
<u n="593" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You liked them before?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0179">well I was expecting those ones</u>
<u n="595" who="S0058">oh right</u>
<u n="596" who="S0179">so I was fine with it</u>
<u n="597" who="S0058">oo <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0179">but anyway <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0058">just it's a <trunc>sh</trunc> cos he er he keeps saying what I wanna do is I wanna go to work and I wanna come back and have my evenings just to enjoy myself <pause dur="short"/> and I'm like you're allowed <pause dur="short"/> it's okay <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to do things <pause dur="short"/> it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="600" who="S0179">Jesus <pause dur="short"/> pff</u>
<u n="601" who="S0058">oh my goodness me <pause dur="short"/> that saved him what? Ten metres? God</u>
<u n="602" who="S0179">Cos of the perspective thing that it hadn't occurred to me he was that</u>
<u n="603" who="S0058">like yeah how close he was <pause dur="short"/> oh my <trunc>goodne</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0179">what? Uh</u>
<u n="605" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> okay this is different <pause dur="short"/> presumably we're just gonna go back onto the</u>
<u n="606" who="S0179">this is er er no this is we're going to Darlington</u>
<u n="607" who="S0058">I know we are <pause dur="short"/> but the there wasn't another way to get onto the A1</u>
<u n="608" who="S0179">assume this is too late</u>
<u n="609" who="S0058">as in I assume we can just get straight back up again</u>
<u n="610" who="S0179">I'd like to think so <pause dur="short"/> god that was er just to see a lorry move that quickly</u>
<u n="611" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0179">to be honest I'm surprised the lorry didn't roll over</u>
<u n="613" who="S0058">I think if we are we basically on the A66?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> road atlas I think <pause dur="short"/> if we need to we can cut up to a road that goes up via Middlesbrough <pause dur="short"/> what do you call it? The A?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0058">a19</u>
<u n="616" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0179">as in that comes in somewhere round here doesn't it?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0058">I'm not sure to be honest</u>
<u n="620" who="S0179">A lot of good you are</u>
<u n="621" who="S0058">oh I'm sorry</u>
<u n="622" who="S0179">sorry? There's a motorway in a mile <pause dur="short"/> this is different <pause dur="short"/> there was no warning about that</u>
<u n="623" who="S0058">no that was really bad</u>
<u n="624" who="S0179">surely</u>
<u n="625" who="S0058">I don't er get where you were supposed to go</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="626" who="S0179">I'm sure we've just sort of inadvertently drove past that psychopath and I forgot <pause dur="short"/> should've been a bit more cautious <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> I assume we're gonna encounter diversion signs? Cos I'm gonna follow the A66 unless something else emerges</u>
<u n="627" who="S0058">yeah well er yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0179">so er this is <unclear/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0058">well er we will come to a roundabout</u>
<u n="630" who="S0179">I like unexpected <unclear/> driving like this</u>
<u n="631" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um <pause dur="short"/> we're gonna come to a roundabout <pause dur="short"/> um where</u>
<u n="632" who="S0179">yes I know <pause dur="short"/> those er roundabout signs gave that away <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0058">so yeah so if you wanna go straight over this one anyway <pause dur="short"/> um and then then it basically goes a bit woolly <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="634" who="S0179">well like I said I I assume there'll be</u>
<u n="635" who="S0058">we can stay on this road and then join the A19 <pause dur="short"/> we er basically we go um east straight across to Middlesbrough <pause dur="short"/> cos we kind of</u>
<u n="636" who="S0179">diverted traffic <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> we'll stick with that then cos we might be able to get just straight back up and back onto the A1 <pause dur="short"/> which would be better</u>
<u n="638" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="639" who="S0058">if we</u>
<u n="640" who="S0179">it arguably would be faster to go across to Middlesbrough</u>
<u n="641" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> in that case we wanna</u>
<u n="642" who="S0179">Cos if we're going <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="643" who="S0058">we</u>
<u n="644" who="S0179">so we're gonna go straight on here <pause dur="short"/> what's <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0058">so and then we're gonna er <trunc>g</trunc> there's another roundabout <pause dur="short"/> do you wanna stay on the A66? Even though the diversion's</u>
<u n="646" who="S0179">well</u>
<u n="647" who="S0058">different</u>
<u n="648" who="S0179">can you well can you look at the route and tell us where the diversion will go?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0058">er it depends</u>
<u n="650" who="S0179">which should be obvious</u>
<u n="651" who="S0058">it it depends yeah it's probably gonna take us straight sort of up and it will just miss that one junction of the motorway</u>
<u n="652" who="S0179">so the motorway has come down to a single carriageway road <pause dur="short"/> jesus <pause dur="short"/> whose fucking great idea was this?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0058">er yeah there was no warning at all about that <pause dur="short"/> that was daft</u>
<u n="654" who="S0179">I didn't plan on seeing Darlington tonight</u>
<u n="655" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> it's not unpleasant <pause dur="short"/> but you know <pause dur="short"/> um so yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's gonna be another roundabout and we can er either follow the diversion which is gonna be the second exit or we could take the third exit which is the A66 <pause dur="short"/> carry on on that whereas <trunc>j</trunc> and then that joins the um A19 at Middlesbrough</u>
<u n="656" who="S0179">are you confident you can navigate?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you'd rather do that</u>
<u n="658" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> let's do that</u>
<u n="659" who="S0058">and then the A19 then just goes up to the coast</u>
<u n="660" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> so we want the A66 <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> great <pause dur="short"/> I like this er <unclear/> anything else</u>
<u n="661" who="S0058">so yeah we want</u>
<u n="662" who="S0179">I like this part of the country you know <pause dur="short"/> I do like the architecture and the</u>
<u n="663" who="S0058">yeah so we want the third exit <pause dur="short"/> teeside A66</u>
<u n="664" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="665" who="S0058">that yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="666" who="S0179">of course a tiny proportion of these cars will actually be meaning to <vocal desc="laugh"/> go this way anyway</u>
<u n="667" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah so</u>
<u n="668" who="S0179">so not here</u>
<u n="669" who="S0058">not here <pause dur="short"/> the next one <pause dur="short"/> well that was an interesting diversion <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0179">we'll make our own diversion damn you</u>
<u n="671" who="S0058">well that takes them a really odd route for that diversion <pause dur="short"/> very strange</u>
<u n="672" who="S0179">yeah I think this one'll be quicker</u>
<u n="673" who="S0058">take them like back along a little B road <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah so now we we stay on this road <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> we're gonna come to another roundabout <pause dur="short"/> we go straight over <pause dur="short"/> actually er we're gonna go through another two roundabouts where we go straight over <pause dur="short"/> but it should be fairly obvious <pause dur="short"/> they it's the  it's the  kind of the major road goes right through</u>
<u n="674" who="S0179">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0058">um then we come to another one where we wanna go right <pause dur="short"/> which is the second exit <pause dur="short"/> it's a sort of T-junction roundabout</u>
<u n="676" who="S0179">okay then</u>
<u n="677" who="S0058">um but I'll give you a shout when we get closer to that</u>
<u n="678" who="S0179">sorry T-function roundabout?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0058">well so it's a roundabout but there's only two exits and <trunc>w</trunc> and one faces left and one faces right</u>
<u n="680" who="S0179">well I suggest we don't refer to it as a T-junction</u>
<u n="681" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="682" who="S0179">that's very confusing of you</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="683" who="S0058">it was nice being in a <trunc>w</trunc> in a sort of lit up bit like that <pause dur="short"/> I could see the map <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0179">yeah true</u>
<u n="685" who="S0058">we should get a little map torch <pause dur="short"/> or would that be too distracting?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0179">phone</u>
<u n="687" who="S0058">yeah no I'm I'm using it I'm not doing er I'm using my phone but it's just</u>
<u n="688" who="S0179">phones are perfect cos they're so low intensity light <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't distract the driver</u>
<u n="689" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say <pause dur="short"/> would a little torch be distracting? Potentially?</u>
<u n="690" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fair enough <pause dur="short"/> it fine like I <trunc>c</trunc> you know I can see enough for this <pause dur="short"/> it's just normally I'm selecting quite odd menu options <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0179">you're not gonna accidentally shine it in my eyes</u>
<u n="693" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0179">football stadium</u>
<u n="695" who="S0058">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0179">are Darlington FC Premier League?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> No they're not</u>
<u n="698" who="S0179">it's a big stadium for a shit team</u>
<u n="699" who="S0058">not that big <pause dur="short"/> yeah so it's straight over this one</u>
<u n="700" who="S0179">got that</u>
<u n="701" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But yeah er I told you it would be obvious <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Darlington Football Club <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what league Darlington are</u>
<u n="702" who="S0179">what league are Preston?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0058">Preston? Oh <pause dur="short"/> preston North End's mm can't remember</u>
<u n="704" who="S0179">there's two clubs in Preston?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0058">no no as in that that's just what they're called I think</u>
<u n="706" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="707" who="S0058">there might be two clubs <pause dur="short"/> but that's that's what they're called <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="long"/> Yeah but not not Premier League <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Do you wanna go to the match at some point?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0058">cool</u>
<u n="710" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0058">have to be a home match <pause dur="short"/> as in in Sunderland <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0179">why?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0058">um well if you wanna go and see Sunderland play</u>
<u n="714" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0058">so that you so you go as a supporter <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you need to be in the <pause dur="short"/> ah no we <trunc>cou</trunc>  we <trunc>cou</trunc>  yeah in all fairness we could buy away tickets <pause dur="short"/> but make sure you get Sunderland tickets <pause dur="short"/> cos the fans are segregated of course <pause dur="short"/> and you need to be in the right end for your team <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="717" who="S0058">otherwise it's a bit it's no it's not as much fun <pause dur="short"/> actually an away game would be good because the fans are really good <pause dur="short"/> no access to A66 East <pause dur="short"/> ah right <pause dur="short"/> that's where we wanna go <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> that's different</u>
<u n="718" who="S0179"><trunc>W</trunc> why is there no access to A66 East?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0058">er pff</u>
<u n="720" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> well quickly navigate</u>
<u n="721" who="S0058">yeah so the next roundabout we wanna go right instead <pause dur="short"/> sorry yeah <pause dur="short"/> at the next roundabout we're gonna go right <pause dur="short"/> which is the third exit <pause dur="short"/> instead of going straight over <pause dur="short"/> okay?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> how far's that roundabout?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0058">um <pause dur="short"/> not far along <pause dur="short"/> maybe a mile</u>
<u n="724" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> again information is good</u>
<u n="725" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> sure <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0179">you need to provide it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="727" who="S0058">I'm hoping that we'll be able to join the A66 at the next junction down</u>
<u n="728" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="729" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so we want the A67 here <pause dur="short"/> which is the third exit <pause dur="short"/> okay?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0179">what does that sign say?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0058">eastbound closed <pause dur="short"/> follow diversion <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> well yeah</u>
<u n="732" who="S0179">not er not another</u>
<u n="733" who="S0058">so it's taking us that way anyway</u>
<u n="734" who="S0179">fucking diversion</u>
<u n="735" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> what is it with them tonight? It might be best to follow this diversion because I don't know when the A66 opens again <pause dur="short"/> so um but <trunc>w</trunc> I'm gonna navigate and use the diversion and take whichever way I think's best</u>
<u n="736" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="737" who="S0058">and <trunc>t</trunc> and give you plenty of time <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0179">so they're going straight on anyway</u>
<u n="739" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0179">diversion is right</u>
<u n="741" who="S0058">so this is yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's here <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so we just carry along er nothing happens for ages anyway on this road</u>
<u n="742" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0058">maybe for um six miles <pause dur="short"/> I don't even think there's any roundabouts</u>
<u n="744" who="S0179">six miles?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we we it goes we're all almost all the way to Middlesbrough</u>
<u n="746" who="S0179">okay</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="747" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like I said we'll see where this diversion takes us and see <trunc>w</trunc> whether we can actually get onto the A66 at all <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> cos if we can't we won't go the way I was thinking</u>
<u n="748" who="S0179">so the A66 would've taken us to the A6? Is that it?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0058">no the er A19</u>
<u n="750" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> we had er one number which was a multiple of three in part of its name</u>
<u n="751" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0179">sh</u>
<u n="753" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Close enough <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> what more do you want?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0179">well between nought and twenty there are <trunc>s</trunc> one and twenty there are six possibilities <pause dur="short"/> I think I did quite well to get one of them</u>
<u n="755" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Not bad <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I love how er yeah we've gone from the A1M to the um er road a with cycle path down one side</u>
<u n="756" who="S0179">that's more entertaining</u>
<u n="757" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It is <pause dur="short"/> true <pause dur="short"/> oh right there is a roundabout <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> straight on here then <pause dur="short"/> oh yes there is a roundabout <pause dur="short"/> yes it's definitely straight on here <pause dur="short"/> tiny one</u>
<u n="758" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure the diversion will be straight on</u>
<u n="759" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="761" who="S0058">well er they er the you wouldn't the the other roads are just minor roads <pause dur="short"/> it wouldn't you wouldn't send us out there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="762" who="S0179">mental note <pause dur="short"/> this drive is a pain in the arse on a Friday</u>
<u n="763" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0179">hm</u>
<u n="765" who="S0058">is it is Friday a day when they do roadworks particularly? Or is it just?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0179">apparently so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> As in I I would've thought that would be a daft choice <pause dur="short"/> but maybe not</u>
<u n="768" who="S0179">again apparently so</u>
<u n="769" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Fair enough <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so er straight over here again <pause dur="long"/> There wasn't even a diversion sign there</u>
<u n="770" who="S0179">there was</u>
<u n="771" who="S0058">was there? Oh I missed that <pause dur="long"/> Okay <pause dur="short"/> on this  on this  road um when we come to it there's gonna be a junction</u>
<u n="772" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> why aren't you overtaking?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0058">rather than</u>
<u n="774" who="S0179">sorry <pause dur="short"/> what were you saying?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0058">um there's gonna be a junction which um there's a short stretch of A road which then take sort of maybe two miles which takes us to the A66 <pause dur="short"/> if the diversion doesn't take well that would be the way I'd navigate <pause dur="short"/> but if the  if the  diversion doesn't take us that way I'm not gonna go <pause dur="short"/> because it might not be open</u>
<u n="776" who="S0179">that's probably that road over there</u>
<u n="777" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah so it's straight over here again</u>
<u n="778" who="S0179">Durham Tees Valley Airport</u>
<u n="779" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0179">how many airports are there round here?</u>
<u n="781" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0179">sorry <pause dur="short"/> airports</u>
<u n="783" who="S0058">no <trunc>Tee</trunc> no <trunc>T</trunc> um Tees Valley's quite big</u>
<u n="784" who="S0179">big compared to Newcastle</u>
<u n="785" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No Newcastle Airport's big</u>
<u n="786" who="S0179">big compared to smaller than Luton <pause dur="short"/> it's smaller than Stansted</u>
<u n="787" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they're quite <trunc>bi</trunc> you know for the Northeast it's</u>
<u n="788" who="S0179">Luton's not very big</u>
<u n="789" who="S0058">no? Okay</u>
<u n="790" who="S0179">my parents live within five miles of the runway <pause dur="short"/> it's not very big</u>
<u n="791" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> fair enough <pause dur="long"/> Ah Teeside <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="792" who="S0179">so nearly at Middlesbrough?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh so</u>
<u n="794" who="S0179">rock on</u>
<u n="795" who="S0058">yeah we're coming up to Yarm and Egglescliffe are just sort of er outskirts of Middlesbrough</u>
<u n="796" who="S0179">no it's interesting <pause dur="short"/> get to see a bit more of the country</u>
<u n="797" who="S0058">that's true  That's true</u>
<u n="798" who="S0179">like expanding my horizons</u>
<u n="799" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Course the A19 goes straight past <anon type="place"/> where you've been</u>
<u n="800" who="S0179"><anon type="place"/>? Oh that's the nice north suburb</u>
<u n="801" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it <trunc>b</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> my auntie and uncle live in a nice bit of the not very nice north suburb of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="802" who="S0179"><unclear/> railway station</u>
<u n="803" who="S0058">that's really cool</u>
<u n="804" who="S0179">not quite sure who it's serving <pause dur="short"/> actually that might not even be a station</u>
<u n="805" who="S0058">er no I think it looks disused <pause dur="short"/> oh no there is a station round here <pause dur="short"/> in fact there's lots of little stations</u>
<u n="806" who="S0179">anyway <pause dur="short"/> so where were we er?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0058">it's the train line to Middlesbrough <pause dur="short"/> okay so um ah Stockton-on-Tees <pause dur="short"/> so yeah so like I said I'm gonna um base what we do next on what the diversion is <pause dur="short"/> because um yeah I don't know <trunc>wheth</trunc> when the A66 opens back up if at all <pause dur="short"/> if not we can just go straight onto the A19 <pause dur="short"/> it's just a slightly longer less you know it's er it's roads like this rather than <vocal desc="laugh"/> dual carriageway A66 <pause dur="short"/> so we'll see what the diversion says</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="808" who="S0179">this would be a lot better if we weren't behind Mr</u>
<u n="809" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0179">hopalong</u>
<u n="811" who="S0058">captain Slow</u>
<u n="812" who="S0179">no don't use that</u>
<u n="813" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh I'm sorry <pause dur="short"/>  James May</u>
<u n="814" who="S0179">this sounds like newer music somehow <pause dur="short"/> the other track the other album's</u>
<u n="815" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0179">a bit more classic <pause dur="short"/> this is</u>
<u n="817" who="S0058">it is yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's got like it's got The Killers on it <pause dur="short"/> so it's er kind of anthems in a newer sense <pause dur="short"/> not anthems in the sense of everyone knows them cos they're really old</u>
<u n="818" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh my eyes are getting tired</u>
<u n="819" who="S0058">well we're not  we're not  far away <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> We're in the right area of the country</u>
<u n="820" who="S0179">again long vehicles turning <pause dur="short"/> stop them</u>
<u n="821" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Don't let them <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Have rules about these things</u>
<u n="822" who="S0179">that <trunc>psychop</trunc></u>
<u n="823" who="S0058">diverted traffic straight ahead here <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0179">that that <trunc>ps</trunc> yeah like that psychopathic delivery driver <unclear/> Cambourne</u>
<u n="825" who="S0058">when?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0179">on the way to work yesterday</u>
<u n="827" who="S0058">I wasn't there</u>
<u n="828" who="S0179">yes you were</u>
<u n="829" who="S0058">oh him</u>
<u n="830" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="831" who="S0058">oh God yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Mad <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0179">I'm just making it up <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0058">no I thought you meant on your way to work</u>
<u n="834" who="S0179">in Cambourne?</u>
<u n="835" who="S0058">you do a bit of Cambourne <unclear/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0179">not exactly a busy bit</u>
<u n="837" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> fair enough</u>
<u n="838" who="S0179">well not exactly a</u>
<u n="839" who="S0058"></u>
<u n="840" who="S0179">indeed</u>
<u n="841" who="S0058">fewer lorries</u>
<u n="842" who="S0179">my back's been remarkably good</u>
<u n="843" who="S0058">maybe it was the the s= the sort of late afternoon swim sort of stretched it out</u>
<u n="844" who="S0179">oo there's an interesting idea <pause dur="short"/> you could</u>
<u n="845" who="S0058">so you could try that as a scientific experiment</u>
<u n="846" who="S0179">you <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="847" who="S0058">to see if that actually helps <pause dur="short"/> sort of really loosens it beforehand</u>
<u n="848" who="S0179">you'd have to do an awful <trunc>lar</trunc> <trunc>l</trunc> large sample size</u>
<u n="849" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0179">to get get er meaningful data <pause dur="short"/> you'd need five on each</u>
<u n="851" who="S0058">true <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh yeah but <trunc>s</trunc> still for a small</u>
<u n="852" who="S0179">how are we going this slowly?</u>
<u n="853" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0179">if it wasn't dark and unlit I'd be overtaking <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> know what we're expecting <pause dur="short"/> but we're on national speed limit for God's sakes</u>
<u n="855" who="S0058">do you think they're drunk and just being a bit cautious?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0179">no I just think they're shit</u>
<u n="857" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe they just don't haven't thought about it</u>
<u n="858" who="S0179">again er <unclear/> do anything that <unclear/> cause you to fail a driving test</u>
<u n="859" who="S0058">hm</u>
<u n="860" who="S0179">and it's not just I don't want to drive quickly</u>
<u n="861" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0179">it's er no it's unacceptable to drive this slowly</u>
<u n="863" who="S0058">so it's straight over this one yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="864" who="S0179">this is quite a long diversion</u>
<u n="865" who="S0058">it is</u>
<u n="866" who="S0179">what is it with diversions tonight?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0179">it seems to be the route of least resistance</u>
<u n="869" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Well we're nearly at the place where er it will sort of</u>
<u n="870" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0058">be sent one way or the other by the diversion</u>
<u n="872" who="S0179">if the A19's shut</u>
<u n="873" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> God <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Diversion <pause dur="short"/> get a boat</u>
<u n="874" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0179">swim</u>
<u n="876" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="877" who="S0179">turn <unclear/></u>
<u n="878" who="S0058">leave your car <pause dur="short"/> it's faster that way <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="879" who="S0179">diversion <pause dur="short"/> here's a pair of roller skates</u>
<u n="880" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0179"><unclear/> thirty</u>
<u n="883" who="S0058">oh right we're going through <anon type="place"/> apparently</u>
<u n="884" who="S0179">ah yes <pause dur="short"/> of course we're in a thirty</u>
<u n="885" who="S0058">so he's  so he's  doing forty</u>
<u n="886" who="S0179">so the car is speeding</u>
<u n="887" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="889" who="S0058">nice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0179">uh <pause dur="short"/> I apologize for that <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't expecting to go through a thirty prior to getting</u>
<u n="891" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0179">to Sunderland</u>
<u n="893" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Okay <pause dur="short"/> so um diversion is pointing us left <pause dur="short"/> which is good <pause dur="short"/> that means we can get back onto the A66</u>
<u n="894" who="S0179">oo Tesco's</u>
<u n="895" who="S0058">so er yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0179">for some reason I've got a real er hankering to go to that big Tesco's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0058">ah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0179">I bet everything everything would be very cheap up there <pause dur="short"/> so hang on <pause dur="short"/> here?</u>
<u n="899" who="S0058">yeah <trunc>l</trunc> left here yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0179">well there were sort of two lefts so</u>
<u n="901" who="S0058">oh sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="902" who="S0179">not entirely obvious which one</u>
<u n="903" who="S0058">well I I I assume that's the one the diversion one <pause dur="short"/> that junction wasn't a roundabout here so</u>
<u n="904" who="S0179">oh great</u>
<u n="905" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I assume it's new</u>
<u n="906" who="S0179">we needed a new map</u>
<u n="907" who="S0058">we needed a new map <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0179">again <pause dur="short"/> when we're sailing along the er <trunc>A</trunc> A1 that wouldn't be happening</u>
<u n="909" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Not so much <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> tend not to have pedestrians anyway</u>
<u n="910" who="S0179">this doesn't look <pause dur="short"/> marked for Life <pause dur="short"/> I assume that's a tattoo <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="911" who="S0058">that's a tattoo yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0179">that's not a good <unclear/></u>
<u n="913" who="S0058">that doesn't sound good <pause dur="short"/> that's not a that's like scarred for life</u>
<u n="914" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0058">wow <pause dur="short"/> this looks dire <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0179">outskirts of Middlesbrough right?</u>
<u n="917" who="S0058"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah which is a village on the outskirts of Middlesbrough <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0179">it's not a village</u>
<u n="919" who="S0058">well <pause dur="short"/> sort of settlement <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Whatever you might call it</u>
<u n="920" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0058">so yeah so now we're heading north through <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> um and yeah we're gonna join the A66 again</u>
<u n="922" who="S0179">oh that's interesting</u>
<u n="923" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> railway</u>
<u n="924" who="S0179">that's either a level crossing or a fire station <unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="925" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I know where we are <pause dur="short"/> we're not on the road I thought we were on <pause dur="short"/> but this is the way the diversion's going and because of that roundabout this isn't on this map <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="926" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> we're coming up to a roundabout</u>
<u n="927" who="S0058">so er straight over</u>
<u n="928" who="S0179">oh look logistics centre</u>
<u n="929" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0179">A K A lorry depot</u>
<u n="931" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0179">I'm enjoying this <pause dur="short"/> this is er unexpected</u>
<u n="933" who="S0058">it's different ain't it really <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought I'd have more fun doing this</u>
<u n="935" who="S0058">fair enough</u>
<u n="936" who="S0179">Cos most people would be getting stressed in this situation</u>
<u n="937" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Ironically it would've been faster just to go with the other diversion rather than trying to do the short-cut because of the second <vocal desc="laugh"/> diversion <pause dur="short"/> but it's not unpleasant</u>
<u n="938" who="S0179">well no we don't know that</u>
<u n="939" who="S0058">no no that's true <pause dur="short"/> we don't</u>
<u n="940" who="S0179">and this way we're seeing more of the country</u>
<u n="941" who="S0058">we are  we are  Seeing more of Teeside <pause dur="short"/> should be seen at least once <pause dur="short"/> once seen never forgotten</u>
<u n="942" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="943" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="944" who="S0179">seen at least once so you know to avoid it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="945" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Pretty much <pause dur="short"/> I love the way everything in um Teeside is called something to do with Durham</u>
<u n="946" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="947" who="S0058">because <vocal desc="laugh"/> Durham's quite scenic and quite historic</u>
<u n="948" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="949" who="S0058">Teeside's</u>
<u n="950" who="S0179">incidentally um <unclear/> and er who's er who while he was working for <unclear/> had a heart and lung transplant</u>
<u n="951" who="S0058">shit</u>
<u n="952" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> indeed <pause dur="short"/> um but so we're gonna rope him into help with the um</u>
<u n="953" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0179">oxygen supply thing</u>
<u n="955" who="S0058">oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="956" who="S0179">well</u>
<u n="957" who="S0058">you know about these things <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="958" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically</u>
<u n="959" who="S0058">God</u>
<u n="960" who="S0179">Cos prior to the operation he was carrying round</u>
<u n="961" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="962" who="S0179">an oxygen source</u>
<u n="963" who="S0058">so I <trunc>thou</trunc> I guess he'll know <pause dur="short"/> he'll have opinions on these things</u>
<u n="964" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="965" who="S0058">fair enough</u>
<u n="966" who="S0179">apparently it was cystic fibrosis or something</u>
<u n="967" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="968" who="S0179">but a heart and lung transplant <pause dur="short"/> that's like so the <trunc>signifi</trunc> your significant organs were someone else's</u>
<u n="969" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="970" who="S0179">that's impressive</u>
<u n="971" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="972" who="S0179">I just think it's <unclear/> medical science has evolved that far</u>
<u n="973" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that you can have <trunc>s</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> such a big part of you replaced and er fine <pause dur="short"/> it's awesome</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="974" who="S0179">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> right</u>
<u n="975" who="S0058">okay so when we reach it we're gonna go um gosh it's difficult I'm not sure yeah so we're gonna go over the top of the A66 I think <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="976" who="S0179">we'll join it</u>
<u n="977" who="S0058">and then join it yeah</u>
<u n="978" who="S0179">after a very short while</u>
<u n="979" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> for a very short period <pause dur="short"/> at which point we'll join the A19 <pause dur="short"/> um so maybe um six miles or so</u>
<u n="980" who="S0179">this er this whole area's quite weird <pause dur="short"/> there doesn't seem to be much countryside <pause dur="short"/> this actually seems to be a  seems to be a  smattering of small places</u>
<u n="981" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay so</u>
<u n="982" who="S0179"><unclear/> the country <pause dur="short"/> I'm assuming we go straight over</u>
<u n="983" who="S0058">straight over this one <pause dur="short"/> and then yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0179">and then right here</u>
<u n="985" who="S0058">and then this next one is right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0179">here?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0058">Middlesbrough A66 <pause dur="short"/> yes this is it <pause dur="short"/> ah this is quiet anyway <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Diversion ends <pause dur="short"/> thanks for that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="988" who="S0179">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> well it's <trunc>sh</trunc> it's been shut</u>
<u n="989" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Fair enough <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> We're first <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="990" who="S0179">hell yeah</u>
<u n="991" who="S0058">or last <pause dur="short"/> depending on which way you look at it <pause dur="short"/> interesting night for an open-top car</u>
<u n="992" who="S0179">it's not open well he's got the top closed</u>
<u n="993" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> has he?</u>
<u n="994" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="996" who="S0179"><unclear/> top</u>
<u n="997" who="S0058">oh okay</u>
<u n="998" who="S0179">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got</u>
<u n="999" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0179">which I believe you've been in</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0058">I have been in it <pause dur="short"/> it's really fun <pause dur="short"/> she took me to the station in it</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0179">with the top down?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1005" who="S0058">oh <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> no sorry not with the top down <pause dur="short"/> no no the top was up</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0179">I've never been in that car</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0058">it's fun <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's quite low <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1008" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0058">I did sort of sink down into it <pause dur="short"/> I had trouble getting out <pause dur="short"/> but there was room in the boot for my case <pause dur="short"/> so you know credit to it</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0179">that's probably why the roof was up</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> fair enough <pause dur="short"/> and it was also stupid o'clock in the morning <pause dur="short"/> bit nippy</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0179">was it?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0058">I say stupid o'clock <pause dur="short"/> eight o'clock <pause dur="short"/> which isn't actually that early</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0179">I thought you meant like two A M or something</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> This was when I was um leaving theirs <pause dur="short"/> and they were gonna bring all my stuff over <pause dur="short"/> but I was coming to yours with a suitcase <pause dur="short"/> which was gonna last me er the first few days in the house</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0179">oh so you went to <anon type="place"/> station?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> this was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> taking me from their house to <anon type="place"/> station so I could go to work then go straight to yours then straight to the house</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0058">and they they brought my stuff to the house later <pause dur="long"/> Ah <pause dur="short"/> that was a odd little while but it was nice</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0058">it was a odd little while living with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but it was nice</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> living with them?</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0179">yarm</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0058">yarm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Not Yarp <pause dur="short"/> yarm</u>
<u n="1028" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1029" who="S0058">it's got a very famous nightclub in Yarm called Tall Trees</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0058">it's got a very famous nightclub in Yarm called Tall Trees <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0179">oh you've actually heard of it? Right</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0058">yarm? Yeah yeah it's yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's <trunc>on</trunc> I've er I've only er I only know it because of Tall Trees and because um</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0179">wow <pause dur="short"/> look at that</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> talk about it <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty cool</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0179"></u>
<u n="1037" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> thornaby <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's where my old maths teacher er my A-level maths teacher lives</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0179">wow <pause dur="long"/> Yeah the conurbations round here are really weird <pause dur="short"/> cos there's loads of pretty big cities all linked by a fairly good dual carriageway network</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0179">which you just don't get in the South <pause dur="short"/> cos everything's round London which is linked by the M25</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0179">so there's not say a direct link between er St Albans and Hemel and Welwyn</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0179">or at least by dual carriageway A road</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0058">so the roads are all smaller?</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0179">yeah because it's</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0058">because</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0179">assumed you either want to go in or out of London or around London but</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0179">not directly between any of the other places</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0058">that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> whereas here because there isn't that really insane motorway</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> indeed</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0058">you just you need those roads <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1054" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1055" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Have you seen the um <trunc>Y</trunc> Vodafone Yoda adverts?</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0179"><trunc>W</trunc> we don't want to go there</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0058">no we don't want to go there <pause dur="short"/> we'll stay on here</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0179">Good navigation tip</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0058">sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0179">er anyway</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1062" who="S0179"><trunc>Y</trunc> Vodafone Yoda?</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0058">the so Yoda's in the new Vodafone adverts <pause dur="short"/> it's really funny <pause dur="short"/> so um there's a guy who's got two phones <pause dur="short"/> and Yoda's like ah I will transfer the contacts from one to the other with the power of my mind <pause dur="short"/> and he's like no no it's fine <pause dur="short"/> vodafone do that automatically Yoda <pause dur="short"/> and he was like oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I <trunc>c</trunc> I can tell I've listened to I've seen this without the sound on <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> This is <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0058">my my interpretation of what was happening <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0179">ah</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Okay so er now we wanna move over to the left <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0058">Cos apparently North and South are both this direction <pause dur="short"/> doesn't give you much warning does it</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0179">not a huge amount <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it's only a fifty though</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0058">true</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0179">wow that's er</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1074" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1075" who="S0058">and so we wanna go North</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0179">oh I could use a pizza now actually</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1078" who="S0179">I'm assuming that's er ah <pause dur="short"/> oh?</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0058">um <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> North <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> They really need more signs <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> they really do <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0058">oh yeah have you been on this</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0179">cool</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0058">before bit before?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0058">oh no this is really</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0179">awesome</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0058">have you not been? Yeah this is really cool <pause dur="short"/> um yeah my dad was driving along this when it was windy that time <pause dur="short"/> you know there was the horrendous gales?</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0179">sorry</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0058">that's alright</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0179">didn't occur to me that was a give way <pause dur="short"/> that's not a give way line</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0179">as in that is a give way line but you need that's a give way line</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0179">Jesus that was frightening <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say hang on where's the feed in line?</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hang on</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0179">fuck</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1098" who="S0179">that's appallingly marked</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0058">yeah that whole spit was just shocking <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You need to know where you're going otherwise you're screwed <pause dur="short"/> yeah so this is the A19 <pause dur="short"/> the really cool bit</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0058">and this is Middlesbrough</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0179">I have been over this bit before but it was specifically where it <trunc>ri</trunc> that bit's rising up to it</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0179">which is quite cool <pause dur="short"/> so what a stupid place to put a junction</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0179">you could probably give your parents a ring and tell them we're in Middlesbrough <unclear/> North</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> are you?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0179">how long does it normally take from here?</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0058">um <pause dur="short"/> er my dad's normally driving</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um I I'm not to be honest I'm not actually sure <pause dur="short"/> about half an hour? But</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0179">oh great</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0058">but like he's <trunc>d</trunc> does drive considerably slower <pause dur="short"/> so er I can give them a ring and just say er they'll know exactly where we are</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0058">should I do that? Yeah?</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0179">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> go for it</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0058">can I just turn this off? Do you mind?</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1119" who="S0058">hello <pause dur="short"/> it's me <pause dur="short"/> um we've just er gone um round Middlesbrough on the A19 <pause dur="short"/> there was a few <vocal desc="laugh"/> diversions <pause dur="short"/> um so yeah so we've just gone round the raised bit <pause dur="short"/> you know where I mean? Yeah? Yeah maybe slightly less</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0179">over the raised bit <pause dur="short"/> over</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0058">okay then <pause dur="short"/> well um um yeah if you put them in that'd be good <pause dur="short"/> um  um not  not for you know um don't put them in straight away but um I dunno well but yeah we'll be</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0179">Don't like them overcooked</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0058">we'll be um yeah maybe slightly less than half an hour <pause dur="short"/> okay then <pause dur="short"/> see you soon <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> bye</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0179"><unclear/> you relay what I'm saying</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0058">no but I was as</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0179">as in don't tell</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0058">what you don't like them overcooked?</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can just imagine your mother nuking a pizza</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0058">I've said don't put them in straight away <pause dur="short"/> and we'll be quicker than she thinks anyway so</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0179">but nonetheless can I just say could you</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0179">please relay what I've said</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0058">sorry I <trunc>d</trunc> didn't know you I didn't know you <trunc>w</trunc> wanted me to <trunc>s</trunc> to to say that</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0179">no I'm just speaking for the sake of it <pause dur="short"/> of course I want you to relay what I'm saying</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0179">or at least take not relay it but take it into account and supply <unclear/></u>
<u n="1137" who="S0058">I did I <trunc>s</trunc> said don't put them in straight away <pause dur="short"/> obviously <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah that was fun <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Twenty-two to Sunderland</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0179">that'll be to the centre</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0179">so we'll make it in twenty minutes or less</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0058">cool</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0179">is this er a pizza delivery?</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0058">sorry?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1145" who="S0058">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1146" who="S0179">I'm extremely tired</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0058">nearly back now <pause dur="short"/> this is the easy bit</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0179">no this is more difficult when your eyes are this tired</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> we should watch that film <pause dur="short"/> the one with the um</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0179">yeah I want to</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0058">yeah we'll er <trunc>f</trunc> try and find it <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be awesome when we can just go fancy watching that film with the pizza delivery guy? Oh yeah let's just go and watch it</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0179">yeah I'm very tired <pause dur="short"/> I'm starting to make mistakes</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0058">so er do you I mean do you think signing up for that LoveFilm thing's worth it? Do you think that'd be a good idea?</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0179">as soon as we get internet <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah no that would be <trunc>d</trunc> I'm not suggesting we sign up for it now</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0179">but if we buy one <trunc>f</trunc> new film at fifteen quid a month that's</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0179">exactly the same thing</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0179">so we'll only buy stuff that we've watched and really like</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> that you wanna watch over and over again <pause dur="short"/> and yeah er so we can try things for the first time on LoveFilm and then</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0058">buy them if they're amazing</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0179">is that that park place <unclear/> shopping centre?</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0058">um the park place?</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0179">oh no it's services <pause dur="short"/> darlington park <trunc>whateve</trunc> no</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0058">oh Herrington <pause dur="short"/> no no no</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0058">no no <pause dur="short"/> that's um that's <unclear/> that's kind of in Sunderland</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0179">that's not in Sunderland</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0058">herrington Country Park?</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0179">no you pillock <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>s</trunc> outlet store</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0058">oh Dalton Park</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1175" who="S0058">oh no no that's in <unclear/> that's um the other direction</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0179">no it's not</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0058">oh no <pause dur="short"/> it's er it's much further north though than this</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0179">I don't believe you sometimes <pause dur="short"/> more specifically I don't believe I let you navigate</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0058">I if I'm  if I'm if I'm  looking at a map and I've found it and then I'd tell you where it was</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0179">yes but just the fact you fundamentally don't know it's in the same direction as Middlesbrough <pause dur="short"/> christ</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> it's twenty miles</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0179">no it's twenty miles five hundred er five hundred yards ago</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> so twenty miles less five hundred yards</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0058">bit more now</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0179">less one thousand yards <pause dur="short"/> keep it up</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0058">how come <trunc>roa</trunc> road signs are still in miles even though everything else has been sort of metrics?</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0179">everything else hasn't been <pause dur="short"/> er a lot of stuff's still in er imperial <pause dur="short"/> er speeds for example</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0179">but er fundamentally they're just a better unit to measure speed and distance in</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0179"><unclear/> used to and it's it's a bigger unit</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it makes more sense</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0179">it is quite useful having both</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0058">Cos I mean like in a lot of countries they measure it in kilometres I guess <pause dur="short"/> and KPH would be the car's measurements <pause dur="short"/> speeds wise</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> but it's quite easy cos you have sort of thirty forty fifty-sixty</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0179">they're very nice speeds <unclear/></u>
<u n="1199" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0179">like sixty miles an hour <unclear/> to a mile a minute <pause dur="short"/> which is</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice to work it out</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0179">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> so you've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="1203" who="S0058">and I think like when we were used to other stuff before they changed it though <pause dur="short"/> like we'd have been used to the old system of weighing things <pause dur="short"/> and you could've said ah well I think people are just intrinsically used to it <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0179">no but I mean because a mile's bigger I think it's a better unit</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no fair enough <pause dur="short"/> I'm just curious cos so much other stuff's been sort of switched over <pause dur="short"/> and like you're not allowed to sell um er you're not allowed to exclusively sell things in imperial units in shops <pause dur="short"/> like food wise</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0179">no it's er the European regulation <unclear/></u>
<u n="1207" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm just curious about why sort of roads <pause dur="short"/> presumably because it's to do with selling between countries and stuff <pause dur="short"/> whereas miles on the road doesn't really affect the other European countries</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0179">well <unclear/> you can still sell stuff in imperial <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0058">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you'd have to have the metric on as well</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0179">no you <pause dur="short"/> would you er just shut up and let me finish what I'm saying</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0058">I'm sorry</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0179">no you don't <pause dur="short"/> if you look at in shops possibly <pause dur="short"/> but a lot of technical steels are still sold in half inch thickness for example</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0058">oh okay</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0179">which is to twelve point five four mil <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0179">it's</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0058">that's interesting</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0179">yeah it's er inches are still in engineering it's still in very common usage <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> pSI as a unit of pressure for example <pause dur="short"/> pounds per square inch</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0058">interesting <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's just sort of yeah <pause dur="short"/> I dunno really <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know why that would be different <pause dur="short"/> cos cos you can't sell food without the metric thing on <pause dur="short"/> because there was a guy in Sunderland like had a massive court battle about it <pause dur="short"/> cos he wanted to keep selling apples in pounds or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and they said no you've gotta have metric on your signs</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0179">incidentally er this was the right choice <pause dur="short"/> this is a much quieter much nicer road</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0058">hm <pause dur="short"/> fair enough</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0179">but a diverted randomly diverted and traffic worked</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0179">road worked er A1M would've been</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I wouldn't say this was an American anthem</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0179">isn't it English?</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> they're American <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um I'm sort of er</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0179">who are they?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0058">the <trunc>K</trunc> The Killers</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0179">are they? Oh I always thought they were English</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0058">how do I you oh no no they're American <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I only know that cos I've read <vocal desc="laugh"/> lots <unclear/> Um and Rufus um wrote a song about Brandon Flowers</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0179">is Rufus Wainwright English or American?</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0058">american <pause dur="short"/> well Canadian <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um and spends a lot I think he lives in America but he's Canadian by birth</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1234" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> um I'm not gonna be exactly sure which junction it is to come off at <pause dur="short"/> so you are gonna have to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1235" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll um <pause dur="long"/> Yeah so we come off um we'd normally um go kind of over this road where we come off at the Durham services</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0179">yes I know</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> come off there</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0179">I do actually this road layout pretty well</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0058">I know <pause dur="short"/> I'll um yeah I'll give you a shout</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0179">I'm just not exactly sure coming at it from this perspective</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0179">oh great</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0058">he's got a cap on</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0179">of course he has</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0058">bad sign</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0179">that's why we need to get past him <pause dur="short"/> because of his er interesting indications</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I love the name <unclear/> Such a good place name</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0179">that song annoys me <unclear/> completely meaningless</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0058">what?</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0179"><unclear/> stupid play on words</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0058">I've Got Soul But I'm Not a Soldier?</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it just sounds like it's meant as a political statement <pause dur="short"/> it's er no</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It <trunc>s</trunc> sounds good <pause dur="short"/> it's easy to sing <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure this bit particularly means very much</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0179">I don't think any of this song means anything</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but still</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0179">that's why I quite like Nickelback songs actually <pause dur="short"/> they're they are I mean the lyrics are very good <pause dur="short"/> they always tell a narrative <pause dur="short"/> they're <trunc>n</trunc> there's nothing just there for its own sake</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I I'm kind of torn about this <pause dur="short"/> because on the one hand I'm like does it really matter if they don't mean er like Idlewild a lot of the lyrics don't really mean anything and it's more about er the way they sound when he sings them <pause dur="short"/> so he sings kind of words round and round quite a lot</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0179">but surely a song should be about something?</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0058">well exactly <pause dur="short"/> I'm sort of torn about whether it needs to be or not</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0179">even if you're just for each person like <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think a song that has associations for a person depending on where they might have heard it <pause dur="short"/> and er what it's about for that person may not be what the song</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0179">is meant to be about <pause dur="short"/> but it should still mean something specific <pause dur="short"/> it shouldn't just be a</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0058">but</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0179">random sequence of sounds</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0058">but is it about the words or is it is <trunc>t</trunc> can the sounds themselves mean something <trunc>e</trunc> and the sort of the sound of the words even if the sense of the words doesn't?</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0179">yeah but you can't just fill it with random words</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0058">no no <pause dur="short"/> I don't mean that <pause dur="short"/> I just mean so you have an instrumental piece of music <pause dur="short"/> can that mean something to you? Even if it doesn't have a story or words</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0058">so</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0179">but that they don't try to put <unclear/> random words into it <pause dur="short"/> that's the point <pause dur="short"/> I've no problem with with no words in it having meaning <pause dur="short"/> but I have a problem with</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> but so</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0179">a song having meaning but in order to sell it they've felt the need to add words</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1274" who="S0179">that don't make much sense with it</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> so if if but if it was a piece of music and you <trunc>o</trunc> and it was just yeah yeah yeah over and over again <pause dur="short"/> there was no other word in it <pause dur="short"/> that would basically be an instrumental</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0179">no it wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> because you've randomly inserted a meaningless word</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0058">but if it's</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1279" who="S0058">to do with the note that that sound is that that <trunc>s</trunc> word is sung at <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0179">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="1281" who="S0058">it's kind of a grey area <pause dur="short"/> er I <trunc>j</trunc> just think it's a grey area <pause dur="short"/> and yeah it doesn't mean anything anyway <pause dur="short"/> it's just a song</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0179">Peterlee</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's your spiritual home</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> business premises <pause dur="short"/> no it's not</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0058">what <unclear/> business premises?</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0179">right twelve miles out <pause dur="short"/> be there in ten minutes or so</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0058">yep</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0179">it's gonna have been about four and three-quarter hours <pause dur="short"/> which isn't bad by any measure</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Considering the diversions we've been on <pause dur="short"/> kind of tour of scenic Teeside</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0179">well <unclear/> for nearly five hours and I've been at work for eight</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1292" who="S0179">it's been quite a tiring day</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> looking forward to crashing out tonight I think</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0179">what are you talking about? You've been sitting there doing fuck all</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0058">sorry you must be looking forward to crashing out tonight I think</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1298" who="S0179"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1299" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You love it</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0179">well I just don't know why there is actually a place in er Tyne and Wear called Pity Me</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's excellent <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> There's Pity Me <pause dur="short"/> there's um what's the other good one? I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> but er there's some classic names</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0179">suck me off ville?</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No er I had a friend who lived in Pity Me though</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0179">of course you did</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1305" who="S0058">ah Hyundai <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's the my only association with Hyundai is now the Tim Minchin song <pause dur="short"/> where he um <trunc>i</trunc> if he really loves me um you'd er I can't remember the first bit <pause dur="short"/> so you get a load of um you'd get a load of parakeets and teach them to fly <pause dur="short"/> and teach them to shit the words Tim is God on my ex-girlfriend's Hyundai <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Just such a good rhyme</u>
<u n="1306" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1307" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> love Tim Minchin</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0179">I wonder if you could do that?</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0058">quite difficult <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1310" who="S0179">I know but birds some birds are quite intelligent <unclear/></u>
<u n="1311" who="S0058">yeah but you'd need all of them to be intelligent <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1312" who="S0179">no you <trunc>d</trunc> oh yeah formation shitting yes</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Quite tricky <pause dur="short"/> okay so maybe eight miles to our junction <pause dur="short"/> so it's not far now</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0179">how do you know that?</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0058">Cos I've just seen which junction we're at <pause dur="short"/> and I'm gonna and <unclear/> you know counted the inches</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0179">I suspect we're less than eight miles out to be honest</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0058">okay</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1318" who="S0179">plus it the sign said twelve a mile or so ago <pause dur="short"/> and that's to Sunderland centre <pause dur="short"/> which is a couple of miles in <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> maybe slightly less then <pause dur="short"/> maybe six to the junction <pause dur="long"/>  Oh yeah so that reckoned eight miles to Sunderland <pause dur="short"/> it was good when we did it from um from the A1 and it was exactly the right distance from there to my house</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0058">um on the signs</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1322" who="S0179">well looking at a map of Sunderland you could argue that <unclear/> sort of area <unclear/> centre</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1325" who="S0058">it depends what you count er um as ever <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0179">well no <pause dur="short"/> like I said <unclear/> Sunderland <unclear/></u>
<u n="1327" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> probably <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/> where I've heard this song before <pause dur="short"/> um Mel C did a cover of it in the early millennium <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't know it was a cover <pause dur="short"/> which is why I was quite surprised to hear Mel C on this album</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0058">it's definitely not <pause dur="short"/> she was Sporty Spice <pause dur="short"/> definitely not her <unclear/></u>
<u n="1330" who="S0179">is this the original?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this is the original one</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0058">oo <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1334" who="S0179">well <unclear/> road</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0058">hm?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1336" who="S0179"><unclear/> down we can experiment and try following this down as far as the A1M</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> could do <pause dur="short"/> might be different <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1338" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0058">and that would of course be simpler because we wouldn't need to mess about going through the middle of Teeside</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0179">oh yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="1341" who="S0058">as in we wouldn't be</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0179"><unclear/> is this our exit?</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> yeah <unclear/> No ours is the one after this one <pause dur="short"/> which is about four miles after it <pause dur="short"/> could be slightly less <unclear/></u>
<u n="1344" who="S0179">funshack</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's the most fun you can have in a shack <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1346" who="S0179">funshack</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0058">it's fun for a shack <pause dur="short"/> I've got no idea what Funshack is <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1348" who="S0179">let's google it</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> let's not <pause dur="short"/> you might get <unclear/> results <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> Okay <pause dur="short"/> so the next exit's gonna be for the A690 <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> which should be signposted some point <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and that's the one that's the the road that comes out from Durham</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0179">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> just stop navigating now <pause dur="short"/> that's fine</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0058">are you sure?</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0179">sure <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1353" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Wow <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1354" who="S0179">Don't wanna see Sunderland that brightly lit up</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1356" who="S0179">this road's still fairly quiet</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0058">yeah it's really pleasant</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0179"><unclear/> I like driving <pause dur="short"/> I just like being <trunc>ou</trunc> I just like being out and getting about</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0179">seeing places</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0179">Cos my major gripe at work really is that I do feel to a certain extent trapped in one location <pause dur="short"/> like I'm er missing the wonderful day by being inside an office</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1364" who="S0179">as in</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0058">but I guess that's</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0179">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's still far more freedom to get about <unclear/> than I ever would've done sort of <pause dur="short"/> but the problem is I <trunc>f</trunc> I almost feel like I feel like I'm not at uni doing work therefore I feel like it's working the holiday which is therefore depriving me from doing holiday things</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0179">slightly different mindset</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0179">whereas my gap year just felt like a prison sentence <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1372" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1373" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0179">what were you saying?</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0058">um <pause dur="short"/> I mean I guess at least with your job you're kind of in one place <pause dur="short"/> and you're <unclear/> work and you don't see the day and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but then sometimes you get sent off to nice places</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0179">occasionally <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0058">which is you know it's kind of a perk</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1379" who="S0058">that a lot of jobs don't have <pause dur="short"/> like I'm not gonna get sent off anywhere for quite some years <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> that just ain't happening</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1381" who="S0058">you know <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0179">that Sunderland South exit was a long way of so they didn't cos</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0058">it</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0179">that was Sunderland North straight on <pause dur="short"/> but in fact it's Sunderland middle</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0179">and Sunderland North</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0058">middle and North <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0179">that's like Cambridge is with three motorways</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0179">it's actually Cambridge has kind of got four <pause dur="short"/> well no <pause dur="short"/> it's got two two of those four are only unidirectional <pause dur="short"/> so  in opposite directions</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0179">so that kind of just leaves three</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0179">actually one of them's not</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0058">half a mile to our junction</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0179">actually one of them's not on a motorway so</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So actually <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1398" who="S0179">really it is three</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0058">CB? Odd thing to see on a bus down here</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0179">up here <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="1401" who="S0058">yay</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0179">actually now I've remembered now I'll remember that you can see that from this exit <pause dur="short"/> that's gonna</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0179">make life a lot easier <unclear/></u>
<u n="1405" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1406" who="S0179">I would've thought this'd be clear of traffic</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0058">this roundabout? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Maybe it's just busy all the time <pause dur="long"/> Ah we're driving past my dentist</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0058">we were driving past my dentist <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1410" who="S0179">were we really?</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0058">just seen it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll be back soon enough anyway</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0179">yeah? Fair enough</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No I think  I think  I'll go home <vocal desc="laugh"/> if it's all the same to you <pause dur="short"/> sorry I think I'll go to my parents if it's all the same to you</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1414" who="S0179">I'm refreshingly surprised that this is a forty <pause dur="short"/> they could very easily have just made it a thirty</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0179">Sunderland's</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's very wide</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0179">fucking bus lanes <pause dur="short"/> why are there so many?</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0058">the this</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0179">I pay road tax <pause dur="short"/> bus users don't</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0058">this road is a pain for bus lanes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1422" who="S0179">it's not too much of an issue with these conditions</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0058">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> it's just this road in particular is quite well-known for it <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> A shop there Make That Bet <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0058">there's a shop er a betting shop there called Make That Bet <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Wow</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0179">catchy</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Just an instruction <pause dur="short"/> same as my condition <pause dur="short"/> it's not a condition that's a description</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1430" who="S0179">I love how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did kind of admit that</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Well fair enough <pause dur="short"/> why give it a stupid name I guess <pause dur="short"/> they could've given it some er weird Latin long name <pause dur="short"/> but actually <unclear/> Let's be straightforward about it <pause dur="short"/> I always think red was a really bad sign for them to choose</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0058">for the dentist <pause dur="short"/> we've just er gone past it</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0058">and the signs red <pause dur="short"/> which I think is a not a good colour for a dentist <pause dur="short"/> it's sort of red with silver writing <pause dur="short"/> but it's not as bad as the one that was just down from my house <pause dur="short"/> er which was black with red writing on it <pause dur="short"/> which really isn't good for a dentist <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1436" who="S0179">why?</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0058">just conjures up the wrong sorts of images</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0179">sort of boudoir?</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> boudoir slash blood slash passion slash <pause dur="short"/> it just doesn't you want cooling whites and blues <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Surely? So it's all gonna be alright <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be clean and calm and</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0179">maybe that's</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0179">what they're trying to get away from</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0179">those houses are quite nice</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0058">they're quite cool</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0179"><unclear/> out</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> she was out <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um um oh what do they call it? There's a word for that</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1449" who="S0058">no no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> something like that <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what they call it <pause dur="short"/> um yeah those houses are quite nice <pause dur="short"/> dunno which what they're like though <pause dur="short"/> but they look quite smart</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0179">problem <pause dur="short"/> just lost a contact lens</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0179">and that's a problem</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0058">do you need to?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0179">er <unclear/></u>
<u n="1455" who="S0058">do you <trunc>nee</trunc> do you need to pull over?</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0179">er yes but I can't really</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> there is a a sort of a a left turn here if you want to take it</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0179">no no that's alright <pause dur="short"/> I can drive one-eyed</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> sure</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0179">I told you my eyes are really tired</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0179">ah no <pause dur="short"/> found it again</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0058">oh good <pause dur="short"/> brilliant <pause dur="short"/> well done <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1464" who="S0179">I know <pause dur="short"/> I'm surprised too</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> Very confusing all these traffic lights</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0179">you see I can't help feeling that a roundabout would have made this</u>
<u n="1467" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1468" who="S0179">a lot easier</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Wow <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> when you see it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah so they've come round they've gotta stop there now <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0179">so there's four er roads going across each other</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1472" who="S0179">roundabout</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0058">shit <pause dur="short"/> roundabout <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1474" who="S0179">it's been thought of <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1475" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> This problem's been solved <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Nice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I had a moment there <pause dur="short"/> that bus is the number four and I had a kind of oo bus for Cambourne moment <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1476" who="S0179">possibly <pause dur="short"/> that might be an expensive ticket</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1478" who="S0179">I hope it's got toilets on it</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1480" who="S0179">seeing as buses aren't actually that comfortable as modes of transport <pause dur="short"/> you see coaches are comfortable fundamentally</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0179">that's better <pause dur="short"/> there is some justice in traffic lights</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1484" who="S0179">uh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1485" who="S0058">oh the four's for Doxford Park</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0058">the four takes you to Doxford Park</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0179"><trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="1489" who="S0058">so it sort of takes you to work <pause dur="short"/> if you work in Doxford Park <pause dur="short"/> and you know it's the next left yeah?</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0179">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1492" who="S0179">seen the lights</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1494" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I have done this enough times though</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0058">I know</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0179">oh well thank you for pointing it out</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0058">I just don't like to assume <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1498" who="S0179">happy Valley</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a very a happy valley in</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0179"><trunc>T</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> for China</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0058">it's alright actually <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's not that bad <pause dur="short"/> ah the parks</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0179">been running through there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1503" who="S0058">wow <pause dur="short"/> literally nothing has changed <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1504" who="S0179">well what were you expecting to change?</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0058">no but <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> some things you know you come back and you think oh wow that <trunc>s</trunc> that sign's new that car's new but no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Guess we were here quite recently</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> excellent</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0179">yeah I've been doing that two-wheeled <unclear/> sensible</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> excellent</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0179">just make sure we've got the <unclear/></u>
</body>
</text>
