<text id="SVKF">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:29:13</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Unemployment, work, university fees, musicals</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON chatting</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> no the the only uh <pause dur="short"/> uh the only problem is like if you have a large community that's that' lost of jobs like uh like as a mining community</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but I never  I never  agree that there's</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well like <trunc>ref</trunc> refugees or overpopulation</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like this is what gets on my nerves d'you know when they say like These kids who can't find work and that and I just think like for all my brother like</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah a lot  a lot  of the time <trunc>w</trunc> there will be  there will be  work <unclear/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">I'm not advocating him as a <trunc>m</trunc> as a good model or as a um someone to follow or as a sort of <pause dur="short"/> You know I think he' um I think he's like could've done a lot better <pause dur="short"/> but one thing I will say is that like if he needs like if he loses a job or if he he just he finds one like the next day or he finds one the next week like</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he's he's certainly great at finding jobs isn't he?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he he's never been unemployed he's never like for any length of time like maybe two weeks</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">he'll just take anything he'll just do anything like he's not  he's not  too proud to just take a job being a cleaner being a working in a factory or anything like he'll just <pause dur="short"/> so for all his bad points which they're numerous and far too many to mention <pause dur="short"/> like at least that's one thing like <pause dur="short"/> I know he'll never  he'll never  be down and out because he always he'll always work</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yes well <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> is he? He um he he likes to to have money doesn't he to spend on things he likes to to have all the latest stuff doesn't he?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I remember  I remember  when he was like when he was sick <pause dur="short"/> well that's part of the reason why he turned out with terrible GSCE results but that <trunc>y</trunc> you know He was doing  he was doing  the milk <pause dur="short"/> he worked on the milk round from <pause dur="short"/> he got up at five in the morning half four in the morning to go on this milk round</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he wanted to yeah maybe wanted to <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">he was collecting glasses at Idols this horrible horrible place in Sunderland nightclub um when he was still at school</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he's just a <trunc>y</trunc> he's just a natural born worker isn't he?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037" trans="overlap">when he was sixteen</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">then he was <pause dur="short"/> then there was a bit where he was working in the furniture shop <pause dur="short"/> so he was working like forty-<trunc>ei</trunc> you know like a full week <pause dur="short"/> nine till five there <pause dur="short"/> but he was working in Idols collecting glasses like Wednesdays Friday Saturdays and Sundays</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">so from</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115">yeah yeah he's done you know loads of hours of work yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115" trans="overlap">until two like <pause dur="short"/> just stupid like <pause dur="short"/> but he's done that all his life and I think <pause dur="short"/> it's one of those things that like you know when you see those um?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037"><trunc>S</trunc> oh there it is there <pause dur="short"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> You know when you see those um? D'you remember that programme we watched about the the bin men? And there was like a bin</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">oh yeah um</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">there was like a bin man from here and then a bin man from like <pause dur="short"/> was it?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">where was it? Kenya Nairobi? And like</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">uh it was Indonesia</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was somewhere like that wasn't it? Really? Was it not <trunc>Nairo</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh well anyway it was somewhere and he like worked</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> um <trunc>Indo</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037">he like worked fifteen hour days <pause dur="short"/> every single day <pause dur="short"/> and like it's like anything if that's what you do if <trunc>u</trunc> if you get to know like if you just get in the groove of doing that then that's what you do like</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he's a very hard working guy isn't he?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037">similarly if you work four hours a day every day like then <trunc>th</trunc> you just get used to that</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115" trans="overlap">mm that was a very hard job yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037">that's just what you get used to so <pause dur="short"/> the thing is he's always like he's just always just worked a lot</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">yeah well it's it's just loads of so</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037">well we were both a bit like that like when I was  when I was  when I was still at home like</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we were saying about the</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">I used to go to like for example on a Saturday I would go to music where I was teaching and stuff and have music lessons myself but <pause dur="short"/> I used to do that from <trunc>ni</trunc> from nine so my dad would pick us up at half past eight</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">go from nine till twelve <pause dur="short"/> then I'd start work um at half past one at Sainsbury's and work till ten PM</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">I did that every Saturday</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">that's that's good for you know for for like um <trunc>b</trunc> yeah for for kids to do stuff like that I think is good yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037" trans="overlap">for two years like <pause dur="short"/> like that's</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115">like uh in a bar whatever</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I dunno why I didn't wanna do anything else like</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">what d'you mean you didn't wanna do anything else?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">like I didn't wanna just stay I suppose I dunno why I didn't wanna just stay at home on a Saturday <pause dur="short"/> cos I went to college all it was when I was at college</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">went to college all week</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">well cos you wanted to have the I mean you wanted to have your own money didn't you?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">you wanted to have your own money didn't you?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">you wanted to apply things in um and that's something that I should've done more myself should have done more work myself um</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115">so <pause dur="short"/> it is it's good to have  to have  people uh doing work like that you know</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">Cos my cousin's um doing it who's uh how old is she like eighteen or something cos she's doing?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037" trans="overlap">who? Uh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">ah <pause dur="short"/> that's what I meant <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah you get the names mixed up  mixed up  don't you uh</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what is she doing? A tiny bit</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">she was working I think in a shop or bar and and or it's like and um</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is <pause dur="short"/> yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a waitress now</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115">aged about eighteen I think and uh</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">no it's she's she is <pause dur="short"/> um she's going to uni this year isn't she?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115">yeah so she's um <pause dur="short"/> yeah no making that money and like uh on top it is really good it's good to have that sort of that extra sort of cushion and that extra money and then can do more stuff but <trunc>a</trunc> also yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">if you if you're making more money then you can save it as well so you can have can save up for uni and like I know I knew people who like went to you know like friends who went from America to um</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">uh to to London you know so they worked very hard with like loads of hours like two jobs</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">I was the opposite like</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">for for to collecting money for the for the <trunc>s</trunc> for uni <unclear/> adapt</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I remember like being really looking forward to like getting a interest free overdraft <pause dur="short"/> like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">yeah that's the so-called pink debt isn't it um but like that's like a lot of people have got overdrafts haven't they but uh</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">but uh</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037" trans="overlap">are you alright?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">but a question of whether they're like  in the long run cos you may end up paying a lot lot lot of interest but uh</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">obviously the the banks must make a profit with them otherwise they wouldn't uh otherwise they wouldn't make it so easy</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I think so cos they you keep like I suppose they keep them as customers like <pause dur="short"/> You know what I mean?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115">yeah I mean that sort of thing's becoming more popular recently</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">and then like you get a mortgage with them or you you know get an ISA or</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the banks have had a lot of trouble recently haven't they with the whole crisis thing so they they're not  they're not  like everyone's favourite but uh</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they have <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">I can <trunc>sm</trunc></u>
<u n="95" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I think <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">I was gonna say I can smell your sandwich that sort of smokiness I I still don't understand what</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115" trans="overlap">hopefully hopefully there isn't something on fire uh</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">I hope I haven't</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">no no I meant like I could</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's funny I can smell smoke and it's getting hotter</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0037">you've left the window open in here</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115">I only it's only open a crack it's not like</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">Don't open the window</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115">it's only open a crack though innit?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">yeah but it's like</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0037">nineteen degrees in there</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> no but it's twenty-one in here so it's not too bad</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you haven't I think you haven't haven't you haven't opened the bedroom window have you?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no no that's totally closed</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">very naughty</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">I just like to have a bit of fresh air coming in</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">well I know but like if it's cold</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">uh so now I think  I think  the overdraft the free overdraft</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">is good in some ways but in other ways um it it does cost in interest so <pause dur="short"/> but it it does give it sort of does give you like perhaps um you know that sort of freedom and</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">like</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I remember  I remember  spending mine before I even went to uni <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if if you used it properly yeah you could uh</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">I remember like buying stuff for uni out of my overdraft</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115">oh right yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">it's bad isn't it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">yeah so I had the overdraft and I had uh yeah and of course you have a student loan which everyone had and also the uh there's the fees which were introduced with like I mean</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think I've got like</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">so there is I mean and of course they're increasing that aren't they uh that's a big thing in the news isn't it that they they dramatically increased</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'll have to work out how much <pause dur="short"/> fees yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">I read that I had the little German uh article from Der Spiegel</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">um talking about student fees and um</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">like uh <unclear/> um and um yeah so like uh</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">sorry student thing</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">I did they did mention like that it was in you know in German from a German perspective but they didn't mention how Britain had got massively higher but it <trunc>w</trunc> it's worse in like America America's like America's pretty pretty hardcore for fees for uni fees I think or they seem to suggest</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true actually</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean um <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>th</trunc> I I do think that that they should've maybe prevented them from going up <pause dur="short"/> like if they were gonna raise them to <trunc>s</trunc> if they're gonna like take away the government contribution that's that's one thing I mean that's not  that's not  great but</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">it it's one thing but then to to allow unis to raise their price</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">even further like um like three thousand on top of that uh</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I think like me  like me  granda's point was like he was saying that like he couldn't go to uni because you had to pay <pause dur="short"/> and then then after that you could pay <pause dur="short"/> like sorry then after that you didn't have to pay but like all the politicians now who are in are ones who are like they they were all the ones who had free university education <pause dur="short"/> it's just so rich that they like <pause dur="short"/> ah so like they had free education but we can't have it now</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well this is the sort of thing that people get you know get really um</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037" trans="overlap">my granda gets so angry at it I mean he he was angry in itself like that even I had to pay I mean which I didn't have to pay actually but <pause dur="short"/> cos the my situation but</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah neither did I because of yeah because of my my family wasn't earning as much at the time <pause dur="short"/> uh no I just yeah I mean I always get a bit sort of uh um I do get a bit like anti-fees sometimes because I think the the the <trunc>g</trunc> the country needs basically the county's gotta spend the government's gotta spend money to to improve the to improve education in a big way</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">but a lot of that is uh is also secondary school education</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">well yeah that's true</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115" trans="overlap">which is which I think a lot of people are just going to school and just wasting the opportunity</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">or the schools aren't good enough and and that's so that's a problem <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I think in a better  in a better  country you should get like should get more  should get more  like opportunities for studying in a better country than um</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">uh like the I I I just I would like to live in a country where where education was free basically <pause dur="short"/> and it was at uni</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> uh is it free anywhere then?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but but there are a lot of um <pause dur="short"/> sorry?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">is it free anywhere?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">in the world like? What about in like the Middle East like?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you mean totally free? Well it used to be free here didn't it like?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">well <trunc>pre</trunc> yeah yes and no no it was never free free like it was never like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it was</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">well <trunc>ob</trunc> well yes a while ago but I don't mean like recently</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115">it it was Blair who introduced the fees wasn't it?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">it was free before that</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">so if you think about it even even Thatcher didn't do that</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty bad</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">uh so yeah they <trunc>s</trunc> people say though don't they they're like even Thatcher didn't X like that that the post office like</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I can't believe she's still alive like <pause dur="short"/> how old is she now?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">hate keeps a person alive <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I know</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">how old is she now?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> that's quote's from uh <pause dur="short"/> Hate keeps a man alive is from uh Ben Hur</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">ah <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>l</trunc></u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">irrelevant film facts</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">uh we watched that on a Sunday once I remember</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">it's a Sunday film and it might just send you into a post stuffing coma</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it might do <pause dur="short"/> too many roast potatoes and a bit Ben Hur <trunc>n</trunc> be</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah so like <pause dur="short"/> um what was I saying?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you wanna a cup of tea or anything?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I was gonna say  I was gonna say  something about fees wasn't I yeah and I but I haven't seen like a full-on comparison of fees across the world but I I'm pretty sure that within Europe places like</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what about in Paris?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">you're gonna probably find that in Scandinavia it's free</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037">D'you think so?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">you're probably gonna find that it's better in many of the European countries</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is it true that that in like?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I'm fairly sure that it's better in German than it is in in England</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037">is it true that in France like that you have to go to your <trunc>near</trunc> your nearby one? Is it that you can go to your nearby one for free but you have to pay if you wanna go to a different one?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but there's something like that in America isn't there about states? Like if you <trunc>cha</trunc> if you wanna go to a different state</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">you have to pay quite a lot more I think which is seems to be a bit bit annoying but</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">uh <trunc>y</trunc> but British unis were making a lot of money from foreign fees because</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">it costs</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">apparently</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">it costs you more as a foreign student in certain places</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">now like fifty percent of postgrads in the UK are foreign fifty percent I mean <pause dur="short"/> that's a lot</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">well I think that's good I think it's it's an <trunc>e</trunc> it's an export isn't it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I don't think it's <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think it's a bad thing but obviously it's uh</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they're bringing in money to the country</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've been hogging the sofa d'you wanna sit here for a while or?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">uh no I'm alright with this uh armchair I like this chair</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037" trans="overlap">sure? You're like me granda that was me grandad's armchair</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0037">the same <pause dur="short"/> nestle in it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">he's uh</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">I wonder how he's doing <pause dur="short"/> I should ring him shouldn't I?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">grandad's and armchairs you know Winning combination isn't it?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I'm sure there used to be two armchairs actually I wonder where the other one's gone</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">did you use to like The Royle Family the the programme?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">I never really watched it I never really got into it <pause dur="short"/> in fact I don't even know if I've seen a whole episode</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah? It's it was  it was  likable really the family was very likable</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">yeah I <trunc>re</trunc> I know the guy with the</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115" trans="overlap">all all the characters were kinda likable like the <trunc>mo</trunc> the mother was like <pause dur="short"/> the mother was um</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">what's her name is it Sarah Lancaster or something?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> sarah Lancaster's no that's not her</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> uh from she was from Corrie wasn't she?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">he was from Brookside the man was from Brookside</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she reminds me a bit of the the <trunc>m</trunc> the mam yeah she that's right <pause dur="short"/> no no the mam  the mam  was from Brookside</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">the man was</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">the mam</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">he's he's Liverpudlian I think pretty sure he was from</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the mum <pause dur="short"/> the mum <pause dur="short"/> the mum was</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115" trans="overlap">pretty sure that the male guy was from Brookside wasn't he?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">Cos he was from Liverpool</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">Don't know</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">yeah pretty sure he was in Brookside <pause dur="short"/> but uh</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">maybe</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">yeah so he was like all but you know he was just like a total sort of like father who's a slob and he's just  he's just  permanently in his  in his  armchair like</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the mam was <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115" trans="overlap">getting his  getting his  boy to bring him tea and everything</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">he just sat he really sort of owned the  owned the  room like he was like the boss</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">the uh</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">like my granda <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well he he sort of dominated the conversation didn't he?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">I don't know I think people might say that the boss of that family is uh</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037" trans="overlap">my nana <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> easily</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's <unclear/> She's uh she's a feisty person</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she's the driving force <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">and <pause dur="short"/> likes a likes likes an anecdote uh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">she doesn't half like an anecdote <pause dur="short"/> in fact we should've like we should've gone and took the recorder we would've just been able to have sat back</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you can't I know it's a shame  a shame  you didn't get paid by the word isn't it?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah I should've <trunc>p</trunc> I should've commissioned</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">I think you if you shouldn't maybe in some ways it's better to get paid by the word I suppose because then</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">but then of course you'd have to wait until like</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">but she doesn't talk particularly fast I don't think <pause dur="short"/> no faster than I do</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">ah it seems like</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's more like it's just a no no no it's just a very feels like a very long time cos her stories are so inane</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115" trans="overlap">seems like a lot of words coming out <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Well it's</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">it's like And then I was in Morrisons and I said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have you seen these fishcakes? And your auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> turned to us and she said I haven't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah starting to feel sleepy <pause dur="short"/> I feel like sleeping <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm about to fall asleep actually</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um no that's fine yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">it's just a brief reenactment there</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">no no couldn't ah we we've got good patiences I mean we we've been talking about like like plants and uh things that are really like not not exciting</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I literally should've just took it round my nana's and been like hi Nana and then just sat back <pause dur="short"/> and she'd have been like purde purde purde pur</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just <unclear/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">she <trunc>w</trunc> then I could've been <pause dur="short"/> actually what I should've done was I should've should've gone round my nana's</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well we we can do that with uh we can do that when we  when we  go to Sunderland</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">yeah September <pause dur="short"/> I went <pause dur="short"/> I should've gone round my nana's</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like you can just take it and take it everywhere and like stick it</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">I should've gone round my nana's and been like Nana have you ever been to America? <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then it'll just be like ah just settle in</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You know she's also a big fan of Steven Seagal as well isn't she?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037">she loves Steven Segal</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that would be something worth talking about</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">I could be like Nana what films have you been watching? And she'd be like</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115" trans="overlap">she likes Steven Segal probably like <unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I can imagine she's be like I've seen that Avatar <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what all the fuss is about <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">I liked Avatar so I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but I I just like the idea that my nana watches <pause dur="short"/> she's not I mean she doesn't half like a bit of you know um Howard Keel and and a bit of Doris and a bit of</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">he's I don't know Howard Keel</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">oh you do <pause dur="short"/> he's in Calamity Jane</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I'm really not that much of an expert in that film</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so in Calamity Jane there's like Wild Bill and then there's like the captain and he's like so Bill he's like a bigger like he he's got a bit of a sort of a shape like you like a <pause dur="short"/> he's like tall and</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't cos I I just don't <trunc>under</trunc> I saw  I saw  <trunc>dir</trunc> I saw it but it's one of them musicals that's sort of massively um anachronistic and</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">you know it's it's anachronistic <pause dur="short"/> is it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">no I'm just saying you know it's a bit like it's it's based on something but it's very liberal with like uh the facts</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah but isn't <pause dur="short"/> yeah but a lot of things are I mean</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">well you should see Seven Brides For Seven Brothers <pause dur="short"/> have you seen that?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's not that doesn't that wouldn't mean that it's a bad film</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037">have you seen Seven Brides For Seven Brothers?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> oh um <pause dur="short"/> bits of it maybe</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">that's a great one</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115">yeah I should maybe should investigate some more musicals</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Seven Brides For Seven Brothers I watched that the other morning that's a Sunday one <pause dur="short"/> so Seven Brides For Seven Brothers there's this guy and he's called like ah what's I don't know anyway he's name begins with an A</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't think it would my like my favourite film of all time</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">and he lives up in the mountains right and he comes down to the  he comes down to the  town like</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah he seemed to like mountains in this one <pause dur="short"/> musicals and mountains go together</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's like a Wild West sort of town and he comes down and he's</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">Brokeback Mountain</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037">he's singing about how he wants to find a wife and <pause dur="short"/> she's gotta be just right and</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh so not Brokeback Mountain then</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he looks at all the other women's in the <trunc>t</trunc> he's singing these songs and gotta not be this and not be that</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115" trans="overlap">would've been funny if Brokeback Mountain was a musical</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">and then he  and then he  sees through the window this woman and she's like she was running the like cook house like the you know the café if you like and um all these men are giving her grief and she's like batting it back at them and she's got real feistiness <pause dur="short"/> um and so then um he decides that she's the one for her for him <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">no I don't it's it's alright I'm just</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Am I getting Nana Jean on ya? Am I doing a really long story?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no no it's alright I mean</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0037">alright then <pause dur="short"/> anyway I'll <trunc>c</trunc> try and cut the story down <vocal desc="laugh"/> So he ends up marrying her takes her home</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115" trans="overlap">this is uh <pause dur="short"/> I I I'm on a comfortable chair so</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">takes her home</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">then he then she realizes that like she's been really romanticising the idea then going to live in the mountains la-di-la <pause dur="short"/> then she realises that he's got these other six brothers like called like Bob like everything A B C D E F like you know what I mean? They've all got like bible names <pause dur="short"/> he's like Abraham like</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like Babraham Cabraham</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> cain Daniel like</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Dabraham Eabraham Fabraham</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean like</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">he's got all these brothers and then they've like got really bad manners they're like a <trunc>p</trunc> pack of wolves and then she eventually she whips them into shape and then she tells them how to like find a woman like how to woo a lady and they go down to town and they find girls that they like and blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> anyway it all takes a bit of a sinister twist when they <trunc>actual</trunc> actually uh kidnap the girls and bring them back to the mountains</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">yeah?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">and cause an avalanche on the way</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">I think</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">so they're stuck there for the whole summer</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115">this is</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sounds like a pretty exciting musical <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh you're trying to <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're trying to stop my story</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">no I'm just like</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">when I'm like in forty years time I'll be Nana Dembry and then I'll just be telling you stories</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> think there's some similarities definitely</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037">well that's my nana introduced us to that film anyway <pause dur="short"/> okay I'll not  I'll not  tell you any more details but it's really good</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">no no I mean <pause dur="short"/> it you <trunc>w</trunc> you were yeah you were  you were  talking about uh something about Jean yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037" trans="overlap">alright so boys kidnap the the girls from the village so they can't be rescued so then the original  the original  woman in it the main woman get really angry at the original the main guy in it cos he <trunc>to</trunc> sort of told them to do it encouraged them</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's not very nice</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">so he goes off to the mountains <pause dur="short"/> meanwhile she has a baby <pause dur="short"/> meanwhile the woman like first of all they hate the <trunc>m</trunc> men who've captured them but then</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115">yeah you would wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">but then after a while they warm to them and realise actually that they do love them <pause dur="short"/> then Spring comes the pass thaws <pause dur="short"/> the townsfolk come up to the the mountains to get to reclaim the women <pause dur="short"/> and there's like a big chase like fanciful sort of silly where they're chasing around and stuff and then then they hear a baby crying and then they say Whose does that belong to? And then all of them say it's mine so then they all of them get married to the brothers because it's not theirs it's the other one's</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115">oh</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You look so bored</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115">no no no no I'm fine uh no it sounds like a</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aw <pause dur="short"/> it is good</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">it's a no it sounds  it sounds  good um</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037">no it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> stop lying <pause dur="short"/> it sounds stupid I told it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh no I like um I like  I like I like  West Side Story so</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've got I've gotta work on my storytelling <pause dur="short"/> no it's not like West Side Story <vocal desc="laugh"/> They all like wear colour coordinating trousers and like</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115">no I like the idea of musicals though I think I'd I'd like to see more like <pause dur="short"/> I think there's a maybe <trunc>s</trunc> not enough like good musicals like proper like satirical comedy musicals</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037" trans="overlap">some good ones <pause dur="short"/> some Tommy <trunc>S</trunc> Tommy Steele ones are nice like um <pause dur="short"/> like Half A Sixpence and stuff and <pause dur="short"/> I quite fancy <trunc>se</trunc></u>
<u n="359" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's there's a great uh there's a great um comedy musical uh made by the director of Lord Of The Rings Peter Jackson</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah? What's it called?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115">it's called Meet The Feebles</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037">oh I've seen it and I'm not a massive fan but yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115">it's probably more of boys' <trunc>pro</trunc> film</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm I think so</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115">it's a bit disgusting but</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but you know  you know  Tim Minchin?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115">I do actually yeah <pause dur="short"/> the stand-up comedian? And piano impresario <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's just wrote the <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure he would like that description</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> he's just written a um</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">I don't know what that is</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115">he's written a <trunc>mu</trunc> an opera has he? A libretto?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">he's written the songs and music to</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115" trans="overlap">book <pause dur="short"/> book and libretto?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037">he's written the songs and the music to uh Matilda so there's Matilda The Opera's on at the moment</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos it's similar to Carrie isn't it and I  and I</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I really fancy seeing that <pause dur="short"/> carrie? Carrie?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">it's similar to Carrie by Stephen King</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> well there's less blood</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115">and it came out at a similar time and I'm not sure which was first actually</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037">I don't think it's that similar to Carrie</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Alright Carrie's Carrie's like a horror</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> There's not that bit at the end <pause dur="short"/> I went to a sleepover and watched Carrie and I was just like uh</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well that's your own fault isn't it?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">and Night Of The Living Dead have you ever seen that?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that must've  that must've  been a <trunc>chee</trunc> a cheery sleepover</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037">have you ever seen Night Of The Living Dead?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">I love that <pause dur="short"/> I love The Living Dead series</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037">oh I saw that when I was about twelve</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115">it's George A Romero</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037">no I must've been older thirteen</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I showed you um</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037">God it was horrible</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">is that? D'you mean the?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037" trans="overlap">one with the pins in his face?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">that's not Night Of The Living Dead</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037">what's that then?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115">uh Hellraiser's the one where he's got pins in his head</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037">oh Hellraiser then</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115">I haven't seen that <pause dur="short"/> there's something about like young kids and horror films isn't there?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0037">oh I hated it</u>
<u n="403" who="S0115">for some reason like like sort of ten year-olds really like eighteen rated films</u>
<u n="404" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I had this friend called Nicki who lived just like <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>w</trunc> on the estate that I lived on like</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh hear we go</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037">alright that's the end of that story</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no no no only joking  only joking only joking only joking</u>
<u n="408" who="S0037">what I can't say about I can't say <trunc>an</trunc></u>
<u n="409" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no no I was only joking because like you know like <trunc>y</trunc> you know when people sometimes like they say that they they're from a very poor like background</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I just said the estate that I live in alright the place that I lived in like</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah no I was it was a joke it was just a joke uh</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037">well it wasn't very funny</u>
<u n="413" who="S0115">sort of backfired</u>
<u n="414" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it did totally backfire <event desc="sound of explosion"/> like that <pause dur="short"/> that was</u>
<u n="415" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like uh whatever the original meaning of that comes from</u>
<u n="416" who="S0037">is it not a car?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0115">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's a canon isn't it? It's where you uh you've lit and it's and you're all gone and fired in your face</u>
<u n="418" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and when you look in the end to see if it's like still going</u>
<u n="419" who="S0115">where you've lit it in like a cartoon and like uh</u>
<u n="420" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Were we not talking about that the other day?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and like and it the the you know you know the the the the um</u>
<u n="422" who="S0037">we were talking about that the other day cos I was saying about like how they end up with this hole in their face</u>
<u n="423" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the the fuse goes down you know the the you light the fuse down</u>
<u n="424" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0115">the fuse goes down</u>
<u n="426" who="S0037">then nothing happens</u>
<u n="427" who="S0115">then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0037">then you pop pop your head round the end</u>
<u n="429" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's like a pause <pause dur="short"/> and you're like that's funny</u>
<u n="430" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I was talking about it the other day</u>
<u n="431" who="S0115">something's wrong with my canon <pause dur="short"/> just gonna put my head in front of the gun of the canon <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0037">Cos we were talking about Tom And Jerry</u>
<u n="433" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0037">should watch some Tom And Jerry <pause dur="short"/> maybe we should get Netflix <pause dur="short"/> have you seen that?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0115">yeah maybe <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah so um</u>
<u n="436" who="S0037">although we haven't got broadband so might need to do that first</u>
<u n="437" who="S0115">night Of The <trunc>Li</trunc> Night Of The Living Dead is the one it's a zombie film <pause dur="short"/> and and it's in black and white</u>
<u n="438" who="S0037">is that the one that like um?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0115">and it has uh the hero is like a  like a  black guy but he he actually gets shot uh at the end of it it's quite poignant actually</u>
<u n="440" who="S0037" trans="overlap">have I seen it?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0115">um because the police assume that he's a a zombie and they kill him even though he was like the hero</u>
<u n="442" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="443" who="S0115">it's like sad ending that</u>
<u n="444" who="S0037">no I don't mean that</u>
<u n="445" who="S0115">night Of The Living Dead has a famous start doesn't it cos it's like it's in a graveyard or something or a park <pause dur="short"/> and they're in a car it's like a brother brother and sister in a car and then like like a zombie just sort of comes up and like attacks the brother or something</u>
<u n="446" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't I didn't mean that <pause dur="short"/> I've never even seen that <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="447" who="S0115">and then the the woman runs runs to this house and then that's why she she they're sort of holed up in in the house and the zombies are coming at them</u>
<u n="448" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't think I've <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0115">you know that's a sort of like a common <pause dur="short"/> there' there's the</u>
<u n="450" who="S0037">but what I was gonna tell you before was that I went to this sleepover once like with this girl called Nicki and what I was trying to say was in the place that I lived like it could um</u>
<u n="451" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah no no fair enough it is it was a council estate</u>
<u n="452" who="S0037">it was like um so like the streets were arranged in like courts like in squares but like so like some of the bits out the back like you had a bit where you could run or like you could get all the way down where you could walk in a long line for a long way like past houses on either side and there was kind of ones like that</u>
<u n="453" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0037">it was kind of in like a <trunc>spo</trunc> like a spoke sort of shape <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0037">the school was in the middle and there was like sort of the <trunc>s</trunc> the spokes of these like uh</u>
<u n="457" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0037">anyway and I went to this sleepover once and we were watching these horror films and that and and like in the end I just like I ran home and I was still in my pyjamas and I ran it was like it must've been about like</u>
<u n="459" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sorry isn't isn't the point of a sleepover to like</u>
<u n="460" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I got too scared <pause dur="short"/> I hate horror <trunc>fil</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know <pause dur="short"/> I'd never seen a horror film before like <pause dur="short"/> I'd never ever seen one <pause dur="short"/> and it was that one with the pins in his face</u>
<u n="461" who="S0115">hellraiser</u>
<u n="462" who="S0037">and I was like I'm just going to the toilet and I just was like <event desc="sound of running"/> and I just ran</u>
<u n="463" who="S0115">really?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0037">I just ran all the way up like up the street like up the thing all the way home and I was like mam <pause dur="short"/> and I was knocking on my door <pause dur="short"/> and obviously like like at the place where I'd been they were like uf thought that something really bad had happened like I'd been <trunc>ad</trunc> abducted</u>
<u n="465" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah thought that you'd been abducted by like the guy with pins coming out of his head</u>
<u n="466" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so my mam made us go back</u>
<u n="467" who="S0115">that's just strange strange behaviour</u>
<u n="468" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no she came back with us and then we went we came back home <pause dur="short"/> I was just scared</u>
<u n="469" who="S0115">fair enough but like running out cos you don't wanna go out  you don't wanna go out  that's the worst  that's the worst  thing you do you know you're getting all the clichés and that</u>
<u n="470" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but running in the middle of the night I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> in your pyjamas <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know but you don't think about it do you you don't think about it <pause dur="short"/> until you're there and you're like I'm gonna get attacked</u>
<u n="471" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's a lot  there's lot  of horror clichés and that's why they made uh they made Scream you know to sort of as like a  like a  sort of self-referential</u>
<u n="472" who="S0037" trans="overlap">just like a child running around <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0115">like postmodern</u>
<u n="474" who="S0037">Tom likes all them things I'm not really</u>
<u n="475" who="S0115">D'you like Scream? Have you seen it?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0037">never really seen it <pause dur="short"/> is Courtney Cox in it?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0115">it's quite <pause dur="short"/> yeah she is <pause dur="short"/> that's how she met um</u>
<u n="478" who="S0037">with the mask <pause dur="short"/> I've seen a mask</u>
<u n="479" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's where she met her husband</u>
<u n="480" who="S0037">he's not her husband any more</u>
<u n="481" who="S0115">ah <pause dur="short"/> celebrity marriages never last do they?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> he's been like <pause dur="short"/> I think he's got like a sex addiction</u>
<u n="483" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> courtney doesn't like to uh</u>
<u n="484" who="S0037">no I <trunc>th</trunc> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> but I think he was having a lot of like extramarital affairs and stuff <pause dur="short"/> from what I know <pause dur="short"/> from what I read in those stupid magazines which are probably completely incorrect anyway <pause dur="short"/> I don't know like just <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0115">uh um <pause dur="short"/> no well yeah but that's what we were talking about before well that's what we were talking about before <pause dur="short"/> is is it on the half hour or?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0037">uh yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0115">are you gonna pause it then?</u>
</body>
</text>
