<text id="SVLK">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:44:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0266 S0267 S0310</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Acquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>Description of what a careers’ dept. at a university does; complex life decisions for students; attitude of students; year in industry in various disciplines; research placements; overseas students; Literacy/Numeracy for employers; Civil Service tests. What to do now retired: art classes, school governor and tracing ancestry</topics>
		<activity>a recently retired university head of careers talking about her work</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0266">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Almondsbury, Gloucestershire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0267">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bristol</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Zambia</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>29</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>PA secretary</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0310">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stockton-on-tees</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>NE</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Careers advisor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0266">is it ah it's recording erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you said that you've just eh retired recently eh what did you retire from?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0310">erm the <anon type="place"/> where I was head of careers</u>
<u n="3" who="S0266">mm mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0310">erm so</u>
<u n="5" who="S0266">what kind of things? so can you tell us a bit about what your job involved</u>
<u n="6" who="S0310">I mean in the last sort of ten eleven years that I was there I was actually managing people who were delivering the service erm although I did continue to see students myself eh about erm ten percent of my time erm I think probably it's more interesting to describe what a careers adviser does rather than what the person who manages them does erm so there's within universities of course university being free agents we're at liberty to kind of define the job how we want to but if erm I mean <anon type="place"/> was the fourth university I'd been in so <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><trunc>w</trunc>which were the other ones?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0310">erm I started off eh at the beginning I was in <anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/> erm and then erm because basically I got married and my husband kept being moved around erm I was at what now is <anon type="place"/> which at the time was <anon type="place"/> and then I was at <anon type="place"/> shortly before it became <anon type="place"/> when it was <anon type="place"/> which was sort of post having children when the children were small that was my sort of going back to work job part time</u>
<u n="9" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0310">and then I went to <anon type="place"/> erm I suppose when they were about six and seven so within the sort of erm if you like the the sort of common threads of the job within universities erm a careers adviser would be allocated to certain disciplines so they would have effectively a kind of portfolio of academic departments so erm for example at <anon type="place"/> we had somebody who erm had been a biochemistry academic so he covered all science and engineering disciplines erm and within that element of the role erm you would erm develop good relationships with the head of department and with usually there would be a particular member of academic staff who would be responsible for things like erm erm supporting the student managing more sort of personal tutoring that goes on through which you would be able to get your services sort of advertised erm in some departments this is where the greatest variation is erm in some universities and in some departments within certain universities but not others there might be a careers module so some careers advisers would also be lecturers erm and some of ours did that in certain departments so in managements and in I can't remember the other department but that would be a taught module that they would mark and so on so that's a quite a different set of responsibilities really because effectively you're having to design a teaching package and so and the funding as a manager gets quite erm a lot more complicated if you're getting internal money from departments for buying out certain careers adviser time erm but the what careers advisers in all universities do would be to see students on an individual basis and to see and to see students on in a group basis so whereas you might if you've got erm a commitment a teaching commitment within the department you'd be slotted into the timetable we also ran erm a programme of erm group work sessions which students could book into erm completely independent of their department so we would cover erm a whole variety of things and that would be we'd we'd sort of debate what was necessary for the forthcoming year and look at movements in the market and what we might need to ensure they know about and erm look at erm how successful they'd been in previous year as to whether we repeated them but you'd always get the sort of four or five core bread and butter sort of topics which are about marketing yourself finding out about employers erm performing at interview passing selection tests erm networking creative job hunting all those sort of bout five or six sort of core eh sessions we would we would run anyway but there might be other things which we'd top it up with depending on perhaps you know if the market had slumped in one particular area or something we might run sessions on erm erm you know alternatives to or</u>
<u n="11" who="S0267">so so did you see it as er your responsibility to guide them into what was out there jobwise?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0310">erm yes <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc>the very frustrating thing for the majority of career services</u>
<u n="13" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0310">is that it's quite rare for it to be compulsory for students to use the service</u>
<u n="15" who="S0266">that's what I was going to ask</u>
<u n="16" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0310">so there is a huge amount of effort that goes into actually advertising it marketing it internally to students and selling them the benefits because we have plenty of data to show that if you use your career service you're going to do better <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0310">but whether that's because the people who would do better tend to but I don't know erm but that's that's always sort of an issue erm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0310">and the other flip side of that issue is if they did all come there's no way we'd have enough resources to see them all</u>
<u n="22" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0310">so erm I mean the workload issue particularly on the one to one basis erm probably during my time quadrupled I would think</u>
<u n="24" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0310">and in addition to that when I first started which was probably thirty years ago we had an hour per student nowadays we have ten minutes</u>
<u n="26" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0266" trans="overlap">what can you do in ten minutes?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0310" trans="overlap">so not <trunc>o</trunc></u>
<u n="29" who="S0267">well the doctor has to see you in three so what can you tell him in three minutes?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0266" trans="overlap">is it three?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0267">yeah three minutes</u>
<u n="32" who="S0310" trans="overlap">three?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0267">three minutes is the allotted time</u>
<u n="34" who="S0266">no</u>
<u n="35" who="S0267">yeah it is that's why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s left the practice she said three minutes they're supposed to <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0310" trans="overlap">it was ten minutes when my daughter was a GP</u>
<u n="37" who="S0267">well I mean you some people can be seen in three minutes can't they?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0310" trans="overlap">but yes it's yes absolutely but <trunc>yo</trunc> they can't predict what's going to walk in through the door</u>
<u n="39" who="S0267" trans="overlap">no they can't so they're actually anticipating <unclear/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0266">and in what year did they mostly come and visit you?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0310">too late</u>
<u n="43" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0310">erm probably that was one of the goals we always had was to gradually shift the percentage that left it until their final year to come erm and one of the benefits</u>
<u n="45" who="S0266" trans="overlap">did did you did you achieve that?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0310">erm yeah it went down to we got it down to about sort of <vocal desc="misc"/> oh I think it's about fifty-five percent of students who came on a one to one basis for a final year and so forty-five percent were pre final year</u>
<u n="47" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0310">erm but final year is too late I mean the biggest and most complex decision is what do I want to do with my life <pause dur="short"/> and you can't decide that you can't steer them through a decision making process when the timetable for some of the major employers is the same as a UCAS timetable so they'd be needing to apply to the traditional big scale high flying employers have closing dates that start in October in some instances they have closing dates which actually started before the students came back</u>
<u n="49" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0310">so you know there was that that was a really hard hitting message that needed to be part of the marketing erm <pause dur="short"/> and you know we were sort of taking a bite out of it every year really erm but that sort of decision making process the other thing that's difficult to get across in a marketing sort of erm to successfully in marketing is that careers advisers have mechanisms for helping you make that decision that really difficult decision too many students the feedback is well I didn't come to see you because I don't know what I want to do no wrong way round</u>
<u n="51" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0310">you come to see us mm right at the beginning if you don't know what you want to do that way we've got two years or so to help you plan find out meet people make decisions decide it's wrong go back to the beginning again</u>
<u n="54" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0310">work work through that erm and</u>
<u n="56" who="S0267">how do you find over the years erm the characteristics of students you know are they? are they the same as ten years ago or are they erm you know more interested or lack of interest or erm very kind of friendly erm what's the respect between you two? and how have they changed over the time</u>
<u n="57" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm I mean I think it's always been the best bit of the job with the students <trunc>o</trunc>on the whole are mostly really nice people and it's really fun actually working with them as far as their sort of focus and ability to sort of negotiate all these complex decisions is concerned erm you always get the whole range you always get the whole range you always get the people who are completely clueless and don't know where to start in the nicest possible way you know they sort of <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0310">this is a bit scary I've never had to make my own decision before erm and at the opposite end of the scale you do get and I think the numbers of those has gone up and up and up really over the last ten years particularly that there is a there is a bigger proportion who actually are rather more clued up and understand rather more about what an employer would be looking for erm I mean the government has been pushing all these sorts of things like skills based stuff for years now erm you know most of them have had some sort of skills portfolio from when they were at school</u>
<u n="60" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0310">so those sorts of words have become common</u>
<u n="62" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and are they valuable because sometimes when you see your children doing them you think what a load of rubbish really</u>
<u n="63" who="S0310" trans="overlap">ah well <trunc>n</trunc>no what a waste of time yes erm I think an awful lot of them are tokenism and and erm I mean when my kids got them at school you know this I can't remember what they're called but the usual sorts of things you know?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and the work experience sorts of episodes and things but were you involved at all with the <unclear/> industry in at university</u>
<u n="65" who="S0310">erm yes</u>
<u n="66" who="S0266">cos I swear that's what erm catapulted my second daughter to success</u>
<u n="67" who="S0310"><unclear/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it really focused her and she went and worked actually for a big company for a year</u>
<u n="69" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes yes there were</u>
<u n="70" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and learned how to do learned everything</u>
<u n="71" who="S0310">yes erm it there there</u>
<u n="72" who="S0266">she went to for she went erm for her when do they do it? is it the second? ah</u>
<u n="73" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0266" trans="overlap">is it after the second year or after the first year I can't remember</u>
<u n="76" who="S0310">it's usually after the second year it's usually the third year out and then held back for the final year</u>
<u n="77" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yes I think that was the second year yeah so she was still quite sort of immature working reasonably hard but not I don't think completely focused about why or what she was doing</u>
<u n="78" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah yes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0266">and then she went for this sort of sponsored year what do they call it? erm intern or placement or whatever</u>
<u n="80" who="S0310" trans="overlap">placement yes yes what subject was she doing?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0266">she was doing erm business</u>
<u n="82" who="S0310">yes that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0266" trans="overlap">whether it was management or <unclear/> I can't remember</u>
<u n="84" who="S0310">business and engineering are the ones <unclear/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0266">but she went to erm <anon type="place"/> and you know was quickly licked into a very slick shape and <unclear/> method of working and given quite a lot of responsibility and it was competitive and it it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0267">so she wanted to get back out to work she wanted to <unclear/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well she just got a taste of what life really was about you know you have student jobs where you're doing this <unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0310">they're not real</u>
<u n="90" who="S0267">no no</u>
<u n="91" who="S0266">but it really got her it sort of wound her up ratcheted her up into this sort of world that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0266">and then she went back to university to do her I suppose it would be her fourth year and she really knew why she was doing what she was doing in her fourth year because she'd been out in the real world</u>
<u n="94" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm yes yes</u>
<u n="95" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0266">and then she had this real taste for what she actually wanted to to go and do and she was applying for things well before</u>
<u n="97" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0267">well that's why <trunc>I</trunc>I mean I think we are going backwards again which is a good thing to apprenticeships because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was <unclear/> on an on an apprenticeship</u>
<u n="99" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0267">erm not done but erm you know he went through the apprenticeship and so did I</u>
<u n="101" who="S0266">mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes that I mean traditionally it's it's what you know what goes around comes around but you know apprenticeships were a really good thing</u>
<u n="103" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah they were</u>
<u n="104" who="S0310">yes because not all of them</u>
<u n="105" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> actually</u>
<u n="106" who="S0310">yeah and not all people want to not all students actually want that sort of sometimes slightly rarefied kind of academic focus all of the time you know</u>
<u n="107" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0266">but it's I rather liken that to you know when you're at school and you have to learn languages and you learn French?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0266">I mean I used to go on holiday with my parents to <anon type="place"/> but I never really eh clued up to the fact that I was learning French because I would actually find it useful in my life and how I would use it later perhaps when travelling or whatever</u>
<u n="111" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0266">and I never really connected the two I just had to do it to pass the O level or something</u>
<u n="114" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0267">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0266">and it's rather like I sort of think very simplified but it's rather like you know going to start a career and think about it while you're at university you've got no idea of exactly</u>
<u n="117" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yes</u>
<u n="118" who="S0266">what? what?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0310">yes</u>
<u n="120" who="S0266">so is that mostly for engineering and business is it?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0310" trans="overlap">but yes we used to help erm it depends on which university you're at really whether it's something that is in the culture and if it's in the culture like it was at <anon type="place"/> then erm there would be even students doing things like sociology would do it it's a great deal harder to find the placements</u>
<u n="122" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0310">and a great deal harder to persuade the students that what they might be doing is relevant for them but theoretically students could do it with any subject</u>
<u n="124" who="S0266" trans="overlap">subject erm and <anon type="place"/> is renowned for its wonderful sports facilities and degrees</u>
<u n="125" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0266">so could those kind of people would they be put into a years' industry or placement?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0310">I mean at <anon type="place"/> any discipline any discipline that we had at <anon type="place"/> had an option</u>
<u n="128" who="S0266">so what kind of thing would they go into though?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0310">they would do erm I mean there aren't degrees at <anon type="place"/> that are actually erm you know actually playing sport there there you know the the erm there's a degree called sport and exercise science which is basically a science degree so they're learning about things like erm anatomy and respiration and erm diet for fitness and you know training regimes and all those sorts of things so they'd either do a research placement in something like perhaps one of the sports bodies or possibly the civil service used to take a lot of them because it's pertinent to research for servicemen under stress as well</u>
<u n="130" who="S0266">right</u>
<u n="131" who="S0310">erm so eh or they would do something some of them did teaching for a year some of them did university research eh and</u>
<u n="132" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0310">ah you know sometimes yeah a few did things like personal training</u>
<u n="134" who="S0266">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="136" who="S0266">and what about did you also help the overseas students?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0310">mm their demands on us were absolutely huge overseas students are hugely hugely motivated and will take up every service you possibly can offer them</u>
<u n="138" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0310">erm it's the number of times the government's changed the regulations about ability to or you know legal situation as far as getting jobs are concerned it's just you know up and down every year really erm but yes in many ways it was they all want to work in the UK basically and erm even under the post study work visa which generated immense sort of optimism that they were automatically going to be able to get a job for two years <trunc>af</trunc> in the UK afterwards erm unfortunately it didn't make employers want them just because they were legally entitled to work it didn't sell them into a job you know an employee wants to take a graduate with a view to the long term they don't want to take somebody who's got to go home after two years</u>
<u n="140" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0310">erm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0267">but although legally they're not supposed to <unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0310" trans="overlap">legally there's a there's a clash between the law in terms of equal opportunities and that was</u>
<u n="144" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0310">I mean one of the things I didn't say was that careers advisers have a sort of responsibility to keep up to date with all those sorts of things so maybe shooting off to see sort of employers probably on average they do I don't know for the whole team we probably did about forty or fifty employer visits a year so then we'd sort of cascade it to other people erm and some of those and in addition to that there would be sort of regular training days on things like updates for post study work visas and those kinds of things erm and there's a very very strong national organisation amongst the university careers advisers far stronger than any of the other professional groupings because erm going back sort of thirty thirty-five years or so when it all sort of started to kick off there was an absolute dearth of information that students could look at on what it's like to be a logistics manager on a wet Thursday afternoon in February what would you actually be doing? erm and so nationally erm people did job studies and we all compiled them into a central sort of well nowadays obviously it's a database erm and they're all updated every three years so your young careers adviser or your recently appointed careers adviser would have sort of portfolio of you know you're going to have to do three job studies or whatever as part of your induction and eh and that's you know it's part of a sort of national commitment to keeping the kind of <trunc>u</trunc> expertise up to date and things as well and it also is brilliant for students you know so all the universities even though it's sometimes difficult within your university to get the university to relax their copyright <vocal desc="laugh"/> but we had to all do that battle and persuade our university that for these particular pieces of work please let us release the copyright you know because the value of it is only if we all do it nationally and the whole thing is you know</u>
<u n="146" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0310">seven or eight hundred or so erm probably more than that now probably a thousand erm job profiles you know there's no value in having six that your university does</u>
<u n="148" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0310">erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0266">did you ever place anyone er overseas?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0310">erm yes I would sort of <pause dur="short"/> the terminology isn't quite what we'd use when you said place</u>
<u n="152" who="S0266">well no I mean for placement for a for a year's perhaps erm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0310" trans="overlap">but but <pause dur="short"/> oh yes I mean all the all the language students erm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0266">would go</u>
<u n="155" who="S0310">yes</u>
<u n="156" who="S0266">what the Erasmus and perhaps?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0310" trans="overlap">and erm yes a lot of them did teaching teaching English for a year</u>
<u n="158" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0310">or they could do an industrial or commercial placement but the numbers of those were quite tiny because in other European countries as you will well know they don't have this culture of any discipline you know you can't become very easily a an accountant or a marketing person or something if you've got a degree in a somebody else's language you know you need in it's much more common in other European countries to have the relevant degree to go into the relevant job but we've got this I think tradition that probably goes back to fourteen hundred you know when the only degrees you could do were classics or theology</u>
<u n="160" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0310">erm and so we have this long term sort of tradition that a graduate here when they're taken on is a trainee <pause dur="short"/> erm in most areas they're trainees whereas if you graduated in Germany say you'd probably would be twenty-seven and you would have done probably five years worth of different chunks of placements and so on and you'd go into a proper job as it were with a certain level of responsibility</u>
<u n="162" who="S0267">and you still have child benefit?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0310">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0267">that's true</u>
<u n="165" who="S0310">really?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0267">that's true yes cos when we were in <anon type="place"/> that's what happened they were paying <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> through her university</u>
<u n="167" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0267">I got a hundred and sixty-four euros a month</u>
<u n="169" who="S0310">really?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0267">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0310">that's magic isn't it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0267">it is yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0310">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="174" who="S0267">so there you go <trunc>appa</trunc>apparently it's because they understood that by the time their children actually got proper jobs they were just coming up to thirty</u>
<u n="175" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="176" who="S0267">they were</u>
<u n="177" who="S0310">yes yeah <anon type="place"/>'s probably about the oldest I think isn't it? in terms of the average graduating age</u>
<u n="178" who="S0267">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0310">but eh yes I I think you know when when membership of the EU first took off and erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> our visits to employers became European so we all trundled off round <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> visiting all these employers cos everybody thought oh they're all going to get jobs over here well I mean it didn't happen did it? cos the cultures and the education systems don't fit so erm ah you know we were there's there's a lot of them who want their first job abroad and by far and away you know if you want to go abroad at all costs then the easiest thing to get into is teaching English because you've got that's your skill that you can offer in many countries is you know highly desirable erm or erm <vocal desc="gasp"/> it there were students we have a lot of international students as well who've got you know erm a cross between different nationalities and so on who've got their own networks and so on erm they also I think benefit by getting a masters level in the UK if they're wanting to go abroad because that four years would have been in France the minimum four years of HE and if you've done one of your years is a placement I don't think they really that's not really counted so just staying on and doing a masters is is the one thing that can help but erm there were I mean we used to have all the you know all the websites and things for getting a graduate job in all these countries but the the record of people actually succeeding in any area other than teaching would be pitiful absolutely pitiful</u>
<u n="180" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0310">and some students are so naïve about it you know I can remember students coming in <vocal desc="laugh"/> and saying you know they wanted to work in Finland or something so I'd say oh yeah we can show you who the employers are and this is the employers <unclear/> students who said but I can't understand this</u>
<u n="182" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0310"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like okay well how are you going to get a job there if you can't speak Finnish? you thought this through properly?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0310">erm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0266">but one is very naïve at that age well a lot of people are I remember not really knowing what I wanted to do</u>
<u n="188" who="S0310">mm mm well there's no reason why young people should know how could they possibly know?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0310">you know they are only ever going to know about a handful of jobs that they've come across in their own lives</u>
<u n="191" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but I mean yeah or they could be informed which I presume is what you're doing so that you can make an informed decision</u>
<u n="192" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0266">I don't remember as you know a late in my teens ever really being told much about <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0267">no</u>
<u n="195" who="S0266">I had a grandmother who expected me to do something and that was about it I didn't</u>
<u n="196" who="S0267">mostly my <trunc>e</trunc> my era or my age group were you were either a teacher or a secretary</u>
<u n="197" who="S0266">females</u>
<u n="198" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0310">yes college of higher education was quite common but the the <trunc>t</trunc>the principle of I mean there's a lot of theories that we work to I <trunc>s</trunc> there's probably three or four different basic theories of careers guidance which is about how <trunc>yo</trunc> what is the theory behind how people get to a decision erm and erm you know there's a psychologically based theory which is theoretically what we'd all work to which is psychological basically which is saying that making the assumption that once you've got a certain academic achievement then it in effect gives you an independence so you can base a decision on your own skills your own values your own sets of interests and so I mean that was the the sort of core assumption that the majority of the career services would be based on but you had to be aware with students that you would also come across students who were going to be making a decision on another basis erm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0266">for example</u>
<u n="202" who="S0310">for example erm a sort of something that's ah sociologically based erm so they may feel they're erm erm you know there are family pressures</u>
<u n="203" who="S0266">following family traditions</u>
<u n="204" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0310">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0310">erm or they can be economically based decisions which tends to be more common if you've got something like a recession and were certainly much more common in terms of people who perhaps haven't moved away from home or was very very common in years gone by you know <unclear/> basically if you lived in a Welsh valley and you were a lad <trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc> the chances are you'd go down the pit because economically that's basically all there was</u>
<u n="208" who="S0266" trans="overlap">pit <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0310">erm so going theoretically anyway and very loosely speaking if you get a higher education you get lifted out of that</u>
<u n="210" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0310">erm and then sort of <trunc>the</trunc>there's another theory about erm can't remember what it was called now but it's about industry experience so making a decision this is where the placement model fits that students can you know if they taste something then they they they're they're involved in actually assessing as part of that they may not realise it but they are assessing themselves against that role</u>
<u n="212" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0310">as they're doing it erm and so they're thinking do I feel comfortable with this? can I actually do it? is it making me want to get out of bed in the morning to come here? do I foresee actually coming back to that and you were saying how your daughter was very motivated <trunc>af</trunc> you know we used to get the reverse as well we used to get a queue of them</u>
<u n="214" who="S0266">mm <unclear/> immediately you hate it</u>
<u n="215" who="S0310" trans="overlap">first day first day after they come back from their placement they were usually people who had gone to investment banks and they were usually absolutely devastated and they said but that's all I ever wanted to do I hated it I hated it and now I don't feel I don't anything and that's much better to find out then than in the year after you know?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but thank goodness yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0310">much better which is the real value of placements cos you can find out what you don't want as well</u>
<u n="219" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0310">but with that sort of model it's very very limiting really because you're only ever going to do one placement or possibly two at most erm but you know that's where sort of networking can expand it so you know one of the other things that we had was a sort of <unclear/> database of graduates from <anon type="place"/> over the last what ten years</u>
<u n="221" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0310">he said yes I'll talk to them I'll talk to them about what I do so you could you know you could give them plenty of opportunities to sort of network you know this is the logistics manager you know ring him on one wet Friday afternoon in February and ask him what he's doing</u>
<u n="223" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0310">and so it's the what students are best at well you say well how are they different now? what they're a bit better at now is actually assessing their own skills but in that what we found and what I felt really quite strongly was what they'd actually forgotten or had had been bypassed was actually what was important to them what their values were</u>
<u n="225" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0310">erm because I think we push skills and skills and skills</u>
<u n="227" who="S0267">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0310"><foreign lang="lat">ad nauseam</foreign> for years and the reason we've done that is because that's what the employer is buying</u>
<u n="229" who="S0267">and competitiveness</u>
<u n="230" who="S0310">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well the employer now also wants erm sound literacy</u>
<u n="232" who="S0310">yes yes that's one of the skills yes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so what's happening now er with people you know who might have masters and goodness sort of knows what but they can't string a grammatically correct sentence together so what's? how are the universities going to handle that or how are they handling that</u>
<u n="234" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm but they can't spell no mm no right <pause dur="short"/> ah yes I mean there's more and more going to university and so that problem is is greater and</u>
<u n="235" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0310">you know I mean but there are employers who are employing who are taking out contracts with language companies to check letters which their graduates write but only where there's a market shortage so they have to recruit people who don't pass you know their their numeracy test one of the tests that they frequently do demand that students do is is numeracy and and erm literacy</u>
<u n="237" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0310">and erm you know we used to run practice ones of those and erm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0267"><unclear/> er going into the foreign office</u>
<u n="240" who="S0310">yes</u>
<u n="241" who="S0267">you do a</u>
<u n="242" who="S0310">classic</u>
<u n="243" who="S0267">yes a classic <unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0266" trans="overlap">my niece failed that three times she was an A star straight student all the way through</u>
<u n="245" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0266">but she couldn't pass it for the life of her</u>
<u n="247" who="S0310">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0266">I don't ah is it asking for something that's</u>
<u n="249" who="S0267" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> it's three Rs actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0266" trans="overlap">is it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0267">well it's</u>
<u n="252" who="S0310" trans="overlap">no I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0267">the online test was a little bit like that there was reasoning verbal reasoning and er</u>
<u n="254" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I think it's</u>
<u n="255" who="S0310">there used to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but are you talking in your childhood?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0267">eh no no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s he he went for the that's why I know about the foreign office he did it online</u>
<u n="258" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm mm did he do a practice test beforehand</u>
<u n="259" who="S0267" trans="overlap">and erm no I just thought <unclear/> when we used to do the bond books he knows all about that do you remember when he was a child we did all the bond books and er you know because he got into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0267">er school which is a boys' grammar erm and then he just sits down and and has been out of the the educational system for some years</u>
<u n="262" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0267">and then just sits down do one of these test without doing</u>
<u n="264" who="S0310">I mean it's about the technique of doing it as well</u>
<u n="265" who="S0267">absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0266" trans="overlap">exam skills</u>
<u n="267" who="S0310">and about you know it's about what what questions are worth doing</u>
<u n="268" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0310">erm is this going to take me too long?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0310">erm and erm you know it is worth practising that you know <unclear/> I mean it was like our most popular session was the practice test</u>
<u n="272" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0310">yes we used to give them individual feedback erm numeracy was the one that most people were duff at</u>
<u n="274" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="275" who="S0310">erm and erm and numeracy is the one which responds to practice more than literacy and spatial reasoning do so erm you know the various online practice things available but yeah but I mean apart from anything else the civil service <unclear/> is one of the toughest ones</u>
<u n="276" who="S0267">yeah it is actually yeah yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0310" trans="overlap">very tough yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0266">and erm do you keep up with? do you trace or follow any of your former students?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm the government demands that we do</u>
<u n="280" who="S0266">oh right but or any that you've had a personal interest in?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0310" trans="overlap">so all these stats <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> not like I used to years ago because there's so many</u>
<u n="282" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0266">but have <trunc>y</trunc> have any become sort of great huge high flyers?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0310">erm oh yes I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what's his name from <anon type="place"/> is what's his name I can't remember his name now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0266">I don't know</u>
<u n="286" who="S0310">his <trunc>hi</trunc> I mean he's CEO of <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="288" who="S0267" trans="overlap">oh he went through there mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0310">erm yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0266">did he go through your hands?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0310">erm oh it would have been before my time</u>
<u n="292" who="S0266" trans="overlap">or your department?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0310">I don't know but er erm I mean the what I <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> real high flyers would probably be probably pretty limited because <anon type="place"/>'s a very new university in proportion to you know <anon type="place"/> and whatnot</u>
<u n="294" who="S0267" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0310">erm but er there were certainly plenty that got good starts and plenty that would come back and talk to students erm and came back for things like careers fairs and so on erm <pause dur="short"/> yes so I mean going back to the do you keep in touch? erm the <trunc>gove</trunc> it's a government requirement that erm we collect destination data for all of them and that's a responsibility that's always delegated to careers services so you have teams on the phone over a period of five or six weeks in the</u>
<u n="296" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0310">usually February March time to find out what they're doing six months afterwards</u>
<u n="298" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0310">and that's what makes the league tables and they classify we classify the jobs erm according to how good they are in a way so the government can produce you know X percent go into graduate level jobs and X percent don't</u>
<u n="300" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0266">so now you've retired and you've had a year</u>
<u n="302" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0266">have you sorted yourself out as to what you're going to do or have you just sort of sat and relaxed for a while?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0310" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I did go back to erm er well I I know I know very well a person who was my opposite number at <anon type="place"/> and she knew I'd retired and she rang me about last July or so and said we've got a problem she said I've got a space I've got a gap for a careers adviser and it's terribly busy in the autumn can you come? so I went back for about three days a week or something in the autumn time to the University of <anon type="place"/> which completely different institution which was really fun it was really nice</u>
<u n="305" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0310">erm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0267">but listening to you you know erm it's very hard to just retire and and and leave all of that behind when it's actually a really big level of career <unclear/> day to day basis</u>
<u n="308" who="S0310" trans="overlap">yes yes it is yes yeah it's erm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0267">so it would would be good to use your expertise somewhere</u>
<u n="310" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0310">mm I mean the really sad thing is</u>
<u n="313" who="S0267" trans="overlap">even in a voluntary capacity I mean <unclear/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0310" trans="overlap">oh yeah yes yes I couldn't be bothered with the hassle of charging people it's just not worth</u>
<u n="315" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0266">yeah but you might do something completely different you're going to the art classes?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0310">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0266">but that's nearly we'll have that one as another conversation I think</u>
<u n="319" who="S0267"><unclear/> challenging <unclear/> in my case I <trunc>pref</trunc> you know <unclear/> is challenging keeps my brain ticking but erm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0310">yes I I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0267" trans="overlap">I panic at art though cos it's not just you know but really there there are the things that eh you need to engage yourself with I think couple of days a month at least</u>
<u n="322" who="S0310">yes</u>
<u n="323" who="S0266">so what what else do you do now? you go to these art classes which we'll talk about another time</u>
<u n="324" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm mm yes yes erm oh I was the school governor at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh right that's very worthy</u>
<u n="326" who="S0267" trans="overlap">oh very good</u>
<u n="327" who="S0310">erm what else have I been doing? i've been doing some family history but that's that and that's really quite interesting because I've kind of tried to go out sideways a bit so we've actually had four trips to meet relations that I've either never met before</u>
<u n="328" who="S0267"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0310">or haven't seen since childhood which has been rather fun</u>
<u n="330" who="S0267" trans="overlap">did you did did you do this through erm erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s ancestry erm package <unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0310" trans="overlap">there's quite a lot of yeah there's quite a lot of different packages</u>
<u n="332" who="S0310" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0310">erm most of what I used is I didn't find ancestry very sort of</u>
<u n="334" who="S0267">accommodating or? <unclear/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0310">I didn't find that the options for the searches were terribly efficient</u>
<u n="336" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0310">I do but I think you can have a fortnight free can't you on ancestry?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0267">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0310">I did pay to register with the ordinary UK census online</u>
<u n="340" who="S0267">very good</u>
<u n="341" who="S0310">erm and I've just started to look at what's it called the <trunc>fam</trunc> the Mormon one the family search family search</u>
<u n="342" who="S0267" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0310">but that's better because it's got parish records in it as well</u>
<u n="344" who="S0267">mm it's a huge thing though isn't it? all time consuming</u>
<u n="345" who="S0310" trans="overlap">it's mammoth yes it is you can get <trunc>ab</trunc> completely addicted</u>
<u n="346" who="S0267" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0266">right thank you ladies</u>
<u n="348" who="S0310">mm</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
