<text id="SVLZ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:43:43</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0684 S0685 S0686</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Car journey from Cornwall to South Wales</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Politics, family history, driving</topics>
		<activity>Discussion about politics on a car journey</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0684">
				<exactage>58</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Aberystwyth</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Wales</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>39 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Freelance book editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Catonese -- grew up in Malaysia</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0685">
				<exactage>57</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Nantyglo, Monmouthshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Welsh</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Aberystwyth</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Wales</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>34 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>wales</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>wales</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>wales</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Professor</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0686">
				<exactage>22</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aberystwyth</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Neutral British</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Aberystwyth/Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Wales/England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years/ 4 years (as a student)</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0684">is this European funded?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0686">erm no it's a lot of it's Chinese-backed investments</u>
<u n="3" who="S0684">but you're not gonna <unclear>get</unclear> that here</u>
<u n="4" who="S0686">no no no Manchester's a very desirable place to be at the moment</u>
<u n="5" who="S0685">well it's become a business area</u>
<u n="6" who="S0686">well the thing is if there's no you know either <pause dur="short"/> either the young people they they stay and they're jobless there you know they don't have much of a a future in these towns so they leave and the towns themselves don't have any teachers because all the young people leave</u>
<u n="7" who="S0685">yeah it's a bit strange <trunc>goi</trunc> I was in the <trunc>c</trunc>car going back one night with er with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my pal and</u>
<u n="8" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0685">he said you know you know everybody respects you here because you've got away you've made something of your life and I thought <pause dur="short"/> that was dreadful <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know</u>
<u n="10" who="S0686">what that people respected you? or that</u>
<u n="11" who="S0685">for that</u>
<u n="12" who="S0686" trans="overlap">for that?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0685">for that for that that you'd actually done it you'd actually up and left</u>
<u n="14" who="S0684">it's the same with all places I mean in <anon type="place"/> if you've gone away and made something of your life you're respected more than if you stay</u>
<u n="15" who="S0685">mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't think I could have stayed I mean er I you know there's a point where you feel like your home town is like your parents you know they are <unclear/> so that you can carve your own life and <anon type="place"/> was so different in many ways from the valleys it could have been <unclear>sixteen</unclear> sixteen hundred miles away not <unclear>sixteen</unclear> miles away but <pause dur="short"/> you know in a sense and I've I've gone that far from home that it's</u>
<u n="16" who="S0686">having gone that far from what sorry?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0685">well you know it's it's you know I thought it was just <unclear/> it's not not really a huge feat it's not like it's gone and lived in a foreign country</u>
<u n="18" who="S0686">it does feel like a a different world though</u>
<u n="19" who="S0685">it is significantly different</u>
<u n="20" who="S0686" trans="overlap">another world yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah erm I'm more comfortable down here than I am in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0686">what with the people?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0685">yeah I can read them down here you you can have</u>
<u n="24" who="S0684" trans="overlap">er do I turn here? no</u>
<u n="25" who="S0685">no</u>
<u n="26" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0685">you can have this very kind of dry humour</u>
<u n="28" who="S0686">yeah you want that one</u>
<u n="29" who="S0685">is it? <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0686">no it's redirected you</u>
<u n="31" who="S0684">is it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0686">it was yeah it's redirecting you</u>
<u n="33" who="S0684">I've got to turn the car</u>
<u n="34" who="S0685">there's a kind of dry humour here that you can operate on erm which is very kind of not deflating of others but self-deflating</u>
<u n="35" who="S0686">do you think it's friendlier?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0685">yeah I do</u>
<u n="37" who="S0684">do you not think so?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0686" whoConfidence="low">it's difficult to know cos it you know the <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0685">in some ways they're a little shy of outsiders erm but once they get to know you they're very loyal</u>
<u n="40" who="S0684">now which way do I go?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0686">go down</u>
<u n="42" who="S0685">down</u>
<u n="43" who="S0686" whoConfidence="low">that way <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0684">I can't see</u>
<u n="45" who="S0686">because you don't get that many outsiders</u>
<u n="46" who="S0684">er?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0685">well it's built on outsiders cos it was a large Jewish Irish Italians smaller Spanish populations</u>
<u n="48" who="S0686">now I mean I don't</u>
<u n="49" who="S0685">not now</u>
<u n="50" who="S0686">you don't get many visitors do you?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0685">no but you know it was it wasn't a town because of the industrial revolution it was built on immigration</u>
<u n="52" who="S0686">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0685">so we've always had erm <pause dur="short"/> it I suppose it thinking like the chapels and the collieries were the were the kind of common denominators it wasn't about</u>
<u n="54" who="S0684" trans="overlap">well why were they voting against</u>
<u n="55" who="S0685" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't know I mean you wouldn't get all that many Polish people moving into <anon type="place"/> area or <anon type="place"/> area you don't get the</u>
<u n="56" who="S0686" trans="overlap">well that yeah that's what they were saying you know like people some people in the valleys have said you know oh immigration sort of things but</u>
<u n="57" who="S0685">it doesn't affect them up there</u>
<u n="58" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah the it's got the lowest levels I think of migrant population in the UK around here</u>
<u n="59" who="S0685">but it's it's in a</u>
<u n="60" who="S0684">cos there are no jobs here</u>
<u n="61" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0686">that's <unclear>very true</unclear></u>
<u n="63" who="S0684" trans="overlap">why would anyone want to move here?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0686" trans="overlap">well I think to me you know a possible explanation could be that you know there there are no jobs there is you know lots of people who don't see a future and they think something has to change and you know they you know the way that the EU has been made a scapegoat</u>
<u n="65" who="S0684" trans="overlap">but this is not</u>
<u n="66" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0684">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0686" trans="overlap">for everything that that they think it's that you know you're going well maybe if we leave Europe there'll be er you know more jobs and</u>
<u n="69" who="S0684">this is how</u>
<u n="70" who="S0686" trans="overlap">for their future but</u>
<u n="71" who="S0684"><unclear/> is made isn't it? by people believing things that are not true <unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah it's just also a history completely forgotten it's about education in the end <unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0684">this is how the Nazis rose isn't it?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0686">well the rise of nationalism and er poor economic times yes</u>
<u n="75" who="S0684">yeah and people thought that oh maybe they the Nazis had the the answer</u>
<u n="76" who="S0686">or that's it isn't it? yeah and <pause dur="short"/> it the the the parallels are frightening but also the lack of recognition of the parallels is also frightening and people don't they don't know they don't remember <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0684">is there going to be a movement now to get back into the EU? or eventually</u>
<u n="78" who="S0686" trans="overlap">well there is there is yeah but that someone I heard like someone said on the radio the other day in erm in twenty twenty years' time it's going to be country that is full of people who want to be in the EU and they will have left because of and the people who voted to leave the EU will have died</u>
<u n="79" who="S0684" trans="overlap">died <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0686">and you know in twenty years' time people are gonna have to live with the consequences of that decision that they didn't want to take</u>
<u n="82" who="S0685" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0684">it seems very selfish doesn't it?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0686">it is and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said they voted for their children didn't they as much as anything</u>
<u n="85" who="S0684">grandchildren</u>
<u n="86" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0686">and it does seem selfish to take a decision based</u>
<u n="89" who="S0684" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="90" who="S0686" trans="overlap">on purely on yourself</u>
<u n="91" who="S0684">well they can see too how much money the EU is putting into</u>
<u n="92" who="S0686">oh yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="93" who="S0684" trans="overlap">the region</u>
<u n="94" who="S0686">I I I you'd think in Wales with all these EU-backed projects you'd be able to see that most of all</u>
<u n="95" who="S0684">because it was all er er up on all the boards</u>
<u n="96" who="S0686">it is you see it on the signs you know EU-funded and everything like this</u>
<u n="97" who="S0684">is it the newspapers so the media <unclear/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0686" trans="overlap">probably yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0684"><unclear/> you know like the Daily Mail or</u>
<u n="100" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0684">you don't know what the Sun was did the Sun and the</u>
<u n="102" who="S0686">oh the Sun was massively</u>
<u n="103" who="S0684" trans="overlap">the Mirror?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0686">pro-Brexit yes the Mirror was as well</u>
<u n="105" who="S0684">well there you are <pause dur="short"/> they wield so much power</u>
<u n="106" who="S0686">you you sell copies by speaking out against the government</u>
<u n="107" who="S0684">David Cameron was a Eurosceptic you know</u>
<u n="108" who="S0686">mm he was yeah but <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="109" who="S0684">well he was best placed actually to argue the case for Europe <pause dur="short"/> but people just weren't listening you you could you could say anything and they wouldn't listen</u>
<u n="110" who="S0686">no no well I don't</u>
<u n="111" who="S0685" trans="overlap">well I think part of it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0684"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0685">was because he was <unclear/> but</u>
<u n="114" who="S0686">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I think Jeremy Corbyn had a much larger role to play that wasn't played</u>
<u n="115" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0686">erm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0684">if he had spoken out we might be in a different</u>
<u n="118" who="S0686">well who knows who knows? I think stronger lead a stronger leader definitely may have er significantly changed things</u>
<u n="119" who="S0684">he didn't seem fazed by the <pause dur="short"/> referendum result did he?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0686">he didn't no he didn't seem like he cared and in contrast you know a politician who I don't particularly like David Cameron was you could see he was near tears when he was announcing his resignation as was his wife you know you felt you know okay I you know I don't I don't like him I don't agree with him but he's obviously had has his convictions and he</u>
<u n="121" who="S0685" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0686">and he believes in them</u>
<u n="123" who="S0684">but it's because they're <unclear/> isn't it? and the people who'll <trunc>v</trunc> the <unclear/> which is going to choose the next leader is <pause dur="short"/> strongly anti-Europe</u>
<u n="124" who="S0686">well they don't choose the next leader themselves I don't think</u>
<u n="125" who="S0684">no they but they put forward the candidates</u>
<u n="126" who="S0686" trans="overlap">they put forward two candidates yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0684">yeah well there you are</u>
<u n="128" who="S0686">but I think a lot of people are hoping to knock Boris out before that cos otherwise they think there'll be a surge <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0684">maybe Theresa May will be a good uniter</u>
<u n="130" who="S0686">erm I don't like her er at all <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure whether Iain Duncan Smith isn't being named because it would like a step backwards given that he'd already been leader in the past</u>
<u n="131" who="S0684">but he's behaved with a bit more integrity hasn't he?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0686">he <trunc>ha</trunc> he has yeah he has but my <trunc>probl</trunc></u>
<u n="133" who="S0684" trans="overlap">but Theresa May is was pro-Europe but she didn't take part in the</u>
<u n="134" who="S0686">I think it was a</u>
<u n="135" who="S0684" trans="overlap">campaign</u>
<u n="136" who="S0686">tactical move wasn't it?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0684">maybe</u>
<u n="138" who="S0686">she saw what was going on</u>
<u n="139" who="S0684">what don't you like about her?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0686">erm it was her who put forward this bill for the thirty-five thousand pound migrant cap</u>
<u n="141" who="S0684">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0686">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's that's quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0684">and she <trunc>want</trunc> oh which one? the European erm human rights legislation</u>
<u n="144" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="145" who="S0684">why?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0686">erm it's to do I thought that was to do with erm the work that MI6 were doing overseas</u>
<u n="147" who="S0684">sorry?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0686">which was suspect because she's erm Home Secretary</u>
<u n="149" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0686">she erm a lot a a within the remit of her role is intelligence services</u>
<u n="151" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0686">so I thought it was something to do with erm that and sort of data privacy as well as erm maybe imprisonment of a terror suspect as well I think so you know this erm how you can hold people without charging them for a longer period and things like that?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0684">which way is is this the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0685">I think it's the <anon type="place"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0686">I remember coming this way er to see <unclear/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0685">right</u>
<u n="157" who="S0686">this is the way we came I remember this bridge <pause dur="short"/> but also erm one of the things I don't like is how people now after the referendum are saying oh erm neither side provided us with enough information about how to vote and I think part of being a responsible sort of active citizen is doing your own research and finding out like you were saying about the miners</u>
<u n="158" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0686">sort of came together to</u>
<u n="160" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0686">to <trunc>b</trunc> to buy this library and to sort of educate themselves I think that's</u>
<u n="162" who="S0685">oh with the internet though there's not really any excuse</u>
<u n="163" who="S0686" trans="overlap">no yeah was</u>
<u n="164" who="S0685"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0686">absolutely no excuse all the information was out there and I don't I I really don't like this sort of ideology that you have to be spoon-fed everything</u>
<u n="166" who="S0685">oh could have just just read the BBC pages that would have been enough to</u>
<u n="167" who="S0686" trans="overlap">well <trunc>absolut</trunc> yeah it wasn't it wasn't difficult and I think the problem of that is is that you end up with these people who do believe everything that they read and everything they see they don't fact check and so when</u>
<u n="168" who="S0685" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0686">they say you know</u>
<u n="170" who="S0684" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0686">the front page of the Daily Mail that says you know immigrants are the number one cause of unemployment erm and strain on our public services in the UK they believe it because they don't they don't check the facts they don't do their <trunc>re</trunc>research because I think</u>
<u n="172" who="S0684">well the but people like Boris Johnson are going to <unclear>reap the</unclear> referendum result for their own ends and to say this is about people being outside er <trunc>a</trunc>about Europe and it isn't it's against the austerity measures and</u>
<u n="173" who="S0686" trans="overlap">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="174" who="S0684">the comeback and and and the lack of funding</u>
<u n="175" who="S0686">well</u>
<u n="176" who="S0684" trans="overlap">but they're not going to they're not going to pay any attention to that</u>
<u n="177" who="S0686">well I think for people like Boris Johnson it's about their political careers really it's not it's</u>
<u n="178" who="S0684">no</u>
<u n="179" who="S0686">I don't think it will ever for Boris Johnson be about the good of the people</u>
<u n="180" who="S0684">I dunno I mean David Cameron to some extent he's got integrity hasn't he?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0686">he does and I think he believed in what he did I I don't like what he did</u>
<u n="182" who="S0684" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0686">but at least you know what you can say of him you see that he had the conviction in his beliefs and the integrity to follow them <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0684">what's the Travelodge in <anon type="place"/> like?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0685">basic <pause dur="short"/> I might go back there or at least try the <unclear/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0684">can you stay in a Wetherspoon's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0685">no not at the town</u>
<u n="188" who="S0686">Wetherspoon's never do rooms I don't think</u>
<u n="189" who="S0684">they do</u>
<u n="190" who="S0686">really? did they?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0685" trans="overlap">that one isn't a hotel</u>
<u n="192" who="S0684">I think in Shrewsbury they do</u>
<u n="193" who="S0686" whoConfidence="low">oh right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0684">you sure it's er not a hotel?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0685">yeah I think I've enquired</u>
<u n="196" who="S0686">Travelodge is always a bit spartan when I've stayed there before</u>
<u n="197" who="S0685">it's okay though I mean it's</u>
<u n="198" who="S0686">well it's a clean and it's it's a bed to sleep in</u>
<u n="199" who="S0685" trans="overlap">it's I was very I mean I was not there very much</u>
<u n="200" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0685" trans="overlap">cos I was travelling around so <pause dur="short"/> but there were a number of mining museums and things like the the the miner library that I'd liked to have gone into but I arrived at the wrong time last time <pause dur="short"/> it'll depend how this steelwork project pans out I think</u>
<u n="202" who="S0686">what what what's the latest that's happening? has it been bought out by this Indian</u>
<u n="203" who="S0685">oh it</u>
<u n="204" who="S0686" trans="overlap">it was under Indian ownership wasn't it?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0684" trans="overlap">and they said it was <unclear/> we should</u>
<u n="207" who="S0686" trans="overlap">without this British</u>
<u n="208" who="S0685">yeah there was the</u>
<u n="209" who="S0686" trans="overlap">oh I remember now yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0685" trans="overlap">cos it's become problematic at the moment erm because it affects so many different sites not just</u>
<u n="211" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0685" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> are just simply for the <trunc>p</trunc>project that I'm working on you know they're not seeing giving copyright er you know a priority at the moment for discussions</u>
<u n="213" who="S0686">no</u>
<u n="214" who="S0685">so all I can do is just they the <anon type="place"/> have given me access to the high er high density images which now I can work with with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on but even if I can't put anything in the public domain until copyright is cleared</u>
<u n="215" who="S0684">and what if it doesn't clear?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0685">well you know you've got a there's no reason why it won't clear you know if the the they're not gonna hang onto the copyright of <unclear>two thousand</unclear> year old glass plate slides are they?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0684">or if want a lot of money?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0685">no they won't they've given it to the <trunc>li</trunc> to the library but they haven't bequeathed the copyright <pause dur="short"/> so the library can put it online so it's public access but for me to work on plates I need the copyright</u>
<u n="219" who="S0686">I imagine it's just getting somebody to sign the <unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> yeah the woman who is in charge of it is on maternity leave so that's another problem <pause dur="short"/> and working with the <anon type="place"/> is another problem cos they're so <unclear>tardy</unclear> and er it's <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0684"><unclear/> here <pause dur="long"/> where are we now? this is <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0685">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0684"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0686">I hope David Cameron isn't <pause dur="short"/> is not remembered for this because that seems unfair</u>
<u n="225" who="S0684" trans="overlap">he will be</u>
<u n="226" who="S0686"><unclear>just cos they don't like him</unclear> so he will be?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0684">he will be</u>
<u n="229" who="S0685" trans="overlap">so like Blair will be remembered for the war</u>
<u n="230" who="S0684">but he did a lot of good before that</u>
<u n="231" who="S0685">yeah but that seems to be eclipsed by the very you know or I mean when it goes bad it goes seriously bad</u>
<u n="232" who="S0686">he secured the first Conservative majority for decades didn't he?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0684">oh did he? <unclear/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0686">almost twenty years</u>
<u n="235" who="S0684"><unclear/> it would have been better if he <unclear/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0684">if the Lib Dems had gone with them again they would have knocked them and he wouldn't have had to honour</u>
<u n="238" who="S0685">well it would also have</u>
<u n="239" who="S0684"><unclear>have delayed the</unclear></u>
<u n="240" who="S0685" trans="overlap">preserved Liberal party</u>
<u n="241" who="S0684">sorry?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0685">it would have preserved the Liberal party</u>
<u n="243" who="S0686">well now the Liberal Democrats are saying if they are elected that they will er go back on the erm Brexit result and they won't invoke erm Article fifty <pause dur="short"/> but erm it's one of those things they can do because they know they'll never be elected all all they can do is strengthen their position within Westminster</u>
<u n="244" who="S0684">but they did a lot when they were in coalition</u>
<u n="245" who="S0686">they did but they</u>
<u n="246" who="S0684" trans="overlap">but people didn't see it</u>
<u n="247" who="S0686">they're unelectable for</u>
<u n="248" who="S0684">yeah it's just</u>
<u n="249" who="S0686" trans="overlap">years now</u>
<u n="250" who="S0684" trans="overlap">it's a shame that no one recognised that they punched above their weight they stopped the Conservatives doing</u>
<u n="251" who="S0686">they did but they went back on some of the most crucial promises that they made <pause dur="short"/> tuition fees</u>
<u n="252" who="S0684" trans="overlap">well you know in coalition you cannot</u>
<u n="253" who="S0685">but they didn't they</u>
<u n="254" who="S0686" trans="overlap">but that was their one that was why young people voted for them and that's why people felt cheated because their that was their almost their flagship policy wasn't it? tuition fees</u>
<u n="255" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah as <trunc>betr</trunc> I mean that was another betrayal <unclear/> or of a different order <pause dur="short"/> I mean if the Conservatives</u>
<u n="256" who="S0684">this is worse though</u>
<u n="257" who="S0685">were limping on a minority it would have been perfect cos they wouldn't have been able to do this</u>
<u n="258" who="S0686">oh this is this is far worse yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0686">but</u>
<u n="261" who="S0685">I mean it would have been slow to pass laws and so forth but otherwise things would have been intact <pause dur="long"/> but you can only see that with hindsight can't you?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0686">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0684">the Labour party is is <unclear/> between two groups isn't it?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0684">the middle class liberal and <pause dur="short"/> the traditional socialist <pause dur="short"/> working class</u>
<u n="266" who="S0686">well I don't I think anyone really knows the difference between the Liberal Democrats and Labour any more what is what is the difference? what's the ideological difference between the two parties?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0686"><vocal desc="laugh"/> because <trunc>La</trunc>Labour are you know quite centre left now aren't they? and you know Liberal</u>
<u n="269" who="S0684" trans="overlap">Lib Lib Dems are very pro-Europe they always have been</u>
<u n="270" who="S0686">oh yeah absolutely but</u>
<u n="271" who="S0684">and they're more they're particularly concerned about <unclear/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0686">yeah but the official <trunc>u</trunc> er Labour party line was that they were pro-Europe</u>
<u n="273" who="S0684">which was not <unclear/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0686">I think well Labour were far well more pro-Europe than the Conservatives were as a whole <pause dur="short"/> in terms of the MPs in Westminster</u>
<u n="275" who="S0684" trans="overlap">did the majority of Tory MPs vote for Brexit?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0686">no I think about a third or a quarter between those sort of figures voted for Brexit and the rest rest voted to remain so it was as in terms of total number of MPs in the House of Commons it was erm it was far below a hundred so less than a sixth of all MPs erm so if it was you know if we actually erm adhered to parliamentary democracy like we do for almost literally every other decision that's taken</u>
<u n="277" who="S0684" trans="overlap">on <unclear/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0686">in the UK then erm we'll be fine <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0684">what do all your friends think?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0686">erm erm some are in the position of most like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they're all quite politically engaged so erm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0684">what does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> think?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0686">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is absolutely disgusted as is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm you know they were they were all as angry as I was</u>
<u n="283" who="S0684">almost?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0686">no all as</u>
<u n="285" who="S0685">have to have a talk with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about this</u>
<u n="286" who="S0684">I'd say he would have been upset</u>
<u n="287" who="S0686">yeah I think he's probably been</u>
<u n="288" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0684">furious yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0685">incensed by Corbyn</u>
<u n="291" who="S0684">yeah he'll be even more incensed by him him</u>
<u n="292" who="S0686">by who?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0684">Corbyn</u>
<u n="294" who="S0686">oh</u>
<u n="295" who="S0685">well he really despises Corbyn</u>
<u n="296" who="S0686">cos he's a member of the Labour there isn't he?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0686">do you know who he voted for in the</u>
<u n="299" who="S0684" trans="overlap">Andy Burnham</u>
<u n="300" who="S0686">Andy Burnham? <pause dur="long"/> I think Andy Burnham would have <pause dur="short"/> actually connected with the working class socialists <unclear/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0684" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0686">a lot better than Corbyn has</u>
<u n="303" who="S0684" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0686">because of his background</u>
<u n="305" who="S0684">why? does he come from a council estate?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0686">I don't think so I think he's he came from like a lower middle class sort of family but he grew up in the north you know he saw all the problems in the north as he grew up you know they were all around him</u>
<u n="307" who="S0684">he's from the same neck of the woods as Jeremy Corbyn isn't he?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0686">is Corbyn from the north?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0684">yeah I think so is he <unclear/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0686" trans="overlap">he's got a house I thought <pause dur="short"/> jeremy Corbyn? well</u>
<u n="311" who="S0684" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0686" trans="overlap">why's he got a house in Islington then?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0684">because he's an MP</u>
<u n="314" who="S0686">for Islington</u>
<u n="315" who="S0684">I don't know look it up I thought he was <unclear/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0685"><unclear/> constituency unless you're in the shadow cabinet</u>
<u n="317" who="S0686">because he lived he lived in Islington before he was head of the Labour party</u>
<u n="318" who="S0684">ah yeah I don't know <pause dur="short"/> have a look I I thought he was from near Liverpool</u>
<u n="319" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="320" who="S0684">maybe I'm wrong maybe I'm getting him muddled up with Andy</u>
<u n="321" who="S0686">where is where's Andy Burnham again? is he</u>
<u n="322" who="S0684">he's a scouser</u>
<u n="323" who="S0686">is he scouser?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0684">from is it the Wirral or Liverpool or <unclear/>? also during the leadership campaign you didn't quite know what he stood for</u>
<u n="325" who="S0686">I thought he I thought that was an unfair criticism that's levelled at him because I thought during the leadership debate he was the person who actually you know cut cut through you know all that political crap that people spout you know and answered the questions so if someone asked him something he answered it you know? it was it was refreshing to me and erm <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>d</trunc> I I thought he I felt like people had it out for him <pause dur="short"/> but like I liked him I still do like him I think he's a you know he's a good politician he's sort of a good one</u>
<u n="326" who="S0684">he'll make a good mayor then</u>
<u n="327" who="S0686">sorry?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0684">he'll make a good mayor</u>
<u n="329" who="S0686">I think so I hope so <pause dur="short"/> I I do hope that David Lammy having lost the mayoral candidacy erm will consider running as Labour because last time</u>
<u n="330" who="S0684" trans="overlap">was he standing against Sadiq Khan?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0686">yeah yeah he said last time er somebody asked whether he would stand apparently erm the leader of the Labour party and he said erm no no he was gonna concentrate his efforts on his er campaign to be London mayor</u>
<u n="332" who="S0684">but not everyone feels up to the job do they?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0686">they don't but</u>
<u n="334" who="S0684">they might not want to</u>
<u n="335" who="S0686">they might not want to but I hope</u>
<u n="336" who="S0684">Alan Johnson was asked and he said no didn't he?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0686">yeah Dan Jarvis was asked as well and he said no</u>
<u n="338" who="S0684">Alan Johnson's gone back to his guitar</u>
<u n="339" who="S0685" whoConfidence="low">has he?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0684">I expect it's not rock any more it's more folky now</u>
<u n="341" who="S0685">right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0684">you know he became a politician because he er his guitar got stolen?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0686">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0684">yeah and then somebody somebody sent him another one I think it was <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but he's from er a very deprived background talks about living in one room and having next to nothing to eat no wait he's from the north no I dunno I can't remember but anyway so <pause dur="short"/> but he's not a bad chap is he?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0685">no</u>
<u n="346" who="S0684">has he ever stood for leader?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0685"><unclear/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0684"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0686">Alan Johnson?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0684">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0686">erm I'm too young to you know remember the anything but the last <trunc>leadersh</trunc> leadership erm campaign because Gordon Brown got handed it</u>
<u n="352" who="S0684">oh</u>
<u n="353" who="S0686">by Tony Blair didn't he so</u>
<u n="354" who="S0684" trans="overlap">well you were still <unclear/> about it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0686">erm and I don't remember Tony Blair</u>
<u n="356" who="S0684" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0686">was back in the nineties wasn't he? so erm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0684">Tony Blair?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0686">I don't remember that</u>
<u n="360" who="S0684">and his er agreement</u>
<u n="361" who="S0686">education education education or something</u>
<u n="362" who="S0685"><unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0684">that it's the reason education was the key to everything</u>
<u n="364" who="S0686">I</u>
<u n="365" who="S0684" trans="overlap">and</u>
<u n="366" who="S0686">I</u>
<u n="367" who="S0685" whoConfidence="low">it is</u>
<u n="368" who="S0684">it is but he</u>
<u n="369" who="S0685" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">it is</u>
<u n="370" who="S0684">didn't act on it did he?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0686">no <pause dur="short"/> I think and a lack of education is why we we have left Europe but I think it's it's not just the education system it's our attitude towards it as a as a country</u>
<u n="372" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0686">yeah like you know teachers aren't respected</u>
<u n="374" who="S0684"><unclear>oh you're clever</unclear></u>
<u n="375" who="S0686">not respected erm professionally people don't want to find out things for themselves you know they learn the bare minimum they have to pass exams</u>
<u n="376" who="S0684" trans="overlap">I think you'll find that's true all over the world</u>
<u n="377" who="S0686">but I think actually I think you'll find that the more unjust your <trunc>syste</trunc> your country government are that like the more engaged people are with elections and election results erm I read a good piece I can't remember who want journalist it was by but he said if you go to African countries which are having their first democratic elections and you talk to anybody on the street you know a fishmonger someone who sells bread erm <pause dur="short"/> they're they're engaged you know with what's happening what's going on they're excited they know about the candidates they they know what they stand for and you know they have their own opinions on the economy on erm things like the you know the prison system and things like that have <vocal desc="laugh"/> and that's just completely absent from from our society I feel you know you go out you you you know this when the BBC do these erm sort of talk to passers-by on the high street? you despair at what people say</u>
<u n="378" who="S0685">they're inebriated by the type of low grade entertainment of which things like the X Factor you know it's that kind of</u>
<u n="379" who="S0684" trans="overlap">distraction</u>
<u n="380" who="S0685">it is they are distracted they they are stupefied by the media in some respects</u>
<u n="381" who="S0684">the media tells them what to think</u>
<u n="382" who="S0685">and it's well and also it removes the state in which to think because they fill it with entertainment</u>
<u n="383" who="S0686">I think maybe also they're <pause dur="short"/> the readiness like the availability of information having it so readily available like all the time can can breed laziness because it's you think oh I can look that up I can look that up and people never do</u>
<u n="384" who="S0685">no it's er you know the difference between information and knowledge isn't it?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0685">I mean knowledge and understanding</u>
<u n="387" who="S0684" trans="overlap">and understanding</u>
<u n="388" who="S0685">er cos I remember when I was young and I was you know the only person ever to go into higher education in the entire family that was a kind of moment of family rejoicing though and people did respect the fact that you went into <pause dur="short"/> you know you'd got er in though in the sense you know of not a very likely candidate</u>
<u n="389" who="S0686">why? because you weren't academic in school?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="391" who="S0686">were there people who were? well <trunc>h</trunc> you know people who were Oxbridge candidates and things like that</u>
<u n="392" who="S0685">yeah we had people going to Oxford every year from our school</u>
<u n="393" who="S0686">oh right</u>
<u n="394" who="S0684">like the big school?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0684"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0685">and they but it was they were former grammar school students</u>
<u n="398" who="S0684">mm?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0685">you know in our school</u>
<u n="400" who="S0684" trans="overlap">going to the town centre?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0685">mm?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0684">we're going to the town centre</u>
<u n="403" who="S0686" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0684">oh</u>
<u n="405" who="S0685" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">we could probably</u>
<u n="406" who="S0684"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0685">but what you did have was a strong sense of erm the education that you have the prospects you have had been bought for you not given to you by the government but bought for you by your <unclear>forefathers</unclear> cos they struggled to get er education I mean I the primary school I went to is called the <anon type="place"/> school and the <anon type="place"/> school was not</u>
<u n="408" who="S0684" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="409" who="S0685"><trunc>st</trunc>state funded it was funded by the chapels</u>
<u n="410" who="S0684">was it?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0685">they built the building <pause dur="short"/> in fact the you know that's that's one of the major differences to the working class today is that they expect the government to do it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0685" trans="overlap">back in my grandfather's day they people would said you want that</u>
<u n="414" who="S0684" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0685">do it yourself</u>
<u n="416" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0685">you know find the money</u>
<u n="418" who="S0684">and er</u>
<u n="419" who="S0686" trans="overlap">ask not what <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="420" who="S0684" trans="overlap">and well</u>
<u n="421" who="S0686" trans="overlap">what your country can do for you</u>
<u n="422" who="S0685">yeah that's the</u>
<u n="423" who="S0684" trans="overlap">that's what</u>
<u n="424" who="S0686">yeah no</u>
<u n="425" who="S0684">that's what the Tories are saying that that that that they're complaining about the working class relying on state welfare</u>
<u n="426" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah there's a measure of that that is true I think of of a kind of culture of dependence of you know a culture of I deserve this</u>
<u n="427" who="S0684">no matter how many children you have</u>
<u n="428" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0684" trans="overlap">the state's gonna help you provide for them</u>
<u n="430" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah yeah er there <trunc>wa</trunc> there wasn't that so you you know families helped families you know and that er do you remember when we were talking about that sense of everybody being a relative that was an expression of that sense of commitment to one another beyond the bounds of of of blood</u>
<u n="431" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0685">and of course things today people will tend to be much more apathised into their little world</u>
<u n="433" who="S0684" trans="overlap">what does what does blood mean? I mean look at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I mean what does blood mean <unclear/> when when they're ill and they they die and you don't even hear?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0685">well yeah there's always those contradictions for the you know again but it wasn't always like that like in your family it wasn't always you know a nuclear war against one another was it? families deteriorate you know you've got a you've gotta you've gotta work hard</u>
<u n="435" who="S0684" trans="overlap">but even <unclear/> that's how people felt towards one another</u>
<u n="436" who="S0685">yeah cos they they were up against common problems <pause dur="short"/> you know there was bickering of course and there were still fallings out <pause dur="short"/> people would be but the consensus was that or a sense of solidarity rather <pause dur="short"/> which is why Conservatism could never work because the sense of the individual before <trunc>s</trunc>social just didn't run that it had made no sense <pause dur="long"/> but nobody was saying you know certainly when the mines were open you know that you were expected to follow in your father's footsteps and go down the mine I mean they would say for goodness sake if you can get out and do something else go get it was horrible</u>
<u n="437" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0685">it was a really horrible job</u>
<u n="439" who="S0686">we don't have miners in our family do we?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0685">yes</u>
<u n="441" who="S0684" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="442" who="S0686">how far back?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0685">erm well it depends my mother worked in in the coal mines</u>
<u n="444" who="S0686">who did?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0685">my mother</u>
<u n="446" who="S0686">your mother worked in the mines?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0685">yeah my mother was a <unclear/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0684" trans="overlap">not inside the mines</u>
<u n="449" who="S0685" trans="overlap">no on accountancy for the mines</u>
<u n="450" who="S0686" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="451" who="S0685">er her mother cleaned for er mining for the miners who er for the</u>
<u n="452" who="S0684">mine owners</u>
<u n="453" who="S0685" trans="overlap">mine owners she was a kind of maid er your <trunc>grandfa</trunc> both your grandfathers were coal miners er your great uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they were miners the only person who wasn't a miner was my father</u>
<u n="454" who="S0686">going back to what you were saying though about <pause dur="short"/> erm about people's sense of entitlement to to things like</u>
<u n="455" who="S0685" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0686">education it's so if people don't have to work for something that they</u>
<u n="457" who="S0684" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0686">take it for granted then they don't they don't appreciate the value of it necessarily do you think?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0685">no but I think that there's</u>
<u n="460" who="S0684">that's a problem the <unclear/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0685" trans="overlap">there is there is an entitlement to education I think</u>
<u n="462" who="S0686">I think yeah there's an entitlement but <trunc>peo</trunc>people take it for granted</u>
<u n="463" who="S0685">yeah no but</u>
<u n="464" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="465" who="S0685"><trunc>i</trunc>in the old days when people were paying you know where education was paid from tax and so forth the the the argument for entitlement was not from the person who wanted education it was from the parents of them who said we have paid for this therefore they are entitled</u>
<u n="466" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0685">to a free education</u>
<u n="468" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0685">but it's not a free education we have paid it</u>
<u n="470" who="S0686">no <trunc>absol</trunc>absolutely but</u>
<u n="471" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0685">yeah I mean why</u>
<u n="473" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0685">it it it is surely one of the signs of a of a developed civilisation that there is free available er <trunc>educa</trunc> that anybody regardless of their background and regardless of whether they were born in this country or not</u>
<u n="475" who="S0684">how come Germany can afford it?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0685">well it's partly if you have the conviction that that is what should be <unclear/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0684">well you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to say she was they were Conservative voters I'm sure she couldn't stand the way do you remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0684">who had a son erm do you remember him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0686">no</u>
<u n="481" who="S0684" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he used to dress in girls' clothes sometimes</u>
<u n="482" who="S0686" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="483" who="S0684">erm she worried about <unclear/> she had him as the result of a one night stand erm I think deliberately and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to complain that you know she just relied on on welfare and she thought it was very unfair and that's why she voted Conservative right she didn't like these scroungers so you know single issues like that become the pretext for voting for a <trunc>partic</trunc> for a party</u>
<u n="484" who="S0686">that's not that's not how it should be</u>
<u n="485" who="S0684">no but</u>
<u n="486" who="S0686" trans="overlap">but it is no</u>
<u n="487" who="S0684" trans="overlap">that's how people <unclear/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0686">because I dunno when I when you think about it from the ground up you know how how do you how do you you know how do you come up with sort of concepts you know like parliamentary democracy? you think you know okay we want a democracy where everybody you know gets an equal say so you know how you know how do we do that? and you think you know but</u>
<u n="489" who="S0684" trans="overlap">but so many things are unequal</u>
<u n="490" who="S0686">yeah well</u>
<u n="491" who="S0684">like understanding and</u>
<u n="492" who="S0686">it is but</u>
<u n="493" who="S0684">access to information <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0686">I'm not sure about access to information</u>
<u n="495" who="S0684">we can't everybody I mean</u>
<u n="496" who="S0686">in this country</u>
<u n="497" who="S0684">like if you grew up in the valleys <vocal desc="cough"/> and you didn't you know you you're your background <vocal desc="cough"/> your family background it makes a difference to your attitude</u>
<u n="498" who="S0686">yeah <trunc>absolu</trunc></u>
<u n="499" who="S0684" trans="overlap">to accessing information</u>
<u n="500" who="S0686" trans="overlap">no absolutely</u>
<u n="501" who="S0684" trans="overlap">on the internet</u>
<u n="502" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0684"><vocal desc="cough"/> if your family didn't read books <unclear/> background and things <unclear/> website for information they would rely on the newspapers</u>
<u n="504" who="S0686">yeah well if you're if your family wasn't politically engaged it's probably highly likely they could grow up not politically engaged as well</u>
<u n="505" who="S0684">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0686">that's I think that's you know it's a fact of life but they think it's any excuse that you can't sort of develop that later on? you know</u>
<u n="507" who="S0684" trans="overlap">apparently it's harder</u>
<u n="508" who="S0686">it's harder yeah but I don't I still don't think of it as an excuse it explains it but I don't think you know just because somebody's grown up you know around crime for example is not an excuse for them to become a criminal it explains you know it explains it but</u>
<u n="509" who="S0684">but <pause dur="short"/> different factors work against you</u>
<u n="510" who="S0686">they do yeah but I think</u>
<u n="511" who="S0684" trans="overlap">and you've got so many more obstacles to overcome</u>
<u n="512" who="S0686" trans="overlap">but I think education should be used as a force to sort of reduce the <trunc>in</trunc>inequality</u>
<u n="513" who="S0684">yeah it depends on how good that education is</u>
<u n="514" who="S0686">it does it does yeah but</u>
<u n="515" who="S0684">it's like</u>
<u n="516" who="S0686">it's what</u>
<u n="517" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0686" trans="overlap">it's not only you know it's it's what's taught as well I've always been a firm believer that</u>
<u n="519" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0686" trans="overlap">politics economics should be taught in school as</u>
<u n="521" who="S0684" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0686">compulsory</u>
<u n="523" who="S0684">underprivileged black people in America for example even</u>
<u n="524" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0684">they they it's a vicious cycle of</u>
<u n="526" who="S0686">mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0684">crime and drugs that is very very hard to break free from</u>
<u n="528" who="S0686">it is yeah but yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0684">it's the same in this country</u>
<u n="530" who="S0686">it is but I think <pause dur="short"/> I think ultimately you know the the blame has you know it has to lie with the individual but you know there are <trunc>obv</trunc> there are other factors that that contribute to it and make it so much harder for some people <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ul</trunc> at the end of the day everyone is responsible for their own actions <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0684">why don't you go into politics?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0686"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0685">well you can because there's a lot of people who started in law that went into politics</u>
<u n="534" who="S0686">I think often</u>
<u n="535" who="S0684" trans="overlap">if you go into local <trunc>cou</trunc> go onto local councils start like that</u>
<u n="536" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah no I think often the best politicians though are those that have like real life experience you know</u>
<u n="537" who="S0684" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0686">not just been politicians all their lives</u>
<u n="539" who="S0684" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0686">but you know know about something else so you know it's something that I wouldn't rule out in later life because I do there are things that I really do feel passionately about but I think it's not something that I'd want to do as a career like you know for my whole life because I think <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="541" who="S0684" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="542" who="S0686">that's not the brand of politics that I believe in</u>
<u n="543" who="S0684">you can <unclear/> locally</u>
<u n="544" who="S0686">you can yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="545" who="S0684" trans="overlap">in local politics</u>
<u n="546" who="S0686">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> I think that's where a lot of people see the most difference in their lives day to day</u>
<u n="547" who="S0684"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum was involved she was a local councillor wasn't she?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0685">oh yeah? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0686">yeah Canada's <trunc>Cana</trunc>Canada's cabinet is made up from people</u>
<u n="550" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0686">you know their science</u>
<u n="552" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0686">and erm science and environment minister is actually someone with a PhD in science and you know erm their business secretary is a successful business er business I can't remember whether they're a man or a woman businessman or woman</u>
<u n="554" who="S0684">yeah no I read that</u>
<u n="555" who="S0686">yeah it's</u>
<u n="556" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="557" who="S0686">I dunno it's it's just fantastic isn't it? you know</u>
<u n="558" who="S0684">what they were chosen</u>
<u n="559" who="S0686" trans="overlap">well cos they're just in</u>
<u n="560" who="S0684">for that</u>
<u n="561" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0684">for that reason?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah but they understand these things you know you Michael Gove was placed as justice secretary with a degree in English and fine there's nothing wrong with a degree in English but <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't imagine he knew you know very much about the intricacies about a legal system <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0684">they rely on advisors don't they?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0686">well I they they do but what why put someone in that position who doesn't know about it? you know you should be the most</u>
<u n="566" who="S0684" trans="overlap"><unclear>because they're your friend</unclear></u>
<u n="567" who="S0686" trans="overlap">qualified person yeah that well that's it isn't it?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0684">where you want with them or you play tennis with him <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="long"/> what was he thinking?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0686">I don't think they were gonna back out into the road to be honest</u>
<u n="570" who="S0684">no but you shouldn't start where were they why were they backing?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0685">I think he started to go he wanted to get a view of the of the river <unclear>or something</unclear></u>
<u n="572" who="S0686">how far out are we?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0684">how far out?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0686">yeah from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0684">one hour twenty-two minutes</u>
<u n="576" who="S0686">okay are you okay driving?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0684">so far keep talking</u>
<u n="578" who="S0686"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just keep talking</u>
<u n="579" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0686">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="581" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0684">you used to be one who talked nonstop <pause dur="short"/> this often resets between <pause dur="short"/> er <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> you know I dunno why</u>
<u n="584" who="S0685" whoConfidence="low">whereabouts? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0684">so what what was it when I bought petrol yesterday the figure?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0686">I can't remember</u>
<u n="587" who="S0684">two three five was it?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0686">I I honestly can't remember mum <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
