<text id="SVNZ">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:23:16</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-07</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0022 S0023</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers’ home, Hungerford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Daily Routine; vices – cigarettes and alcohol; common sense vs. intelligence; different cultures/feminism</topics>
		<activity>Husband and wife sitting on the sofa talking about various real and hypothetical situations</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0022">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kettering, Northamptonshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hungerford, Berkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>PA to director</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- Advanced; Spanish -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0023">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Taplow, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hungerford, Berkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>IT consultant</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0022">okay so we're recording now?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0023">yep</u>
<u n="3" who="S0022">okay so tell me about your day cos you haven't done that yet</u>
<u n="4" who="S0023">oh well I think it was raining on the way it was a bit miserable <pause dur="short"/> eh but it cheered up a lot this afternoon and then when I was there the day went past pretty quickly and I did eh</u>
<u n="5" who="S0022" trans="overlap">did you have to deal with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0023">no</u>
<u n="7" who="S0022">well that was lucky</u>
<u n="8" who="S0023">yeah it was good <pause dur="short"/> I did a useful errand though I went to Sainsbury and got some milk <pause dur="short"/> that was my I got some money out of the kitty</u>
<u n="9" who="S0022">okay</u>
<u n="10" who="S0023">and em bought some milk for the tea</u>
<u n="11" who="S0022">well just for oh okay</u>
<u n="12" who="S0023">well no it's shared milk <pause dur="short"/> if you get em the milk there's a shared pot of money but it goes in the fridge</u>
<u n="13" who="S0022">okay</u>
<u n="14" who="S0023">and even if we're fifty people em well because there are fifty you'll find it doesn't last very long</u>
<u n="15" who="S0022">no <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="16" who="S0023">did you go shopping?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0022">em no <pause dur="short"/> I went to the gym and em then I went swimming and em so I didn't after that I didn't want to go to em shops with wet hair and we didn't really need anything so no I didn't</u>
<u n="18" who="S0023">mm fair enough</u>
<u n="19" who="S0022">that was that <pause dur="short"/> okay so shall I ask you one of these questions?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0023">yeah go on</u>
<u n="21" who="S0022">okay <pause dur="short"/> which vice would you indulge in if it had no side effects?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0023">smoking</u>
<u n="23" who="S0022">why?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0023">because it's lovely</u>
<u n="25" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/> In what way is it lovely?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0023">well you know if you are ever feeling a bit stressed you go you can have a nice cigarette and it calms you all down although it actually stresses the body but it relaxes the mind and you can em eh get an excuse to go outside as well and have a chat with people and get away from from the desk</u>
<u n="27" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0023">but it isn't very good for your health</u>
<u n="29" who="S0022">it isn't <pause dur="short"/> but even before the smoking ban came in there were lots of places who chose not to have they chose to be non-smoking <pause dur="short"/> wasn't that a pain to have to go outside all the time?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0023">eh well I'd already stopped before the ban came in so it didn't really affect me</u>
<u n="31" who="S0022" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> okay but how do you I mean if you are a non smoker you <trunc>s</trunc> smoke smells horrible <pause dur="short"/> if someone blows smoke in your face it tastes horrible <pause dur="short"/> how do you get past that?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0023">how do you how did you get past it?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0022">well what I mean is that your first for most people the first taste of cigarette is horrible</u>
<u n="34" who="S0023">yeah it's just to push past it <unclear/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0022">I know but why would you push past it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0023">oh I see  I see  em well I first smoked a pipe which is a bit unusual but that was very strong it nearly made me sick when I first tried it <pause dur="short"/> but I thought I'd be like Sherlock Holmes and very clever so</u>
<u n="37" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0023">so I eh I tried that and that was oh terribly strong but I did push past it <pause dur="short"/> it's funny it's a bit like drinking beer I never liked beer for years</u>
<u n="39" who="S0022">no that's true</u>
<u n="40" who="S0023">but I sort of I trained myself to do it by just trying it</u>
<u n="41" who="S0022">okay</u>
<u n="42" who="S0023">it's funny what you'll do in the cause of em sociability I suppose</u>
<u n="43" who="S0022">did you have many friends that smoked?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0023">eh yes yes a few</u>
<u n="45" who="S0022">oh</u>
<u n="46" who="S0023">there was a bit of peer pressure involved</u>
<u n="47" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0023">so I took up cigarettes after a year or two of pipe smoking</u>
<u n="49" who="S0022">okay</u>
<u n="50" who="S0023">you've never smoked though have you?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0022">well em <pause dur="short"/> not</u>
<u n="52" who="S0023">ah I'm gonna get a confession now</u>
<u n="53" who="S0022">well no you could  you could  never say that I smoked as such <pause dur="short"/> but em I think I <trunc>ha</trunc> first tried smoking like many other things I hasten to add when I was twenty-one</u>
<u n="54" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0022">and em <pause dur="short"/> I didn't mind it <pause dur="short"/> I'd sort of take other people's cigarettes and have a drag and I kinda quite</u>
<u n="56" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0022">like almost sort of liked it and then if I went to parties or something then I might just sort of take some cigarette and have a drag and and that was it</u>
<u n="58" who="S0023">well I didn't know that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0022" trans="overlap">and I kind eh well I know but I didn't know you then <pause dur="short"/> I kind of liked it <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then I was in Italy em and then I I did that one night and then I inhaled oh my god I nearly died</u>
<u n="60" who="S0023"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0022">so that was the end of that I think <pause dur="short"/> oh and then when I was in Poland I em my friends had these cigarettes that cost the equivalent of forty P a packet so you can imagine what they were like</u>
<u n="62" who="S0023">lovely</u>
<u n="63" who="S0022">em yeah so that was but I think that was the last eh the last time I actually tried a cigarette</u>
<u n="64" who="S0023">it was a cigar wasn't it?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0022" trans="overlap">was eh was yeah on our wedding day when I tried your cigar and it was revolting <pause dur="short"/> so yeah that was my experience of smoking</u>
<u n="66" who="S0023">mm <pause dur="short"/> that was a good question <pause dur="short"/> what would be eh your answer to it?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0022">what my my preferred vice?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0023">yeah presumably not smoking?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0022">not smoking em well I've never really been interested in in drugs so cos I don't well I'm gonna contradict myself here <pause dur="short"/> I was going to say I don't like the idea of a mind-altering substance cos I'd like to be in control but then I was going to say alcohol</u>
<u n="70" who="S0023">right</u>
<u n="71" who="S0022">so I would love to be able to think oh you can drink not not to getting really drunk but <pause dur="short"/> I think now you you just have to you know after every glass of wine you have to think ooh I shouldn't do this I shouldn't do that and I thought oh I just wish if that was removed so you could have <pause dur="short"/> I don't know half a bottle of wine a night</u>
<u n="72" who="S0023">do you find it has more more or less of an effect as you get older?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0022">em probably more</u>
<u n="74" who="S0023">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="75" who="S0022">I think I had I think but there are I think the trouble is though that alcohol is is well wine is em is stronger new world wine is stronger and em</u>
<u n="76" who="S0023">well that's just</u>
<u n="77" who="S0022" trans="overlap">and that stuff that's fifteen percent the stuff we just had</u>
<u n="78" who="S0023">it's not us getting weaker then <pause dur="short"/> as we get older</u>
<u n="79" who="S0022" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well it is a bit of both</u>
<u n="80" who="S0023">yeah I think</u>
<u n="81" who="S0022">I think it is a bit of both and I think if you I think if you're <pause dur="short"/> the trouble is that if you're tired you need a lot of sleep but of course wine although or any alcohol <pause dur="short"/> although it it sends you off to sleep quite quickly initially it it stops you <pause dur="short"/> I think it stops you having good regular sort of deep sleep patterns <pause dur="short"/> so you wake up in the middle of the night and need to go to the loo or need a drink of water or whatever</u>
<u n="82" who="S0023">yeah it makes you thirsty</u>
<u n="83" who="S0022">whereas and also I think that em because the trend is to drink more wine with things like red wine you have all the congealers and and things that I think can give you more of a headache whereas if you have</u>
<u n="84" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0022">something like gin or vodka I think that <trunc>ob</trunc> obviously it's still got the alcohol effect but I think the whole sort of fuzzy head thing is less likely to happen <pause dur="short"/> so yes if it had no  if it had no  effect on your health then yes I'd love to be able to sort of drink a social amount of alcohol let's say I do <pause dur="short"/> and how how brilliant would it be to drink and not have to worry about driving?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0023">ah that would be handy</u>
<u n="87" who="S0022">what if you could drink and and it it could relax you but it you could still drive? That would be so cool because we could go out to restaurants and things</u>
<u n="88" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0022">and not have to worry about thirty pounds for a taxi</u>
<u n="90" who="S0023">that's right it would save money on taxis and it's so annoying when other people are having fun and you're not <pause dur="short"/> I mean you can have fun but it there's a certain point when people have been drinking and they're laughing so much more easily than normal and you're sitting there going mm that wasn't so funny</u>
<u n="91" who="S0022">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah there's nothing worse than being really sober in front of loads of people a bit squiffy <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0023" trans="overlap">but you don't get in the mood <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I hate that <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit annoying but yeah you should probably get used to it and you know around here you have to drive don't you?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0023">so em yeah that that would be a good drug to invent now wouldn't it? One with no eh no after effects or you could take an antidote straight away and it would cure you and then you'd be back to normal that's</u>
<u n="95" who="S0022">but I don't  I don't  Well I was going to say I don't take alcohol primarily for the  for the  effect but I must do to a certain extent because if I didn't then I'd just have Ribena which would be a lot cheaper</u>
<u n="96" who="S0023">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0022">if it really if the effect really didn't have any <pause dur="short"/> effect</u>
<u n="98" who="S0023">as opposed to what the taste you mean? I suppose</u>
<u n="99" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah because like for example it's always  it's always  struck me as rather odd like say something like vodka and em <pause dur="short"/> say if you have vodka and orange it it just tastes like orange</u>
<u n="100" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0022">and I've always thought that was a bit odd because why would you have an alcoholic drink that you can't taste?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0023">so you can get drunk</u>
<u n="103" who="S0022">well yeah I know but I I always think that sounds really really immature <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather have something that I like the taste of</u>
<u n="104" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0022">but anyway <pause dur="short"/> should we do you do you ask me one of your questions</u>
<u n="106" who="S0023">okay <pause dur="short"/> which is more important intelligence or common sense?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0022">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> well this is an interesting one <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="108" who="S0023">I mean you could say you've got so much of both my love that's wonderful</u>
<u n="109" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0023">but maybe a more eh you know descriptive answer would help</u>
<u n="111" who="S0022">well that's very interesting isn't it? Because you hear about these people ah like well <pause dur="short"/> I was going to say maybe people that are on the sort of autism spectrum who are incredibly clever</u>
<u n="112" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> interesting</u>
<u n="113" who="S0022">and could be very and have a really really high level of intelligence but they can't  they can't  deal with the most basic things</u>
<u n="114" who="S0023">so they can be brilliant at maths for example can't they?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0022">yeah yeah but it's</u>
<u n="116" who="S0023" trans="overlap">but then they can't do up their trousers or something ridiculous</u>
<u n="117" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0023">or cross the road or certainly they're poor at social skills aren't they? Traditionally</u>
<u n="119" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yes yes a lot of people who have got very high intelligence</u>
<u n="120" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0022">em I suppose eh from a sort of survival point of view common sense is more important but but do you know what you how often have you and I said that if people just  if people just  did the job they had to do and and got on with it then it would be so much</u>
<u n="122" who="S0023">but what's that then?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0022">businesses would run so much smoothly <pause dur="short"/> what do you mean?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0023">what's that common sense or intelligence?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0022">no that's common sense to me</u>
<u n="126" who="S0023">mm mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0022">so for example oh I don't know em if I'm <pause dur="short"/> if I'm ringing up about your em if I'm ringing up about your car insurance and I want to ask something really really you know really sort of basic that isn't that's that's <pause dur="short"/> I can't think of an example say I want to ask a really basic point</u>
<u n="128" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0022">that basically I'm ringing up cos I'm doing your admin you're at work and blah blah blah and then say oh no we can't give it to you because em</u>
<u n="130" who="S0023">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0022">because of what's that stupid law? The Data Protection Act or something</u>
<u n="132" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0022">but then having said that it's probably not their fault but what else? Em <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> I can't think of an example now but em what do you think?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0023">well I think it's a  it's a  bit of a trick question really because if you  if you  have one without the other you're really a bit stuck</u>
<u n="135" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0023">and what is common sense apart from intelligence that's become a regular you know eh activity <pause dur="short"/> I suppose what they mean by common sense perhaps is the things people do habitually which isn't quite the same as intelligence so you know it would take a lot of intelligence to eh to invent the bicycle but it doesn't take eh but it only takes common sense to say em eh to ride it just practice <pause dur="short"/> there's a different level of skill that's involved there</u>
<u n="137" who="S0022">that thing's gone off <pause dur="short"/> is it alright?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0023">em hopefully it's still working let's find out <pause dur="short"/>  Trying to save battery probably</u>
<u n="139" who="S0022">em I suppose you wouldn't have you'd have no em you'd have no well would you? Well I was going to say that you wouldn't have like some brilliant inventors <pause dur="short"/> would you have those without intelligence? Would you have brilliant businessmen? Would you have Steve Jobs without intelligence? You you don't create something like em the iPad just from common sense do you or do you? Maybe because some of the things some of the useability of say an iPad or an iPod or an iPhone or whatever is is more sort of intuitive than than using a sort of traditional computer</u>
<u n="140" who="S0023">I think my yeah <pause dur="short"/> you might <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know what you're saying <pause dur="short"/> what there're getting at I think is that if you have intelligence apart from real life then it's inapplicable</u>
<u n="141" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0023">and it seems like Spock say in Star Trek <pause dur="short"/> you don't know who Spock is do you?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> well I know who he is</u>
<u n="144" who="S0023">he's the one with the pointy ears <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="145" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0023">he basically he lives by logic and he has no emotions or very few and so he is seen as intelligence but without eh he has got common sense though but he just doesn't have feelings so <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0022">I suppose it's it's it's interesting isn't it how you define them but I suppose the the question sort of getting at the sort of the basic sort of <trunc>ra</trunc> rationalizing</u>
<u n="148" who="S0023">yeah that's yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0022">as opposed to thinking of greater <pause dur="short"/> for example if em when I think of intelligence I think of people who are maybe sort of quite academic who can <trunc>ap</trunc> ah who can apply  who can apply  stuff <pause dur="short"/> em like someone like my dad who's very he can  he can learn  he can learn stuff sort of by rote but he can't apply it at all</u>
<u n="150" who="S0023">so how do those terms apply to him?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0022">em well what I'm thinking of obviously not very clearly is that to me intelligence is something that is more academic that is a  is a  higher level <pause dur="short"/> it is thinking of say for example em when you start reading between the line or if you're  if you're  studying literature and you start looking at symbolism and <trunc>y</trunc> you're you kind of have to <trunc>lo</trunc> look for things that isn't look for things that aren't sort of staring at you</u>
<u n="152" who="S0023">oh okay</u>
<u n="153" who="S0022">and you have to almost make deductions about things mainly</u>
<u n="154" who="S0023">so logical logical original thinking and identification of the facts as opposed to doing things out of habit would be one way of looking at it</u>
<u n="155" who="S0022" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="156" who="S0023">well I think you could do a question now cos it was a bit tricky that one</u>
<u n="157" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It was quite tricky wasn't it?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0022">ah this is interesting <pause dur="short"/> which other culture other than this presumably <pause dur="short"/> which other culture would you choose to be born into?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0023">ooh culture?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0023">so that could be any time or place couldn't it? Is that right?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0022">eh possibly</u>
<u n="164" who="S0023">em well I'd say Greek civilization</u>
<u n="165" who="S0022">really?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know they'd be a lot of things bad about it but eh it was an incredible time I mean ancient Greece in the time of eh Aristotle and Plato and people like that</u>
<u n="167" who="S0022">but you wouldn't have electric blankets or iPods</u>
<u n="168" who="S0023" trans="overlap">I know but it's warm in Greece I wouldn't worry about that <pause dur="short"/> but you'd have this amazing culture that was blossoming and changing for the better and making discoveries every like day every day but I think at an incredible pace <pause dur="short"/> and their worship of eh eh art and em their their view of man and so on I think was it would be refreshing and em and thoroughly enjoyable <pause dur="short"/> obviously very threatening because of all the wars and so on that people had then and you wouldn't be as safe but it would be eh an exhilarating sort of time</u>
<u n="169" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0023">I think</u>
<u n="171" who="S0022">mm that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="172" who="S0023">probably wouldn't live nearly as long we'd be dead by now probably</u>
<u n="173" who="S0022">no <pause dur="short"/> that was quite interesting cos I'm thinking as a woman I think</u>
<u n="174" who="S0023">eh</u>
<u n="175" who="S0022">the first thing that springs to mind with me is thinking okay what culture do women have em near equality with men?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0023">Good point</u>
<u n="177" who="S0022">em <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I would kind of think of contemporary cultures and em I mean even if I think about  even if I think about  Europe even if I think say southern Europe they're still more patriarchal I'd say than we are <pause dur="short"/> em eh I think if you go towards northern Europe then they're probably more equal but then em you've probably got socialist em politics</u>
<u n="178" who="S0023">eh mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0022">em then that I suppose that leaves America which I haven't really thought about</u>
<u n="180" who="S0023">it varies a lot depending on which part you go to as you know</u>
<u n="181" who="S0022">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0023">very very different</u>
<u n="183" who="S0022">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but there's still it's a funny thing because although I mean I think that em <pause dur="short"/> although there are  Although there are  there are areas obviously where women haven't got equality with men I think Britain is is pretty high in the list</u>
<u n="184" who="S0023">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0022">but every now and then you still come across real sort of misogyny and these sort of dark age ideas em</u>
<u n="186" who="S0023">like when?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0022">well I was thinking about oh gosh a few weeks ago I was just listening to Jeremy Vine and he was oh there was some story about a Canadian policeman who said to  who said to  women if you don't want to get raped then don't dress like sluts or something like that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0022">and and first of all I thought well that is goes back to our common sense cos that's kind of common sense but then I was listening to what people were were were ringing in with and there was such misogyny <pause dur="short"/> there was this idea that em well you know if you flaunt it what do you expect? And I thought oh I know okay okay so if a woman suggests that she might be em she might be interested in maybe meeting a man then it's alright for any man to just come and take her <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's absolutely ridiculous</u>
<u n="190" who="S0023">were any of the callers women?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0022">yeah they were old women</u>
<u n="192" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah interesting</u>
<u n="193" who="S0022">em but there another <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah this morning I was watching em your favourite darling Big Fat Gypsy Weddings and em it was talking about who gypsies who had married non-gypsies and how some of their relationships work and some of them haven't cos they have in their in the gypsy culture it's a very you know the women stay at home look after the they look after the children they and they clean  they clean  all the time <pause dur="short"/> the men sort of are real men they drink and they fight you know eh deal with horses and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and I kind of thought from watching it I thought the relationships which are most likely to work is when you have a gypsy marrying a <trunc>non</trunc> a gypsy woman marrying a non-gypsy man because a a a non-gypsy man probably isn't gonna be too worried about a woman that wants to stay at home and look after the children and clean a lot</u>
<u n="194" who="S0023">no he'd be jolly glad probably</u>
<u n="195" who="S0022">whereas the opposite if you had a non</u>
<u n="196" who="S0023">oh yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0022">gypsy woman</u>
<u n="198" who="S0023">yes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0022">and her husband expected her to clean all the time and you know</u>
<u n="200" who="S0023">yeah that wouldn't work</u>
<u n="201" who="S0022">never change a nappy and and not be present at the birth of a child and all the rest of it I think that would be harder</u>
<u n="202" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0022">but anyway <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm not quite sure what other culture I would like to be born in em but I suppose it would have to be it eh but eh definitely have to be and maybe even somewhere like Australia I think</u>
<u n="204" who="S0023">but in the present time you mean?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0022">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> I think you know I couldn't be in a time where there was for example no contraception I mean that would be unthinkable</u>
<u n="206" who="S0023">oh yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0022">couldn't be in a time where you know women couldn't be couldn't give their opinions on things</u>
<u n="208" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0022">so</u>
<u n="210" who="S0023">well good answer I think</u>
</body>
</text>
