<text id="SVPK">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-10-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0444</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living room while watching TV</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Work and friend’s relationship with boyfriend. </topics>
		<activity>Girl chat</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, complaining, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements, apologising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0444">
				<exactage>25</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Oxford, UK</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Pearson marketing executive</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0444">that would be my point cos it's just a point of principle that I don't really wanna take the job search too far</u>
<u n="2" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0444">while I'm not on full hours because I just don't think that's <unclear/> application</u>
<u n="4" who="S0439">oh no of course not no</u>
<u n="5" who="S0444">and I know a lot of people would apply <pause dur="short"/> and be like I'm ill but who cares but er from both sides apart I don't wanna apply to a company when I'm still poorly and achieve <unclear/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0439">and also you kind of don't wanna turn <pause dur="short"/> not turn your back on <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> but you don't wanna be like oh you've supported me through my illness and now <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="7" who="S0444">and now I'm fucking off</u>
<u n="8" who="S0439">now I'm pissing off yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0444">or I've used that tack you'd never want it to be the case that they'd turn round and be like oh but you were on sick leave then but were you that sick?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0439">yeah exactly yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0444">if you could search for job and that's not</u>
<u n="12" who="S0439">you don't wanna damage your relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0444">and also don't want it to be the case where they think oh we moved you from a certain subject to another one and you weren't happy so you've now left and it's kind of like well <pause dur="short"/> yeah it it doesn't look great</u>
<u n="14" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0444">but I'm just like you know what?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0439">but after six eight months I think that's probably fine</u>
<u n="17" who="S0444">yeah I mean that's the thing like the hospital treatment is like the first batch of it is pretty much coming to an end erm and then they're going to reassess and see what more <unclear/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0444">cos the problem is that everyone else in the <unclear/> that I've been going to has been receiving lots of extra help from their doctors and their GPs or other hospitals</u>
<u n="20" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0444">so I haven't had anything <pause dur="short"/> like my doctor er you know nobody has been telling me how many hours to do</u>
<u n="22" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0444">and what is good and what is bad and what to look out for nobody</u>
<u n="24" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0444">I've been trying to dictate all of this myself and I could've got it completely wrong in some in fact in some ways I think I have erm which is why I'm struggling with <unclear>this problem</unclear></u>
<u n="26" who="S0439">but if you've never <trunc>bee</trunc> you've never been through this before <pause dur="short"/> like you <trunc>canno</trunc> well obviously not in a work environment so</u>
<u n="27" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no not in a working context <pause dur="short"/> and that's the thing and <pause dur="short"/> when I went to the when I talked to the specialist they were like what? you mean you've had no help? and I was like no the GP just said that you guys would sort me out with this <unclear/> they were like oh right at the end of the like you know the three appointment programme well we'll have to sit down and review what you're doing cos a lot of the people in the clinic it is really <pause dur="short"/> it's it is quite depressing in a way but they are all off work or chosen not to work or you know they they they can't walk more than ten minutes and <unclear>I'm going you know it's terrible</unclear> <unclear/> but like you know and <pause dur="short"/> some of them are bed bound and some of them go to a doctor's appointment and that's it they're laid up for a week and er <pause dur="short"/> you know it is quite extreme</u>
<u n="28" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0444">I'm not I've not ever been that bad that one appointment is enough to set me off but also</u>
<u n="30" who="S0439">but also <pause dur="short"/> I think the <trunc>dist</trunc> the difference between you is that you're driven and you don't <pause dur="short"/> you don't use this illness as an excuse</u>
<u n="31" who="S0444">no and it just <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0439">for you to <trunc>n</trunc> like get out of things cos I think I think some people would take this as like</u>
<u n="33" who="S0444">no I think</u>
<u n="34" who="S0439">take this opportunity to be like oh I need this much time off work because I've got chronic fatigue syndrome or like</u>
<u n="35" who="S0444">I miss being at work I miss</u>
<u n="36" who="S0439">yeah exactly I think you've <trunc>mi</trunc></u>
<u n="37" who="S0444">I miss being at work and I miss being able to <unclear/> and be spontaneous</u>
<u n="38" who="S0439">you've got that drive</u>
<u n="39" who="S0444">and that's what I've missed and that's what I'm starting to get back now</u>
<u n="40" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0444">is getting that bit of drive so me looking at stuff like you know I've had my inbox <pause dur="short"/> I've er got a separate inbox for it piling up of all the industry news and analysis and research</u>
<u n="42" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0444">and stuff that I find interesting</u>
<u n="44" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0444">and would use in <trunc>in</trunc> er like in interviews and things like that that's all been piling up and for the first time like in months this week I actually started to look through it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0444">and started to make notes and er and that's me starting to get that drive back and I was like oh I'm gonna go you know and I'm going on a lot of training courses over the next couple of weeks which should be quite good</u>
<u n="48" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0444"><unclear>and it helps</unclear> cos you know I've still got that question of do I want to be in marketing?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0444">is it marketing but not in a publishing industry? or is it definitely publishing that I wanna be in? but maybe not marketing</u>
<u n="52" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0444">or is it publishing but just not <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> like</u>
<u n="54" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0444">I don't know whether you can really like <pause dur="short"/> isolate the different things but I sense like er I've noticed some of the girls yesterday I just said you know cos they were asking about like the house and stuff and how that was going and I was kind of like well you know it's it it's kind of starting to run its natural course like</u>
<u n="56" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0444">it's er I'm it's kind of mm kind of done <unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0444">yeah not in any bad way but it's kind of yeah I wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>pr</trunc>like pretty much I wouldn't want to be there beyond like next December hopefully I won't be anyway if I move jobs but I was kind of saying <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I was like so it's not essentially all or none</u>
<u n="60" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0444">but actually <unclear>in the sense that</unclear> oh maybe I can do this cos you know it's starting to <pause dur="short"/> you know I could start to function a bit more I've <trunc>starte</trunc> I've had a holiday</u>
<u n="62" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0444">I'm able to have a holiday I'm able to see my friends yay</u>
<u n="64" who="S0439">and like living with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was always like it's nice and convenient and good price and stuff but it hasn't really been able to give you the freedom of living on your own</u>
<u n="65" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="66" who="S0439">or having your own space</u>
<u n="67" who="S0444">well put it this way</u>
<u n="68" who="S0439">like you've got a room but it's not the same</u>
<u n="69" who="S0444">happily</u>
<u n="70" who="S0439">mm?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0444">er <unclear/> there are ten people in the house <unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0439">oh my god why are there ten people in the house?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0444">so so there's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s the dad?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0444">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is her son</u>
<u n="76" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="77" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="long"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her daughter who is staying for a month because they've decided to move over here to England</u>
<u n="78" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="79" who="S0444">there was also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> today and yesterday who sleep over at weekends so</u>
<u n="80" who="S0439">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> friend of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="82" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0444">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had you know one or two friends like that were just round and it was like oh <unclear>I need need to get out of here now</unclear></u>
<u n="84" who="S0439">she's a forty-year-old he parties like a twenty-year-old</u>
<u n="85" who="S0444">yeah she is</u>
<u n="86" who="S0439">but</u>
<u n="87" who="S0444">I was like anyway I don't do that as a twenty-year-old like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0439">do they go in your room? do they stay in your room?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="90" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="91" who="S0444">oh gosh no no and that's one of the things I <trunc>w</trunc> like I'd <pause dur="short"/> it's it's kind of never said but they they wouldn't like</u>
<u n="92" who="S0439">yeah you rent that you buy you pay for that space and you get that space yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0444">yeah and if it has <vocal desc="laugh"/> sounds ridiculous but I've kind of done stuff like I kind of unpacked like they knew that I was coming to view so I was like well I've got all my toiletries for going away it's a bit I can just</u>
<u n="94" who="S0439">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0444"><unclear/> put my suitcase on it if they move my suitcase</u>
<u n="96" who="S0439">you'll know</u>
<u n="97" who="S0444">it's gonna be pretty obvious and usually I leave my bag in quite a <trunc>m</trunc> like a messy way especially since seeing erm <unclear/> how you do not wanna make your bed again I thought oh gosh <unclear/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0439">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos Buzzfeed is the knowledge for knowledge yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0444">oh I'm <trunc>s</trunc> I'm reading Buzzfeed articles <unclear/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0439">I read so many Buzzfeed articles <unclear/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0444">that was pretty much my life reading on the way <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0439">but I do that as well like erm when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sometimes has parties I don't mind if <trunc>li</trunc>like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this weekend letting you sleep in her room like I don't mind if she has one or two friends over who I've met and who I know</u>
<u n="103" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0439">but she had like she's had a few house parties over the summer and I was like I'm really sorry but er the one thing I don't want is anybody going in my room</u>
<u n="105" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0439">I don't want them going in my bathroom I don't want them using my room</u>
<u n="107" who="S0444">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0439">because I just don't trust them and I don't trust them when they're drunk</u>
<u n="109" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="110" who="S0439">and it's just drunk people going in your room and going through your personal things and it's just it's not fair</u>
<u n="111" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah it was like er <pause dur="short"/> it was erm <pause dur="short"/> at the house party where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> met the the guy</u>
<u n="112" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0444"><unclear/> erm <pause dur="short"/> they started like they got drunk and started putting red wine all over the stairs on the carpet and they put Coke like Coca-Cola on the walls and it was like oh gosh like</u>
<u n="114" who="S0439">and whose house was this?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0444">one of the girls from er you wouldn't know her cos she's just started <unclear/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0439">yeah <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0444">erm and it was like oh no I mean they managed to get all the stuff out but it is it is that kind of thing I mean you know yeah they have to come into my room if the fuse goes cos erm that's where the fuse box is</u>
<u n="118" who="S0439">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0444">and yeah okay some of them use the shower if they're in a hurry but usually they'll knock on the door or ask if I'm using it or you know whatever so</u>
<u n="120" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0444">so you know it is that kind of thing but to be honest it's just I don't feel like I've really been there that much I I don't</u>
<u n="122" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0444">I'm not <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really there that often cos you you know quite a lot of weekends you know I've been like I was in <anon type="place"/> and then you know and then I'll probably be at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and then I'll be at home in <anon type="place"/> and like I'm hardly ever there really like</u>
<u n="124" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I'm like when me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do spend time together we have to schedule in time together to spend as like like good friend like</u>
<u n="125" who="S0444">yeah I remember you saying yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0439">cos like this week so this week what have I done? erm Monday I was at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s because it was her last day</u>
<u n="127" who="S0444">mm yep</u>
<u n="128" who="S0439">Tuesday I went running so and I had my hair cut beforehand so I didn't come home till like half nine</u>
<u n="129" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0439">Wednesday I went I went round <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s after <trunc>h</trunc> after work and had dinner with her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> Thursday I had netball until half nine so Friday yesterday was the only day I'd actually properly seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all week</u>
<u n="131" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0439">because she'd been at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s at the weekend and I had been at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all weekend and so she wasn't here anyway</u>
<u n="133" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0439">so er yeah I because we're just so busy just seeing each other like even just being in the house for long periods of time is like I spend hardly any time in this house at the moment</u>
<u n="135" who="S0444">yeah you're so busy</u>
<u n="136" who="S0439">yeah it's manic and I like it I like being busy I like doing stuff but like this weekend it's just nice to have a chilled weekend where you just</u>
<u n="137" who="S0444">oh good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0439">no no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0444">I was <trunc>w</trunc>I was worried that I might be like depriving you of some kind of like <unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0439">oh oh no no no trust me no</u>
<u n="141" who="S0444"><unclear>oh good</unclear></u>
<u n="142" who="S0439">I have enough social stuff in my calendar to last me a lifetime</u>
<u n="143" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so yeah I'm just making you have a chilled weekend just the my worry about your life busyness I'm just like mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0439">no I'm very good thank you I am good with a nice chilled</u>
<u n="145" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0439">chilled evening I'm just gonna put the lights on though cos it's a little bit dark</u>
<u n="147" who="S0444">I was gonna say <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> I'm not liking it getting so dark so soon</u>
<u n="148" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I went to I had netball the other week and erm I went into <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s room and I was like okay <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm just popping out now to netball and then I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> why are you sitting in the dark watching TV? and she was like it just caught up with me I was like</u>
<u n="149" who="S0444">it does that to me <unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0439">yeah it just creeps up on you doesn't it?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0444">and I was like <unclear/> I don't know</u>
<u n="152" who="S0439">yeah it's really peculiar she she was like it's I I was watching it in the daylight and and now er now er dark <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0444"><unclear>and now it's</unclear> <unclear/> especially <unclear/> I don't wanna move</u>
<u n="154" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0444">I'm not moving <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0439">just a penalty dunno what accent that was supposed to be</u>
<u n="157" who="S0444"><unclear>has he</unclear> got like a glittery like number on the back?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0439">who? the South Africans?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0444">the South Africans</u>
<u n="160" who="S0439">yeah it's gold isn't it?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0444">yeah but it's kind of like a pattern so it kind of looks glittery from a distance</u>
<u n="162" who="S0439">what are they called? they're called the Springboks aren't they? what does springbok mean? is that a kangaroo or something? or? I dunno</u>
<u n="163" who="S0444">I thought it was <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0439">ah some rugby players are absolutely gorgeous</u>
<u n="165" who="S0444">what are they doing now? <unclear/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0439">oh he's having a penalty because he did a spear tackle on him</u>
<u n="167" who="S0444">oh okay <unclear>that's cool</unclear></u>
<u n="168" who="S0439">but it wasn't an intentional spear <trunc>p</trunc> spear tackle it was just kind of how he fell and he ended up rolling onto his neck</u>
<u n="169" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="170" who="S0439">and then onto his back</u>
<u n="171" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="172" who="S0439">he did like a <trunc>bi</trunc>he did like a bit of a forward roll</u>
<u n="173" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0444"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">but could you imagine a sixteen stone seventeen stone man doing a <trunc>forwa</trunc>forward roll?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's really funny there's a boy in my office called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439">and he's a very skinny kind of tallish maybe five <pause dur="short"/> ten maybe five something like that he's he's tallish he's not small erm ginger hair very skinny looks a bit like what you could imagine one of the Weasley twins to look like but not as tall</u>
<u n="180" who="S0444">yeah I've got you yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">and he plays rugby this boy is ten stone and he is playing rugby against fifteen stone boys he's twenty-two</u>
<u n="182" who="S0444">he's gonna get thrown up in the air</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">he comes into work every week with broken noses last week he came no not last week <unclear>I mean</unclear> a month ago <unclear>when</unclear> he came with a broken nose and massive bruises under both eyes he has cuts on his face he has limps</u>
<u n="184" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">and I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm sorry I'm sorry boy when are you gonna accept that just rugby is not your sport like seriously have you not thought of something like a <trunc>lis</trunc> little less contact? like cricket or</u>
<u n="186" who="S0444" trans="overlap">not your sport <pause dur="short"/> football</u>
<u n="187" who="S0439">yeah football or basketball although you're not really tall enough for basketball</u>
<u n="188" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">but badminton tennis you know there are lots of sports out there</u>
<u n="190" who="S0444">swimming</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439">swimming yeah and he's just like he was like</u>
<u n="192" who="S0444">why do you do it?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0439">he was like well I like rugby I'm good at it I'm like you might be good at it against like ten-year-olds</u>
<u n="194" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">but not against fifteen stone</u>
<u n="196" who="S0444"><unclear>I mean</unclear> he's like a featherweight really</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like there is no way like have you <pause dur="short"/> like some of these players on the pitch are like twenty years old</u>
<u n="198" who="S0444"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is like</u>
<u n="200" who="S0444">half the size yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439">half the size of them and you're just like</u>
<u n="202" who="S0444">that blondie he's like a right <unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0439">I know some of <trunc>th</trunc> er some of them are beautiful though beautiful muscly bodies</u>
<u n="204" who="S0444">but the concussion like issue is quite off-putting</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">oh yeah George North last season got concussed in three matches and wasn't allowed to play</u>
<u n="206" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0439">it's so dangerous apparently the average professional erm career span for an American footballer is four years because of the amount of <trunc>concu</trunc></u>
<u n="208" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0439">the amount of concussion they get do you remember? I know that you you'll appreciate this cos you like Gray's Anatomy as well</u>
<u n="210" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0439">do you remember that Gray's Anatomy episode where erm Mcdreamy was doing an operation on a NFL player?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0444"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="213" who="S0439">and the NFL <trunc>pl</trunc> and he was like you're such an amazing player you know I'll get you back on the pitch you know I'll help you and the NFL player was like I don't want to</u>
<u n="214" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0439">please don't fix me because if I go back on the pitch and I get concussed again I won't even remember my own child</u>
<u n="216" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0439">and he was like okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0444">but I wanna fix you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">and then they killed Mcdreamy</u>
<u n="220" who="S0444">oh my gosh I know</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439">he died he died in a car crash didn't he?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0444">I I yeah <unclear>I guess</unclear></u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">same as George to be honest that's a bit</u>
<u n="224" who="S0444">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean <pause dur="long"/> it's because they kind of announced that he was gonna leave in advance it was like oh how they are gonna get rid of him?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">but Meredith's still in it isn't she?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439">she's been doing it for a very long time now I can remember when it first started</u>
<u n="230" who="S0444">yeah it was like eleven ten or eleven years ago now</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">and that first episode where she has that one night stand with Mcdreamy</u>
<u n="232" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0439">and then kicks him out and then finds out he's her boss and you're like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0444">I didn't watch it from the beginning you see</u>
<u n="237" who="S0439">ah didn't you?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0444">I watched it a couple of episodes afterwards but my mum</u>
<u n="239" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0444">my mum and sister saw it <unclear/> oh I'll I'll watch it</u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">when she goes up to him and she's like I want you and then he's like this is my wife <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0439">she's like shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0444">I kind of wanna make <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> watch it <unclear/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0439">do you think he'd appreciate it?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0444">oh hell no</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0444">but I'm like this is why I am the way that I am</u>
<u n="249" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0444">this is why I'm all about the emotional speeches</u>
<u n="251" who="S0439"><unclear>oh I am yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="252" who="S0444">look at that like</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439">that is a good emotional speech by Meredith Gray and she's like she's like me she's awful at emotion</u>
<u n="254" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there was a Buzzfeed article I think you've probably read it Girls Who Don't Like Feelings</u>
<u n="255" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0444">I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0439">I don't like feelings</u>
<u n="258" who="S0444">but you but you are sentimental babe</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439">I am</u>
<u n="260" who="S0444">that's the thing with the people that you really care about like the postcards in the box you are really sentimental and er when you <trunc>d</trunc>when you do feel things and allow yourself to feel them things will hit you hard like</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0444">you know you're human but you kind of just</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439">in the small things <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0444"><trunc>i</trunc>it it takes it takes it takes quite a bit</u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0444">to <unclear>take it</unclear> that way</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439">takes a while <pause dur="short"/> it takes a while to get through my wall of pain and doom and</u>
<u n="268" who="S0444">you er you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are actually scarily similar</u>
<u n="269" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0444">does that sense? it's like why did I not recognise that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0444">it is quite true</u>
<u n="273" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0444">I mean I know you you might not really think the best of each other at the moment but it is quite true that like in terms of like your attitude towards people in terms of like when <unclear>you make your judgements</unclear></u>
<u n="275" who="S0439">I'm sure we'd get on</u>
<u n="276" who="S0444">I think it was just not really the right context or whatever and it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I think I was just <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think I was just angry at him that he kind of ruined your birthday</u>
<u n="278" who="S0444">oh that's alright <pause dur="short"/> I had a nice birthday</u>
<u n="279" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0444">I liked just seeing everybody it was so nice like</u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0444">having you there having like the <anon type="place"/> guys there having the <anon type="place"/> guys there having <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there having <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> turn up later on like it was just so nice having a day like</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0444"><unclear>everybody</unclear> <unclear/> was there <unclear/> erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">like I'm definitely not somebody who celebrates their birthday though in March and I'm not someone who thinks that the world should revolve around me on my birthday and stuff but</u>
<u n="286" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439">I just expected a bit more from him that was all <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0444">I don't know we we we we aired it out</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439">good</u>
<u n="290" who="S0444">on on the evening er when we well when we got to my house pretty much</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0444">I am not happy with this and he was like I am not happy either and like we both just kind of</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0444">ranted for quite a while but <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> it's I pretty much turned around I said look you know this goes for any of my friends you can have your own feelings about them I cannot convince you</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0444">to think about a certain person in a certain way you know that that's not my job erm but all I expect you to do and all I ask you to do is respect that person</u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0444">and appreciate and understand how much that person means to me as a friend and how much</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0444">they have been there to for me as a friend and it was like you know it was quite easy <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> think of the box</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0444">you know and it was that kind of thing like I <trunc>w</trunc>I was like you know but you know <unclear/> like yes that she is one the most important people you know</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0444">okay you may not be best friends from day one but <pause dur="short"/> you know as long as you have that respect for her as one of my good friends</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0444">respect the fact that she looks after me she supports me and I support her and I look after her when she needs it and you know that she's important to me that's what I ask at the moment</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">yeah the thing is like</u>
<u n="308" who="S0444">you know and that you know it's fine and whatever happens happens but I I'm just like you know and vice versa it goes for you it's like you respect the fact that he's my boyfriend</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0444">I'm making my choices and you know</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">that's the thing like</u>
<u n="312" who="S0444">and it's the kind of thing that as long as you <pause dur="short"/> if you thought that I was making a completely wrong choice further down the line <unclear/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">I would <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="314" who="S0444">you would say something and I <trunc>w</trunc> I</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">I would tell you yeah like that's why like I never pretend with you like <pause dur="short"/> like yeah like today in the car when I <trunc>s</trunc> like when I said like that I wasn't impressed with him I wasn't gonna lie to you like erm but <pause dur="short"/> I like on the day like even after everything after like all of last year when like he said he didn't have a spark with you like all of that</u>
<u n="316" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439">I didn't dislike him</u>
<u n="318" who="S0444"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="319" who="S0439">and I don't like I don't dislike him now I think it was just</u>
<u n="320" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">but you know <trunc>w</trunc> like Mr Darcy says like</u>
<u n="322" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">you know the first like first impressions <unclear/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0444"><unclear/> but not <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">no like erm was it when a good reputation is lost it's lost forever</u>
<u n="326" who="S0444">lost forever kind of thing</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439">and like and I <trunc>d</trunc>I do get over that now like sometimes I'm really just like I instantly don't like somebody I'm like I'm not making any effort with you but with him like I genuinely do want to make effort I think it was just on that day</u>
<u n="328" who="S0444">yeah it was just that day no exactly I think that I think</u>
<u n="329" who="S0439">it was just hard and I just</u>
<u n="330" who="S0444">I think he was er kind of the same but the thing is that both of you reacted in the same way to each other <unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">but I don't think I did anything wrong like I don't</u>
<u n="332" who="S0444">as in like he <trunc>w</trunc> he was like oh well you know she she didn't come and say hello or anything so I didn't you know it was that kind of thing I was like I wasn't there for the entirety of it</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0444">so I <unclear/> okay</u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0444">you know but I was kind of like</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439" trans="overlap">like hate the <trunc>i</trunc> <unclear/> not just him but I hate the idea of anybody disliking me when they don't know me</u>
<u n="338" who="S0444">oh no it was more but he had the kind of thing where he was like well she hasn't talked to me much so</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0444">I don't you know</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439"><unclear>do you know</unclear> that was my fault cos I didn't want to talk to him cos I thought his behaviour was appalling <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I didn't so I didn't talk to him so that so that was my that was my bad</u>
<u n="342" who="S0444" trans="overlap">well I <trunc>f</trunc>I figured that bit <pause dur="short"/> I figured that bit and I was just like <unclear/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">that was my bad I do</u>
<u n="344" who="S0444">I'm not gonna say oh yeah I really <unclear/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I take no I take complete responsibility</u>
<u n="346" who="S0444"><unclear/> actually <unclear/> I probably told him that you know</u>
<u n="347" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0444">she probably hasn't seen the best of you either but</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">no no I take responsibility for probably not also saying hello to him</u>
<u n="350" who="S0444">oh I know but you know I don't <pause dur="short"/> but that's the thing</u>
<u n="351" who="S0439"><unclear/> next time <unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0444">I don't I don't I don't have to tell both of you to act in a certain way with each other</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439">no no no</u>
<u n="354" who="S0444">that's not my job my job is just to go er look I'm the person that</u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0444">both of you love to pieces and for that reason you will respect each other and hopefully find things to bond over when you actually realise how similar you are as people</u>
<u n="357" who="S0439">yeah like I know next time like if I ever meet him it'll be fine</u>
<u n="358" who="S0444">oh yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0439">just as long as he doesn't do something stupid <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0444">well</u>
<u n="361" who="S0439">I'm a very scathing woman <vocal desc="laugh"/> I protect my girls to the end <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear>ah no but it's true it's just that</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I know but that's what that's what you need and you know that's what I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was like you know cos er you know I was in a position where I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought one of his friends was a complete twat</u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0444">and told him not as in his friend</u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0444">but told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got really defensive and I was like well think of it like it wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> once I got to realise that that was him</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0444">and er you know cos it was the guy in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't know you might not remember the story who kind of said oh yeah I slept with my ex's best friend or whatever and it was like what? like</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439">what a dick <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0444">it's the lowest er pretty much and he'd said er I'd never met him before</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0444">and then it was like oh you know I dunno it was just it was just a bit of a weird one to begin with and I kind of just said oh you're a <unclear/> <unclear>dick</unclear> right?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0444">like erm <pause dur="short"/> and you know me I would never really say that about someone straight out</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439">no no yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0444">and I was like oh god right okay well of course er alright to their faces and I'm like you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a bit like I'm not happy about the fact that I even said that</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0444">then I <pause dur="short"/> I was like the difference was that when I realised that that was actually him being him not him trying to impress a certain</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0444">thing but him being him yeah okay in that aspect he was a dick and <unclear>that I suppose</unclear></u>
<u n="381" who="S0439">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0444">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> agrees and his friends do that this guy has no particular like <pause dur="short"/> social tact</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0444">in a way so then when I realised that that was him but then I saw him later on and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was plastered out of his face and I didn't know this then he was like are you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gonna get home okay?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0444">is he gonna be alright? are you gonna be alright <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0439">like he did care</u>
<u n="388" who="S0444">yeah and it was when <unclear>that</unclear> came out I was like you're not you're not a dick you're just</u>
<u n="389" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="390" who="S0444">you know in that instance and I was like think of it like that with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you took what she said a certain way <pause dur="short"/> in the sense of he took it as a criticism <unclear>when</unclear> it's not a criticism although you <unclear>didn't</unclear></u>
<u n="391" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0444"><unclear>I dunno</unclear> you know and I know you didn't mean it that way</u>
<u n="393" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0444">I know the meant that I know the way that you meant it and I was kind of <unclear>going for</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I know the way that she meant it because she meant it in a nice way</u>
<u n="395" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0444">trying to put you at ease</u>
<u n="397" who="S0439">I was trying to be nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0444">but then it kind of didn't put you at ease it just made things worse</u>
<u n="399" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0444"><unclear>I mean</unclear> gosh right <pause dur="short"/> but anyway and I was kind of saying you know think of it like that <pause dur="short"/> you kind of reacted to that but then you you haven't had the <event desc="sound of clicking fingers"/> moment where he's like oh that's how she <trunc>i</trunc> she's a person</u>
<u n="401" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0444">she sees it from that way like</u>
<u n="403" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0444">do you know what I mean? so I was just like okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0439">yeah it's just not worth like arguing about like and yeah like I have complete respect for you and I respect your relationship and I trust that you know what you're doing</u>
<u n="406" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0439">and like I <pause dur="short"/> like I am all for somebody that <pause dur="short"/> cos a lot of people not a lot of people but people didn't like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hates <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm er genuinely does not like him at all</u>
<u n="408" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0439">and when I was dating him she did not like him</u>
<u n="410" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0439">but so I'm very used to someone telling me that they don't like my boyfriend</u>
<u n="412" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0439">and I think but with her I was like okay you don't like him that's fine I can understand why you don't like him <pause dur="short"/> we'll leave it at that and then I think yeah you're not gonna get on well with everybody</u>
<u n="414" who="S0444">no you're not</u>
<u n="415" who="S0439">and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> never really got the time to bond anyway not that they would <vocal desc="laugh"/> but</u>
<u n="416" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0439">but like and like I do hope that if I meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the future like it'll be fine and I'll explain to him I was like I was just trying to be nice <vocal desc="laugh"/> like I wasn't trying to be a bit like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0444">yeah I know and I <pause dur="short"/> I know that and I know that <trunc>y</trunc>I know that you would do that and I know that he would do that and I'm quite you know I just I just put it plainly I said look you know</u>
<u n="419" who="S0439">you're gonna have to grow to like her one day cos she's not going anywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0444"><unclear>sure</unclear> but also it's that kind of thing where you know it it's that kind of thing <unclear>where I said</unclear> you don't have to love each other</u>
<u n="421" who="S0439">no no no at all</u>
<u n="422" who="S0444">you just have to er respect each other</u>
<u n="423" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0444">and hopefully you will like each other and I</u>
<u n="425" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0444">I do think that when hopefully you kind of <unclear/> that you both are just like <unclear/> <unclear>you just bond over</unclear></u>
<u n="427" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0444">that's that I'm not I'm not gonna be able to get a word in for the rest of the night like that's just how it will be</u>
<u n="429" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0444">but <unclear>like I just say yeah okay</unclear></u>
<u n="431" who="S0439">but I think also like I've grown to appreciate the fact that I'm quite <pause dur="short"/> I've been told that I'm quite intimidating and like like</u>
<u n="432" who="S0444">who told you this?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well basically whenever I go round <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't really talk to me like he's fine er <trunc>w</trunc>we</u>
<u n="434" who="S0444">well he he's quite boring because he's scared of you</u>
<u n="435" who="S0439">well that's what she says she says I think he's intimidated by you because you're not <pause dur="short"/> a normal woman I was like</u>
<u n="436" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0439">okay what does this mean? she goes well you're very</u>
<u n="438" who="S0444">is this <unclear>a good</unclear> compliment or an insult?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0439">yeah I was like where is this going <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? she <unclear>says</unclear> well you're very strong</u>
<u n="440" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0439">and you're very like <pause dur="short"/> confident in what you say</u>
<u n="442" who="S0444">it's not</u>
<u n="443" who="S0439">it's and I'm like</u>
<u n="444" who="S0444">it's not that <unclear/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0439">is that a good thing? or? I'm <trunc>s</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm like I don't want to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0444">no it is a good thing I see what she means it's more about how <pause dur="long"/> it's more about how assured you are</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0444">and er it's more that people do just get that straight <event desc="sound of clicking fingers"/> off I'm not taking any shit kind of</u>
<u n="449" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0444">that and that is not a bad thing it's just <pause dur="short"/> you know it might be different</u>
<u n="451" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0444">to me or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like let's be nice to everyone kind of thing</u>
<u n="453" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0444">you know and it's not <pause dur="short"/> you know for a lot of people that kind of I'm not gonna take any shit from you comes further down the line in a in a</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0444">in a certain friendship or relationship whereas you are just kind of <event desc="sound of clicking fingers"/> hey what you see is what you get</u>
<u n="457" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0444">that's it this is what I want if you don't like that we're done</u>
<u n="459" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0444">and that's fine you go for it</u>
<u n="461" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0444">if er if somebody's intimidated by that</u>
<u n="463" who="S0439">it's <trunc>j</trunc>it's just</u>
<u n="464" who="S0444">let them be <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know that at certain points I was like wow</u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0444">okay but it never stopped me from being your friend or talking to you <unclear/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0439">that's what's <pause dur="short"/> the people who know me the closest I was like like what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said after she said that she goes like when I first met you I could probably understand why he would be intimidated by you</u>
<u n="468" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0439">but now that I know you it makes me laugh</u>
<u n="470" who="S0444">yeah it's more like it's it's more about just getting the chance like</u>
<u n="471" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0444">with with er with a lot of people it's more about just getting the chance to know them</u>
<u n="473" who="S0439">just to get to them yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0444">like <unclear>think er</unclear> you know oh that's really sweet <unclear/></u>
<u n="475" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0439"><unclear>I know</unclear> she's just like well I <trunc>th</trunc>I think he's just like you're not cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> very much views women as objects <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0444">oh okay yeah that</u>
<u n="478" who="S0439">not not in a</u>
<u n="479" who="S0444">not in a <unclear/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0439">not in a horrible way like he'll do anything for you</u>
<u n="481" who="S0444"><unclear>but</unclear> he dates them he likes that like</u>
<u n="482" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0444">he likes them he's very nice to like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0439">he respects <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and he loves <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I don't think it's because he sees her in that way erm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0439">but he doesn't he doesn't think he doesn't really see women as women he sees them as like objects really</u>
<u n="487" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0439">and he isn't really interested in them unless they're there for that reason</u>
<u n="489" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0439">so I think with me like I'm round their house a lot and I think with me because he can't have that type of relationship with me he's kind of lost for what type of relationship he can have with me</u>
<u n="491" who="S0444">to have cos it's like you're not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like you're not like the girl that <unclear/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0439">I'm sleeping with yeah so I think he is a bit like I don't know <trunc>w</trunc>I don't know what we are so he kind of like has a little mini panic <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="494" who="S0439">this <trunc>f</trunc> this advert's really creepy</u>
<u n="495" who="S0444"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0439">it's just that's just weird <vocal desc="laugh"/> although Chris Robshaw is a very beautiful man that's just creepy <pause dur="long"/> what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> you can't ban other people from like drinking Lucozade</u>
<u n="497" who="S0444">er sorry like <unclear/> or what is it? like</u>
<u n="498" who="S0439">Trinidad and Tobago</u>
<u n="499" who="S0444">yeah are they er are they even in it?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0439">I don't think they are no Samoa</u>
<u n="501" who="S0444">Samoa yes</u>
<u n="502" who="S0439">sunny Samoa</u>
<u n="503" who="S0444">sunny Samoa</u>
<u n="504" who="S0439">no Lucozade for you <vocal desc="laugh"/> are you a home nation? no you're not <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0444">but they do <trunc>c</trunc> do they do they class Ireland as a home nation? they do don't they?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0439">yeah they do</u>
<u n="507" who="S0444">interesting</u>
<u n="508" who="S0439">part of the United Kingdom</u>
<u n="509" who="S0444">but it's technically not</u>
<u n="510" who="S0439">isn't it?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0444"><unclear>it's kind of like the</unclear> Republic</u>
<u n="512" who="S0439">oh yeah Northern Ireland <pause dur="short"/> not Eire my sister got told off in school for calling it Eire</u>
<u n="513" who="S0444">yeah?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0439">yeah don't know why <pause dur="short"/> it's quite an old-fashioned term for it I guess</u>
<u n="515" who="S0444">er yeah it's quite er I think like <trunc>m</trunc>maybe because it's <pause dur="short"/> er I dunno like <unclear>whether it</unclear> could be it's not even that republican <unclear/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0439">no yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0444">they <unclear>just thought</unclear> oh that's not the <trunc>c</trunc> you know correct term to use <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> do you watch Gogglebox?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0439">I don't but I think I'd be really good on it</u>
<u n="519" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> you'd be brilliant on it</u>
<u n="520" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think I'd be ridiculous on Gogglebox <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0444">I think you would throw things at the TV</u>
<u n="522" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0444">like this is shit</u>
<u n="524" who="S0439">I would be like what is this? <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> why is there a <trunc>pro</trunc></u>
<u n="525" who="S0444">what is this advert?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0439">oh it's for EDF Energy isn't it? or for some type of energy isn't it?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0444">can I can I just watch it?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0439">yeah of course yeah it's the monkey isn't it? with energy I think oh creepy hair</u>
<u n="529" who="S0444"><unclear/> ah is that a gorilla? or a?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0439">I think it's supposed to be an orangutan</u>
<u n="531" who="S0444">yeah yeah it's an orangutan</u>
<u n="532" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0444">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0439">an orangutan on a fairground ride</u>
<u n="535" who="S0444">I proper love that <pause dur="long"/> I think it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0439">oh SSE Energy</u>
<u n="537" who="S0444">right that's it</u>
<u n="538" who="S0439">I knew it was some type of energy though</u>
<u n="539" who="S0444">well done</u>
<u n="540" who="S0439">the Hairy Bikers</u>
<u n="541" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="542" who="S0439">Location Location Location</u>
<u n="543" who="S0444">yes</u>
<u n="544" who="S0439">please don't say you watch Strictly Come Dancing</u>
<u n="545" who="S0444">oh gosh no</u>
<u n="546" who="S0439">good that's what I like to hear</u>
<u n="547" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0444">I'm just like no</u>
<u n="549" who="S0439">The Polar Express it's not even it's not even Christmas <vocal desc="laugh"/> Rumor Has It has Jennifer Aniston in it therefore it's going to be shocking</u>
<u n="550" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's a Christmas film <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0439">poor Jennifer Aniston <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm so horrible about her I'm just like</u>
<u n="552" who="S0444">but she is married to Justin Theroux now</u>
<u n="553" who="S0439">she is</u>
<u n="554" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0439">she did get married to him didn't she? bless her heart</u>
<u n="556" who="S0444">I know <unclear/></u>
<u n="557" who="S0439">I can't believe I am blessing the heart of Jennifer Aniston like</u>
<u n="558" who="S0444">what is going on?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0439">she is stunning and amazing she's just an shit actress Bride Wars? <unclear/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0444">no don't do it</u>
<u n="561" who="S0439">no good?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0444">it's got Anne Hathaway in it but it's one of her bad films</u>
<u n="563" who="S0439">I haven't <unclear/> does Anne <trunc>Hathaw</trunc>does Anne Hathaway have any good films? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0444">Princess Diaries</u>
<u n="565" who="S0439">okay Princess Diaries er can Miss oh no Miss Congeniality's Sandra Bullock <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0444">Sandra Bullock</u>
<u n="567" who="S0439"><unclear>what a disaster</unclear></u>
<u n="568" who="S0444">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0439">I was <unclear/> like Miss Congeniality's amazing</u>
<u n="570" who="S0444">tragic tragic</u>
<u n="571" who="S0439">tragic</u>
<u n="572" who="S0444">she couldn't get <unclear/> <unclear>Miss Congeniality</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I love it so much in Friends when Chandler <pause dur="short"/> when Monica's like okay we can <trunc>d</trunc>we can do your favourite thing and he's like watch Miss Congeniality one and two she's a spy who becomes a model <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0444">I do love a bit of Miss Congeniality <unclear>that</unclear> <shift new="singing"/> mustang Sally <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0439">she's so good</u>
<u n="576" who="S0444">love it <unclear/> <unclear>in a minute</unclear></u>
<u n="577" who="S0439">are you bathrooming?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0444">I am</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
