<text id="SVWU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:05</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0336 S0337</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Scottish referendum, online forums</topics>
		<activity>Making dinner at home</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0336">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Wegberg</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0337">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Peterborough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0336">so has the erm boy online been getting a bit of an ear bashing then? is it literally just the three of them that are talking about</u>
<u n="2" who="S0337">a lot of people were saying no</u>
<u n="3" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0337">erm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0336">and and I mean is it is it people from the UK or people from America like <unclear/> and just for the sake of like getting on board with it</u>
<u n="6" who="S0337">China? there's no one from fucking China on our forums</u>
<u n="7" who="S0336">no that's <unclear/> China</u>
<u n="8" who="S0337">why'd you say it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0336">from like abroad</u>
<u n="10" who="S0337">China not China though</u>
<u n="11" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0337">where do you think we are?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0336">I don't know obviously it's like primarily like US people on that forum isn't it?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0337">erm we are almost all US Europe and Australia slash New Zealand</u>
<u n="15" who="S0336">okay so these people that have been kind of saying no when he's saying yes what's are they from the UK? from Scotland or</u>
<u n="16" who="S0337" trans="overlap">er there's quite a lot of people from Australia get involved actually</u>
<u n="17" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0337"><unclear/> with it</u>
<u n="19" who="S0336">have you seen I saw a mock up the other day and I and I realise again it's all like propaganda stuff but I saw a mock up of what like flag we might have to choose if Scotland go</u>
<u n="20" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah that's right that's right</u>
<u n="21" who="S0336">and they've got like the wallabies haven't they on <trunc>to</trunc> erm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0337">oh no I've not seen that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0336">oh</u>
<u n="24" who="S0337">I've seen the actual <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0336">oh I haven't seen any of the <unclear>gyms</unclear> I thought it's quite funny cos</u>
<u n="26" who="S0337" trans="overlap">the union jack but the blue's actually green erm there's some other stuff with just white and erm cross and crosses</u>
<u n="27" who="S0336">yeah but with the blue taken out basically</u>
<u n="28" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0336">yeah it was quite embarrassing erm it must have been like from the last general election but I followed the Lib Dems on Facebook</u>
<u n="30" who="S0337">really?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0336">and erm they shared something the other day which was like oh you know share this if you don't want Britain to look like this and what they've done is like they'd erm they'd got like a map of the UK and like just cut it short obviously without Scotland there but then like in the background they had like the union jack and like there's a load of Scottish people being like it wouldn't look like this it would have blue like blah blah blah kind of missing the point a bit in that they were just talking about like</u>
<u n="32" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0336">the shape of the UK or whatever but like it is like petty little things like that though that make you realise that actually like to try and untie Scotland from the rest of the UK</u>
<u n="34" who="S0337">is a lot of work</u>
<u n="35" who="S0336">is such work yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be huge and I'm annoyed that it's gonna be as huge as it was cos I I really don't know how it's managed to gain such momentum like I think it's laziness on the part of like</u>
<u n="36" who="S0337">the no campaign</u>
<u n="37" who="S0336">Downing Street yeah absolutely like for them to to have let it gain such momentum is a fault on their part isn't it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0337">there's so much more I want to go off on but I've not read enough about it so</u>
<u n="39" who="S0336" trans="overlap">no well that's the thing and like like</u>
<u n="40" who="S0337">perhaps not like <unclear/> matter</u>
<u n="41" who="S0336">I feel like half educated about it to be fair and I haven't done enough research but if I was in Scotland right now I would know my facts like how else would you be able to vote if you hadn't done your research like they it it's just such such a defining vote that you wouldn't vote without thinking would you? <pause dur="short"/> I am frankly surprised though that a lot of the older generation do seem to be swaying towards no when in theory</u>
<u n="42" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yes the <unclear>youngers</unclear></u>
<u n="43" who="S0336">yeah which kind of shows that there isn't a lot of strength in in what's being said cos I feel like</u>
<u n="44" who="S0337">right well <unclear>come in</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> where's that? is that me?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0336">never mind</u>
<u n="46" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0336">I'll have a look at the form thing topic after dinner</u>
<u n="48" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear>no idea</unclear></u>
<u n="49" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> why no idea?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0337">no no it makes sense though</u>
<u n="51" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm a bit pissed off that erm the ultrasound thing is a bit of a fail</u>
<u n="52" who="S0337">erm yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0336">did it feel like a waste of your afternoon?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0337"><vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah he didn't even he didn't even look at the right like <unclear>data</unclear> if that makes sense</u>
<u n="55" who="S0336">why was he a dick then? what happened?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0337">oh he just walked in stuck his <unclear>bum drawer</unclear> out bit of a not really giving a shit like like the space erm what else was there? erm didn't really ask many questions just started just started doing it the nurse is nice she's nice enough</u>
<u n="57" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0337">but she started I asked if I was allowed to eat she said you shouldn't've <unclear>she was</unclear> quite young to be honest erm so you shouldn't've I don't really normally do this I normally get MRI</u>
<u n="59" who="S0336">mm mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0337">at the <anon type="place"/> keeps I keep typing</u>
<u n="61" who="S0336">MIR yeah I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't that</u>
<u n="62" who="S0337">anyhow erm <pause dur="short"/> she was like yeah I don't really work here normally work on the other department but you know I just had to come here and just be an assistant once in a while okay should I have eaten? no you shouldn't have eaten I was like okay well I had a banana for breakfast and then I realised I shouldn't have I've had a coffee today she's like mm that's okay erm normally when we look at the gallbladder if you eat something fatty and it empties the gallbladder I'm thinking <unclear/> my gallbladder for that's not been mentioned before I <unclear/> I didn't say anything so oh right okay great erm obviously had the ultrasound on the stomach and he was looking all the way up here all the way down my right side all the way round the top and I'm thinking</u>
<u n="63" who="S0336" trans="overlap">that's not where</u>
<u n="64" who="S0337">that's not where it's been an issue I'm just sat there like okay and he's like no I didn't find anything great so it all looks normal yeah? yeah it all looks normal great he just didn't like <unclear/> ask enough questions</u>
<u n="65" who="S0336" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/> that's <unclear>annoying</unclear></u>
<u n="66" who="S0337">yeah erm but yeah I wasn't there for long as you can tell I was really quick</u>
<u n="67" who="S0336">that's good and at least it meant you didn't have to stay too late either</u>
<u n="68" who="S0337">at work</u>
<u n="69" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0337">well it was absolutely fine today I just <unclear/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I was actually thinking today that you've been loads better recently though</u>
<u n="72" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah erm it's cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s picked up er dropped off er <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gave to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a load of old <unclear/> so <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0336">no I mean I mean with your tummy and stuff</u>
<u n="74" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oh tummy yeah yeah yeah yeah I guess</u>
<u n="75" who="S0336">I didn't really I don't really feel like you've been complaining anywhere near as much</u>
<u n="76" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I thought you meant like finishing work</u>
<u n="77" who="S0336">no no no I just meant that actually like erm we were we obviously we still need to find out what is wrong so we can do stuff but like I feel like some of the advice he's already given you like to cut down on like the fizzy drinks and sugar and all that kind of stuff like I know you're still having it but</u>
<u n="78" who="S0337">not as much</u>
<u n="79" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it is help yeah exactly it is helping <trunc>ha</trunc>having like reduced it a little bit</u>
<u n="80" who="S0337">it's the fruit juice I think</u>
<u n="81" who="S0336">do you know interestingly enough I've actually read a couple of things this week about fructose cos like quite well everybody is now jumping on the bandwagon of saying it's like the worst thing in the world erm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0337">well look as you can tell when like lactose was the worst thing in</u>
<u n="83" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0337">erm lactose free stuff's everywhere</u>
<u n="85" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0337">might be fructose next so I'm just always ahead of the game</u>
<u n="87" who="S0336">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0337">or just slightly ahead</u>
<u n="89" who="S0336">well that is one way to look at it I suppose</u>
<u n="90" who="S0337">well yeah cos with the lactose stuff you couldn't get that milk you could only get it in green and it wasn't always there</u>
<u n="91" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="92" who="S0337">you couldn't get the other stuff the other stuff you could get was like actually dairy free stuff sort of like</u>
<u n="93" who="S0336" trans="overlap">as in like soy stuff yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0337">yeah erm and now lactose free stuff's everywhere</u>
<u n="95" who="S0336">yeah and I mean that I mean that's really good for those that are like properly lactose intolerant they're like the lactose free stuff their range has increased loads and actually it the point where there's such a market for it that compared to <unclear/> can actually start</u>
<u n="96" who="S0337" trans="overlap">do you want <unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0336">yeah jumping in and bringing out new products which can only bode well because it took me ages enough to find like a vanilla ice cream that you could eat</u>
<u n="98" who="S0337">oh yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0336">which is nice but like every once in a while you want something a little bit more exciting than vanilla so it'd be nice for people to have a lactose free choices rather than simply be like oh well this is this is the lacto free choice <trunc>rathe</trunc> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0337">yep <pause dur="short"/> I erm <pause dur="short"/> just trying to work with <unclear/> but anyway back to work stuff</u>
<u n="101" who="S0336">mm mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0337">erm yeah I've not been too busy obviously we've got I think it's five orders that are really bad shit just hitting the fan and I've got that other customer that's just causing me a bit of leg ache</u>
<u n="103" who="S0336">mm mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0337">I'm gonna speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about it and see if he can help out or give us some advice</u>
<u n="105" who="S0336" trans="overlap">well you've still got a fair bit of holiday to take between now and Christmas as well haven't you? so</u>
<u n="106" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0336">try and get try and work yourself into a position where you can actually afford to have</u>
<u n="108" who="S0337">oh erm <unclear/> try Glastonbury next year I know I've just come back and</u>
<u n="109" who="S0336">oh there's no way I wanna commit to that right now</u>
<u n="110" who="S0337">no you have to though sometime</u>
<u n="111" who="S0336" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah I don't think I wanna go there's there's nothing stopping you going</u>
<u n="112" who="S0337">how much is it? it's a lot isn't it?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0336">erm yeah but I think you get a lot for your money and it I think I think it would actually be a good weekend but I my heart's</u>
<u n="114" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0336">my heart's not in it and I'd rather save my money and do other stuff</u>
<u n="116" who="S0337">yep <unclear>agreed</unclear> erm I might I might talk to the guys then I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s up for it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="117" who="S0336"><unclear>dur</unclear></u>
<u n="118" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0336">did you make <unclear/> the eighth of November <pause dur="short"/> erm most of my friends are on board</u>
<u n="120" who="S0337">er <unclear>could've</unclear> asked my friends then eh</u>
<u n="121" who="S0336">yeah basically yeah I don't know I know Glasto'll probably be amazing but I feel like I'm not I think I'd resent spending the money at this point cos I don't actually have that much</u>
<u n="122" who="S0337">please could you grate this down to that that line there on the right</u>
<u n="123" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> a bit though can you bring it here or are you gonna make me get down</u>
<u n="124" who="S0337">erm oh I'll bring it over to <unclear>two secs</unclear> oh Sainsbury's do <unclear/> resale</u>
<u n="125" who="S0336"><vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0337">mm <unclear/> was the best idea</u>
<u n="127" who="S0336">that's fine</u>
<u n="128" who="S0337"><unclear/> was probably a better idea</u>
<u n="129" who="S0336" trans="overlap">so erm <trunc>aft</trunc> on Thursday of this vote then how when are we gonna know? is it gonna be like the general election in that we won't really know till Friday morning?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0337">I think it'll be so close you won't really know</u>
<u n="131" who="S0336">so erm I've seen</u>
<u n="132" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it's not like the US election where you can sit there and watch it</u>
<u n="133" who="S0336">so in terms of like on the you know</u>
<u n="134" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it is it is it is you wait till the next day to sort out the <unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0336">yeah erm on the off chance then that yes votes somehow like manage to succeed like have you read in a couple of the papers they've suggested that erm a lot of people have like panic moved money and stuff like that and erm they are genuinely concerned that there's no it's gonna cause a little bit of a crash because people apparently people having to transfer money into like you like I mean I don't know how it'd work into like UK like</u>
<u n="136" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0336">yeah well I don't <unclear/> it's <unclear>worth</unclear></u>
<u n="138" who="S0337"><unclear>shares</unclear></u>
<u n="139" who="S0336">oh made me laugh today I erm turned around to talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and erm she was on Minecraft website</u>
<u n="140" who="S0337">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0336">and I turned around</u>
<u n="142" who="S0337">wish I had <unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah I turned round and I giggled and she was like oh yeah I was just been reading about it on the news and I was like oh yeah I did read about that the other day they guy sold it hasn't he? she's like yeah he's made a small fortune I'm like yeah but every</u>
<u n="144" who="S0337" trans="overlap">two and a half billion or something</u>
<u n="145" who="S0336">yeah like something crazy and she was like I don't really know what it was it's like oh well I think my boyfriend's played it a little bit he's kind of explained it to me</u>
<u n="146" who="S0337" trans="overlap">me?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0337">played it once it was terrible</u>
<u n="149" who="S0336">I was like</u>
<u n="150" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0336">yeah and she was like what is it? and I was like kind of got the impression it's a bit like Lego online like I don't really know you like you seem to like build stuff and like whatever erm and she was like and I said well something <unclear/> as well they keep referring to this like <unclear>gap</unclear> guy as some like loner coder that just sits in his room like playing with computers</u>
<u n="152" who="S0337">yeah it's <unclear/> erm I play Minecraft once I didn't enjoy it Minecraft's the equivalent of having like</u>
<u n="153" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0337">ah <unclear>that's</unclear> your leg</u>
<u n="155" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0337"><unclear>exactly that</unclear> unless you've seen that <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0336">no but I've just seen the videos you've shown me</u>
<u n="158" who="S0337">they're terrible</u>
<u n="159" who="S0336">like where you go</u>
<u n="160" who="S0337">it's just</u>
<u n="161" who="S0336">you go and kill lambs or something</u>
<u n="162" who="S0337">yeah it's just nothing to do on it oh great you can build this oh yeah great <unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0336">and then</u>
<u n="164" who="S0337">and then someone deletes the server <unclear/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0336">but the guy's laughing now though isn't he? like</u>
<u n="166" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was talking about how she really wants like this like epic bat cave <vocal desc="laugh"/> with like really cool speakers and like state of the art like computers and whatever and I was like</u>
<u n="168" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Minecraft <unclear/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0336">well I think she was trying to imply that this loner coder type thing probably has like a fairly nice set up at home</u>
<u n="170" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0336">and I said yeah but that's why he's a loner like the nicer you make stuff at home like if you create yourself this like awesome bat cave that has everything you could possibly wanna do you're never gonna leave your house <vocal desc="laugh"/> like that's so not healthy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0337"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> god it's so hot sitting here with that <vocal desc="cough"/> I really wanna put the fan on but can't</u>
<u n="173" who="S0336">erm this is really like greasy</u>
<u n="174" who="S0337">yeah sweat</u>
<u n="175" who="S0336">is that like er?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0337">that'll do that'll do</u>
<u n="177" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0337">you're doing good erm <unclear/> I'm really <unclear/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0336">erm <pause dur="short"/> I think we need to ring your mum this evening as well <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> er I suppose you I don't suppose you have spoken to her yet have you?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0337">oh</u>
<u n="181" who="S0336">what are you doing? why have you just cut the end off? is it horrible?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0337">its just gone hard <unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="184" who="S0337">probably be okay it's gone really sweaty as well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0336">I haven't actually read the news at all today thinking about it</u>
<u n="186" who="S0337">the news?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0336">yeah has anything pivotal happened?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0337">stuff in Ukraine's kicking off still helicopter crashed in the North Sea just off <unclear/> Humber north coast not sure didn't bother reading it stuff in Ukraine</u>
<u n="189" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0336">don't know how much of this you actually need that seems like quite a lot of hard cheese</u>
<u n="192" who="S0337">yeah that'll do <pause dur="short"/> no actually you could do a bit more and we could use some of it in this then keep some of it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0336">got nineteen pound to my name</u>
<u n="194" who="S0337">winning when do you get paid? tomorrow?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0336">Thursday</u>
<u n="196" who="S0337">Thursday? eighteenth? you get paid on the sixteenth</u>
<u n="197" who="S0336">eighteenth baby <pause dur="short"/> can't wait</u>
<u n="198" who="S0337">you got petrol yet?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0336">yeah I er well I've got a <trunc>da</trunc></u>
<u n="200" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0336">I've got a day's worth of petrol which is all that I need isn't it? so</u>
<u n="202" who="S0337">why?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0336">because there's only one day before I get paid</u>
<u n="204" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0336">erm what was I gonna say? might try the train next week</u>
<u n="206" who="S0337">for real?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0336">yeah I'm just wondering whether like maybe doing the train like once or twice a week will just break up the monotony of the drive a little bit</u>
<u n="208" who="S0337"><unclear/> today</u>
<u n="209" who="S0336">it wasn't that bad in the grand scheme of things but</u>
<u n="210" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0336">it's just not a very its not very fun and like certainly not very fun on your own and it's quite boring and you know at least if I got the train I would have a nice walk to and from the train station so it'd give me a bit of exercise or what have you and I'd probably get like the ten past eight train in and be in work for like quarter past nine and then I'd be able to get the five o'clock train home hopefully so I'll be home for like six so my working day'll <pause dur="short"/> shift ever so slightly on those two days</u>
<u n="212" who="S0337">as long as you're happy</u>
<u n="213" who="S0336">I don't know I'm just gonna try and <trunc>s</trunc> try a few things out</u>
<u n="214" who="S0337"><vocal desc="misc"/> it's so hot</u>
<u n="215" who="S0336">erm I think we're gonna end up having a really busy weekend</u>
<u n="216" who="S0337">why? oh we've got oh</u>
<u n="217" who="S0336" trans="overlap">can you take this off my hands please? <pause dur="short"/> yeah I just think erm obviously we're I'm gonna end up rushing home from work on Friday to get to your parents house and then we're at my dad's all day Saturday and then at some point we've got to try and do some jobs and maybe even do some painting <unclear>and stuff</unclear></u>
<u n="218" who="S0337">oh oh <pause dur="short"/> sign my life away <unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0336"><unclear>soz pal</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gets back from <unclear>Belize</unclear> this week I mean today</u>
<u n="220" who="S0337">where did she go?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0336">either to <trunc>d</trunc> either a week today or a week yesterday for six days yeah I think she sooner <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh I didn't get to hear back from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually need to take the stuff <unclear>to him</unclear></u>
<u n="222" who="S0337">you didn't hear back from him or you didn't</u>
<u n="223" who="S0336" trans="overlap">no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> erm so you know the erm like radio I've got in my car?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0337">the radio</u>
<u n="225" who="S0336">mm mm you know its got that little Ipod adaptor in the glove compartment?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0337">yep</u>
<u n="227" who="S0336">how easy do you think it would be if I took that to Halfords for them to change that cable for like a universal cable that'll fit in my phone and whatnot?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0337">should be easy they probably <unclear>are</unclear> plugged in to a USB port into your car somehow</u>
<u n="229" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0337">back of the stereo or something should be easy I think you can just go and ask</u>
<u n="231" who="S0336">yeah cos I'm just thinking like it's actually quite handy in terms of like moving forward having music in the car and stuff if I could hook my phone up</u>
<u n="232" who="S0337">what you want is radio four</u>
<u n="233" who="S0336">no no an hour long trip erm journey home I couldn't</u>
<u n="234" who="S0337">yeah you'd learn something</u>
<u n="235" who="S0336">well like who who the fuck wants to learn something on their way home from work?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0337">I do <unclear>feels</unclear> good</u>
<u n="237" who="S0336"><unclear>no thanks</unclear></u>
<u n="238" who="S0337">oh grow up</u>
<u n="239" who="S0336">I wanna listen to music full blast don't really care even what</u>
<u n="240" who="S0337">newsbeat</u>
<u n="241" who="S0336"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="242" who="S0337">so</u>
<u n="243" who="S0336">what are we gonna do about our Geordie Shore this evening?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0337">cry</u>
<u n="245" who="S0336">we need to like invest in some new TV</u>
<u n="246" who="S0337">Walking Dead it's so <unclear>expensive</unclear></u>
<u n="247" who="S0336">no I really can't stand the concept of vampires and zombies and stuff I really hate it</u>
<u n="248" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it's not about zombies it's more people <unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it's about zombies</u>
<u n="250" who="S0337">no it's not it's not <vocal desc="sigh"/> well I'm gonna start watching it and you're just gonna have to miss out tried Spartacus didn't like it you don't watch Deadliest Catch but that's just finished I think its just finished go and check dead's on the Boardwalk's going on erm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0336">Homeland'll be back on soon enough</u>
<u n="252" who="S0337">yep can we just try Walking Dead? it's something that I've missed out on</u>
<u n="253" who="S0336">I will literally give it a few episodes and if I really hate it then I'm quitting</u>
<u n="254" who="S0337">four episodes</u>
<u n="255" who="S0336">deal</u>
<u n="256" who="S0337">or maybe more I don't know how many there are per season</u>
<u n="257" who="S0336">I'll give it half a season</u>
<u n="258" who="S0337">half a season yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0336">I'll give it half a season and if I don't like it you'll have to watch it in your own time when I'm not around</u>
<u n="260" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/> bullshit I'll watch it when I want</u>
<u n="261" who="S0336">well no what am I gonna do while you're watching it</u>
<u n="262" who="S0337">practice <unclear/> practice <unclear/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0336">practice <unclear/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0337">you need to find a practice girl before I get you a laptop do you want a laptop still?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0336">yeah but I wanna do it in my own time if you bully if you bully me into it you're gonna make me hate it before I've even got into it</u>
<u n="266" who="S0337">yeah your own time will be when I'm watching Walking Dead</u>
<u n="267" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0337">or I can just get two monitors and <unclear/> Walking Dead</u>
<u n="269" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I don't enjoy I don't enjoy sitting in that room like away from everything <unclear>at night</unclear></u>
<u n="270" who="S0337">well it's alright I'll just be in the room next to you watching Walking Dead</u>
<u n="271" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that room needs sorting I hate spending time in it it's horrible</u>
<u n="272" who="S0337">it's not very nice even I don't like it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0336">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s proposed the first weekend in October for a ribs night</u>
<u n="274" who="S0337"><vocal desc="misc"/> erm okay</u>
<u n="275" who="S0336">I said that you're probably busy on the Friday</u>
<u n="276" who="S0337">I might be busy on the Friday</u>
<u n="277" who="S0336">yeah so we're thinking the Saturday and she said she doesn't mind having it at hers but she also would appreciate that it might be nice for us to host with our spanking new table and whether you want</u>
<u n="278" who="S0337" trans="overlap">who is it? you me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> her</u>
<u n="279" who="S0336"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0337">it's not enough ribs we might have to go buy some more ribs</u>
<u n="281" who="S0336">there's three racks of ribs</u>
<u n="282" who="S0337">yeah and I could easily eat one myself <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> could easily eat one himself his self and you're gonna <unclear/> down with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0336">no we make enough that you can have half a rack of ribs and plenty of other stuff</u>
<u n="284" who="S0337">other stuff? I can do like erm chicken wings as well</u>
<u n="285" who="S0336">yeah exactly we'll have a little like <trunc>Te</trunc>Texan feast</u>
<u n="286" who="S0337">tex-mex</u>
<u n="287" who="S0336">yeah?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0337">I can't remember what the restaurant's called but there's one in I think there's one in maybe one in York York but there's one in Maltern North Yorkshire erm I went with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s family <unclear>a few</unclear> times and there was a tex-mex can't remember what it's called <unclear/> I remember going on a Good Friday once Easter and I felt really bad because</u>
<u n="289" who="S0336" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the fish pie</u>
<u n="290" who="S0337">no cos I ate the meat on Good Friday <unclear/> eat meat on Good Friday are you?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0337">you tell <unclear>them</unclear></u>
<u n="293" who="S0336">devout Christian that you are</u>
<u n="294" who="S0337">yeah you know me</u>
<u n="295" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="297" who="S0336">so how serious is your mum about us having to have Christmas on the first weekend of December? is that something I should put in my diary?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0337">yes that is when my brother's <unclear>around</unclear> so that's when she wants to do Christmas</u>
<u n="299" who="S0336">right</u>
<u n="300" who="S0337"><foreign lang="ger">was ist das?</foreign></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="301" who="S0336">I erm half expected that you might finish off the lawn on that one evening this week</u>
<u n="302" who="S0337">yeah I looked at that this evening I was just like</u>
<u n="303" who="S0336" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0337">lawn could be cut I haven't actually look at the fact that the the grass had grown a lot so oh okay the grass is growing then In looked at the stuff that I hadn't cut it was like oh that's nearly <unclear/> should be cut</u>
<u n="305" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0337">and I didn't do it as you can tell</u>
<u n="307" who="S0336">well yeah obviously</u>
<u n="308" who="S0337">obviously obviously</u>
<u n="309" who="S0336">if I'm gonna be coming in a bit late I'm gonna be really annoyed if every time I come in you're just sat at that computer you know that don't you?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0337">erm I had chopped onions I boiled the kettle I got everything ready</u>
<u n="311" who="S0336">you know where I'm coming from though</u>
<u n="312" who="S0337">I know where you're coming from when I was coming in late you <trunc>we</trunc> you weren't ready all the time</u>
<u n="313" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0337">I'm allowed a couple of days grace</u>
<u n="315" who="S0336">most evenings most evenings I had done something yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0337">yeah and I prepared some of the dinner</u>
<u n="317" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> chopping an onion doesn't count as</u>
<u n="318" who="S0337">two onions and I had crying by the end of it</u>
<u n="319" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and I drank some coke</u>
<u n="321" who="S0336">congrats</u>
<u n="322" who="S0337">a little drop of coke <unclear/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was wondering when you were gonna tell me off about that what also did you make a point of hiding the chocolate or did you take it to work?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0337">why where is it?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0336">I don't know</u>
<u n="326" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0336">but I literally the other day I thought oh I swear we had more chocolate in and I obviously I knew you'd kind of bought it for yourself but I was</u>
<u n="328" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/> was it</u>
<u n="329" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0337">it's definitely hidden</u>
<u n="331" who="S0336" trans="overlap">but I suddenly become quite aware that I couldn't find it and I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's actually gone out of his way to hide it</u>
<u n="332" who="S0337" trans="overlap">way to hide it yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0336">why? I'm not as bad as my brother what I wouldn't</u>
<u n="334" who="S0337" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="335" who="S0336">I wouldn't have just demolished it</u>
<u n="336" who="S0337">you've eaten quite a lot of chocolate recently I just thought maybe not <unclear/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> gimme a break gimme a break it's not like I'm not it's not like I've had the most normal week ever and you're punish you're punishing me</u>
<u n="338" who="S0337">the chocolate is for me</u>
<u n="339" who="S0336">what all of it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0337">all of it yeah it was the same price as yours</u>
<u n="341" who="S0336">so?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0337">so the reasons</u>
<u n="343" who="S0336">no the amount of times</u>
<u n="344" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah me <unclear/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0336">right okay</u>
<u n="346" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0336">I'm not being funny how many times do we eat out and you eat twice as much as me? you don't see me going oh you pay your your share you pay for your own food</u>
<u n="348" who="S0337" trans="overlap">you don't finish your food I <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> I've finished it for you</u>
<u n="349" who="S0336" trans="overlap">how many times there's there's two boxes of ice creams in there you eat two you can get through two ice creams in a day you don't go at me going oh that's your share</u>
<u n="350" who="S0337" trans="overlap">you get through a lot more</u>
<u n="351" who="S0336">my share you can't</u>
<u n="352" who="S0337" trans="overlap">you gonna cut these at all? or just put them in like that?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0336">just maybe shred the bigger ones in your fingers as you kind of put them in you can't just pick and choose what you do and do not want to share</u>
<u n="354" who="S0337"><vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0336">you bully</u>
<u n="356" who="S0337">I think you're trying to bully me</u>
<u n="357" who="S0336">absolutely not I just think it's outrageous</u>
<u n="358" who="S0337" trans="overlap">that whole box of sharing Maltesers</u>
<u n="359" who="S0336">I don't give a shit</u>
<u n="360" who="S0337">and I have a couple of bars of chocolate that I want to reserve for myself</u>
<u n="361" who="S0336">a couple of bars?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0337">three bars</u>
<u n="363" who="S0336">that's then three big bars of chocolate</u>
<u n="364" who="S0337">yeah but you're already trying to eat and I've not touched them yet I'll buy you some new ones</u>
<u n="365" who="S0336">that's so ridiculous</u>
<u n="366" who="S0337">I'll buy you some new ones don't you worry</u>
<u n="367" who="S0336">well no I'll start dividing the food shop depending on what we actually eat and you'll end up paying a lot more than me</u>
<u n="368" who="S0337">okay I pay my way <unclear>so</unclear> you don't <unclear>get</unclear> the chocolate</u>
<u n="369" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0336">well now I know how it is</u>
<u n="371" who="S0337">you can have what which one do you want?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0336">I have no idea I can't even remember what you bought? I just thought it'd be nice to have a couple of</u>
<u n="373" who="S0337" trans="overlap">because you didn't you weren't interested in them you were too busy getting your fix</u>
<u n="374" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0337">fix of Maltesers</u>
<u n="376" who="S0336">I just wanted a couple of squares of chocolate and you made it such a big deal</u>
<u n="377" who="S0337">I'm sorry there's no more Maltesers for you babe you ate them all</u>
<u n="378" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0336">you're such a <unclear>bully</unclear> I'll remember this when you're ill and you crave something I'll be like</u>
<u n="380" who="S0337" trans="overlap">you're not ill</u>
<u n="381" who="S0336">fuck off</u>
<u n="382" who="S0337">okay I'm ill then and I crave chocolate and ice cream <unclear/> add parsley to everything</u>
<u n="383" who="S0336">please don't</u>
<u n="384" who="S0337">why?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0336">it doesn't bizzo it doesn't belong in a risotto</u>
<u n="386" who="S0337">part just <unclear/> to it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0336">it doesn't do shit</u>
<u n="388" who="S0337" trans="overlap">have you got any chives you got any chives?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0336">it doesn't</u>
<u n="390" who="S0337" trans="overlap">give me chives no so</u>
<u n="391" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="392" who="S0337">it's not gonna add</u>
<u n="393" who="S0336" trans="overlap">add that really really pointless herb that's not going to do anything to a massive risotto</u>
<u n="394" who="S0337">yeah it just looks better</u>
<u n="395" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it looks better it's just the most retarded reason to add it</u>
<u n="396" who="S0337">it'll <unclear/> like that's why you have it on garlic bread <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos it looks better</u>
<u n="397" who="S0336">pepper I agree with</u>
<u n="398" who="S0337">pepper's good</u>
<u n="399" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> those mushrooms actually look really appetising and you know I wouldn't normally say that about mushrooms</u>
<u n="400" who="S0337">they look wicked man right I'm done I hope there's enough chicken in there I don't really <unclear>cut</unclear> them all up</u>
<u n="401" who="S0336">I don't think it needs a lot with a risotto and everything</u>
<u n="402" who="S0337" trans="overlap">risotto</u>
<u n="403" who="S0336"><unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0337">do you want any er <vocal desc="laugh"/> tomatoes in there?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0336">no thank you right lets plate plate up <pause dur="long"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="406" who="S0337">right two plates</u>
<u n="407" who="S0336"><vocal desc="cough"/> erm probably don't need like huge plates do we really for that?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0337"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0336">how was your lunch even though you had to wait till two? <pause dur="short"/> worth the wait?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0337">do you want a knife? do you want that?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0336">erm no I probably won't need a knife for when I</u>
<u n="412" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/> drink?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0336">erm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0337">er yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0336">I have a feeling I've already got one</u>
<u n="416" who="S0337">got a water</u>
<u n="417" who="S0336">is that the only cheese you've stirred in?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0337">yeah the rest will be I'm gonna add my cheese <unclear>at the end</unclear></u>
<u n="419" who="S0336">that's such a lot of hard cheese though you'll really take it for granted that that's really strong cheese it's not even been grated finely either like I think I've got a drink I mean I just</u>
<u n="420" who="S0337">you got water?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="422" who="S0337">use the small plates oh why did you use the small plates? use the big plates</u>
<u n="423" who="S0336">I've set the table erm have you got a drink? do you need a drink?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0337">I need a drink squash please</u>
<u n="425" who="S0336">squash erm blackcurrant's at work do you want the orange? <unclear/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0337">you <unclear/> the blackcurrant?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0336">yeah apparently that's what we do isn't it?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0337">yeah when we replace it or we get someone else to</u>
<u n="429" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do you want summer fruits or <unclear/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oh I'll have summer fruits I thought you liked summer fruits why don't you take summer fruits</u>
<u n="431" who="S0336">yeah but you don't have hot summer fruits when you're feeling poorly do you? hot blackcurrant</u>
<u n="432" who="S0337">woah damn girl</u>
<u n="433" who="S0336">it looks really nice though you've done a good job</u>
<u n="434" who="S0337">really?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0336">yeah it looks yummy what I mean that is just the most piddly portion why I mean actually saying that you've given us two huge portions so it just seems like the most pathetic portion to leave</u>
<u n="436" who="S0337">okay which one's yours?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0336">well no don't because <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay that's probably fair</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
