<text id="SVXP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:45:15</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-04-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0453 S0454</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANONs home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Food, prisons, immigration, current events</topics>
		<activity>Partners talking about current affairs.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explianing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0453">
				<exactage>33</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Abu Dhabi</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UAE</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1.5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Lawyer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0454">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>British - Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Exeter</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Japanese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0454">okay this is recording now <pause dur="long"/> mm so the food banks this is really good by the way</u>
<u n="2" who="S0453">okay</u>
<u n="3" who="S0454">especially the chips</u>
<u n="4" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0454">they're better than last time</u>
<u n="6" who="S0453">what you mean the rest isn't that isn't that good?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0454">no I'm just saying the chips are better than last time</u>
<u n="8" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0454">no so this article on food banks I was reading</u>
<u n="10" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0454">it was saying there's now a thousand food banks across the UK which is huge</u>
<u n="12" who="S0453">yeah so I mean who do they feed? is it?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0454">yeah the I mean</u>
<u n="14" who="S0453">just kind of I mean whoever just turns up</u>
<u n="15" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0453">or is it means tested I mean?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0454">I don't know I don't think it is so I guess that's part of the problem with assessing like if people really need them like if you're a student</u>
<u n="18" who="S0453" trans="overlap">what's to stop yeah?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0454">what's to stop you just going there and getting free food?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0453">or a or a banker</u>
<u n="21" who="S0454">or a banker exactly and these like erm pay what you feel cafés</u>
<u n="22" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0454">there's two of them in London now one of them's in a really poor area so there probably is poor people going there</u>
<u n="24" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0454">but the other one is <trunc>r</trunc> in a really like posh area where they're apparently it's filled with bankers and then you think like what's the point of that? I mean maybe the they say most people there are very generous in what they pay they pay over five pounds for a very simple meal</u>
<u n="26" who="S0453">ah so you're still paying it's not free</u>
<u n="27" who="S0454">pay as you feel no I'm talking about the pay as you feel cafés now</u>
<u n="28" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0454">but you know they're very generous but the point is how do we know that these like food banks and food cafés are serving who they're supposed to?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0453">well I think the principle of a food bank is a good one because if you think about how much food wastage there is out there</u>
<u n="31" who="S0454">yes</u>
<u n="32" who="S0453">from your average café like Costa at the end of the shift they throw away all the muffins and stuff if they're if they're due to expire the next day cos they simply can't display them even though they're still alright for a few days</u>
<u n="33" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah but</u>
<u n="34" who="S0453">and they throw them away</u>
<u n="35" who="S0454">but the problem is that food banks aren't stocked with leftover food it's like you or me going to the supermarket now and spending say twenty pounds</u>
<u n="36" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0454">and then giving that food we've just bought to a food bank</u>
<u n="38" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0454">so they're not really being used in that way the other one that erm the food what were we saying before? about the pay what you feel cafes that's different those two in London only use erm food that's about to expire or food that has been donated by businesses</u>
<u n="40" who="S0453">oh okay</u>
<u n="41" who="S0454">so that seems to be a better use</u>
<u n="42" who="S0453" trans="overlap">what part what part of London is that in? that pay as you feel café?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0454">I don't know I'll have to look it up</u>
<u n="44" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0454">yeah I remember reading about it last week cos when we were in Australia we saw that pay as you feel concept much more widely used but it's</u>
<u n="46" who="S0453">did you?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0454">yeah like they had erm at the convent they had pay as you feel yoga</u>
<u n="48" who="S0453">mm okay</u>
<u n="49" who="S0454">erm pay as you feel obviously food and I saw a stand on the high street in Melbourne saying pay as you feel balloons and like face painting</u>
<u n="50" who="S0453">that's nice</u>
<u n="51" who="S0454">but that concept in the UK seems to be brand new</u>
<u n="52" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0454">erm obviously it's all started by volunteers</u>
<u n="54" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0454">like in Australia and UK but which I mean you could say it's kind of exploiting people as well I mean these are still businesses</u>
<u n="56" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0454">but I suppose if the money's going to a good place then you know who cares? they're not doing it for profit but you'd think they could pay people minimum wage</u>
<u n="58" who="S0453">from where?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0454">well people if people are paying as you feel and for example they've got maybe it's quite a good business model one in a sort of posh area of London where bankers go and they're paying actually over the odds because the food was free you have to remember</u>
<u n="60" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0454">so there's no overheads for the food and they're not paying any staff fee so if they're paying five pounds for that meal that's actual pure profit unlike a real restaurant where they'd be spending out huge amount you know probably the biggest expense is wages and then the food itself so that could actually be subsidising the other café where people can't afford to pay as much</u>
<u n="62" who="S0453">true but don't they have to rent premises to do this?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0454">mm yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0453">so I mean that's massive</u>
<u n="65" who="S0454" trans="overlap">so they do have that overhead</u>
<u n="66" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah that's a massive expense</u>
<u n="67" who="S0454" trans="overlap">plus the electricity and water</u>
<u n="68" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm and there's no guaranteed levels of income here you know they're just</u>
<u n="69" who="S0454">mm true but these have been going for years in Australia like the one at the convent in Melbourne</u>
<u n="70" who="S0453">mm that's a convent though</u>
<u n="71" who="S0454">no no but it's like erm it shut down as a convent</u>
<u n="72" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0454">and the council were going to sell it off privately for erm flats</u>
<u n="74" who="S0453" trans="overlap">development</u>
<u n="75" who="S0454">development but the local community cos they loved the convent decided to buy it they bought it between them they raised money themselves</u>
<u n="76" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm right</u>
<u n="77" who="S0454">and they put in a business plan to the county council saying we want this to be developed as artist residence you know not as in they live there as in they work there erm and also these kind of community cafés and so they put in this really great business plan and they found backers you know charities who would come in it's really over subscribed for the artist residence and it's been hugely successful I mean it's a tourist thing now people go there to visit and they do like loads of courses but they do make money because those artists in residence are allowed to sell their work and they have erm like natural health clinics and you actually pay quite a a lot of money to go to them</u>
<u n="78" who="S0453" trans="overlap">okay mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0454">so it's it's not just you know sort of ticking over some some of those are actually making money</u>
<u n="80" who="S0453">well that's nice</u>
<u n="81" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0453">that's good I mean but I'm assuming that these ones in London aren't there yet</u>
<u n="83" who="S0454">no I mean it still seems to be very new concept</u>
<u n="84" who="S0453" trans="overlap">early days</u>
<u n="85" who="S0454">and I wonder if I mean I suppose if they're registered charities then they wouldn't pay business tax would they?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0453">yeah they'd have all those charity charitable exemptions</u>
<u n="87" who="S0454">yeah and you'd think the same for food banks but yeah going back to the food banks</u>
<u n="88" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0454">I I just don't know like how meaningful it is to say there's a thousand food banks you know that if people are exploiting them for free food when they're not actually poor or not in the sense of poverty I mean like students don't really need to use it</u>
<u n="90" who="S0453">yeah I mean even even you know people that live in that area it's actually quite handy it's almost like your think about your charitable kind of clothing bank</u>
<u n="91" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0453">where you and and shoe bank where you sort of donate <trunc>clo</trunc>clothes and shoes</u>
<u n="93" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0453">it's kind of in the same bracket isn't it? only with food</u>
<u n="95" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yeah it is</u>
<u n="96" who="S0453">so if you live in that area you're probably more likely to give because to be honest you're about to go on holiday there's a there's a bunch of stuff that's going to go off unless you you know donate to this bank</u>
<u n="97" who="S0454" trans="overlap">true</u>
<u n="98" who="S0453">and someone can make use of it but er</u>
<u n="99" who="S0454">yeah but what they said in this Guardian article is that the people who use it erm are often people who have mental health problems and maybe can't work</u>
<u n="100" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0454">erm you know aren't capable of going to work erm drug addicts obviously cos you know they're not earning er homeless people but they also said there was an alarming rise of people who were actually working obviously the unemployed but people who were working full time</u>
<u n="102" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0454">but in minimum wage jobs and they were using food banks and that is worrying</u>
<u n="104" who="S0453">mm yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0454">but again we don't know whether they're just trying to save money they've just you know sort of oh free food</u>
<u n="106" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0454">that'll save me fifty quid a week</u>
<u n="108" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0454">and they're just using it for that rather than actual poverty</u>
<u n="110" who="S0453">yeah erm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0454">I dunno what do you think?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0453">I think the idea is a good one erm although I think we're saying that this whole how does this interact with the welfare state? and is this like a cop out for the welfare state with the cuts and everything?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0453">I mean <trunc>t</trunc> the counter argument to that is you've got a lot of people riding that welfare state that that</u>
<u n="115" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0453">have zero incentive to get out of it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0454">mm true</u>
<u n="118" who="S0453">and and er and and and there must be a way of of of reducing that reducing that the that parasitic lifestyle</u>
<u n="119" who="S0454">so in some ways you're saying like the recent cuts in welfare and like the sanctions if you don't comply with the rules might just this rise in food banks might just be a a kind of reaction to that and if we leave it another year or two we might see reliance go down as people start to find work and you know?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0454">start to rely on themselves rather than constantly relying on handouts either from the government or for from like well-meaning people in the community?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0453">it's possible but I think you'll always get people that will be will want to lead that lifestyle</u>
<u n="123" who="S0454">yeah and the homelessness and drug addiction that's not going anywhere</u>
<u n="124" who="S0453">no</u>
<u n="125" who="S0454">erm it's not going to to be honest is it? you can't stop people</u>
<u n="126" who="S0453">no erm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0454">so there'll always be people who need free food</u>
<u n="128" who="S0453">yeah I think the the issue that London faces as well is is this whole you know the abundance of wealthy Russian Chinese Arab</u>
<u n="129" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0453">erm investors in real estate</u>
<u n="131" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0453">that just leave their properties empty</u>
<u n="133" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0453">so</u>
<u n="135" who="S0454">people are forced out</u>
<u n="136" who="S0453">yeah so buyers for buyers are forced out you know buyers that erm are don't have that level of wealth</u>
<u n="137" who="S0454">even renters</u>
<u n="138" who="S0453">but even renters cos it basically stops the rental market it it it stops property from it removes property for the rental market</u>
<u n="139" who="S0454">yeah and that has a knock on effect because then people have to commute further and as we know like commuting in London is so expensive that that will eat up a huge an increasingly large chunk of their wages whereas before those people might have lived in zone one and zone two</u>
<u n="140" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0454">basically no one can afford to unless they're über rich now</u>
<u n="142" who="S0453">absolutely</u>
<u n="143" who="S0454">and even then they can't buy you know they're so</u>
<u n="144" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0454">if the Russian oligarchs are coming in and buying that means even rich British people you know there's not very many of them so even they're forced to to buy further out in the suburbs</u>
<u n="146" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0454">and that forces up prices</u>
<u n="148" who="S0453">absolutely yeah that's that's that's a big issue erm I don't know what the way round it is although whether you restrict foreign ownership I mean that's what the Gulf does</u>
<u n="149" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0453">in the Gulf you can't</u>
<u n="151" who="S0454">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="152" who="S0453">you</u>
<u n="153" who="S0454">just erm just have certain areas where they can buy</u>
<u n="154" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0454">which are earmarked and not in like obviously really desirable central locations they have to buy further out in new developments</u>
<u n="156" who="S0453">although the problem with that is the desirable and really central locations the properties are so expensive that they tend to be outside your average erm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0453">you know British buyers' budget</u>
<u n="159" who="S0454">mm but that's inflation</u>
<u n="160" who="S0453" trans="overlap">so true but I can't see it's not going to drop dramatically if they introduce this kind of restriction it'll take time in London it's almost</u>
<u n="161" who="S0454">well yeah because when they sell we can't stop people who've already bought right? so</u>
<u n="162" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0454">they're going to hold on to it and when they sell yeah that's when there's be a drop but that could be twenty years away I mean these people are using them as like piggy banks basically they say don't they?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0453">the other difference is you know the Gulf States generally don't allow you to hold another passport</u>
<u n="165" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0453">so there's a clear way mechanism of erm distinguishing between foreigners and locals</u>
<u n="167" who="S0454">true</u>
<u n="168" who="S0453">whereas in the UK there isn't that restriction so</u>
<u n="169" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0453">you could be Russian an oligarch you could have lived in the UK for ten years and you can qualify for a for citizenship</u>
<u n="171" who="S0454">true</u>
<u n="172" who="S0453">particularly when you're talking about the investor types that tend to qualify for these things quicker because they're bringing their money into the country</u>
<u n="173" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0453">so it's a complex one</u>
<u n="175" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0453">erm but it's</u>
<u n="177" who="S0454">housing's a huge issue</u>
<u n="178" who="S0453" trans="overlap">you know yeah it is and everyone keeps banging out banging on you know UKIP about erm immigration and sort of erm the the the immigrants that come in economic migrants erm but actually you know whilst I think it's important there are constraints on how many people can come in I think that's important but</u>
<u n="179" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0453">at the end of the day these people do the job the sorts of jobs that your average Brit is not simply not going to do</u>
<u n="181" who="S0454">yeah but these like Polish and Romanian workers they're not the ones buying our property in the centre of London</u>
<u n="182" who="S0453">no exactly so there's two different issues you know everyone keeps banging on about the economies migrants but what about the wealthy migrants?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0454">mm they're the bigger issue with housing</u>
<u n="184" who="S0453">I think so mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0454">and then the effect that has on people's take home pay as they are forced to pay more for rent and live further away</u>
<u n="186" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0454">to lose more time commuting and</u>
<u n="188" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0454">yeah for sure but no one seems to be talking about that with this election campaign like</u>
<u n="190" who="S0453">no no one wants to piss <unclear>those people</unclear> off</u>
<u n="191" who="S0454" trans="overlap">they're talking about food banks and welfare but no one ever goes near housing like especially the second home issue or the foreign buys</u>
<u n="192" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm it's cos yeah it's cos the I mean it's landlords are glad that there is this inflation and high rents</u>
<u n="193" who="S0454">mm yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0453">and er and property owners in general</u>
<u n="195" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0453">erm and they're probably quite a quite an influential lobby so</u>
<u n="197" who="S0454">yes that's true and of course it's richer people who are in that position and they're the ones who are probably in power so you know MPs nothing to stop them owning like ten properties is there?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0453">no exactly and we saw that problem Horizon the other day about the the increase in er in sort of private landlords that are referred to by councils cos they've got a dearth of council housing</u>
<u n="199" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0453">and they still need to house people</u>
<u n="201" who="S0454">yeah that was outrageous</u>
<u n="202" who="S0453">the the ruthlessness that they had for the money</u>
<u n="203" who="S0454">and they what they were charging for like a you know a caravan literally caravans like ten thousand a week you know that guy was making</u>
<u n="204" who="S0453">and the really poor hygiene sanitary conditions</u>
<u n="205" who="S0454">but I mean that seems to be a problem about law enforcement if something is substandard</u>
<u n="206" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0454">we already have laws in place to to close hotels down for example</u>
<u n="208" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0454">erm looks to me more like environmental health or whoever it is that deals with enforcement is hugely overstretched and they they need a lot more because I mean imagine <trunc>te</trunc> you know it's not enough just to go and inspect right let's say you go and you inspect</u>
<u n="210" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0454">and you find it's substandard well you wouldn't take someone to court immediately you would then have to write a report</u>
<u n="212" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0454">and give that landlord the chance to put it right which is going to take let's say you know six weeks two months I don't know</u>
<u n="214" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0454">and agree a time frame and then you'd have to go back and inspect a second time and it's not up to scratch you'd probably still give them a third chance right? so now six months will go by and only then would you start to think right we need to take this guy to court</u>
<u n="216" who="S0453" trans="overlap">fine this guy yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0454">and that would take hours and hours to prepare for you know cos they're not legal experts these environmental health people they would then have to refer that to their lawyers who are I'm sure are really overworked too</u>
<u n="218" who="S0453">yeah I mean there's a few issues there one is the cuts to the environmental health inspectors themselves and</u>
<u n="219" who="S0454">yeah that's worrying</u>
<u n="220" who="S0453" trans="overlap">and the fact they haven't got the man power to do this given the number of properties out there the increase in the number of people relying on this kind of you know <trunc>the</trunc>these kinds of erm hotels and hostels</u>
<u n="221" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0453">but secondly <trunc>er</trunc> but I mean it's also the police cos we saw that they get involved</u>
<u n="223" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0453">but there have been police cuts as well</u>
<u n="225" who="S0454">that's right</u>
<u n="226" who="S0453">so they're probably now prioritising murders you know the big sort of stuff</u>
<u n="227" who="S0454">and even when they do <trunc>pro</trunc> erm prosecute and succeed you saw the fines they were tiny like erm that guy who had that house condemned</u>
<u n="228" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0454">he only got fined er he got fined five thousand pounds</u>
<u n="230" who="S0453" trans="overlap">five thousand pounds yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0454">but he's been raking in ten thousand pounds a month so</u>
<u n="232" who="S0453">no I think it was more than that like he was making like eight hundred thousand pounds year</u>
<u n="233" who="S0454" trans="overlap">it was a week or something <pause dur="short"/> a year so five thousand pounds</u>
<u n="234" who="S0453">is no skin off his nose</u>
<u n="235" who="S0454" trans="overlap">is a is a slap on the wrist he might as well keep on doing it</u>
<u n="236" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0454">so there seems to be a bigger problem there that we've got laws but the fines are are not in proportion to what these people are earning and they need to be</u>
<u n="238" who="S0453">yeah absolutely so there's that issue but then there's the broader strategic issue as we were saying of how tough can you be with the people that potentially finance your election campaign?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0454">true and not only that if you're going to be really tough with them is there an alternative on the market? and it looks like the housing stock is so dire in a lot of places that there really isn't anywhere alternative to home these people which they're obliged to no thanks</u>
<u n="240" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0454">so they're left with kind of no choice but to to not be too harsh on these landlords because what can they do?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0454">erm yeah it's a tricky one and I guess you see a lot of landlords wouldn't want these people in their homes they're not going to rent out you know a really nice two bed flat to people who are you know are are taking this erm you know free housing because presumably they're unemployed and have problems so you're not going to want to rent out anywhere nice so it kind of almost encourages the the rogue landlords to let out somewhere substandard because they are going to get you know probably wrecked</u>
<u n="244" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0454">right? you're going to have and also you're not going to the neighbours aren't going to want these social this social housing on their doorstep because it's going to bring down the value of their property and it's true unfortunately</u>
<u n="246" who="S0453" trans="overlap">it's going to bring along the riff raff</u>
<u n="247" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0453">so what do you think about the election and you know the election issues and? coming up on Thursday</u>
<u n="249" who="S0454">yeah I think the Tories will win</u>
<u n="250" who="S0453">yeah I agree</u>
<u n="251" who="S0454">Labour will do well though better than last time</u>
<u n="252" who="S0453">you reckon?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0454">it's further cos a lot of people who used to vote Labour went right off them with the whole Iraq war right? I mean I always used to vote Labour or Green but once Tony Blair and you know blatantly lied and we all knew that even before you know the those documents came out proving that you know there was no proof of these weapons of mass destruction like we all knew that it was about oil and the fact that he was pretending it was something else really just turned a lot of voters off him I mean we thought we might as well vote for the Tories then because you're no better before they had the moral high ground</u>
<u n="254" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0454">so I think they'll have gained some ground because that's long enough ago that people have maybe sort of forgotten it</u>
<u n="256" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0454">but I still think the Tories will come out because of the economy</u>
<u n="258" who="S0453">yeah but Ed Miliband is a joker though</u>
<u n="259" who="S0454">that's the other thing he's not very <trunc>cha</trunc></u>
<u n="260" who="S0453" trans="overlap">he's got zero charisma</u>
<u n="261" who="S0454">yeah and you need charisma</u>
<u n="262" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0454">like</u>
<u n="264" who="S0453">he looks a bit of an idiot</u>
<u n="265" who="S0454">he looks a bit sort of wet behind the ears doesn't he?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0453">yeah he looks like a sixth former who's found suddenly found himself at the top of the of a political party</u>
<u n="267" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yeah and then that idiotic interview with Russell Brand you know when he was trying be really cool and</u>
<u n="268" who="S0453" trans="overlap">and say got</u>
<u n="269" who="S0454">gotta gotta go this and we gotta do that in that plummy accent</u>
<u n="270" who="S0453">he does he was sort of like oh you know like let me just explain you gotta do this and then you gotta do that and it just did it was completely incongruous it didn't</u>
<u n="271" who="S0454">it didn't work and it just looked like he was desperate for votes and oh look I'm going to go and find a celebrity now and do an interview</u>
<u n="272" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0454">and you also thought like what's Russell Brand doing? is he trying to endorse the Labour party? like he's supposed to be independent of this</u>
<u n="274" who="S0453" trans="overlap">Russell Brand is Russell Brand is just a narcissistic erm Essex boy I mean that's what he is he just goes on</u>
<u n="275" who="S0454">yes</u>
<u n="276" who="S0453">you know he's like oh d'you know what I mean? like</u>
<u n="277" who="S0454">and probably went to a private school himself</u>
<u n="278" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0454">and it puts on his accent to a large extent yeah I agree but I mean if he if he's supposed to be this anti-establishment figure then he shouldn't be courting just one party I mean you might as well talk to all of them and if he's trying to do good then try and push his cause across and ask them what are you doing about homelessness? what are you doing about immigration? and you know back them in to a corner</u>
<u n="280" who="S0453">mm so let's look back on this coalition government over the last four years</u>
<u n="281" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0453">four or five?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0454">I don't know four?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0453">yeah and just say what's gone well and what hasn't</u>
<u n="285" who="S0454">economy</u>
<u n="286" who="S0453">economy has gone well</u>
<u n="287" who="S0454">because we were in a recession right? this time five years ago</u>
<u n="288" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah it's recovering well</u>
<u n="289" who="S0454">but I mean of course it wasn't just the UK that was in a recession then it was basically all of Europe all of the world even Australia so</u>
<u n="290" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0454">to some extent you could say that did the Tories really do that? I mean they could have it could have just naturally got better</u>
<u n="292" who="S0453" trans="overlap">happened anyway yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0454">couldn't it?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0453">could have yeah could have but but erm I think some some of the policies might have helped stimulate economic activity so for example</u>
<u n="295" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0453">erm you know what they did with the SDLT stamp city land tax before I think it was just a</u>
<u n="297" who="S0454">flat rate</u>
<u n="298" who="S0453">a flat rate</u>
<u n="299" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0453">and then they made it a threshold so it was you know three percent if it's above a certain value</u>
<u n="301" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0453">and then and then above really a much higher value than it becomes subject to a higher rate</u>
<u n="303" who="S0454" trans="overlap">that's good yes no that was good and it it was fairer on the first time buyers and people at the bottom of the ladder that they weren't paying nearly as much it gave them a chance but I think it was a lot more than that they had to make cuts basically big cuts er because it wasn't sustainable what Labour was doing ploughing enormous amounts of money into education but there was no improvement in results</u>
<u n="304" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0454">so it was kind of throwing money at the wall and you know like for example when I taught in the secondary school they had all these laptops that they brought in erm and we never used them because someone decided some health and safety committee after they were bought that it wasn't safe to have all these leads trailing everywhere so we basically weren't allowed to use them so schools were spending out huge amounts of money on technology that they then didn't use</u>
<u n="306" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0454">and they shouldn't be allowed to do that I mean the the money has got you know some money has to be put towards technology but ultimately technology becomes out of date so quickly</u>
<u n="308" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0454">and the cost of maintaining equipment is so huge and schools don't have often you know some sort of technical support officer who is capable of fixing say laptops that they become useless very quickly so what is introduced needs to be thought through very carefully</u>
<u n="310" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0454">and the money instead should be spent on facilities like the buildings themselves bringing in the right number of teachers er so it wasn't sustainable what they were doing and they've cut you know and they've had to cut the education budget quite harshly so that was one way they saved money but some of the other cuts like erm you okay to keep going?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0454">erm some of the other cuts like in the police force and in jails I completely disagree with</u>
<u n="314" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0454">like I mean that's I don't think the jails were ever extravagant anyway they were never overstaffed</u>
<u n="316" who="S0453" trans="overlap">no they were overcrowded</u>
<u n="317" who="S0454">they were overcrowded we desperately need new jails and they've still not been built and the same with the police force crime is falling I mean so they say but crime is also being monitored less if you've got less policemen so</u>
<u n="318" who="S0453">yeah for sure so so erm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0454" trans="overlap">it's kind of a meaningless statistic if you cut the number of police officers and then say oh we've got less crime</u>
<u n="320" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0454">have we? or have we just got more evasion of crime?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0453">mm true</u>
<u n="323" who="S0454">like illegal immigrants they haven't got a hope</u>
<u n="324" who="S0453">true erm the other thing is they've introduced this help to buy scheme</u>
<u n="325" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0453">which was intended to provide a springboard for first time buyers and lower income</u>
<u n="327" who="S0454">but it's crap</u>
<u n="328" who="S0453" trans="overlap">people I think it is crap because the problem is that people don't read the fine print and they just thought that this</u>
<u n="329" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0453">oh help to buy great the government is going to help us out</u>
<u n="331" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0453">and lend us erm I think it's eighty percent</u>
<u n="333" who="S0454">yeah it's huge</u>
<u n="334" who="S0453">eighty percent of the property value</u>
<u n="335" who="S0454">I think it's something like that</u>
<u n="336" who="S0453">when you read the fine print though you find that the repayment terms are subject to minimum repayment amounts of ten thousand pounds your average Joe Bloggs doesn't have that money that easily</u>
<u n="337" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0453">second thing is that it's not like a conventional mortgage where you pay interest on the amount borrowed you you pay back so they've lent you eighty percent you pay back eighty percent of the value of your property when you come to pay it back so it needs to be valued and in these in these times of high inflation and high property prices and property price increases naturally the government is going to make a killing</u>
<u n="339" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yeah make a yeah that's true</u>
<u n="340" who="S0453">out of that erm and and and it might be on less favourable terms to these people than they they would get from a commercial mortgage</u>
<u n="341" who="S0454">yeah because some of the banks now are offering brilliant mortgages fixed rate mortgages like Coop's offering</u>
<u n="342" who="S0453" trans="overlap">low interest rate</u>
<u n="343" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yeah one percent interest which is phenomenal it's really great</u>
<u n="344" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0454">so you think it's not really worth it I mean you've got to scrape your deposit together still but I guess that's the main problem first time buyers have is where where is that money coming from?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0454">and I mean no bank's going to accept less than twenty percent</u>
<u n="348" who="S0453">these days no</u>
<u n="349" who="S0454">so I mean because property prices are so high it's substantial</u>
<u n="350" who="S0453">what else has gone well? I mean there cos there's a few other things there there are more new houses being built</u>
<u n="351" who="S0454">yeah that's positive</u>
<u n="352" who="S0453">now is that is that a policy or is that just <trunc>me</trunc> you know responding to demand?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0454">no it's a policy but like because there's been a policy of not building I suppose more to the point</u>
<u n="354" who="S0453" trans="overlap">true</u>
<u n="355" who="S0454">for you know probably since we were born</u>
<u n="356" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0454">since Thatcher's time</u>
<u n="358" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0454">and well I mean that's not been sustainable either cos what we've got now is the situation where the housing stock doesn't match the demographics of families any more before people had you know three four children</u>
<u n="360" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0454">and so they needed a house er two up two down</u>
<u n="362" who="S0453">yeah now it's more apartments</u>
<u n="363" who="S0454">now yeah <trunc>th</trunc> we need apartments people are marrying later and they're you know</u>
<u n="364" who="S0453">if at all</u>
<u n="365" who="S0454">if at all and when they do have children it's one or two</u>
<u n="366" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0454">so what we need is flats basically and unless you live in a big city</u>
<u n="368" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0454">it's pretty hard to find flats especially new build what you get is you know converted terraces and they're not designed for it the bathrooms aren't there for example so you you get these shared entrance ways it's not ideal at all and what we really need is erm purpose built flats new builds</u>
<u n="370" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0454">and also I I suppose with erm you know a lot of factories moving abroad</u>
<u n="372" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0454">in the past that those areas are very you know neglected</u>
<u n="374" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="375" who="S0454">but are in good locations often quite central like Liverpool and Birmingham have got you know these derelict areas but you know actually quite prime real estate and all of that needs to be redeveloped into flats and then you know Birmingham's done a good job actually I was there a couple of years ago and they've really developed erm these old factory areas into shopping centres and it looks pretty good</u>
<u n="376" who="S0453">in terms of urban regeneration</u>
<u n="377" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0453">so I mean other pluses and <trunc>nega</trunc> minuses you've got you've had the child sex abuse cases that have come out</u>
<u n="379" who="S0454">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="380" who="S0453">Jimmy Saville Rolf Harris it's <trunc>go</trunc> it's good that those have been pursued I suppose</u>
<u n="381" who="S0454">but then it's all seems like that's gone on for so long that both Labour and the Tories</u>
<u n="382" who="S0453">have turned a blind eye</u>
<u n="383" who="S0454" trans="overlap">are yeah exactly turned a blind eye that went on definitely when the Tories were in power before and they knew about it</u>
<u n="384" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0454">and someone knew about it and didn't do anything about it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0453">yes and</u>
<u n="387" who="S0454">and then the MPs themselves were involved</u>
<u n="388" who="S0453">well yeah this is the thing that I have a major problem with but also coming back to the Jimmy Saville and Rolf Harris have you noticed that in the last week there's been some additional stories about them</u>
<u n="389" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0453">that have come out? and I'm thinking you know I don't think it's a coincidence that in the lead up to the election the these stories are coming out</u>
<u n="391" who="S0454">that's true yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0453">as in look you know look what we're doing the Tories to this or the Tory coalition government to pursue these guys</u>
<u n="393" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0453">when actually the Tories have been grossly negligent with with with child sex abuse use with er their own government the institutional abuse that happened in that hostel I can't remember the name with high level MPs involved a lot of whom are dead but under Margret Thatcher's government</u>
<u n="395" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm true</u>
<u n="396" who="S0453">and I don't think like you said it's it's erm coincidental that they're those aren't being pursued at the moment and I guess they're still investigating cos of the sheer scale of this thing but I think you're right that no decision will be made until the new government comes in and they decide what they want to do but I just hope that if it is the Tories that get elected as we're expecting</u>
<u n="397" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0453">erm that they that they pursue this issue because I think the public will be expecting it</u>
<u n="399" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0453">and and the media in the UK you know they're quite ruthless they won't let this this let this go</u>
<u n="401" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0453">and it will it'll be a matter of time before someone starts saying why is nothing being done about this?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0454">yeah true</u>
<u n="404" who="S0453">and it may be that you know some of the perpetrators are dead erm but others aren't and some are already inside doesn't matter they they get additional charges</u>
<u n="405" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0453">erm they should someone needs to pay for what happened</u>
<u n="407" who="S0454">and what do you think about this rule erm now in prisons? that before if you were a erm child sex offender a convicted offender your details were not released to other prisoners like what you were in for was kept confidential</u>
<u n="408" who="S0453" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0454">for the simple reason that</u>
<u n="410" who="S0453">you'd get your your head kicked in</u>
<u n="411" who="S0454">I mean you you might get killed yeah or certainly you'd be treated worse than other prisoners a</u>
<u n="412" who="S0453" trans="overlap">oh for sure</u>
<u n="413" who="S0454">and that's apparently all stopped under the Tories and now they're you know releasing what people have done</u>
<u n="414" who="S0453">mm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0454">that to me is wrong like</u>
<u n="416" who="S0453">yeah I agree</u>
<u n="417" who="S0454">if the state says that you know you're you you know you did this you you are guilty of this and this is your punishment let's say ten years in prison then we don't have the right to impose or turn a blind eye to further abuse in the prison system because the prison itself is supposed to be punishment so</u>
<u n="418" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0454">to me that's really wrong it's ethically questionable I don't I'm not making excuses for these people</u>
<u n="420" who="S0453" trans="overlap">I yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0454">but I'm just saying the the sentence is already passed down by the courts</u>
<u n="422" who="S0453">yeah they were they were sentenced to incarceration not incarceration and abuse</u>
<u n="423" who="S0454">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0453">but yeah I absolutely agree with you but this probably happens anyway because the prison officers know what they're in for</u>
<u n="425" who="S0454">yeah of course they do</u>
<u n="426" who="S0453">and they get all chummy with certain prisoners and they tell someone and word gets round</u>
<u n="427" who="S0454">but that would be but the point is in the past they could have been sacked for that or even taken to court themselves over that for you know breach of confidential information but now they wouldn't be doing anything wrong everybody knows it's supposed to be all open</u>
<u n="428" who="S0453">true as lawyers though when we look at confidentiality obligations they're very difficult to enforce</u>
<u n="429" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0453">because it's very hard to isolate the source of the disclosure erm as as the person that should have disclosed it I mean it's hard to to tell</u>
<u n="431" who="S0454">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="432" who="S0453">that guy says I but I didn't you know the prison officer might say I I didn't tell anyone it must have been the prisoners themselves they asked him</u>
<u n="433" who="S0454">true</u>
<u n="434" who="S0453">and it's his word against the prisoners and guess who's gonna be believed generally before the courts? it'll be</u>
<u n="435" who="S0454">true</u>
<u n="436" who="S0453" trans="overlap">the prison</u>
<u n="437" who="S0454">but the point is there was a bit of an incentive and also just morally you know they might not have done that</u>
<u n="438" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0454">but now it's all open</u>
<u n="440" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0454">it's very dangerous and apart from the understaffing these other changes to me they're just wrong</u>
<u n="442" who="S0453">right yeah I</u>
<u n="443" who="S0454" trans="overlap">we're looking it's prison suicides have gone up a lot in the last two years and</u>
<u n="444" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0454">I would have thought it was a combination of those two things less staff but also more abuse</u>
<u n="446" who="S0453">yeah absolutely I I but I think you're right that the prison system is is flawed</u>
<u n="447" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0453">that there needs to be needs to be another way of doing this</u>
<u n="449" who="S0454">and the other thing cos you know my dad works in erm a prison</u>
<u n="450" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0454">that you know you sometimes question whether a lot of people should be in prison I don't mean the child sex offenders or any kind of sex offender they they do need to be there but other people for example burglars where there's no er there was no violence involved do they really need to be there? is this the the best use of the prison space we have which we've already accepted is very overcrowded?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0453">you know I mean some <trunc>go</trunc>good ideas have come up like this restaurant that they did in I think it's in Brixton I don't know if you</u>
<u n="453" who="S0454">yeah I saw that</u>
<u n="454" who="S0453">where they've basically staffed it with inmates erm and they make great food and they make money out of it you know they so</u>
<u n="455" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0453">and that's that's good I think I think application towards a <trunc>pro</trunc> you know a work erm er objective would be good</u>
<u n="457" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="458" who="S0453">because I mean you know I'm not talking about the Chinese labour camps or anything like that</u>
<u n="459" who="S0454">no</u>
<u n="460" who="S0453">cos I think they'd still do they still have erm labour camps in China but but I'm thinking there must be an alternative to slapping someone behind bars</u>
<u n="461" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0453">because the rate at which inmates are going into prison is far higher than the rate of releases so</u>
<u n="463" who="S0454">yes and the reoffending rate is</u>
<u n="464" who="S0453" trans="overlap">is really high</u>
<u n="465" who="S0454">very very high</u>
<u n="466" who="S0453">yes so it doesn't take a rocket scientist to work out that unless we build more prisons this this this whole system is gonna crumble</u>
<u n="467" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0453">it's gonna it's gonna everything is going to come to a head</u>
<u n="469" who="S0454">and also the prisons we've got are very very old now as well and some of them need to be shut down not to mention they were built in a different time where family support was not recognised as being erm a key component of stopping reoffending so some of these prisons like Dartmoor were built in the most isolated out of the way place on purpose to prevent them having any access with anybody erm and that was a high security prison in the past you know for murderers and rapists who probably weren't going to be released ever and it was thought they didn't have any chance of being rehabilitated anyway now what we've got is those same prisons are completely out the way but they don't have it's not a high security prison anymore it's a low security prison so the people in there aren't dangerous they have a greater chance of being rehabilitated but their family are not able to visit</u>
<u n="470" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah yeah mm cos it's so far away</u>
<u n="471" who="S0454">they're almost no public transport you know the it's miles even from the nearest city Plymouth er miles and miles and miles and people can be put in Dartmoor prison who aren't from Devon or Cornwall they can be from anywhere in the UK</u>
<u n="472" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah yeah absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0454">and the thing is we all know that poverty is a major factor in why people go to prison so can those families really afford to drive down from let's say Manchester to see them and what? stay in a hotel nearby? there aren't any hotels nearby</u>
<u n="474" who="S0453">the problem is the problem is you can't you can't just have there isn't room to have prisoners imprisoned according to where they live</u>
<u n="475" who="S0454">well they're supposed to be unless it's like a obviously a very violent prisoner where you can't put them in the local jail because it's not secure enough but</u>
<u n="476" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0454">no they are meant to to house you near where you live the problem is they're so overcrowded that they can't</u>
<u n="478" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah they are yeah and there are areas that that produce a <trunc>lo</trunc> a tonne more prisoners than others</u>
<u n="479" who="S0454">right though Dartmoor is never going to produce that many prisoners so</u>
<u n="480" who="S0453" trans="overlap">exactly unless you know I don't know you</u>
<u n="481" who="S0454" trans="overlap">it's in a bad location what they need to do is build one say on the road by Bristol next to a motorway this is another thing they're thinking about with the new generation of prison it needs to be close to a major artery and public transport so that people can visit</u>
<u n="482" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah yeah true I mean in <trunc>Da</trunc> yeah yeah I mean in Dartmoor you know the crime erm aspect yeah it it it probably doesn't produce may criminals you know unless you're killing killing</u>
<u n="483" who="S0454">there's no one there</u>
<u n="484" who="S0453">and like burying body parts on Dartmoor which might have happened before</u>
<u n="485" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0453">or you're like erm cutting erm sort of trimming erm National Park hedges and making off with like erm <trunc>fe</trunc> protected flowers and stuff like that</u>
<u n="487" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0453">hardly you know hardly a hotbed of crime but London has loads of prisoners and it has quite a few prisoners but nowhere near enough to cope cope with the numbers that are being er that are that are being convicted</u>
<u n="489" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yes no yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0453">er so er</u>
<u n="491" who="S0454">someone needs to invest the next government need to invest heavily in</u>
<u n="492" who="S0453" trans="overlap">someone needs to invest exactly all of this needs</u>
<u n="493" who="S0454">building new prisons in the right places</u>
<u n="494" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yes absolutely not only building new prisons but also thinking about strategies and alternatives to this prison system so</u>
<u n="495" who="S0454" trans="overlap">yes yeah this is another problem</u>
<u n="496" who="S0453">so I don't know you bring in trainers er plumbers I don't know trained plumbers that can that can train these guys on</u>
<u n="497" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm but you could do that in prison is what some people say</u>
<u n="498" who="S0453" trans="overlap">acquiring skills</u>
<u n="499" who="S0454">like that Dartmoor prison is actually a training prison and they do they are supposed to receive courses in for example carpentry</u>
<u n="500" who="S0453" trans="overlap">learn a craft</u>
<u n="501" who="S0454">and they do and they're allowed to sell what they produce in the prison shops but perhaps that needs to be rolled out much more widely</u>
<u n="502" who="S0453">oh for sure</u>
<u n="503" who="S0454">that instead of having the odd training prison here and there</u>
<u n="504" who="S0453">it needs to be a systematic</u>
<u n="505" who="S0454" trans="overlap">needs to be systematic</u>
<u n="506" who="S0453">I think you're right</u>
<u n="507" who="S0454" trans="overlap">all prisons where you know there's some hope of people being rehabilitated and released need to be saying okay these are the courses on offer to you and like you said that Brixton restaurant thing's been hugely oversubscribed like everyone wanted to do it because they saw ah there's there are jobs in this field and it's a cool job to do these right? cooking it's</u>
<u n="508" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0454">celebrities</u>
<u n="510" who="S0453">yeah it is and I so I think we need to focus on what trades we can er trade skills and craft skills we can give these guys because this is going to give some purpose to their otherwise erm you know wandering lives</u>
<u n="511" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0453">erm and it's also going to mean that we could generate some good out of out of their erm their incarceration you know have whether it's erm in the the sort of benefit of of er selling on what they produce</u>
<u n="513" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0453">or erm or just getting them in a frame of mind that is less likely erm to result in them reoffending</u>
<u n="515" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="516" who="S0453">which I think is</u>
<u n="517" who="S0454">the other thing I wonder erm is more <trunc>ha</trunc>having more open prisons I think Isle of Wight which is an open prison so the prisoners are not dangerous so they're allowed out in the day</u>
<u n="518" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0454">to you know go around the town or whatever but in the evening</u>
<u n="520" who="S0453" trans="overlap">that's cos there's bugger all on the Isle of Wight though</u>
<u n="521" who="S0454">oh that's true but no there's old people</u>
<u n="522" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0454">but in the evening you know they have to come back there's a curfew and someone's monitoring so it's more like a a safe house I suppose you could say and of course they can do courses and things within the prison grounds but why not have that why not let them erm do that more and let people earn as well? like just because you're in prison does that mean you shouldn't be able to make a living? because I think this is a problem when they release prisoners they they are given erm like a rail warrant it's called they're given free transport to whatever city they're from in the UK and about forty pounds</u>
<u n="524" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0454">but the truth is forty pounds these days isn't gonna even get you into a flat so we've got a huge problem here where people are being released with no support and no money behind them</u>
<u n="526" who="S0453" trans="overlap">not enough to get up on their</u>
<u n="527" who="S0454">and why should the government give it to them for free? erm and <trunc>th</trunc> and then what are they going to do? they're going to go out and reoffend because you haven't given them much option unless they've got family willing to take them in then what are they going to do? they're going to sleep rough they're going to get hungry they're going to commit a crime</u>
<u n="528" who="S0453">yeah yeah unless they've got family and friends</u>
<u n="529" who="S0454">yeah okay but this is a problem where you know people in prison don't always have that</u>
<u n="530" who="S0453">true</u>
<u n="531" who="S0454">they're and that's one of the reasons they've gone into it not only were they say from a poor background with little in the way of educational erm qualifications to get them anywhere but then they don't have that support network and someone coming out of prison after say five years inside is institutionalised they're not very likely to think oh I'll pop down the job centre and I'll wait a couple of weeks while they sort out my benefits you know it's all wrong</u>
<u n="532" who="S0453">yeah I mean that's what they're that's what the erm that's what the probation officers and the social workers are supposed to do they're supposed to help them reintegrate into society</u>
<u n="533" who="S0454">but there aren't enough</u>
<u n="534" who="S0453">there aren't enough absolutely</u>
<u n="535" who="S0454">I mean there the there aren't enough half way houses the government doesn't provide half way houses what they need is sheltered accommodation when they come out there's charities doing that work but there aren't enough and that to me is criminal that we haven't thought through what happens on release</u>
<u n="536" who="S0453" trans="overlap">no true</u>
<u n="537" who="S0454">and if you're releasing someone with no money behind them and no support it it's kind of obvious what's going to happen next</u>
<u n="538" who="S0453">yeah I mean the system needs to allow these people to reintegrate into society and if we complain about reoffending rates you know this is certainly going to be a contributing and contributory factor to that</u>
<u n="539" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0453">erm but I think we should erm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0454">people shouldn't be released until it's clear where they're going to stay that night</u>
<u n="542" who="S0453">yeah the problem is</u>
<u n="543" who="S0454">that needs to happen and that needs to be if if they don't have family and friends who are able to say yes I'm taking them then the government has to provide hostels for them it's the only way otherwise you might as well just say you know go out and reoffend</u>
<u n="544" who="S0453">so what you're saying is the the new investment needs to be not just in refurbishing and building new prisons</u>
<u n="545" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0453">but also building housing</u>
<u n="547" who="S0454" trans="overlap">what we do afterwards not just building housing but how there's no point releasing a prisoner without having a plan for them</u>
<u n="548" who="S0453">yeah but that plan could be thrown away</u>
<u n="549" who="S0454">it could be but at the moment there is no plan</u>
<u n="550" who="S0453">no</u>
<u n="551" who="S0454">for the vast majority of prisoners there's no one supporting them I mean people are literally released from the gate no one is there to meet them you know you know they need to know where they're going to sleep that night</u>
<u n="552" who="S0453" trans="overlap">but they can they can contact people people can come and visit them while they're in prison they can write to people they can say tell them</u>
<u n="553" who="S0454">we we're saying that people you know these are the lucky ones who have family who are willing and able to visit</u>
<u n="554" who="S0453" trans="overlap">or friends</u>
<u n="555" who="S0454">but as we just say the prisons are all over the shop</u>
<u n="556" who="S0453">or friends</u>
<u n="557" who="S0454" trans="overlap">so they might but they might not be able to</u>
<u n="558" who="S0453">that's true</u>
<u n="559" who="S0454">if they're from Manchester and the prisons on Dartmoor they're going to get one visit a year probably and that's the truth of it</u>
<u n="560" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah this this is true</u>
<u n="561" who="S0454">not to mention prisoners are moved round the country all the time</u>
<u n="562" who="S0453">they are</u>
<u n="563" who="S0454">so it's you know</u>
<u n="564" who="S0453">some of it depends on the level of security that that you know</u>
<u n="565" who="S0454" trans="overlap">it's not just that though it's about overcrowding again so you know there's Dartmoor prison is never an issue of security it's always about they're full</u>
<u n="566" who="S0453" trans="overlap">it's about overcrowding it's it's yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0454">or they're not full and this one is near a hospital this let's say you're in Dartmoor prison and you develop er a heart problem</u>
<u n="568" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0454">now they're not going to keep you in Dartmoor prison because they know if some if you have a heart attack in the night you might well die because the nearest hospital is one hour's drive away and you're going to have to get a doctor out from an hour away from Plymouth to that prisoner so they're not going to put they're not going to keep that guy there they're now going to move him to anywhere else in the UK which is near a hospital</u>
<u n="570" who="S0453" trans="overlap">near a hospital</u>
<u n="571" who="S0454">and that's what needs to happen and so they shift you know these prisoners around so they shift that one out of let's say Nottingham and then they move the one from Nottingham down to to Dartmoor</u>
<u n="572" who="S0453" trans="overlap">some of it is bad behaviour though or abuse by other prisoners or <unclear/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0454" trans="overlap">some of it's bad behaviour they get they get violent and then they have to be moved for you know their safety or</u>
<u n="574" who="S0453" trans="overlap">there's a lot of factors yeah yeah other prisoners' safety yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0454">but I mean they've still got cells there which are designed for one person holding two</u>
<u n="578" who="S0453">segregation units</u>
<u n="579" who="S0454">and this has this has been going on for ages they're not supposed to do that cos it's been outlawed ages ago but I mean they literally don't have space</u>
<u n="580" who="S0453" trans="overlap">oh right okay but they but they've got two beds?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0454" trans="overlap">that's wrong yeah they've got two beds but I mean you if you've got a tiny cell designed for one person and you put two in and they're there twenty-three hours a day you're asking for trouble</u>
<u n="582" who="S0453" trans="overlap">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="583" who="S0454">you're asking for them to kick off at some point</u>
<u n="584" who="S0453">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="585" who="S0454">and then you've got nowhere to hold them elsewhere</u>
<u n="586" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0454">if things do go wrong so</u>
<u n="588" who="S0453">this is true you're right you're right</u>
<u n="589" who="S0454">this is yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0453">it's not a it's not a vote winning erm thing</u>
<u n="591" who="S0454">that's the problem people yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0453" trans="overlap">no one people don't like prisons</u>
<u n="593" who="S0454">yes people don't like <trunc>pr</trunc> they think good they're in prison and they fight good</u>
<u n="594" who="S0453">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0454">er they're in prison they deserve it oh you say the facilities aren't very good in prison you know cos they're overcrowded who cares? they deserve it</u>
<u n="596" who="S0453">so unless unless there's public attention I mean you seem quite concerned about this but</u>
<u n="597" who="S0454">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0453">your average voter isn't so <trunc>un</trunc><trunc>un</trunc>unless and until it becomes an election issue governments aren't going to care</u>
<u n="599" who="S0454" trans="overlap">that's the trouble isn't it? no you're right</u>
<u n="600" who="S0453">and and they're in for four years and they don't they don't give a toss you know they're just there to to to basically erm polish their erm legacy and reputation and and do what erm er what what what's likely to be popular and look popular and that's it</u>
<u n="601" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0453">this is not this is not in that category of erm of policies isn't it?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0454">that's true it's not a vote winner</u>
<u n="604" who="S0453">is it? sorry</u>
<u n="605" who="S0454" trans="overlap">and it's it's erm an expense as well it's going to be something that if you did tackle it would need huge amounts of money thrown at it so that's not going to be popular with anyone when we're saying that schools can't have money schools are facing a funding crisis</u>
<u n="606" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0454">and then we're going to talk about giving a lot of money to the prison service for people who have done something wrong I mean most people are going to say that money should be spent on schools or hospitals</u>
<u n="608" who="S0453">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0454">but for me it's a <trunc>b</trunc> matter of basic human rights like that and also if you want to stop people offending in the first place or reoffending then you need to tackle this problem</u>
<u n="610" who="S0453">yeah and I think one one area that you know that the revolution will be televised kind of seemed to highlight quite a lot is enforcement of taxes against big corporations</u>
<u n="611" who="S0454">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0453">that are actually liable for huge amounts</u>
<u n="613" who="S0454">that's right you but part of the problem with that is the government is scared if they take on say Costa coffee</u>
<u n="614" who="S0453">of pissing of the big lobbies</u>
<u n="615" who="S0454">Starbucks or whoever it is but it's not just that those companies will threaten to move elsewhere</u>
<u n="616" who="S0453" trans="overlap">elsewhere</u>
<u n="617" who="S0454">and that's what HSBC has threatened to do <trunc>la</trunc> you know just this last week</u>
<u n="618" who="S0453" trans="overlap">after the whole tax crackdown</u>
<u n="619" who="S0454">after this whole Swiss scandal and then the MPs you know really jumping on them cos of the election they had to</u>
<u n="620" who="S0453">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0454">then of course they've just immediately gone fine we'll withdraw our headquarters from London and we won't have this problem any more so that's what they're worried about that they'll move to countries who are less stringent</u>
<u n="622" who="S0453">true</u>
<u n="623" who="S0454">and then we've not only you know lost the tax you know the tax that we already weren't getting but we've also lost jobs</u>
<u n="624" who="S0453" trans="overlap">but also the business and jobs yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="625" who="S0454" trans="overlap">the business and the what they were what they were bringing to the country but too bad I'm sorry it's just that's tough like we have to to tackle these people you can't expect the individual to pay when we see these huge corporations getting away with it</u>
<u n="626" who="S0453" trans="overlap">this is true yeah this is this is the trouble it's the it's the people at the bottom of the rung that wind up paying erm you know <trunc>pa</trunc> basically contributing most to government revenue because they don't understand the tax system they don't have these the the the ways and means to avoid erm to legally avoid paying tax and they can't sit down with with erm HMRC and say okay look we'll pay you half or we'll pay you a quarter they can't negotiate a deal</u>
<u n="627" who="S0454" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah that's right</u>
<u n="628" who="S0453">and</u>
<u n="629" who="S0454">and that's wrong</u>
<u n="630" who="S0453">it is wrong so anyway yeah shall we er</u>
<u n="631" who="S0454">call it a day?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0453">call it a day yeah brilliant</u>
<u n="633" who="S0454">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh sorry</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
