<text id="SW55">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:18:44</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0192 S0227</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In ANON's spare bedroom at Dad's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Computers, Kelly Brook, documents, banking, corpus linguistics, flights, scanning, cooking</topics>
		<activity>Sorting out paperwork with Dad</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0227">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crayford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>customer services agent</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Spanish -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0192">Chinese chess</u>
<u n="2" who="S0227">er yeah I kept my old case but the software inside is quite erm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0192">is new yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0227">is quite fast and</u>
<u n="5" who="S0192">is this working this time?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0192">good</u>
<u n="8" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0192">I need to once I <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="10" who="S0227">sporadic but</u>
<u n="11" who="S0192">once I do these contracts I need to scan them in I don't really need to print as such it's just</u>
<u n="12" who="S0227" trans="overlap">er scanning might it will scan but er it it it will scan but not directly off it will use that to scan but I'm having to run it off this but it can still scan</u>
<u n="13" who="S0192">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0227">there was a problem with it</u>
<u n="15" who="S0192">alright as long as it's through the computer or whatever I just need to scan oh you've got Kelly Brook again</u>
<u n="16" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she's ageing with you I imagine</u>
<u n="18" who="S0227">indeed</u>
<u n="19" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0227">yes yes it wasn't a her better month</u>
<u n="21" who="S0192">she looks quite old there</u>
<u n="22" who="S0227">er her nicer month was last month</u>
<u n="23" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0227">because she's</u>
<u n="25" who="S0192">she doesn't look so nice in that one</u>
<u n="26" who="S0227">no er</u>
<u n="27" who="S0192">yeah that one's not bad</u>
<u n="28" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0192">is that your old calendar</u>
<u n="30" who="S0227">yep <pause dur="short"/> there's a few extra ones in the er July was quite nice <pause dur="short"/> I I don't know what the other months are I I I'm pleasantly surprised but July was quite nice</u>
<u n="31" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah when you can see her nipples you can never go wrong with that</u>
<u n="32" who="S0227">that's why I keep her I keep it er I threw one of the years away cos it wouldn't fit on there and it was like the the <trunc>th</trunc>the least favoured pictures I</u>
<u n="33" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got all of his erm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0192">that's a nice picture of the house</u>
<u n="36" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="37" who="S0192">where are my documents?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="39" who="S0192">and I'm still sleeping in there?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="42" who="S0227">there's that</u>
<u n="43" who="S0192">student loans</u>
<u n="44" who="S0227">that's your card but erm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did more than this come this is just an empty</u>
<u n="46" who="S0227">yeah yeah that that erm is is all in there</u>
<u n="47" who="S0192">the student loan stuff is in there is it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0227">yeah there's a bit more student loan probably here</u>
<u n="49" who="S0192"><unclear/> so</u>
<u n="50" who="S0227">sorry there's a bit more</u>
<u n="51" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="52" who="S0227">and there's a bit of student loan there <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0192">anything else?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0227">erm <pause dur="short"/> I think that's about it erm what you er wanted I I think I put it straight here</u>
<u n="55" who="S0192">cool</u>
<u n="56" who="S0227">and it wasn't erm ah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'll have a look through it and make sure I've got everything</u>
<u n="58" who="S0227">Lloyds bank is that yours? something about an overdraft facility? or is that mine?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0192"><anon type="financialDetails"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0227">no that's mine</u>
<u n="61" who="S0192">yeah that's <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="62" who="S0227">or is that yours?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0192">Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0227">no that's you</u>
<u n="65" who="S0192">that's mine yeah <pause dur="short"/> er that's no mine</u>
<u n="66" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="67" who="S0192"><unclear/> first aid training</u>
<u n="68" who="S0227" trans="overlap">so that's your University of <unclear/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0192">oh yeah don't need that <pause dur="short"/> that's yours is it?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0227">yeah that'll be mine <pause dur="short"/> so I think that's your <trunc>doc</trunc> your <trunc>s</trunc> your your erm what's it's called? so those paperwork I scanned and sent you is in that envelope</u>
<u n="71" who="S0192">everything should be up here <pause dur="short"/> I'll have a look then</u>
<u n="72" who="S0227">I've gotta download some photographs and send them to work</u>
<u n="73" who="S0192">is that for work? terms and conditions Barclaycard <pause dur="short"/> oh it doesn't look any different <pause dur="short"/> I take it the pin doesn't change <pause dur="short"/> never got that money off Barclaycard in the end</u>
<u n="74" who="S0227">you mean what the PPI?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0192">yeah it just was</u>
<u n="76" who="S0227">I think if you'd have pressed it you will probably if you had put it through a if if you put it through one of those PPI erm ambulance chasing companies they will take about a third if you're quite happy out of principle to say well <trunc>loo</trunc> I'll let you do all the <trunc>r</trunc>running you'd probably get the money</u>
<u n="77" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0227">they'd take thirty percent of it but</u>
<u n="79" who="S0192">I was just it was made more complex by the fact I was in a different country</u>
<u n="80" who="S0227">yep</u>
<u n="81" who="S0192">had I have been here I'd have probably done that but er</u>
<u n="82" who="S0227">well yes cos I think I think they've got a standard response in that it everyone sends a letter <pause dur="short"/> they will contest it hoping that er a number of these will fall by the wayside</u>
<u n="83" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0227">and just accept it <pause dur="short"/> others will be more tenacious and they will carry on <pause dur="short"/> and they're the ones <unclear/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well they were quite cheeky as well I'd actually just before this whole process asked them to up my credit allowance my credit limit</u>
<u n="86" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0192"><unclear/> I think I was at about five grand or something like four and a half grand and I told them I wanted more and they said no they denied me for an extension but then when I was applying for this they then sent me a completely random thing through the post saying congratulations I've been granted an extension and put it up from four and a half to seven seven</u>
<u n="88" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0192">so I got like seven thousand seven hundred</u>
<u n="90" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0192">so at that point I was <unclear/> I I really felt like they did that to</u>
<u n="92" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0192">to kind of stop me</u>
<u n="94" who="S0227">it</u>
<u n="95" who="S0192">I can't be certain</u>
<u n="96" who="S0227">it's nice to have that as a cushion</u>
<u n="97" who="S0192">yeah I don't really use it and then if you don't use it they start trying to take it away again and it's like why?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0192">why take it away? I mean I might use it</u>
<u n="100" who="S0227">I'm trying to use it yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0192">I haven't done anything wrong</u>
<u n="102" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> now they're trying to push you into it so that they you know they get the interest</u>
<u n="103" who="S0192">so then my overdraft has been cut thank you very much <pause dur="short"/> so I mean all they've done by shutting down this overdraft now is I'm gonna go and shut down this bank account</u>
<u n="104" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0192">so that they've just lost a customer basically</u>
<u n="106" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0192">it didn't cost them anything to allow me to</u>
<u n="108" who="S0227" trans="overlap">if I was you I would I would I would keep some I wouldn't close it down <pause dur="short"/> I've still got one that I had from Royston that's got about twenty-three P in it because you never know on a rainy day if you're gonna need it cos it's quite er a process to open up a bank account</u>
<u n="109" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0227">so I'd just keep it there</u>
<u n="111" who="S0192">yeah I mean I er yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0227" trans="overlap">cos if someone ever <pause dur="short"/> you know if you ever er prepare for a rainy day if someone whoever is coming to look at your assets you can split your assets up and they'll think that you've only got one bank account why would you have two?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0227">so always it doesn't it doesn't cost you and it will you'll have to put effort to close it so don't just leave a couple of quid in there and let it run <pause dur="short"/> I've had a like I've said I've had erm a Royston account for er thirty years</u>
<u n="115" who="S0192"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> what do you think to erm having a joint account?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0227">erm yeah it's okay</u>
<u n="117" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I were kind of gonna join our accounts or whatever you know</u>
<u n="118" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> well er I'd discuss that funnily enough with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she doesn't seem to want to go down that route herself</u>
<u n="119" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="120" who="S0227">but that's her own neurosis erm erm in principle I'd say it's a good idea because you can save yourselves money like if you erm I said to her look join my premier because I she pays for gold and I pay for <trunc>prem</trunc>premier</u>
<u n="121" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0227">fuse with mine and you save yourself the money of paying for the gold account</u>
<u n="123" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean for us for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I every time we transfer money home we get charged about thirty pounds and then we're sending we're currently sending it into two bank accounts</u>
<u n="124" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="125" who="S0192">and like I'm gonna get my final pay now and they owe me August pay and a bonus month's pay like my severance basically</u>
<u n="126" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0192">so that's effectively four payments between the two of us</u>
<u n="128" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0192">and I was saying to them look could you not just pay us August pay and my severance pay</u>
<u n="130" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0192">into one bank account at the same time?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0227">yes yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0192">therefore costing me thirty pound in fees but now I'm having to pay a hundred pound in fees no a hundred and twenty pound in fees</u>
<u n="134" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0192">thirty for each of the four transactions</u>
<u n="136" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="137" who="S0192">it would just be easier if we</u>
<u n="138" who="S0227">yeah well if she's up for it I would go for it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0192">yeah I'm pretty sure she is</u>
<u n="140" who="S0227">cos it's makes financial sense</u>
<u n="141" who="S0192">pretty sure she is <pause dur="short"/> yeah I need to fill out these forms and then scan them in send them back to them <pause dur="short"/> yay</u>
<u n="142" who="S0227">so you you'll be proofreading I guess <pause dur="short"/> will it be something like that?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0192">proofreading?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0227">what is it you're doing for this er this little job?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0192">ah with the recording?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0192">yeah I just explained to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so Cambridge University Press</u>
<u n="148" who="S0227">yes <pause dur="short"/> I never read any of the stuff I just knew it said Cambridge University in the in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0192">yeah it's not it's kind of done through them <pause dur="short"/> basically they're there's something called corpus linguistics</u>
<u n="150" who="S0227">okay</u>
<u n="151" who="S0192">corpus being body linguistics</u>
<u n="152" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0192">language body of language <pause dur="short"/> they're erm they did a corpus about five or ten years ago and they collected three hundred million words from the British public in written down</u>
<u n="154" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0192">and then they use that corpus so you can come up with a phrase er let's think of er an idiom for example it's raining cats and dogs</u>
<u n="156" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0192">we now all have these words in the database so any phrase that I wanna search the frequency of in the language I can type it in and it'll tell me out of one million words how many times does this occur? what position does it occur in? so they've now managed to find out like which words are the most commonly used</u>
<u n="158" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0192">all this kind of things and it's been useful for ELT textbooks like teaching English textbooks</u>
<u n="160" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0192">and all this kind of stuff</u>
<u n="162" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0192">and the learners like to hear you know that when they hear this version and this version do we say thanks or do we say thank you? well</u>
<u n="164" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0192">thanks is seventy percent more common than thank you</u>
<u n="166" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0192">in British written language <pause dur="short"/> so now they're collecting a spoken corpus and they want something like a hundred thousand hours of recordings from the British public</u>
<u n="168" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right okay</u>
<u n="169" who="S0192">so I'm getting these it's pretty good pay I'm getting paid eighteen pound an hour</u>
<u n="170" who="S0227">that's good</u>
<u n="171" who="S0192">for every hour of recording I do is eighteen pounds</u>
<u n="172" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0192">now I have to at the end I have to go back obviously if I'm recording friends get rid of anything incriminating</u>
<u n="174" who="S0227">that's yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0192">get rid of anything where there's background noise</u>
<u n="176" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0192">in the car <pause dur="short"/> I recorded once in the car and it was the car was a bit too noisy so I'm hoping that your car is a little quieter <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well we had er did we have the windows open or did we?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0192">no we had the windows done up so it should be okay</u>
<u n="180" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="181" who="S0192">outside is too windy to do it</u>
<u n="182" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0192">so it I have to do some more work afterwards and I fill out consent forms and all this kind of stuff</u>
<u n="184" who="S0227">okay</u>
<u n="185" who="S0192">but you know it's about an hour and a half's work for every hour</u>
<u n="186" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="187" who="S0192">you get paid so it's not bad</u>
<u n="188" who="S0227">no not at all well it's all all helps doesn't it</u>
<u n="189" who="S0192">I mean it's kind of the perfect job for when I come home really <pause dur="short"/> I don't have to go for a job interview or</u>
<u n="190" who="S0227">yes definitely</u>
<u n="191" who="S0192">I was quite pleased to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh I'll show you that er thing I was on about like what what I showed to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm and copied your mum in but he he didn't erm he didn't respond</u>
<u n="193" who="S0192">what thing was that?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0227">this</u>
<u n="195" who="S0192">okay yeah where you can search for the flights <pause dur="short"/> he just didn't respond to it did he?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0227">no er</u>
<u n="197" who="S0192">have you got a bin in here or a shredder or something?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0227">er I'll I'll <trunc>t</trunc>take it downstairs</u>
<u n="199" who="S0192">alright I think it's all shredding <unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0227">that's all the planes at the moment in the real life that are around</u>
<u n="201" who="S0192">oh wow</u>
<u n="202" who="S0227">that's quite frightening isn't it</u>
<u n="203" who="S0192">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0227">so if you go like here <pause dur="short"/> let's go to</u>
<u n="205" who="S0192">does show you though that when you're a bit paranoid about the plane crashing or something how many there are</u>
<u n="206" who="S0227">yep <pause dur="short"/> so if you look at that that</u>
<u n="207" who="S0192">oh there are a lot of planes</u>
<u n="208" who="S0227">that flight there is <pause dur="short"/> you see it moving?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty <trunc>s</trunc>so find the one closest to flying over us now</u>
<u n="210" who="S0227">that's er</u>
<u n="211" who="S0192">Indianapolis to <trunc>st</trunc> to London</u>
<u n="212" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0192">Stansted</u>
<u n="214" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0227">so it's outbound it's obviously gonna curl round</u>
<u n="217" who="S0192">do a loop and land?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0227">yeah er er it's er oh no it's actually er what? no that's it actually that's it should have landed it's come in</u>
<u n="219" who="S0192">yeah it seems to have gone past the</u>
<u n="220" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0192">the airport</u>
<u n="222" who="S0227">so I don't know why it's doing that er</u>
<u n="223" who="S0192">maybe he can't land</u>
<u n="224" who="S0227" trans="overlap">let's see where this is going</u>
<u n="225" who="S0192">there are quite a few plane's coming in</u>
<u n="226" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> let's see where this one's going <pause dur="long"/> it hasn't got one for that one <pause dur="short"/> try that one</u>
<u n="227" who="S0192">it's cos you're double clicking click once</u>
<u n="228" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="229" who="S0192">there you go <pause dur="short"/> heathrow to JFK</u>
<u n="230" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0192">surely that other one's to JFK too or somewhere in the states</u>
<u n="232" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0192">yeah that's a nifty piece of software isn't it</u>
<u n="234" who="S0227">that's and so I tried to so what I did was I</u>
<u n="235" who="S0192">presumably it's got like a five minute delay on it or something</u>
<u n="236" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I</u>
<u n="237" who="S0192">oh uhu</u>
<u n="238" who="S0227">loads there and I was coming over and and tracking</u>
<u n="239" who="S0192">you were trying to <pause dur="short"/> were you actually tracking my flight?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0227">I was trying to find it but I couldn't with the numbers that you gave me</u>
<u n="241" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="242" who="S0227">cos you can use this <pause dur="short"/> type</u>
<u n="243" who="S0192">like type it in</u>
<u n="244" who="S0227">type to to to find the plane <pause dur="short"/> so I couldn't find it <pause dur="short"/> but you can see over this area there's not a great deal of planes</u>
<u n="245" who="S0192">no yeah I came</u>
<u n="246" who="S0227">like this one here is</u>
<u n="247" who="S0192">I came on on that exact route I came up kind of across this way and then over that way</u>
<u n="248" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0192">it's going to Ulan Bator</u>
<u n="250" who="S0227">so it's going to</u>
<u n="251" who="S0192">Mongolia</u>
<u n="252" who="S0227">yeah so it's going to um <trunc>Inch</trunc> er it's going to Incheon</u>
<u n="253" who="S0192">yeah from <trunc>Mongol</trunc> from Mongolia</u>
<u n="254" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0192">from Ulan Bator</u>
<u n="256" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0192">what about this one?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0227">that one here?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="261" who="S0192">not the <unclear/> it's getting to somewhere and</u>
<u n="262" who="S0227">yeah yeah god knows</u>
<u n="263" who="S0192">it's going to <unclear/> I have no idea where that one have you?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no idea <pause dur="short"/> so it was quite a a cos like I said you could watch them and and you have this software like on your Ipad and you're sitting in the garden and you see a plane going over you can see what that plane is</u>
<u n="265" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0227">by erm just seeing that it's passing over us</u>
<u n="267" who="S0192">it's pretty impressive isn't it</u>
<u n="268" who="S0227">erm yeah I put my Sat Nav er when we went to France France I actually got it to work on the plane <pause dur="short"/> and the take-off speed was about a hundred and seventy erm <trunc>th</trunc>then you took off and it went quickly to three hundred and then it stayed at three hundred for a while we went north then we went west and then we went south east which is the correct direction to go <pause dur="short"/> and er I think they were trying to catch up on time because I lost it as we come to the English Channel <pause dur="short"/> but the speed there was about five hundred and thirty-five miles an hour but the towns were just literally going off <pause dur="short"/> I've got a five inch screen so it's just</u>
<u n="269" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0227">they were just literally just moving like that</u>
<u n="271" who="S0192">and you're allowed to have this on on the plane?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="273" who="S0192">are you?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> now they the the all the technology all they've got to do is put things it says you can use your phones and that just put them in flight mode</u>
<u n="275" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0227">so er yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0227">so you can use this er but I couldn't get a er I couldn't get lock on with er er when I came back from France I had it locked on at the airport but as it started to taxi to take off I lost the signal and I couldn't get it back</u>
<u n="279" who="S0192">oh gone</u>
<u n="280" who="S0227">so that was it but I think I was er lucky that I was able to get it cos I'd tried the year before and I I <unclear/> I thought I'll give it another go erm and erm what I done was I'd actually locked up before I'd got on the plane I went in the plane you know and we were by the window so I could get it so that was</u>
<u n="281" who="S0192">mm that's nice</u>
<u n="282" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that was actually quite interesting because but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was going ooh it'll break I said the plane could go twenty thousand miles an hour it's digital you see it's not mechanical</u>
<u n="283" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="284" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0227">for god's sake</u>
<u n="287" who="S0192">she's thinking it's going to</u>
<u n="288" who="S0227">yeah yeah the cogs it'll break</u>
<u n="289" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0227">bless her so that's quite funny <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0192">all good <pause dur="short"/> so I need to fill out these forms and</u>
<u n="292" who="S0227">right I'm going to get I'm going to get changed</u>
<u n="293" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0227">and er you can see your <trunc>be</trunc> your boudoir erm right scanning <pause dur="short"/> if you want to scan <pause dur="short"/> pop this thing in and I I said try trying to drive you through <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna test it with anything you like</u>
<u n="295" who="S0192">I mean I do do have something to scan downstairs actually</u>
<u n="296" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm just pop in anything just to to get it up and running</u>
<u n="297" who="S0192">oh right we're not gonna scan the actual thing</u>
<u n="298" who="S0227">no just <trunc>any</trunc>anything you like erm just to erm if I'm driving it through the erm thingy er through the package here which is your erm <trunc>s</trunc> er where the hell is it from?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0192">Cannon</u>
<u n="300" who="S0227">it it's malfunctioning I I'll try it now just to see if it will work but it had been <trunc>mal</trunc>malfunctioning right er auto-scan <pause dur="short"/> scan</u>
<u n="301" who="S0192">yeah I need to fill out some documents and then scan them in</u>
<u n="302" who="S0227">let's see what happens</u>
<u n="303" who="S0192">is this my water? mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="305" who="S0192">I thought so</u>
<u n="306" who="S0227">right I think we'll go through all this but then it will say erm unless it's fixed itself</u>
<u n="307" who="S0192">so you actually haven't finished getting Game of Thrones have you?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="309" who="S0192">have you got one to watch later or?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0227">well yeah erm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0192">what do you watch it with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> normally do you?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0227" trans="overlap">er no I don't watch it with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I I <unclear/> but there you go</u>
<u n="313" who="S0192">it's not working</u>
<u n="314" who="S0227">cannot scan for these reasons</u>
<u n="315" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="316" who="S0227">so I've not bothered trying er I've tried half-heartedly to get to the bottom of that so in order to scan now er just go to erm control panel</u>
<u n="317" who="S0192">there's always another way round</u>
<u n="318" who="S0227">er view devices and printers</u>
<u n="319" who="S0192">you're a Windows 7 aren't you</u>
<u n="320" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0192">have you seen Windows 8?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0227">yes I've seen it but I don't particularly like it I've got</u>
<u n="323" who="S0192">I've got it on my new laptop</u>
<u n="324" who="S0227">yeah I've got it on erm erm a pirated copy</u>
<u n="325" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0227">like everything I have is virtually pirated <pause dur="short"/> erm but erm it's got erm what's it called erm the the the outlook's completely different and that and so you get used to certain things really so that erm I've got it cos it shows a lot of interest but I've never bothered to upload it <pause dur="short"/> right it's</u>
<u n="327" who="S0192">it's actually okay</u>
<u n="328" who="S0227">start scan</u>
<u n="329" who="S0192">although it takes some getting used to but it's not too bad</u>
<u n="330" who="S0227">yeah I suppose it's just like everything really isn't it <pause dur="short"/> erm would it be</u>
<u n="331" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they've made it more like a mobile phone though</u>
<u n="332" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="333" who="S0192">you know with all these apps and</u>
<u n="334" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="335" who="S0192">whatnot but it it looks nice and it I guess for me cos my last laptop ran so</u>
<u n="336" who="S0227">well yes</u>
<u n="337" who="S0192">poorly but this one runs quite nicely</u>
<u n="338" who="S0227">that's quite sensible <pause dur="short"/> here's the er I don't know if you'll I'm sure you'll remember your password for it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0192">I'm pretty sure I gave you this to give to</u>
<u n="340" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="341" who="S0192">wasn't this your cousin? or someone was gonna take it?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0227">yeah never did cos I er er in fact I er</u>
<u n="343" who="S0192">cos I mean I don't I don't want it</u>
<u n="344" who="S0227">I know it's <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="345" who="S0192">I'll have that Cadbury's Milk Tray though</u>
<u n="346" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0227">when I said when I find it yeah I can I can throw it then because I know it's in here somewhere</u>
<u n="348" who="S0192">these are nice cupboards aren't they? nice and <unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0227">yes yeah they're not bad</u>
<u n="350" who="S0192">so it's</u>
<u n="351" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0192">everything that you've erm you said I can borrow has that been arranged? you've like put that aside?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0227">er no no we'll have to we'll have to er erm do that with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> right er let's see what we've got here</u>
<u n="354" who="S0192">alright what size is the table that you said?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0227">er well what we'll do is we'll talk about this while we're having our tea</u>
<u n="356" who="S0192">yeah okay</u>
<u n="357" who="S0227">erm where the hell has it gone? I've <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="358" who="S0192">I've got the list with me so we can run through and see er who's definitely got that stuff</u>
<u n="359" who="S0227" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="360" who="S0192">if you haven't that's fine</u>
<u n="361" who="S0227">let's go to would it be there? downloads no I I'm not sure where it'll have gone <pause dur="short"/> where the hell did it go? ah users <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my pictures probably in here</u>
<u n="362" who="S0192">what is it you're looking for?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0227">er that's the scan that I just did</u>
<u n="364" who="S0192">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0227">erm cos when you're gonna scan</u>
<u n="366" who="S0192">yeah I need to know where it goes</u>
<u n="367" who="S0227">exactly <unclear/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0192">are you still studying French?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0227">er Spanish as well at <trunc>the</trunc> imported item</u>
<u n="370" who="S0192">really</u>
<u n="371" who="S0227">right that's it <pause dur="short"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0192" trans="overlap">can you put a shortcut to that folder on the desk maybe?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0227">eh?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0192">on the desktop</u>
<u n="375" who="S0227">er let's sort by name refresh saves view extra large now where's it gone? imported pictures</u>
<u n="376" who="S0192">so you need to find that folder so maybe go up one</u>
<u n="377" who="S0227">um</u>
<u n="378" who="S0192">cos you're actually inside the folder er no that takes you back doesn't it you don't want to refresh</u>
<u n="379" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0192">er maybe click on this drop down thing</u>
<u n="381" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0192">or back to libraries yeah where did you come from</u>
<u n="383" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0192">just before this? and what did you click on?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0227">it's in libraries so it's gonna be in my <trunc>pic</trunc> I think it'll probably be in my pictures <pause dur="short"/> probably <pause dur="short"/> image</u>
<u n="386" who="S0192">what was the folder called again?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0227">erm yeah it's there <pause dur="short"/> er erm if I <pause dur="short"/> there there it is</u>
<u n="388" who="S0192">okay so go back on that one</u>
<u n="389" who="S0227">there's your card</u>
<u n="390" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0227">so if I keep that minimised</u>
<u n="392" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if you go back here</u>
<u n="393" who="S0227">alright I I can erm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0192">go back one and then right click on this and there should be one that says</u>
<u n="395" who="S0227">send to desktop</u>
<u n="396" who="S0192">send to desktop</u>
<u n="397" who="S0227">desktop yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that one</u>
<u n="399" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="400" who="S0192">where is it?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0227">where's it gone? ah here it is <pause dur="short"/> I will leave it there</u>
<u n="402" who="S0192">drag that over there yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0227">so over there so that's</u>
<u n="404" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="405" who="S0227">everything we use you scan will go into that</u>
<u n="406" who="S0192">I'm not sure I actually saw you do the scanning part</u>
<u n="407" who="S0227">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> well when you come to scan</u>
<u n="408" who="S0192">I'll give you a shout</u>
<u n="409" who="S0227" trans="overlap">erm give it a go and if if it's not erm if it's not working out <pause dur="short"/> right I'm going to er</u>
<u n="410" who="S0192">got to have all these documents <pause dur="short"/> do you have a pen lying around or?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0227">no downstairs</u>
<u n="412" who="S0192">yes <unclear/> downstairs</u>
<u n="413" who="S0227">I'll get changed and then erm <pause dur="short"/> sort out the erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0192" trans="overlap">did you say we're having chilli for dinner?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0192">yeah is it</u>
<u n="417" who="S0227">you like chilli don't you? your brother doesn't like it</u>
<u n="418" who="S0192">he doesn't like it?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="420" who="S0192">what doesn't he like about it?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0227">well I think it's the chilli beans</u>
<u n="422" who="S0192">ah they're</u>
<u n="423" who="S0227">the kidney beans</u>
<u n="424" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're really good <pause dur="short"/> do you use like canned kidney beans or?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0227">yeah just but they're poisonous you have to cook them properly</u>
<u n="428" who="S0192">yeah I I just use the dried ones though</u>
<u n="429" who="S0227">yeah they cook them properly the ones I use are cooked properly before you cook them</u>
<u n="430" who="S0192">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
