<text id="SW6A">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:53:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0190 S0192 S0227</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In father's car between Bedford and Northamptonshire</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Greetings, the children's home, recordings, ex-husbands, friends, my brother, university, heating, truth and lies, cheating, smoking, master's degrees, modules, plagiarism, plants, curry, birthday cards, cats, train journeys, ANON's family, dentures, swimming, snacks, weather, cooking, satellite navigation, Brighton, linguistics course, mature students, cycling, Christmas, laptops, pidgins &amp; creoles, teaching, Christmas day arrangements, my brother's girlfriend, assessment, work, travel, childhoods, international universities, Ann's children, moving house, money, mortgages &amp; rent, homeless people, South Korea   </topics>
		<activity>Returning home for my father's 55th birthday</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0190">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>St Neots. Cambs.</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>55</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Activity co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0227">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crayford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>customer services agent</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Spanish -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0227">haircut</u>
<u n="2" who="S0192">you alright dad how you doing? yeah I have yeah good to see you happy birthday</u>
<u n="3" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0192">in the car</u>
<u n="5" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0192">yeah I did have my hair cut ah have you erm been waiting long?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0227">no no was that an arduous journey?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0192">erm it's gonna be harder on the way back</u>
<u n="9" who="S0227">why's that?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0192">for some reason on that Sunday I'm going back on the Sunday there's roadworks er</u>
<u n="11" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="12" who="S0192">I have to stop at three bridges and catch a bus or something</u>
<u n="13" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0192">so it's gonna take me four hours to go home</u>
<u n="15" who="S0227">that sounds a bit painful</u>
<u n="16" who="S0192">it's a little bit crap</u>
<u n="17" who="S0227">yeah oh well you're ahead of time anyway</u>
<u n="18" who="S0192">yeah I managed to get on an earlier train</u>
<u n="19" who="S0227">yeah good</u>
<u n="20" who="S0192">so that's good how you been?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0227">yes not too bad not too bad</u>
<u n="22" who="S0192">you round <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0227">yes yeah I er I'd seen him at erm the erm there was a gathering cos one of the members of staff from the home <unclear/> when I was a child has come back from America she's er erm was here on holiday she was erm English girl who met an American cos of <unclear/> base then she married him and they have a couple of kids it does make me feel old cos I remember her children being young and now the oldest is forty-one</u>
<u n="24" who="S0192">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="25" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0192">how old is she then?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0227">oh she's pretty old I still called her I still addressed her as auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0192">yeah fair</u>
<u n="29" who="S0227">when I met her so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he was going so I thought okay at was at er <trunc>Milt</trunc> er <anon type="place"/> near Milton Keynes</u>
<u n="30" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="31" who="S0227">that's where the home moved to or the the nuns moved there so</u>
<u n="32" who="S0192">so she worked there?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0227">she worked at <anon type="place"/> down here</u>
<u n="34" who="S0192">yep</u>
<u n="35" who="S0227">erm but erm she's yeah so she's met her husband she <unclear/> out <unclear/> in town they got married and they're still living they're still married and er the kids have grown up they live near Dallas</u>
<u n="36" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="37" who="S0227">so she was over</u>
<u n="38" who="S0192">that's Texas isn't it?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0227">yeah so I er I thought if er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s going I'll er I'll put in an appearance and er</u>
<u n="40" who="S0192">that was today then?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0227">no that was erm a couple of weeks a couple of Saturdays ago</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192">oh okay</u>
<u n="43" who="S0227">so I went and they were given a erm a DVD which I had been given one before so I thought it was just gonna be the same one again but it wasn't it was photographs which a load of photographs erm but there was some er nine millimetre cine film that was been converted over to DVD</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192">are you in any?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0227">well surprisingly I actually am erm not in many of the photographs and not in much of the cine but as I was going through it I thought that's me</u>
<u n="46" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0227">I'm about fifteen almost sixteen er I had to double take I thought that's got</u>
<u n="48" who="S0192" trans="overlap">long blonde hair</u>
<u n="49" who="S0227">well my hair's dark actually quite dark</u>
<u n="50" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="51" who="S0227">cos it's in black and white</u>
<u n="52" who="S0192">yeah oh yeah of course</u>
<u n="53" who="S0227">and we and the first shot is next to me of the erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother who's died no no in Spain erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s hair was very light so his hair looks considerably lighter than mine but I thought no that that is me that that can't be anybody else and then there's the next shot is in the playroom which erm must have been after this meal and there's the camera goes on to me and this I'm sitting next to this girl should I say this girl's sitting next to me who was called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and erm she was the same age as me then the camera pans away then it comes back to us then it pans away and then it comes back to us and then it pans away and that's it</u>
<u n="54" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0227">and so I was surprised cos I knew that not being a favoured child and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well that I wasn't gonna star in any of the too many of of the photographs</u>
<u n="56" who="S0192">why weren't you favoured? were you</u>
<u n="57" who="S0227">I don't know we just weren't</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192">poorly behaved or</u>
<u n="59" who="S0227">no I don't I I don't think so</u>
<u n="60" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just not from the right background or</u>
<u n="61" who="S0227">no no no I don't think that either erm probably cos I came in at I was nine so I wasn't a a young that young</u>
<u n="62" who="S0192">you couldn't mould you as well as they</u>
<u n="63" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0192">could other people</u>
<u n="65" who="S0227">er to be honest a lot of the pets you know the favourite ones we call them are dead <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a pet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a pet he's dead er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a pet he's dead <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't a pet he's dead er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't a pet he's dead erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0192">a lot of dead people</u>
<u n="67" who="S0227">he's dead yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0192">what's the percentage of dead to living? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0227">quite a lot and a lot of them were either suicide er or erm drugs or or alcohol</u>
<u n="70" who="S0192">oh terrible</u>
<u n="71" who="S0227">yeah so erm yes so erm I'll show you the footage er and see if you can recognise me</u>
<u n="72" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0227">I won't I clearly thought that that's me that has to be me and then when I started looking I thought that is definitely me cos then you go into your minds you're looking at it as though you're now looking in the mirror</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0227">and thinking woah that looks different but then once my mind's eye started to look at it I thought that's me that is me it can't be anybody but</u>
<u n="76" who="S0192" trans="overlap">made you feel a bit older though</u>
<u n="77" who="S0227">well it was forty years ago if I'm fifty</u>
<u n="78" who="S0192">bloody hell yeah you're fifty-five today aren't you?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0227">yes tomorrow I will be closer to sixty than fifty</u>
<u n="80" who="S0192">how does that feel?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0227">er <unclear/> not a but</u>
<u n="82" who="S0192" trans="overlap">although you're already closer aren't you? I mean you're fifty-five so you've completed fifty-five years this is your fifty-sixth year</u>
<u n="83" who="S0227">oh well yeah if you look at it that way yes yeah thanks for that that makes it even worse</u>
<u n="84" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry</u>
<u n="85" who="S0227">that yeah yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0192">a lot of people forget that don't they when you turn an age you've completed that many years</u>
<u n="87" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah exactly yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0192">you've done fifty-five years</u>
<u n="89" who="S0227">exacta mon</u>
<u n="90" who="S0192">start off at zero</u>
<u n="91" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0192">and even then you could add another nine months on that you're in the womb</u>
<u n="93" who="S0227">yes I know</u>
<u n="94" who="S0192">so you're almost fifty-six</u>
<u n="95" who="S0227">an an age yes been around for a while</u>
<u n="96" who="S0192">that makes me almost thirty though so I don't really like that either</u>
<u n="97" who="S0227">no yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0192">that's fair erm did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> watch the video with you or</u>
<u n="99" who="S0227">oh well she saw it cos there's there's a little bit there's a couple of bits with her but it's very bleep brief but there is one bit with I can recognise it</u>
<u n="100" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0227">I'll show you that bit as well I don't know if you'd recognise her</u>
<u n="102" who="S0192">cos she worked there as well didn't she?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0227" trans="overlap">she's about eighteen at the time yeah she's <trunc>eight</trunc> not the same when I left was I left July the second seventy-six and she went around about March seventy-seven</u>
<u n="104" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="105" who="S0227">so</u>
<u n="106" who="S0192">you weren't there together?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0227">no but I I was when I went back cos of <unclear/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0192">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0227">I was then but not er</u>
<u n="110" who="S0192">did you work there though? why did you go back?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0227">well I I worked well there was something that drew me to go back bit like a salmon</u>
<u n="112" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0227">going back to where it was spawned</u>
<u n="114" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean it was your home wasn't it for a long time so</u>
<u n="115" who="S0227">yeah yeah so there was something</u>
<u n="116" who="S0192" trans="overlap">understandable</u>
<u n="117" who="S0227">that made me go back and then er because one of the girls was there I took a bit of a shine to erm I that kind of prompted me to go back more but I'd gone back in seventy-eight but erm I didn't feel particularly welcome cos I I think still <unclear/> the taint of the erm not being one of the favourites was still there but when I went back now again in in eighty-two I could drive and and acquired a lot more polish I was more charmed more accomplished more <unclear>able to</unclear></u>
<u n="118" who="S0192">of a man</u>
<u n="119" who="S0227">I I <unclear/> found me infinitely more useful to them and then I I went rose through the rank very quickly and became the head nun's favourite male so that was quite good</u>
<u n="120" who="S0192">but were you working there though? were they like paying you or anything?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0227">well no I was unemployed yes I got paid but I was unemployed I was I had two jobs one was to check paperboys erm when they delivered their runs and I didn't really do that I just made it up and got the money</u>
<u n="122" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0227">and erm the other job was erm I got money from the Ghana fund didn't ask for it but I was given it and I was at erm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0192">the Ghana fund</u>
<u n="125" who="S0227">yeah erm there was a Ghana fund er from Africa erm and then from some reason I was getting money from from that we'd go up and get it every week</u>
<u n="126" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0227">plus I I was getting that plus my checking up on the paperboys for the for the Citizen and also I was getting my my unemployment benefits I was actually better off then financially than I'd been when I'd been before I resigned from work</u>
<u n="128" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0227">I had more disposable income strangely</u>
<u n="130" who="S0192">how long did this Ghana fund last for?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0227">I don't know but erm erm I remember it being for at least a year</u>
<u n="132" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what like a few months or a few years or whatever?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0227">being at least a year</u>
<u n="134" who="S0192">that's cool</u>
<u n="135" who="S0227">er so yes I so I didn't <trunc>hav</trunc> I had the use of a car the only thing I had to do was put petrol in it if it was you know mine if I was going somewhere but I didn't have to pay for insurance tax wear and tear or anything like that</u>
<u n="136" who="S0192">why was that?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0227">I could just the <trunc>ca</trunc> the home's car</u>
<u n="138" who="S0192">oh it was their yeah they were still <unclear/> you use it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0192">that's pretty good and did mum work there at this time?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0227">er she did yes she did er yes <trunc>eigh</trunc>eighty-three was when I met your mum er er yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0192">have you got any kind of air in here? it's quite warm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0227">yeah she er I was looking for for a girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when I went into the guard room and bumped into your mum I think erm your your mum's initial take on me was that she found to be boring but probably the reason was was I realised she she was just freshly married so er</u>
<u n="144" who="S0192">stayed away</u>
<u n="145" who="S0227">she well you would do wouldn't you really? you would then talk about things that are not kind of</u>
<u n="146" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0227">but er then er</u>
<u n="148" who="S0192">yeah I don't know much about her first husband at all in fact I know nothing I don't even know his name</u>
<u n="149" who="S0227">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0227"><trunc>i</trunc>ironically <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s name is middle name is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0192">but named after your friend</u>
<u n="153" who="S0227" trans="overlap">after yeah not him</u>
<u n="154" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0227">yeah that just turned out to be a coincidence yeah his name was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> spelt with an E</u>
<u n="156" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0227">and er</u>
<u n="158" who="S0192">so how long had they been married when you met mum?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0227">oh about a year at the most</u>
<u n="160" who="S0192">and how long was she married to him for?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0227">about eighteen months yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0192">so they divorced pretty quickly then</u>
<u n="163" who="S0227">er yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0192">some reason in the back of my head I got I had the feeling that she was still married to him when you had me</u>
<u n="165" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="166" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="167" who="S0227">no no she was er</u>
<u n="168" who="S0192">she had divorced him</u>
<u n="169" who="S0227">yes she had divorced him then</u>
<u n="170" who="S0192">why did that fall apart so quickly?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0227">er me</u>
<u n="172" who="S0192">really quick</u>
<u n="173" who="S0227">me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0192">fair</u>
<u n="175" who="S0227">me <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's the reason why</u>
<u n="176" who="S0192">so you went from boring to breaking apart her marriage in the matter of about six months?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0227">er longer than that there was a what happened was if you it didn't really kick eighty-three was when I met her I think she might have started to take a shine to me although I initially like she said she thought I was boring but the looks obviously erm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0192">helped <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0227"><unclear/> made an impact</u>
<u n="180" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0227">and I had a girlfriend there anyway and erm she then we kind of fraternised a bit well quite a lot but not nothing <trunc>goin</trunc> cos I still had a girlfriend so I was yeah just a bit of flirtation</u>
<u n="182" who="S0192">bit of banter</u>
<u n="183" who="S0227">bit of banter yeah that's it then erm the home was cutting down and they were making people redundant so your mum rather than having redundancy there was <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s was taking on some so she went to work at <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s as well cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s on the scene <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was at the home</u>
<u n="184" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0227">as a fifteen year old there's one photograph of him</u>
<u n="186" who="S0192">he's a bit younger isn't he?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0227">yeah so erm what happens then is is that I she's moved to that and the only reason I will go there now is to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and but I think I think I'd bumped into her in <anon type="place"/> or something like that and then I think it started to er she started to go into overdrive erm doing most of the pursuing er really er and I was then starting to make excuses to my girlfriend as to why <vocal desc="laugh"/> what was <unclear/> and the rest is history</u>
<u n="188" who="S0192">was there a point then there where you kind of both decided that you're gonna break up you know finish her first marriage or was this something she decided or</u>
<u n="189" who="S0227">oh well I she probably erm yeah once I was on the scene erm I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> found out about it</u>
<u n="190" who="S0192">did you get any problems from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0227">no I thought I was there I was just saying to to and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> answered a strange thing about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this was a woman who'd been a child at the home herself but now was a fully blown blown adult she was about seventy and she was in a wheelchair she was er quite frail when she was in a wheelchair and there was some kind of centenary thing your mum was going to it presumably her husband was I was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s blue-eyed boy I was going out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I was supposed to be erm who was her blue-eyed girl and I was supposed to be wheeling madly around on this wheelchair well I'd done my back in I still did the wheelchair but I felt incredibly exposed because I thought if if something kicks off now I'm really not at my best at all er fortunately your mum went he didn't so that didn't but I thought you're right on my home turf here er I don't think you're <trunc>gon</trunc> it's gonna kick off I'm physically bigger than you he's about the same kind of he was slimmer</u>
<u n="192" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0227">and</u>
<u n="194" who="S0192">more like my build</u>
<u n="195" who="S0227">but but no no <trunc>sli</trunc> your build but but erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s height</u>
<u n="196" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="197" who="S0227">she likes small men I'm the biggest man she's ever been with of all her boyfriends I they're all small</u>
<u n="198" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0227">and</u>
<u n="200" who="S0192">so did you ever meet this guy like talk to</u>
<u n="201" who="S0227">yeah yeah yeah er we in the same room we never actually spoke I don't think I I didn't know him if I'd have known him I couldn't have done what I did</u>
<u n="202" who="S0192">and over the next bunch of years did he contact her or</u>
<u n="203" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="204" who="S0192">he just kind of they divorced and that was it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0227">they they divorced</u>
<u n="206" who="S0192">where is he? <unclear/> guy</u>
<u n="207" who="S0227">er last he he was working in he worked in a TV shop in in <anon type="place"/> he was working there for years I don't know if she still works there now or not</u>
<u n="208" who="S0192">high flyer then yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0227">er but er obviously they weren't meant to be if there had been any children I wouldn't <unclear/> have entertained</u>
<u n="210" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="211" who="S0227">but I was young erm she was young erm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0192">how long had she been seeing him before she married him? she seems like she dived into it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that I don't know I know that</u>
<u n="214" who="S0192">did they go to the same school or something?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="216" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="217" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="218" who="S0192">so it can't have been long then</u>
<u n="219" who="S0227">no she'd had a couple of boyfriends er before him er some guy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then it was then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came on the scene <pause dur="short"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going back at the <unclear/> he'd been like boyfriend and give a bit probably a bit strange cos she was fifteen and and he was fourteen ah one would kind of assume that he never looked big for his age are you with me?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0192">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0227">he's not like a six footer where you'd go well bloody er at fourteen you looked eighteen cos you're so tall</u>
<u n="222" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0227">so he didn't have that so probably a little bit strange at the time but when age moves forward it doesn't become so strange any more and then he moved off to Leighton Buzzard so she then <unclear/> and then er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came along after this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> guy and then er they got married and er she was all living the married life but I think it erm erm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0192">was obviously unsatisfied</u>
<u n="225" who="S0227">came along and <unclear/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0192">quickly tore that apart</u>
<u n="227" who="S0227">and er well was it quickly? cos I said I met her in eighty-three but nothing actually happened until eighty-four that summer</u>
<u n="228" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0227">so it was a good half a year to a year afterwards that er obviously I</u>
<u n="230" who="S0192">and then you had me pretty quickly didn't you after that?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0227">well no there was a there was a erm <unclear/> a courtship and then I I went to dump her she didn't like being dumped so she did everything she possibly could to cos I I'd been going out with another girl and then I finished with her to start with your mum and then where your mum had been the bit on the side the main and the main the main girl then became the bit on the side</u>
<u n="232" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0227">I managed to convince them that both of them that this was gonna be a working progress thing and they both agreed to that</u>
<u n="234" who="S0192">so you were with both of them for some time?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0227">yeah and they knew about it how I managed to talk them into it I I was very good at very good <vocal desc="laugh"/> at the gab in them days that that last for three months the understanding erm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0192">the question is did you manage to get them both at the same time?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0192">now that'll be real work wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0227">yeah well I I could never convince them to do that</u>
<u n="240" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0227">no no no that would have been no no no that'd have been no nice thought</u>
<u n="242" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s living with er well it is my mum as well so obviously not a nice thought but</u>
<u n="243" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="244" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s living with three girls at the moment</u>
<u n="245" who="S0227">oh I did say I I because I copied your mum in I kept it quite clean I I could have been a bit more graphic and said well that's the ironing <vocal desc="laugh"/> the washing and the your cooking sorted for the next year</u>
<u n="246" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah and everything else</u>
<u n="247" who="S0227">cos well that's why I didn't put that in cos I I copied your mum</u>
<u n="248" who="S0192">yeah I mean it was implied so yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0227">yeah I did say</u>
<u n="250" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I I'm glad that he's with er rather than being with like three Chinese boys or something</u>
<u n="251" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0192">that don't really wanna chat</u>
<u n="253" who="S0227">no no</u>
<u n="254" who="S0192">or do anything have you heard from him again or</u>
<u n="255" who="S0227">er no I don't know if he's sent me a card or what I haven't heard anything he may have sent me an email he hasn't sent me a phone he hasn't rang or he hasn't text so so he won't so send something not er an email</u>
<u n="256" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0227">or might be something I said to him don't bother about getting me a present but I said that in front of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm so that he didn't get me anything but obviously a a card would have been nice or a call but</u>
<u n="258" who="S0192">yeah I didn't get you card I'm afraid</u>
<u n="259" who="S0227">no it's don't worry</u>
<u n="260" who="S0192">ta-da</u>
<u n="261" who="S0227">well you're here so it's not about the card</u>
<u n="262" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0227">erm his place is nice</u>
<u n="264" who="S0192">oh yeah you saw it</u>
<u n="265" who="S0227">very it's almost like it it's almost like I've never been to Center Parcs but if you imagine Center Parcs as being like little houses that are in the middle of the woods</u>
<u n="266" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0227">it's exactly like that</u>
<u n="268" who="S0192">oh nice</u>
<u n="269" who="S0227">yeah so it's nice erm yeah figured out the heating or something but I said well</u>
<u n="270" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0227">see if there's a boiler figure it out and if not go and speak and speak at reception erm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0192">I take it he doesn't pay for that? the bills are included</u>
<u n="273" who="S0227">yes that should all be included yeah there should be heating</u>
<u n="274" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so yeah definitely definitely whack the heating on then</u>
<u n="275" who="S0227">yeah erm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0192">have you been having well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I haven't even touched our heating at all we've <trunc>turne</trunc></u>
<u n="277" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no er well I've just started just er in the morning cos obviously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s there</u>
<u n="278" who="S0192">yeah of course</u>
<u n="279" who="S0227">but uh we've been having this fan heater in the in the lounge</u>
<u n="280" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0227">and keeping the central heating off</u>
<u n="282" who="S0192">that's a bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0227">erm that'll probably stop though in October erm he was on about his stomach and I said well that might be although you say you're not nervous it might be your body's way of</u>
<u n="284" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0227">of producing yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I've had a bad stomach since I've come back and I'm pretty sure it's anxiety</u>
<u n="287" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0192">well cos once I started uni it calmed down a little bit</u>
<u n="289" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0192">erm I was feeling IBSey again which I haven't felt for a while</u>
<u n="291" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0192">and was kind of like every night I went to bed my stomach was gurgling and turning</u>
<u n="293" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0192">and feeling really kind of tense</u>
<u n="295" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0192">erm it's kind of calmed down a bit so I think it might be a bit of anxiety for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because it's it's quite often tacit isn't it? it's not necessarily conscious it's erm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah so I did say say say that to him I said to you know my biggest concern with him is that erm he'll females like with me got in the way <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0227">of things and I'm hoping that he he can erm focus to task erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I <trunc>sa</trunc> I haven't sent him an email but I felt cos he seems a bit too truthful sometimes and sometimes it's better not to say something to hurt someone's feelings and er like he'd said that erm he'd been quite not totally graphic but quite more than explicit er about when he was in Thailand yes he wasn't had a girlfriend but he was like you know probably she didn't want to hear it I don't know if he's told her now that he's sharing with three females</u>
<u n="300" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0227">because if that was her if that was me that would not be music to my ears</u>
<u n="302" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="303" who="S0227">if I was her the paranoia</u>
<u n="304" who="S0192">he's he's like me in that respect I've</u>
<u n="305" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="306" who="S0192">erm I think after you and mum broke up I went on this truth rampage</u>
<u n="307" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="308" who="S0192">that like I'm not gonna lie I'm not gonna say anything not truthful</u>
<u n="309" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="310" who="S0192">or hide anything</u>
<u n="311" who="S0227">yep</u>
<u n="312" who="S0192">and I quite hurt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the first couple of years that we were together</u>
<u n="313" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="314" who="S0192">cos I just basically told her that I didn't want a relationship</u>
<u n="315" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0192">I didn't wanna be tied down</u>
<u n="317" who="S0227">yep yep</u>
<u n="318" who="S0192">I didn't wanna do this</u>
<u n="319" who="S0227">yep</u>
<u n="320" who="S0192">I never cheated on her or anything like that</u>
<u n="321" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="322" who="S0192">but I was brutally honest with the</u>
<u n="323" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes the the truth yeah sometimes erm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0192">it's not about lying</u>
<u n="325" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="326" who="S0192">it's about not telling things that don't need to be said</u>
<u n="327" who="S0227" trans="overlap">exactly I I don't call that a lie</u>
<u n="328" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="329" who="S0227">I call that an omission</u>
<u n="330" who="S0192">it's withholding yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0227">but it's not a lie because if you said well is there any girls there? no</u>
<u n="332" who="S0192">but</u>
<u n="333" who="S0227">that's a lie if you said erm what's it like? oh that's good blah blah blah and you haven't mentioned anything it's like I got your mum once I had been unfaithful this was before we were married but she asked the wrong question she said had you been sleeping this was with my ex have you been sleeping with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="335" who="S0227">I said no cos I I hadn't I'd done lots of other things I hadn't been asleep she asked the wrong question <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0192">the thing is er</u>
<u n="337" who="S0227">so I never lied are you with me?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0227">cos I was very clever you had to get me on the correct question then well did I lie or not? and er have you been sleeping with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="341" who="S0227">well no I was I was honestly I couldn't believe it because it was true she asked the wrong goddamn question but there you go I wasn't going to lead her and say well no you need to ask me another question no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0192">no I think in hindsight with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I</u>
<u n="343" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh crap is that thing on?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0192">yeah yeah of course</u>
<u n="345" who="S0227">oh right edit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0192">nobody's gonna hear anything you so it's fine</u>
<u n="347" who="S0227">right it's okay</u>
<u n="348" who="S0192">erm I think in hindsight erm although it may have been difficult with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I for the first couple of years I think it's actually made us stronger</u>
<u n="349" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0192">in the long run</u>
<u n="351" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0192">cos we've been honest about how we feel</u>
<u n="353" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0192">with kind of each other but</u>
<u n="355" who="S0227">well</u>
<u n="356" who="S0192">it was definitely difficult for the first couple of years</u>
<u n="357" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0192">I didn't really I just didn't wanna be in a relationship for the first couple of years really</u>
<u n="359" who="S0227">well no</u>
<u n="360" who="S0192">I had a bit of a problem actually two years when I last came home I decided while we were travelling to get everything out in the open and though I did kind of cheat on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> once when we were right at the beginning of our well I say right at the beginning kind of the first year of our relationship</u>
<u n="361" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0192">I got really drunk she left the club</u>
<u n="363" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0192">I got with one of our friends</u>
<u n="365" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0192">she want and this girl has liked me for a while and she tried to get me to go back to her house I walked her home and said that I couldn't do it and so I didn't I just</u>
<u n="367" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0192">I just snogged the girl that was it</u>
<u n="369" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0192">but I didn't tell that was the one secret I had from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that I didn't tell her</u>
<u n="371" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0192">I then told her while we were travelling because you know we were taking our relationship to the next level</u>
<u n="373" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0192">so I kind of wanted to be honest</u>
<u n="375" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0192">lo and behold that girl who we hadn't seen for ages now my other friend is with so when I come to <trunc>Bright</trunc> I visited Brighton last year to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's with her</u>
<u n="377" who="S0227">er oh dear</u>
<u n="378" who="S0192">so it all came out cos I'd only told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about her a couple of months before we came over even if though it had happened four or five years before</u>
<u n="379" who="S0227">yeah yeah oh</u>
<u n="380" who="S0192">so we we all got into a bit of an argument that weekend</u>
<u n="381" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="382" who="S0192">we all got kind of drunk</u>
<u n="383" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="384" who="S0192">and so</u>
<u n="385" who="S0227">and <trunc>dru</trunc>drunk wasn't a good place to start</u>
<u n="386" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no so er</u>
<u n="387" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="388" who="S0192">I kind of wish I hadn't said</u>
<u n="389" who="S0227">no sometimes like erm what with that thing and when I did get rumbled by your mum she decided er she'd been unfaithful but with some other bloke she never even knew er where at least with this one I I was kind of torn between your mum and her and I'd I was just trying to keep everybody happy but obviously you you someone was gonna get upset</u>
<u n="390" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0227">and so she then confessed to er something that would happen when I've gone with my friend and that was it as soon as I heard that I completely turned it around <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like oh I was like the moral high ground where is it? and then suddenly like oh there it is I'm right back up there now and and I was able to turn it round because I you I I I felt like saying you shouldn't have said that you should have kept the moral high ground</u>
<u n="392" who="S0192" trans="overlap">power struggle</u>
<u n="393" who="S0227">and <vocal desc="misc"/> but you gave me an in as soon as you said that I cos I was like you know this is a person that that I've been with a long time you know I still had some kind of feelings for I said this bloke you didn't know anything about this bloke goes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0192">do whatever</u>
<u n="395" who="S0227">yeah so I was able to turn it around</u>
<u n="396" who="S0192">one does have to wonder if we're built for monogamy really</u>
<u n="397" who="S0227">well</u>
<u n="398" who="S0192">at least long term monogamy it isn't</u>
<u n="399" who="S0227">well yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0192">I mean it seems not otherwise there wouldn't be so much divorce and so</u>
<u n="401" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="402" who="S0192">many people cheating on each other and</u>
<u n="403" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="404" who="S0192">all this kind if stuff</u>
<u n="405" who="S0227">with with men it's considered sordid with women they they it is equally sordid but they like to dress it up in love they put a a they shroud it in in something to make give it meaning</u>
<u n="406" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="408" who="S0192">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> okay if I record her?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0227"><trunc>y</trunc> she was last time</u>
<u n="410" who="S0192">yeah have you asked her since then?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0227">no er no I'm sure she's fine though just do it just mention it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0192">yeah I will do so erm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0227" trans="overlap">give me some royalties</u>
<u n="414" who="S0192">can't just to let you know I'm kind of smoking again at the minute</u>
<u n="415" who="S0227">well</u>
<u n="416" who="S0192">er that's gonna stop</u>
<u n="417" who="S0227">yes obviously the new stresses of the new</u>
<u n="418" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but I am I've been quite stressed the last couple of weeks</u>
<u n="419" who="S0227">yeah the new stresses I know</u>
<u n="420" who="S0192">I haven't been smoking a lot but</u>
<u n="421" who="S0227">no that's fine</u>
<u n="422" who="S0192">having one here and there</u>
<u n="423" who="S0227">yep it's fine</u>
<u n="424" who="S0192">yeah just thought I'd let you know</u>
<u n="425" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I I'd be surprised if you didn't cos erm obviously erm the the take up of the course and everything</u>
<u n="426" who="S0192">well I mean the problem had I had I not been smoking for the last few months before I came home I think I would have been fine but</u>
<u n="427" who="S0227">yep</u>
<u n="428" who="S0192">but the problem is when I started working at the university I met had to re-socialise again with a whole bunch of people and quite a few of them smoke and it got to the point where I would have one or two when when I saw them but that meant that when I came home</u>
<u n="429" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah therein lies the problem yes</u>
<u n="430" who="S0192">the crutch was there again</u>
<u n="431" who="S0227">yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0192">so I kind of</u>
<u n="433" who="S0227">how are you finding the erm the the course?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0192">yeah tough a lot of work but it's er it's good</u>
<u n="435" who="S0227">the good thing about you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is that your you can bounce things off of each <trunc>ot</trunc> you're doing the same thing are you with me?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0192">well we are but we aren't</u>
<u n="437" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0192">I'm doing four modules and out of those four modules <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s only in one</u>
<u n="439" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="440" who="S0192">so</u>
<u n="441" who="S0227">but at least that's some kind of bounce</u>
<u n="442" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0227">you can bounce ideas off</u>
<u n="444" who="S0192">I mean we're both doing linguistics</u>
<u n="445" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0192">but where as I'm <trunc>do</trunc> I my four modules are we're both doing the core module which is research and language and use</u>
<u n="447" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0192">and then I'm doing pidgins and creoles syntactic theory</u>
<u n="449" who="S0227">yep</u>
<u n="450" who="S0192">and erm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0227">you're speaking all French and some language</u>
<u n="452" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0192">and what's my final one? er language description and analysis</u>
<u n="455" who="S0227">ah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing language variation which is sociolinguistics dialects that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="457" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="458" who="S0192">she's also doing second language acquisition so we're doing kind of different stuff</u>
<u n="459" who="S0227">oh right okay</u>
<u n="460" who="S0192">but it crosses over</u>
<u n="461" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0192">it does</u>
<u n="463" who="S0227">yes well before you everything you were doing is more or less the same isn't it?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0192">erm as in what we've been working or</u>
<u n="465" who="S0227" trans="overlap">with like your teaching TEFL's and stuff</u>
<u n="466" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yes yeah the yeah qualifications <unclear/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0227">you can use each other as as bouncing er sound boards for it</u>
<u n="468" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and I mean still now we can and actually it's kind of easier because you have to there's a big worry about plagiarism</u>
<u n="469" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0192">and they don't often get couples working together</u>
<u n="471" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0192">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were a bit worried if we did the same modules we could get accused of plagiarising each other</u>
<u n="473" who="S0227" trans="overlap">accused of yeah yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0192">so or colluding so erm this way we're not definitely</u>
<u n="475" who="S0227">yes yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0192">it's kinda going on is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0227">I hope so the house is open</u>
<u n="478" who="S0192">yeah sure she is take my shoes off</u>
<u n="479" who="S0227"><unclear/> love? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s old room I wanted it but she got in first it's the woman it's the woman cave</u>
<u n="480" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0227">instead of the man cave</u>
<u n="482" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0227">how's your lemongrass? is it still</u>
<u n="484" who="S0192">good yeah and it's erm proliferating yes it's definitely growing that one's really coming on isn't it? that's not the lemongrass oh it is</u>
<u n="485" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh erm yes it's <trunc>lemon</trunc> yeah it's just that it's old so like I could use it for cooking but I don't because it's four years old</u>
<u n="486" who="S0192">that blight on my <trunc>cacti</trunc>cactus is spreading I think</u>
<u n="487" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="488" who="S0192">I don't know what to do about that</u>
<u n="489" who="S0190" trans="overlap">hiya</u>
<u n="490" who="S0192">you alright <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? how you doing?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you alright</u>
<u n="492" who="S0190">ah I was just getting changed</u>
<u n="493" who="S0227">back earlier than</u>
<u n="494" who="S0192" trans="overlap">good to see you again oh how are you doing?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0190">alright?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0192">good</u>
<u n="497" who="S0190">settling in?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0192">yeah yeah definitely</u>
<u n="499" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0192">did you mind if I record? I've just kind of got it on</u>
<u n="501" who="S0227">so don't start singing er</u>
<u n="502" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="503" who="S0192">are you sure?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="505" who="S0227">I did that for breakfast this morning erm we went to erm it twice we went to it no parking in the it's off <anon type="place"/> the pub on the corner do you remember if you come out from home go up the crescent</u>
<u n="506" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0227"><unclear/> on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0227">if you crossed over you go towards the flats well then over there is a pub</u>
<u n="510" who="S0190">right</u>
<u n="511" who="S0227">opposite <anon type="place"/> the model shop</u>
<u n="512" who="S0190">right</u>
<u n="513" who="S0227">erm that's where they do it the car park is tiny full up and there's nowhere to park absolutely nowhere there so we drove there went no okay we'll drive to <anon type="place"/> have a look at a job come back we came back went no so I said right I'm starting on the sandwiches so then I had so I never had any breakfast this morning</u>
<u n="514" who="S0190">ah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0227">I just went I just got up and went</u>
<u n="516" who="S0192">where are we going this evening then?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0227">er Indian walking</u>
<u n="518" who="S0192">oh nice</u>
<u n="519" who="S0227"><trunc>ter</trunc> er <anon type="place"/> down erm in town just walking down there</u>
<u n="520" who="S0192">you've been there before?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0227">yeah we've been there before yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0192">good stuff</u>
<u n="523" who="S0227">er <unclear/> you haven't been there but your brother's been there er</u>
<u n="524" who="S0192">I've been to ones with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in Bedford</u>
<u n="525" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="526" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0192">Blue Ginger or something</u>
<u n="528" who="S0190">Blue Ginger yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0192">and some other one have you been to that one as well then?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0227"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0190">erm I've been to <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0192">yeah good?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0190">yeah it is nice</u>
<u n="534" who="S0192">what kind of curry do you normally go for?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0190">usual erm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0192">what's the usual? oh rogan josh?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0190">rogan josh chicken</u>
<u n="539" who="S0192">what like a lamb? oh chicken one yeah okay</u>
<u n="540" who="S0190">chicken</u>
<u n="541" who="S0192">what do you normally go for?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0227">I don't know yet probably be something different er</u>
<u n="543" who="S0192">do you ever share? do you ever get a few different curries and and share a bit each or</u>
<u n="544" who="S0190">sometimes but er it's a case of how much you're getting</u>
<u n="545" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah if dad eats it all</u>
<u n="546" who="S0227">exactly</u>
<u n="547" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0227">so you've got a blight? so your lemongrass is growing?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0192">yeah I I'm I've got a bit worried that I've over watered it slightly the soil's quite moist and I am worried about root rot so I'm just not watering it now</u>
<u n="550" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0192">and cut cut</u>
<u n="552" who="S0227" trans="overlap">slow down on the</u>
<u n="553" who="S0192">but if it's if the blight keeps producing I'm tempted to give it back to give it back to him say whatever you were doing was good whatever I'm doing isn't good it was producing a fruit have you ever seen it before? you know you said it produces flowers?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="555" who="S0192">it also produces a very small pink edible fruit</u>
<u n="556" who="S0227">oh right is it like</u>
<u n="557" who="S0192">like a little pink thing that's sticks out of it</u>
<u n="558" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="559" who="S0192">cos I thought it was a flower</u>
<u n="560" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="561" who="S0192">and I looked it up and think no apparently you can eat it it's just a little fruit</u>
<u n="562" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh right that's why what I think the flower is</u>
<u n="563" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0227">that's what I wanna say the flower is is that thing</u>
<u n="565" who="S0192">oh so it doesn't flower it doesn't open like a flower</u>
<u n="566" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no you don't know no a lot of <unclear/> I think it does flower a little bit when</u>
<u n="567" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I think it should flower and then fruit like afterwards</u>
<u n="568" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah in in the winter I've put it in here</u>
<u n="569" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="570" who="S0227">oh right nice</u>
<u n="571" who="S0192" trans="overlap">cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0227">in the winter I've put it in here in the summer in the summer I've put it in there</u>
<u n="573" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> are like the best chocolate ever</u>
<u n="574" who="S0227">ah I might have to open one of these cos I</u>
<u n="575" who="S0192">I just feel terrible I didn't even get him a card</u>
<u n="576" who="S0190">oh you're worse than my sons they're awful</u>
<u n="577" who="S0192">but I kind of felt like I popped out here I am you know I'm actually here</u>
<u n="578" who="S0190"><unclear/> here that make a double whammy after</u>
<u n="579" who="S0192">what is that? that's phenomenal</u>
<u n="580" who="S0190">I didn't make it as you can see <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0192">no was that from you? that is a ginormous card</u>
<u n="582" who="S0227">I think <unclear/> well you could have made it I wouldn't have I wouldn't have doubted it I would have said</u>
<u n="583" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I know but I just think</u>
<u n="584" who="S0227">she does make cards so</u>
<u n="585" who="S0192">you do?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0190">I do I made er those <unclear/> classes er</u>
<u n="587" who="S0192">you went to classes?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0227">I don't know where to start</u>
<u n="589" who="S0190">just to learn techniques and things</u>
<u n="590" who="S0192">do you have anything you can show me?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0190">yeah I will later</u>
<u n="592" who="S0192">ah that'd be good</u>
<u n="593" who="S0190">I'll go and get my box out and show you</u>
<u n="594" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0190">yeah need to go er shopping and get some slippers and that</u>
<u n="596" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0190">for them need to go shopping to get slippers and that</u>
<u n="598" who="S0227">oh right okay</u>
<u n="599" who="S0192">do you need some slippers?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0227">yeah erm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0190">yes he had an accident in <unclear/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I stood in the cat stuff</u>
<u n="603" who="S0192">oh gosh</u>
<u n="604" who="S0190">and it was just <unclear/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0192">did you normally have that there?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0190">no but she's had two or three accidents</u>
<u n="607" who="S0192">she's become incontinent</u>
<u n="608" who="S0190">so erm but she we bought cat litter but she started eating it</u>
<u n="609" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's cos she's blind</u>
<u n="610" who="S0190">you know straight fresh cat litter</u>
<u n="611" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's not normal I take it? no shouldn't be eating cat litter</u>
<u n="612" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="613" who="S0190">would you like a drink?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0192">yeah just a water</u>
<u n="615" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you see <unclear/> for a few hours so <unclear/> then</u>
<u n="616" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0190">how come anyway what what time you're an hour early</u>
<u n="618" who="S0192">yes yeah erm I managed to get out of university quicker than I'd anticipated and got on a quicker train erm so that was good erm I've got a bit of a problem getting home though typically there's there's works on the line on Sunday when I go back</u>
<u n="619" who="S0190">oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to say this</u>
<u n="620" who="S0192">yeah so instead of two and a half hours it's gonna take me over four to get back and I have to catch a bus in London somewhere</u>
<u n="621" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0192">or something or other <unclear/> it's horrible</u>
<u n="623" who="S0227">you could write your dissertation on the way up here</u>
<u n="624" who="S0192">actually I did do some work on my laptop on the on the train</u>
<u n="625" who="S0227" trans="overlap">if you use use the time</u>
<u n="626" who="S0192">but it got quite busy</u>
<u n="627" who="S0190">who was that from?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it was that was from your mum and dad</u>
<u n="629" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0227">I've got to phone and thank obviously at some time</u>
<u n="631" who="S0192">there was quite a rude lady on the train I thought I mean she she was seemingly disabled so I can't really judge she was in a wheelchair but she definitely got out of the wheelchair and like stood up and walked around and did some stuff but she was in the gantry where people get on and she sat in this like electric wheelchair but she proceeded to recline it as far back as it went and then people at Gatwick airport were trying to squeeze past her bags and she's just lying there with a book like just full recline just taking up the whole thing</u>
<u n="632" who="S0190">that's ignorant isn't it?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0192">I thought it was a bit</u>
<u n="634" who="S0190" trans="overlap">by people that</u>
<u n="635" who="S0227">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0192">it's a bit I don't know she just looked kind of fat to me I don't know if she was actually <vocal desc="laugh"/> if anything was wrong with her I had to laugh</u>
<u n="637" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/> multitask <pause dur="short"/> I'm getting pictures of monkeys or gorillas</u>
<u n="638" who="S0190">oh perhaps you remind them of something</u>
<u n="639" who="S0227">maybe</u>
<u n="640" who="S0192">oh has he got lots of monkeys?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0227">oh I got a <unclear>cow</unclear> on that one</u>
<u n="642" who="S0192">hey the likeness is uncanny it has to be said</u>
<u n="643" who="S0190"><unclear/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad's birthday today as well</u>
<u n="645" who="S0190">is it?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0192">mm except he's seventy</u>
<u n="647" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes I was about to say she must have I I forgot to mention that that has she gone to her dad's cos I think his birthday's the same day as mine</u>
<u n="648" who="S0192">she did want to that was the original plan before we came home we said we'll both go to see our dads on on their birthdays but they've gone to Belgium actually erm he's really into flea markets</u>
<u n="649" who="S0227">okay yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0192">so they've gone to some famous flea market in Belgium but he's <trunc>seven</trunc> he's seventy this year so he's a good bit older than you</u>
<u n="651" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah fifteen years yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0192">I mean her mum's her mum's only fifty-five I think so</u>
<u n="653" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear>how old's</unclear> her sister? Oh right so there's quite an age difference</u>
<u n="654" who="S0192">there's quite a difference between the two of them yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="657" who="S0192">but he's got a whole other family <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got erm a half-sister stepsister half-sister</u>
<u n="658" who="S0227">half</u>
<u n="659" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0227">step is is through marriage but no blood</u>
<u n="661" who="S0192">no she's in her forties with like children</u>
<u n="662" who="S0227">oh good lord</u>
<u n="663" who="S0192">she doesn't see them very often I think her dad's calmed down quite a bit as he's got older</u>
<u n="664" who="S0227">yeah it has it does have a tendency to do that to you</u>
<u n="665" who="S0192">I mean he has no teeth</u>
<u n="666" who="S0227">oh I've still got mine</u>
<u n="667" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0227">apart from the ones that I lost in an accident</u>
<u n="669" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0227">that wasn't my fault</u>
<u n="671" who="S0192">it's kind of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fault though he had some teeth remaining but just kind of one here or one there</u>
<u n="672" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="673" who="S0192">so she told him to have the rest removed and get dentures so he did but then he found the dentures were giving him a gag reflex so he never keeps them in</u>
<u n="674" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0192">so now he's and his mouth has changed shape now because he doesn't have any teeth so</u>
<u n="676" who="S0190">yeah <unclear>well</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0192">his dentures don't fit either</u>
<u n="678" who="S0227">no the jawline'll</u>
<u n="679" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so she feels kind of responsible good oh that was my water thank you <unclear/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0227">that was <unclear>with</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it it never gets easier you just go faster</u>
<u n="681" who="S0190"><unclear/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0227"><unclear>bus</unclear> one cycling</u>
<u n="683" who="S0192">have you been out on the bike?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0227">er not probably for a month now I haven't no I've been erm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0190">more than a month</u>
<u n="686" who="S0227">I've been erm doing the gym bit cos my mate come round er last Friday er don't know if it was the beer talking or not he goes cos I had like a short sleeve shirt he goes your arms he goes have you been in the gym? I said well I'm doing the basics they're looking bigger</u>
<u n="687" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0192">muscle or fat?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0227">muscle</u>
<u n="690" who="S0192">muscle</u>
<u n="691" who="S0227">but erm unfortunately here there's this is what really I need to address but because I've got such a weak core</u>
<u n="692" who="S0192">cos your back <unclear/> it's difficult to do the</u>
<u n="693" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="694" who="S0192">erm never been into swimming have you really?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0227">I don't mind if I'm at the sea but I don't like to go to a <trunc>sw</trunc>swimming pool and know they've</u>
<u n="696" who="S0190" trans="overlap">excuse me to interrupt but are you remembering who these are from cos you know what he's like he'll say to me what</u>
<u n="697" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah money from my sister so far er money from your parents</u>
<u n="698" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah cos you had your cakes</u>
<u n="699" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="700" who="S0190">from</u>
<u n="701" who="S0227">yeah she sent me a text this morning I text back</u>
<u n="702" who="S0192">who are the Lindt balls from?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0190">me</u>
<u n="704" who="S0227">from yourself</u>
<u n="705" who="S0192"><shift new="singing"/> simply the best <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="706" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="707" who="S0192">they're literally the best chocolates in the world I think</u>
<u n="708" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I've got to remember their money and also there's a drink by the looks of it as well</u>
<u n="709" who="S0190">yeah one of the good ones from what I can see that's mum and dad</u>
<u n="710" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0192">in Korea this I don't know how much they are here but a box like this is about fifteen to twenty pounds in Korea</u>
<u n="712" who="S0190">no they're about you can get them for a fiver if you're lucky</u>
<u n="713" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh right a whole box like that? but erm they were going out of date in kind of like a it's a version of Tesco's that they have in Korea called Homeplus and we watch them week after week get cut in half cut in half cut in half in the end we were able to buy them for a pound a box like that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I just bought like four boxes and</u>
<u n="714" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh good lord</u>
<u n="715" who="S0192">kind of munched them it's terrible</u>
<u n="716" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I'll put this in here</u>
<u n="717" who="S0192">but of course dad so you're not eating sugar are you dad so this is very</u>
<u n="718" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well yes now you can have some</u>
<u n="719" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no no no I give up with that one completely</u>
<u n="720" who="S0227">would you like one?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0192"><unclear/> I mean if you're opening them I'll definitely have one but erm</u>
<u n="722" who="S0190">want one for your cake?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0227">oh yes as well so I'll have a couple of these as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0190"><unclear/> no thank you</u>
<u n="725" who="S0192">thank you very much I won't say no definitely not</u>
<u n="726" who="S0227">it is from your mum and dad</u>
<u n="727" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="728" who="S0192">have you ever frozen these? do you like cold chocolate?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0190">yes I do</u>
<u n="730" who="S0192">they're quite good frozen quite nice</u>
<u n="731" who="S0227">so I've got wine and money from your mum and dad and <unclear/> money from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and money from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> trying to remember</u>
<u n="732" who="S0192">blueberry</u>
<u n="733" who="S0190">yes</u>
<u n="734" who="S0227">yes they're nice</u>
<u n="735" who="S0192">mm blueberry muffins</u>
<u n="736" who="S0227">I might have the muffin first actually so nice</u>
<u n="737" who="S0192">how's the weather been the last few weeks? cos it's been really nice in Brighton</u>
<u n="738" who="S0190">on and off it's been quite chilly sometimes</u>
<u n="739" who="S0192">yeah the last week it's got colder I I'd say but prior to that was it colder or</u>
<u n="740" who="S0190">but today it hasn't <unclear/> erm today it hasn't been too bad I had to take my jacket off when I was out cos the sun was quite warm across the</u>
<u n="741" who="S0192">what you've had the sun out?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0190">oh gosh yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0192">Brighton's been just very close and cloudy all day like really overcast</u>
<u n="744" who="S0227" trans="overlap">sun here</u>
<u n="745" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0190">couple of times your dad got the central heating on in the morning</u>
<u n="747" who="S0192">it did brighten up as I took the train but it was really thick on the coast today</u>
<u n="748" who="S0190">I mean two or three mornings we got up and it was just like there's a fog</u>
<u n="749" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="750" who="S0190">it was heavy mist</u>
<u n="751" who="S0192">in general though it's been quite nice in Brighton <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I have sat on the beach a couple of times we've been probably putting in about seven hours of study every day so it's phenomenal</u>
<u n="752" who="S0227">you're about a degree and a half further south than here</u>
<u n="753" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0192">certainly makes a difference</u>
<u n="756" who="S0227">I think <trunc>may</trunc></u>
<u n="757" who="S0192" trans="overlap">being on the coast makes a difference</u>
<u n="758" who="S0227">at night you've got warmer temperatures</u>
<u n="759" who="S0192">yeah think it's erm it's a bit milder there I think overall I looked at the temperature charts the average lows in winter are like three</u>
<u n="760" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0192">I mean it's not really that cold</u>
<u n="762" who="S0227" trans="overlap">especially by the coast you won't get so many frosts</u>
<u n="763" who="S0192">no there won't be frost probably won't be much snow either will there I doubt</u>
<u n="764" who="S0227">not a great deal no be inland</u>
<u n="765" who="S0192">not usually by the coast</u>
<u n="766" who="S0190">do you want okay dad's a little bit backward in coming forward</u>
<u n="767" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how how far what time are we gonna go off</u>
<u n="768" who="S0227">seven</u>
<u n="769" who="S0192">seven</u>
<u n="770" who="S0190">seven</u>
<u n="771" who="S0192">then yes I'll have a coke if that's alright</u>
<u n="772" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="773" who="S0192">are these homemade?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0190">yes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made them for us</u>
<u n="775" who="S0192">oh fantastic I do like muffins <pause dur="short"/> blueberry works very well</u>
<u n="776" who="S0227">yes blueberry's nice</u>
<u n="777" who="S0190" trans="overlap">mine used to turn out alright this is my recipe that everybody uses but I can't make them now</u>
<u n="778" who="S0192">oh it was your recipe?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0190">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="780" who="S0192">have you ever had them with white chocolate? blueberry and white chocolate that's good</u>
<u n="781" who="S0190">yeah erm oh also you can put anything in them really just the <unclear>batter</unclear> and just put <trunc>an</trunc> whatever you like fruit jam nuts</u>
<u n="782" who="S0192">my friend my American friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> loves making muffins</u>
<u n="783" who="S0190">oh</u>
<u n="784" who="S0192">every time we go round he makes blueberry muffins or something</u>
<u n="785" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="786" who="S0192">they're very good</u>
<u n="787" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="788" who="S0192">everything's set up in my flat now thank you again for everything like between the families we were just really I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I turned around yesterday and like how did we get so much stuff?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0192">where did this all come from?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0190">no that's good</u>
<u n="792" who="S0227">that erm tamarind I've forgotten that I'd put it in for you</u>
<u n="793" who="S0192">I tell you what it's good in shepherd's pie</u>
<u n="794" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="795" who="S0192">I don't have any Worcestershire sauce and Worcestershire sauce is made from tamarind</u>
<u n="796" who="S0227">oh is it?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0192">I didn't realise yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0227">no neither did I no</u>
<u n="799" who="S0190">I did</u>
<u n="800" who="S0192">er so I used it in substitutes pretty good</u>
<u n="801" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0192">I just used some mustard and some of that <unclear/></u>
<u n="803" who="S0227">you can get that erm tamarind stuff from Tesco's</u>
<u n="804" who="S0192">I have actual tamarind now</u>
<u n="805" who="S0227">oh right because like with that sauce cos it says erm open and eat with use within a couple of weeks or something like that</u>
<u n="806" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="807" who="S0227">is I I also put an ice cube tray in there cos like again I forgot to you're probably thinking well you had an ice cube tray</u>
<u n="808" who="S0192">yeah no I've been using it it's good</u>
<u n="809" who="S0227">was erm like over put for ice obviously it's straightforward to use or like your tamarind use when you want to do and then just fill up then you've got tamarind cubes then are you with me?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0227">you go pop and</u>
<u n="812" who="S0192">I've been using the sauce in the cooking but otherwise I've bought some tamarind concentrate</u>
<u n="813" who="S0227">okay</u>
<u n="814" who="S0192">which when you open it lasts for months it doesn't doesn't really go off</u>
<u n="815" who="S0227">okay that's good</u>
<u n="816" who="S0192">right I've still got a lot of the <unclear>caf lime leaves</unclear> as well you gave me loads</u>
<u n="817" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="818" who="S0192">probably</u>
<u n="819" who="S0227">but it's grown <trunc>sin</trunc> you can see how the how it's grown in height</u>
<u n="820" who="S0192">and you could sell I mean these leaves in Sainsbury's you buy like four leaves and it's like three pounds so</u>
<u n="821" who="S0227">yeah it's good</u>
<u n="822" who="S0192">so we're gonna be like thirty pounds worth of</u>
<u n="823" who="S0190"><unclear/> the blight though you wasted a lot didn't you</u>
<u n="824" who="S0227">did I?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0190">it got the blight and you had to throw a whole <unclear>load</unclear> away</u>
<u n="826" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes threw away a bit of it yeah</u>
<u n="827" who="S0192">do you know what the blight is? is there</u>
<u n="828" who="S0227">er yes that gets suffers from erm caterpillar which is on the caterpillar but it suffers from erm oh what's it called? <pause dur="short"/> er brown spot or something like that you know?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0192">you know specifically what what it is?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah and then afterwards pin them off</u>
<u n="831" who="S0192"><unclear/> know how to treat it <unclear/> this one</u>
<u n="832" who="S0227">oh it's in the old oh it's arrived</u>
<u n="833" who="S0192"><foreign lang="ger">was is das?</foreign></u>
<u n="834" who="S0227">erm sat my new satnav</u>
<u n="835" who="S0192">mm mm cos you got lost on the way home</u>
<u n="836" who="S0227">yeah it's very it was misbehaving it wasn't just on the strength of that it it was erm starting to I can use it round I can feel it feel my thumb on my way round Bedfordshire with it to go to places where erm it will get you where you're going but it's not I don't trust it any more as in that's the fastest route</u>
<u n="837" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="838" who="S0227">it's taken me around <unclear/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0192">were you with dad at the time when</u>
<u n="840" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no I was</u>
<u n="841" who="S0192">no yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0227">thank you my love that's a very nice present</u>
<u n="843" who="S0190">it's from it's from the boys</u>
<u n="844" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I know yes I know</u>
<u n="845" who="S0190">as well</u>
<u n="846" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="847" who="S0190">they've put a good bit into it</u>
<u n="848" who="S0227">yes thank you</u>
<u n="849" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0227">I will thank</u>
<u n="851" who="S0192">so are you</u>
<u n="852" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be here in a little while</u>
<u n="853" who="S0192">did you get done on the congestion charge and all that?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0227">I don't know because we were there on a Saturday I mean</u>
<u n="855" who="S0192">oh you shouldn't do</u>
<u n="856" who="S0190">no you shouldn't do</u>
<u n="857" who="S0192">oh okay</u>
<u n="858" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent a <unclear/> what are you doing jumping red lights? I said I <trunc>recl</trunc> responded I was exaggerating</u>
<u n="859" who="S0192">I didn't know I thought you know last time you picked me up from the airport we were going all round all round I thought you're getting old</u>
<u n="860" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no no no no no no <unclear/> I was consciously not going in the bus lanes cos I know that if you do those you'll cop a fee</u>
<u n="861" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="862" who="S0227">I was consciously not stopping in the grids which I would here because I know that the erm if you do the the cameras are set to take up and you get the fine then er the speed limits you weren't gonna bust those you couldn't get that fast</u>
<u n="863" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="864" who="S0227">erm then it was the erm er the congestion fee</u>
<u n="865" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="866" who="S0227">and that was it really</u>
<u n="867" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="868" who="S0227">so I thought well I think cos we're there on a Saturday rather than a Monday to Friday erm</u>
<u n="869" who="S0192">should be alright</u>
<u n="870" who="S0227">and I wouldn't wanna be paying for the privilege of going for a traffic jam from basically south London all the way it was just <unclear>heavy</unclear> traffic</u>
<u n="871" who="S0192">no it's terrible</u>
<u n="872" who="S0227">it was heavy traffic so er right do you want one more of these?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0192">no no no I've had enough sugar thank you</u>
<u n="874" who="S0227">I'll put them away</u>
<u n="875" who="S0192">I'm looking forward to the curry</u>
<u n="876" who="S0227" trans="overlap">cup of tea put my cards out er another bag for you</u>
<u n="877" who="S0192">that's quite a collection of cards this one towers above</u>
<u n="878" who="S0227">yes yes I know all all go in the erm in the lounge I might have another one of these actually cos they're <unclear/> are they do you want another one of these buns <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0192">no no erm maybe after the curry</u>
<u n="880" who="S0190" trans="overlap">another of those buns</u>
<u n="881" who="S0227">they're nice</u>
<u n="882" who="S0192">when will you come up when will you come back up to Brighton? <unclear/> in the New Year?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0227">well probably New Year yeah cos obviously want it a big warmer yeah so</u>
<u n="884" who="S0192">have you been to Brighton much <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at all?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0190">once I think but I couldn't tell you remember</u>
<u n="886" who="S0192">it's quite nice</u>
<u n="887" who="S0190">is it?</u>
<u n="888" who="S0192">yeah it is quite nice</u>
<u n="889" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they went for the stag</u>
<u n="890" who="S0192">my erm my area's not bad</u>
<u n="891" who="S0227">no it's not bad at all</u>
<u n="892" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't live in a bad area</u>
<u n="893" who="S0190">don't you?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0192">erm some of the neighbours are a bit crazy but erm they leave us alone but I've heard a bit of shouting in like outside</u>
<u n="895" who="S0190">is it sort of</u>
<u n="896" who="S0192">I think genuinely crazy not like you know people fighting or anything I think we have a crazy lady that lives on the other side of the road <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0227">how about the one erm who your neighbour who got lost a <unclear>key</unclear> have you had any more dealings with them?</u>
<u n="898" who="S0192">no I bumped into them once but that was it</u>
<u n="899" who="S0227">ah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or something but</u>
<u n="901" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="902" who="S0192">the building's nice the rooms are nice there's a good quality everywhere like</u>
<u n="903" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="904" who="S0192">I haven't really seen too many I haven't seen any problems or any rough looking people around there's one area where I go shopping where it's cheaper like Aldi and it kind of seems a bit more like Bedford around there</u>
<u n="905" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="906" who="S0192">but otherwise it seems a bit more you know the class is a little bit higher I think</u>
<u n="907" who="S0227">mum's been down hasn't she?</u>
<u n="908" who="S0192">she visited yes one afternoon but not for very long erm</u>
<u n="909" who="S0227">that's a long way to go for</u>
<u n="910" who="S0192">I know yeah I thought so</u>
<u n="911" who="S0227">were they just passing? were they going to Devon?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0192">oh they were just passing yeah erm she'd intended to come Saturday and Sunday but erm something happened with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s daughter or something and they couldn't come so</u>
<u n="913" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="914" who="S0192">they had to come down on Sunday they were probably there for about four hours</u>
<u n="915" who="S0227">oh right so they were there for a reasonable amount of time</u>
<u n="916" who="S0192">I I cooked some scones and we had cream tea and then we took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out to the park erm</u>
<u n="917" who="S0227">okay oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came as well so the whole family</u>
<u n="918" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0227">came okay</u>
<u n="920" who="S0192">so it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came down try and get mum down on her own next time maybe and</u>
<u n="921" who="S0227">well she can if she trains</u>
<u n="922" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0227">I mean she can't drive by herself</u>
<u n="924" who="S0192">no no of course</u>
<u n="925" who="S0227">but if she trains it's not a problem you can pick her up at the station</u>
<u n="926" who="S0192">it's nice there though I've got I'm only fifteen minutes from the sea really as the</u>
<u n="927" who="S0227">yeah that sounds <unclear>far</unclear> when one immediately thinks of a car but no it's fifteen minutes by foot by foot</u>
<u n="928" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no fifteen minute walk yeah just go down into it</u>
<u n="929" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="931" who="S0227">it's all downhill isn't it from your house?</u>
<u n="932" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it's all downhill</u>
<u n="933" who="S0190">what's the uni like?</u>
<u n="934" who="S0192">university's I think quite nice the campus is nice it's very well facilitated it's a lot <trunc>bet</trunc>better than <anon type="place"/> where I went before but I don't like the architecture it was built in the sixties</u>
<u n="935" who="S0190">oh art deco deco whatever</u>
<u n="936" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it's this glass plate university thing</u>
<u n="937" who="S0227">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="938" who="S0192">same as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s actually it's the same they built another eight universities around the country in the sixties and they're all called glass plate universities <anon type="place"/> was the first <anon type="place"/> was the second and then there was a few others and they're all kind of very modern</u>
<u n="939" who="S0190" trans="overlap">the digs er for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> brilliant aren't they? we loved it</u>
<u n="940" who="S0192">yeah is it nice?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0227">we didn't managed to saw the uni but we saw his where he is it's</u>
<u n="942" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh it's lovely it's like little holiday village</u>
<u n="943" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0190">it's set amongst the trees</u>
<u n="945" who="S0192">what a great place to live for a year</u>
<u n="946" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="947" who="S0190">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="948" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="949" who="S0192">I never got to live on campus I was always off campus</u>
<u n="950" who="S0227">yes yeah you didn't did you?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0192">no it was erm <anon type="place"/> quite a small university there's only I mean <anon type="place"/> now has got like thirteen thousand students <anon type="place"/>'s got about fifteen thousand <anon type="place"/> had five <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="953" who="S0192">erm and you could only fit probably normally a British university will only fit the first year on campus anyway</u>
<u n="954" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="955" who="S0192">you can't and maybe some international students but we could probably only fit about half of the first year on campus so</u>
<u n="956" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="957" who="S0192">the other half had to kind of live but I actually I had a good time and we we were still in university accommodation but just off off campus</u>
<u n="958" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0192">but the course is really good people are really friendly and nice it's quite intense</u>
<u n="960" who="S0190" trans="overlap">how many are on your course?</u>
<u n="961" who="S0192">erm there's only twelve of us on the <trunc>appl</trunc> the MA applied linguistics course</u>
<u n="962" who="S0190">and that's you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well on that?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0192">yep erm</u>
<u n="964" who="S0190">there's only <trunc>twel</trunc></u>
<u n="965" who="S0192">and out of the twelve only three of us are British erm we have two people from Saudi Arabia we have</u>
<u n="966" who="S0227"><foreign lang="ara">alal rakba</foreign></u>
<u n="967" who="S0192">we have a Polish person we have a Dutch person we have cos it's linguistics so they've been studying linguistics in their own country</u>
<u n="968" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0192">and they've come to kind of do it in England I'm actually taking some third year undergraduate courses erm you can choose to do one postgraduate or two third year undergraduate modules so it's actually kind of more work I have to do more study and I'm effectively splitting more of my time so I have to go into university more I have to read more and do all that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="970" who="S0227"><trunc>wha</trunc>what end are you doing this extra work for?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0192">erm just because the module was more interesting I</u>
<u n="972" who="S0227">ah</u>
<u n="973" who="S0192">that's what I er I'm doing a module in pidgins and creoles and then I'm doing a module in syntactic theory which is basically cognitive science so</u>
<u n="974" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="975" who="S0192">I'm doing a cognitive science module er but they're with they only run them for undergraduates in their third year</u>
<u n="976" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="977" who="S0192">the level's quite hard I mean</u>
<u n="978" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0192">I'm doing more because I'm also doing my postgraduate modules as well</u>
<u n="980" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="981" who="S0192">but erm I'm actually with undergraduates so my classes are a little bit bigger for those two classes probably like fifteen to twenty students whereas in my postgraduate classes probably only about six students in each class cos although there's twelve of us that's split between a bunch of different modules so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing one module that crosses over with English language teaching so she's doing second language acquisition erm and then that's quite a large class and they're all teachers they're all more teachery</u>
<u n="982" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="983" who="S0192">but it's good we also have a mandatory three hour erm it's called roles they do like they get researchers to come in and give speeches about linguistics every couple of weeks so we have to go in and do that as well so I'm actually doing quite a few more hours than I was doing at my undergraduate</u>
<u n="984" who="S0227">yes at least you don't have to like go and only have a few hours of tuition and you've got to go and research everything yourself</u>
<u n="985" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0227">cos I don't think with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s because erm one of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s nest nieces erm that is what she has to do but the majority of it is <trunc>re</trunc>research but like with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with like computers you've got to be actually on these computers you can't say well go to the library and <trunc>re</trunc>read books about it and pull off the net</u>
<u n="987" who="S0192">I mean he'll have to do that as well obviously</u>
<u n="988" who="S0227">yeah but he he needs to have obviously front end like the business end of of</u>
<u n="989" who="S0192">well the next step up once you go to PHD is not taught at all it's just research</u>
<u n="990" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="991" who="S0192">all research so they're preparing us for that now so although I have three hours a week for each module they tell us that we're expected to do between ten to twenty hours additional on top of that per module</u>
<u n="992" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="993" who="S0192">so I I'm currently putting in about seven hours of study a day</u>
<u n="994" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0192">maybe eight hours</u>
<u n="996" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="997" who="S0192">I have reading wise I do four modules and every module has a weekly reading list and then a wider reading list on top of that but the weekly reading list is about ten books</u>
<u n="998" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="999" who="S0192">per module and maybe one to two chapters in each book so total is about forty to fifty chapters a week that I have to read</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0192">which is ridiculous so there's a lot of reading and then we come in and basically if you haven't done the reading you can't talk about in class what what you've done the reading about</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0192">but we've been doing erm I was analysing German today and in my syntactic analysis class I definitely feel more like I'm doing a linguistics course so</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1004" who="S0190">here <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1005" who="S0227">I I would imagine that you're glad that this is a one year course and that this intensitly intensity you wouldn't wanna go in for three years</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0192">no not at this level no</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0227">too too onersome</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0192">if I had the money I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I would have liked to have maybe done it part time cos you can do it over two years</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0192">and then it's I guess easier because you're spreading that same workload over two years</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0227">just spread the load yeah</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0192">but it would just cost so much to stay in England for two years doing that</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah indeed yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0192">it's good the lecturers are nice it's quite a high standard</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0227">I mean cos you're like you said because you're doing your <trunc>M</trunc> your master's you're quite mature students even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0227">he's going to be older than quite a few of his peers</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0227">because er they're gonna come fresh out of school and they're eighteen where he he's a little more seasoned he's bimbled into work</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0192">he's travelled</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0227">he's travelled he's he's been to quite a few places if you think</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0192">for his age yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0227">for his age I think he's been to he's been to San Francisco he's been to the Canary Islands he's been to German he's been to France he's been to</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0192">Korea</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0227">Korea</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0192">Japan</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0227">Japan</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0192">Cambodia</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0227">Cambodia Thailand</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0227">that for a person his age yep this isn't like just going over to France and Benidorm or something you know this is travelled so</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0227">this will make him quite an interesting person</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0192">whether or not undergraduates care though I think is the problem I found in my undergraduates courses they're like they didn't seem to it doesn't faze them that I've been living out of the UK for six years</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0192">I thought that was quite an interesting feature but they're no</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0192">no interest whatsoever just</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0192">but erm there are a few people on the MA course that are fresh out of their undergraduate</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0192">so I er I there's the only other British person is called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she's only twenty-one she's just graduated from thingamajig so she seems quite a bit younger to me</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0192">but erm</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0192">no it's nice if you well when you come up I'll er we can take you up to the campus what's really nice is that it's only a ten-minute train which is lovely and it's only a ten-minute walk to the train so</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0192">I feel like I can get to and from university very quickly</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0227">how far is the actual university from</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0192">it's about seven kilometres from home</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0192">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I cycled once</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0192">but</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0227"><unclear/> a you haven't it's <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cycled again the problem is once we get on to <anon type="place"/> there's a very clear run for about four kilometres and it's nice but between where I live and <anon type="place"/> there's a lot of roadworks and a lot of one-way roads and it's not very safe cycling I don't think</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0227">mm mm</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0192">there's no like cycle paths or anything</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0192">erm and also with my classes Monday I've got a long day I'm in from ten until six</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0192">so I don't really feel like cycling</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0227">cycling</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0227">at the beginning and the end of that no</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0192">no and then and also I have to take in three folders three sets of books my lunch all that kind of <trunc>th</trunc> I've just got no no space</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0227">no no</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0192">Tuesday and Wednesday I'm in at nine o'clock so I don't really feel like getting on my bike that early</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0192">either maybe I will once I'm more in the in the swing of things and Thursday I'm off then Friday is the only day that I could but this week I couldn't because I knew I was coming home so</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0227">well at least it's it's for a year and not that you're not enjoying it but it it it that <trunc>int</trunc> you know this intensity and that I mean and you won't have to after June which compresses it down even further you'll still be doing it but you won't be having to go in every day cos you'll be dissertations won't you so</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yes yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0227">you'll be like you know you can <unclear/> back I'm just gonna put these cards in</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0192">they've already got us thinking about that</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0227">well</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0192">trying to come up with a dissertation thesis</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0227">I wouldn't <unclear/> even think your brother's has got more discipline but he's still very much lastminute dot com like</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0192">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a bit of a worry</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0227" trans="overlap">er I phoned him about erm where are you? erm cos he hadn't <trunc>contact</trunc> I my mate erm come round for a bit some beers but before he come round I copied I sent him an email copied <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in going I'm not sure if if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he knows <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he knows your mum</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0227">I said I'm not sure if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum's taking him or not I said yeah I waiting to hear from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he didn't respond to that and this was like on the Monday and I'm thinking well he's supposed to be going on the Saturday and my mate wants to yeah I I I said either it'd be this Friday but it's a long shot cos I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will or erm it's gonna be in the middle of October so I then on Wednesday thought I haven't heard anything from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'll ring him so I rung and he goes I'm just on the way back from the airport and this was er like was it Wednesday or the Thursday?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0190">Wednesday I think</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0227">I think christ you know you're leaving it right up to the</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0227">the wire you're coming home and then erm you're going to as you know I think it could have been the Thursday cos I said to him about erm erm coming on Friday and he said well mum was kind of you know erm coming to see me I said not a problem I said erm come on Saturday with your bike I said but I'll come round yours on Friday we'll load up cos what I didn't wanna do was erm have to go to his to load up on Saturday okay I'm not trying to avoid your mum but</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0227">erm load up and that when and then we've got it's a detour to go there it's not straight to Canterbury it's the going the wrong way</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0227">when when we went to yours with a van actually going that way was no no not out it was on the flight path so that wasn't a problem so he came Saturday morning erm and I'd gone to his Friday afternoon after work loaded up got it back here that was to see if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was coming or not so I think it was the Thursday that that I rang yes I think it was <vocal desc="laugh"/> so he was coming back on Thursday to be going to uni on</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0192">cutting it fine definitely</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0227">yeah and me thinking</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean I told you in Cambodia he cut it fine quite a few times</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0192">I kind of part of me wished that he's missed his flight or missed a bus or something so it had taught him a lesson but</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0227">he hasn't he's got to instil a discipline</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0192">it will fly for the first year he'll be okay that mentality he'll get through and he'll get an okay grade but come the second yeah and definitely the third year he can't be like that you have to be extremely organised</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0192">especially once you get to MA level there's no way you could be unorganised</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0192">there's absolutely no way</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0227">you're the <trunc>pers</trunc> you're the only person that can tell him I can't tell him your mum can't tell him to up his game cos he'll say what games that?</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0192" trans="overlap">told him</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0227">you haven't got a clue what you're talking about you what game? You've never played the game and I'll be going well actually you're right</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1107" who="S0227">although I did study I I had day reliefs for seven years at college so I do know the disciplines of it</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0227">but not like you do and he will accept it from you more than me cos he'll say er you've done it so I'm gonna I'd be I'm wise to not take council from you</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0192">my concern I think part of what they test you on in a degree I'm not saying what you're graded on but like with regards to the working world when you get a job you have to you know they they're expecting longevity you get a job they don't want you just changing job every six months every year so</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0192">I think half of the reason that a degree is as long as it is is to prove that you can focus on something for that long</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0227">and keep with it</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0192">and keep with it</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0192">and that's where people fail because I've got friends that take it almost right to the wire I've got friends that are doing really well for two and a half years</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0192">and then that last half a year and that worries me with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1119" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0192">that he won't stick through for the three years</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0227">I would rather slowly walk through the erm course than lie down for most of it and find out that I've gotta run like hell for that last hundred metres</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and sprint right at the end yeah</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0227">yeah the tortoise and the hare</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0192">he might pick that up now it took for me to go to university to learn that because let's face it prior to me going to university I was a terrible student</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes no yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0192">I didn't turn up I didn't do anything</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0227">yeah you've learnt through experience like I said I'm hoping the the female in Spain who seems quite a nice lady seen photographs of her very nice erm that her or the ones on the course now will deflect him from mediate him</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah did you meet did you meet his housemates or</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0227">er one of them</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0192">one</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0227">yeah erm American girl</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0192">oh okay</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0227">yeah so cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was locked in the toilet she almost became a student herself</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you got locked in the toilet?</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I'm in the toilet I can't get out and I'm thinking oh crap</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0192">did you get out? obviously</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0227">well actually yes we did but it was like oh god are we gonna have to bust the door down or something? that's a great start erm oh by the way er we've bust your door cos the the Mrs was <vocal desc="laugh"/> stuck in the toilet it we got out and that but er as we kind of met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was locked in the toilet so it was quickly became clear that er you had a brief intro when when we finally released her</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1139" who="S0227">and and the girl departed up the stairs</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0192">you weren't embarrassed were you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0190">no the</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0227">I think you were just relieved to get out the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1143" who="S0190">well yeah I just thought cos there's no way I could go out the window was there?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0192">you were considering it obviously</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that was well that was my <unclear/> I was thinking is there a window there? thinking can I get in or get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in or something to try and figure it out but from this side of the door apart from breaking it down we can't have a go at that lock can't</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0192">how did you do it?</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0190">it was one of those it's not like erm you know like if you've just got like a handle like that</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0190">and where the lock is it's just that little button that you twist</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0192">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0190">and I think your dad ended up pulling the door from the other side which cleared it so it would flip back but I couldn't get it to flip but it wouldn't turn it just <trunc>ja</trunc>jammed</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0192">oh god</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0190">I'm thinking oh gosh here we go <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1155" who="S0192">but you made it out?</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0190" trans="overlap">just <unclear/> yeah I made it out</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0192">isn't there somebody on your side of the family at university? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or some</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0190">no she's finished</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0192">oh she's finished</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0190">yeah yeah she's finished er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s erm</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0192">she was doing drama wasn't she or something?</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0190">she was but she changed she's working for <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> now having done her degree for two years erm she's after another job at the moment sounds quite good if she gets it</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0192">brilliant</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0190">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s at oh in London at uni she's doing her you know second year she's doing history erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gone to erm <anon type="place"/> erm and she's doing oh I don't know now she's changed her course and my nephew's also there</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0192">oh wow</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0190">doing a course so</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0192">so quite a few people then</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0190">so then all the family now are doing something or other</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0192">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0227">spoke to I rang <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's er <unclear/> she said she's sent some chocolates although I'm sure she said <unclear/></u>
<u n="1171" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh no I was gonna say that's about the third box she's sent we've haven't got any of them so I think there's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1172" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the postman's eating them</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I think they're in <unclear>her imagination</unclear> bless her</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0190">it's unusual for her cos she's usually very good</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0227">the text well she give me something what was it for Christmas wasn't it or something? I got a Christmas present I can't remember what it is but she came over</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0190">we didn't have a Christmas present this year</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0227">did I?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0190">no we didn't have Christmas presents this year last year she'd erm well I meant the last Christmas the Christmas before we did</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0190">you we had that set of nice knives I had a mug</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0227">oh yes</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0190">you had erm pass what did you have?</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0192">I don't know how you remember that kind of stuff I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1185" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I don't I don't remember <trunc>la</trunc>last year</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0190">I have to remember because that doesn't really</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0227">I don't remember</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I forget what I've bought other people</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0227">yeah I I forget that I forget what I've got stuff I've got I acquire stuff and I'm not sure where it comes from</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0192">when we visited our friends in Tennessee <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I pointed out a couple of things and went oh that's nice and like you bought us that <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't didn't remember doing that at all</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0192">there's a few things we bought them</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0190">his memory's getting terrible</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0190">and mine's not brilliant by any means</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0190">and mine sort of stops halfway through things like I lose track</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0190">but this morning dad came in and we want a cup of tea and I said right I'm going now so he said I'll see you about three so I said no it won't be three I'll see you at five no I'll see you at three so I goes aren't you picking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up at twenty past four for the train? he said oh yeah I beg your pardon</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1201" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0190">I'm beginning to think well</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's quite funny that two the comedy sketch isn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1204" who="S0227">yes no memories</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0192">just part of getting older isn't it?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0227">no nothing arrived</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0190">I can't bear the chemo now can we</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0227">we'll have to put it down to old age my love that's why my</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0192">my short term memory is not great I have to take a lot of notes and that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0190">I do now especially for dates on the calendar and that</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0192">mm I mean we there's so much technology nowadays that we don't really need to remember certain things you can just</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0190">yeah but then I think that's not good I think you need to</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0227">if it if it goes yeah if <trunc>fai</trunc> bit like you when I'm on a calculator for simple math and then the calculator fails and you're going I don't remember how to do it by paper or mentally yeah so if you are over reliant on</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0192">I mean that's fair those core skills you shouldn't shouldn't really forget</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0227">I think</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0192">but like if I didn't have my laptop all the work that I have to hand in and everything I don't know how I'd keep on top of it I'd just have pile I don't know how people did degrees before this kind of thing I'd just be stacks of paper everywhere</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0227">yes <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah that's why I think it's that boring cos everything had to be put on to paper didn't it?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0192">yeah gosh that would have been tiresome writing a thesis up and then getting it wrong a bit and having to go <vocal desc="laugh"/> rewrite forty thousand words</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0227">read or type it or whatever</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0227">dum dum dum and then you make mistakes it's like oh god I'm gonna throw it away rather than just delete and</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0227">cut and paste or nothing</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0192">problem is that people don't back up well enough now so <trunc>peop</trunc> I'm terribly worried about you know later on in the course just losing everything it's gone</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0227"><trunc>b</trunc><trunc>bu</trunc>back it up yeah</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm trying to keep it on the cloud I mean</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0227" trans="overlap">can you put it on can't you put it on the cloud?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0192">yeah I've got</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0227">well put it on mine as well</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0192">I've got it on a hard drive I've got it on a USB and I've got it on a cloud so</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0192">hopefully that'll be fine but this cloud so many I can give you a copy as well just incase</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0227">yes that's fine not a problem right I sent her that</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0192">I've got a presentation to give in a couple of weeks on erm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0227">already?</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0192">I have to give a presentation on Nigerian pidgin phrenology supersegmentals and phonotactics should be interesting</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0227" trans="overlap">good luck with that</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I know pidgins and creoles is quite interesting but it's really difficult to study because instead of studying a language I'm studying hundreds of languages and you're trying to work out basically it's about the genesis of pidgins and creoles how were they developed? so not only do you need to understand the lexifier language which would be the super straight so for example English creole or a French creole you kind of need to know a bit of French a bit of Spanish</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I've heard of French creole but I've never heard of English creole</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0192">I mean erm Nigerian pidgin English Jamaican that's an English creole</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah man</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0227">yeah it's creole course it is isn't it? yeah creole</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0192">erm I've been to a couple of places in Nicaragua and Honduras that were er English creoles on the Caribbean coast</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0192">erm which at the time fascinated me</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0192">but so you need to know about lexifier languages what gave them their words but then you also need to know about the substrate which are the African languages that</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0192">give them their grammar and give them all this kind of stuff so it's really quite complex</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0227">I bet it is</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0192">and there's no theory there's no set er <trunc>n</trunc> it's all just</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0192">you know this is the best idea at the minute but it changes</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0192">syntax is even heavier</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0192">doing like as I said it's cognitive science</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0192">every book's like a six hundred page maths book of like it's it's all about the language faculty and and it's trying to work out language of the mind and like basically do you know Noam Chomsky?</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0192">he revolutionised linguistics and a whole bunch of other departments he's actually the tenth most quoted person in modern books now and the er</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh right cos I don't read books I</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0192">the other nine are dead</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0192">in in the top nine are like Plato Aristotle and Chomsky's like</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0192">in the top ten which must be crazy to feel</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0192">you know I'm in the top ten of the most <unclear/></u>
<u n="1273" who="S0227">and still alive</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0192">cos basically the behaviourists before that in the fifties were saying that children learn language through positive reinforcement and negative reinforcement from their parents and from their peers</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0192">but Chomsky turned around and came up with what's called Plato's problem and the poverty of the stimulus where he's saying well how can children produce sentences that they've never heard?</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0192">it's not possible that they just hear the sentence and thus then regurgitate it</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><trunc>r</trunc>regurgitate</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0192">and how is it that a child will hear a mistake yet know that it's a mistake?</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0192">you'd think that they'd replicate the mistakes</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1284" who="S0192">these kind of things so since this the fifties sixties it's exploded and it's just gone on and they've been trying to make and they've worked out that the're are <trunc>pro</trunc> there are what's called universal grammar theories there are parameters that basically the child sets so for example null subject in English we have to have the subject we have to say I play</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0192">but in Spanish they have a null subject language</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0192">because the inflection <foreign lang="spa">hablo</foreign> I speak</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1290" who="S0192">you don't need to say <foreign lang="spa">yo hablo</foreign></u>
<u n="1291" who="S0227">yeah you don't have to emphasise the er the the the I yeah</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah so there's lots of these parameters and they found that all these parameters are binary it's either the language is that or the other and there's like a list of different parameters and basically the last fifty years they've been finding the core parameters but but again it's all theory</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0192">and it's really difficult to prove so</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0192">and the problem with it is that it started off as transformational theory and then moved on to principles and parameters it then in the eighties and nineties was called government and binding theory now it's called the minimalist programme they keep changing it because the the theory's developing so</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0192">trying to learn about all this is a bit you know there's like</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0192">so many theories to try and get through before you actually get to the core of it</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0227">good luck <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1302" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know the problem I was thinking</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1304" who="S0192">as well how do I apply this in the classroom? you know</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0192">how am I gonna use this knowledge?</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0227">yes plenty with those who who there <trunc>w</trunc> who are willing subjects to learn <trunc>rath</trunc> you'd wanna be teaching people who want to be there not people who have been forced to be there</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0192">no yeah of course</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0227">cos if they're forced to be there you'll be going this I'm never gonna impart this to these people</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0192">but I mean mine and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s ultimate goal we don't wanna be teaching English language we wanna be teaching linguistics</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0192">for the future but er we you know we need to have a PHD before we can be doing that so that's a long way off</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1314" who="S0192">it may never happen <unclear>but</unclear></u>
<u n="1315" who="S0227"><unclear/> well yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0192"><unclear/> try</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0227">you've gotta get your master's first get get a get a job do PHD part time if you can</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0192">I mean we may do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I have seriously considered trying to go to America or Canada to do a PHD because it's easier to get funding as a foreign student than it is as an as a native student</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0192">more more people get funding when they cos the the university it's good for the university to have foreign students so they fund people to come into the university</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0192">it would also be a way of getting our foot in the door with another country</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0227">yeah but would it pay for your like your accommodation and <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0192">funding would if we got the correct funding</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0192">would cover everything</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0192">they can fund people up to fifteen to twenty thousand pound a year for four years <unclear/></u>
<u n="1329" who="S0227" trans="overlap">er well I would definitely go in two off two prongs at the same time I'd be trying to look for work and seeing if I could do this</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0227">rather than just relying on one <unclear/> relying on the PHD</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no I mean our plan our plan after this is to go and work in the Middle East and save up the money so that we have enough money to self-fund ourselves</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0192">and then if we get funding then we can just save that money we don't need to do it</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0192">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="1337" who="S0227">I'm gonna get changed I suppose we're too early to go for the role call of thank yous isn't it? phoning people up</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0190">yeah my dad won't be home I don't think</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0190">neither will <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm I don't know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are doing</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0227">we'll go see them on Sunday anyway but I might probably phone them beforehand we're not going out till seven are we? so</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0190">no not going till quarter to seven</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0227"><trunc>quar</trunc>quarter to seven <unclear>you'll</unclear> walk down</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0190"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0192">do we have a reservation? <unclear/></u>
<u n="1346" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1348" who="S0192">thank you for reserving that I kind of just left it I didn't I don't really know <trunc>anywh</trunc>anywhere around</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0227">well no <unclear/> how you could organise anything from down there <unclear/></u>
<u n="1350" who="S0192">I don't know anywhere</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1352" who="S0190">well we didn't it it was difficult to know which one to choose from here but er we decided to pick something in <anon type="place"/> just so that your dad now I can't drive</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0190">otherwise <unclear>you were gonna've had</unclear> to pay for a taxi from somewhere</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0190">there and back erm</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0192">so we can have a beer or something <unclear/></u>
<u n="1358" who="S0227">oh yeah yeah sure yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0192">beer does complement curry rather well</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0227">it <unclear>is</unclear> indeed it does right I'm <unclear>gonna play with this soon</unclear></u>
<u n="1361" who="S0190"><unclear/> take it out so we can have a look?</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0190">are you gonna take it out so we can have a look?</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0192">yeah open it up</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0227">I'm quite good at resisting things <unclear/></u>
<u n="1366" who="S0192">very patient</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0190">I just wanna make sure it's not broken</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0192">no it works</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0227">I'll go and get my one out of the car cos er I need to er</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1371" who="S0227"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yes I will I will well you're gonna come up at Christmas</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0227">erm I'd say there's a brilliant incentive there</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0192">I</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0227">cos you're mum's gonna <unclear/> I believe Christmas Day is going to be we're gonna be I don't know where we're gonna be is it <anon type="place"/> or something? I'm not sure it's all up in the air but</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh okay so you're not here cos I've been worried</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0227">no no it's no it's not in that's not in stone but your mum is going to want you to be with her</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0192">I know I've kind of when we've spoken about it before I've assumed that you won't mind if I'm not here on Christmas Day and mum <trunc>w</trunc> really wants me to be</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1381" who="S0227">don't tell her</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0190">well I want you <unclear>here</unclear></u>
<u n="1383" who="S0192"><unclear/> but in <trunc>hinds</trunc> I know in hindsight I've been thinking well that's a bit rude of me to assume that <trunc>y</trunc>you don't aren't so bothered either but</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0227">yeah erm there's a</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1386" who="S0227">there is another way of doing this <unclear>that that flushes the interest out</unclear> it's a little <unclear/> but it's the sort of thing I would've said <vocal desc="laugh"/> er whoever comes and gets me from <anon type="place"/> is where I am at Christmas cos it would be</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah come and pick me up</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0227">it would be massively audacious for <trunc>ei</trunc> for this to go either way but I'm just gonna give it in one way that mum says oh get your dad to pick you up and he can drop you at mine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1389" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1391" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0227">I feel like er I don't think she'd your mum didn't even give me a chauffeur's uniform</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1394" who="S0227">you know so erm I mean tongue in cheek but we haven't we haven't finalised anything and to be fair er I don't have this emotional baggage</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0192">no you</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0227">that mum has got</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0192">yeah I presumed that you wouldn't be so bothered</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear>and it's</unclear> and I I make things although she doesn't see me pulling the strings I pull the strings to make things easier for her</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0227">so she doesn't get upset and stuff like that cos I don't get <unclear/></u>
<u n="1401" who="S0192">well tentatively I was thinking Christmas Eve Christmas Day at mum's and then Boxing Day and</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0227">yep</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0192">the day after at yours <unclear>if that's okay</unclear></u>
<u n="1404" who="S0227">yeah fine like I said it er cutting it down the middle and that erm is a bit like that fable where they the the the <trunc>chi</trunc> the <trunc>f</trunc> the two mothers are fighting <vocal desc="laugh"/> over the child and the king the wise king decides <trunc>h</trunc> which mother's gonna get it and they can't decide so he says well I'll cut the baby in half</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1406" who="S0227">and the one of the mothers er immediately goes for that and the other mother goes no</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0192" trans="overlap">please don't cut me in half <unclear/></u>
<u n="1408" who="S0227">no give it to her he then gives it because he you know the blah blah blah it's stupid to try and do things like that you know</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1410" who="S0227">it's more stress than anything else for er for the person collecting and for the for the other person being collected so no just have your your er your Christmas Eve your <trunc>Box</trunc> your Christmas Day and then whatever <unclear/></u>
<u n="1411" who="S0192">I mean would that work? cos actually thinking about it if <trunc>everyo</trunc>if everyone's having a drink on Christmas Day then getting between houses</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0227">well no <trunc>w</trunc>we'll</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0190">well we haven't <vocal desc="sigh"/> this is the er the thing that caused the problems last year which is why we went to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and we all stayed over because like you sort of said nobody can have a drink otherwise</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0190">erm but normally we alternate which year we have one with my family Christmas Day and then the opposite swaps around but that's all had to change cos <unclear>they</unclear> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s now got his own house and so's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er my sister-in-law's lost both her parents in the last couple of years so erm they don't have my brother always wanted to stay at home Christmas Day erm they don't have er the parents to come now only my parents and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has obviously got her eldest has got er a boyfriend now the one that she's erm shared accommodation went to uni with erm and they're hoping to get a place of their own so I at the moment it's just we've just said it's gonna come to an <trunc>e</trunc> a <trunc>sa</trunc> a time when we can't all be together any more</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0190">cos we're too big</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0227">it's it's become too big</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0227">I mean we could potentially get an <trunc>ad</trunc> er an invite from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> again we could get an invite from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we could get an <trunc>in</trunc> er one thing we have kind of agreed er well all all the family's agree that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s parents now are too old to be doing this they've got the house</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0227">so it's not a problem but it's too much work for them</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0192"><unclear>it's a lot pressure for them</unclear></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0227">they've earned their spurs they' now have earnt the place to do you know to go somewhere else not have it themselves but the brother's house is next door er which is the old family house I think you may have been there once erm so I mean we could potentially get an <trunc>o</trunc> er an an invite from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we don't know do we? we don't know</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0190"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1426" who="S0227">cos now that <trunc>s</trunc> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't there</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0190">I doubt it because</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0227">unless erm</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0190">erm well they we went there last year don't forget cos we came over or was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s? did we go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s last year? because we came from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s we stayed over Boxing er on Christmas night gone out Boxing Day I think we came back here didn't we? and then I think we went to did we go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s? or did we go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s?</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s? I can't remember</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0190"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0227">I can't <trunc>honest</trunc> we may have <unclear/></u>
<u n="1433" who="S0190">you see by rights it should be I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s on Christmas Day</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0190"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1436" who="S0227">I mean if I wanted to <unclear>go</unclear></u>
<u n="1437" who="S0192">becomes stressful doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1439" who="S0190"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1440" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0227">if I wanted to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1442" who="S0192">because we all want to be together but you just can't</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0190">there's just too many of us</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0192">Skype Facetime <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1447" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I could say well where was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> last Christmas? he wasn't with us was he? no so he must've been with er your mum</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0227">he wasn't here so I could say oh well it's my turn now but to be honest <unclear>I said</unclear></u>
<u n="1450" who="S0192" trans="overlap">process of elimination well <trunc>h</trunc>have you heard what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s talking about at the minute?</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0227">er not going to Spain</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh he's going to see</unclear> <unclear/> Spain</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah mum sent me an email saying you've gotta convince <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not to do that blah blah blah blah blah I was like well it's up to him I'm not gonna tell him what to do</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0227" trans="overlap">actually I I actually had put that nut in his head</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0190">the more you try and put that into into er er saying no the more likely he's want to</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0190">and the other thing is surely it's better for him to go out <unclear/> I know she perhaps wants to see him but it's my mind it's better for him to go at Christmas when he's not taking time out of uni</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0192">yes</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0190">as opposed <trunc>s</trunc> er <trunc>c</trunc> trying to get away <trunc>f</trunc> in the middle when his studies <unclear/></u>
<u n="1460" who="S0192">that's perhaps it doesn't need to be Christmas Day I mean he'll break up probably early December and not go back until maybe even February depending on what his course is gonna be so</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1462" who="S0190">but he was talking about her coming here wasn't he?</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0192">they're pretty tight then</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0192">if he's willing to introduce her to the family</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0227">well</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0192">then it's</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0227"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1469" who="S0190">well I don't not saying he will</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0227">I I I don't know</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0192">oh just to?</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0190">erm</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0227">I had kind of put that idea in his head but I</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it was you was it?</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0227">put that idea in his head even earlier by going don't go now go at Christmas but he went now and he's kind of</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0192">and now wants to go at Christmas also</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0227">and he wants to go at Christmas as well to be honest <vocal desc="sigh"/> your mum might be a little bit but</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0192">I know</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I think she's got to give him leeway</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0227">but it's a nice it's a nice change erm</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0192">it it's unfortunate that it happens the one year I'm back</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0227">it's musical chairs it's now you're at home and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to be there apparently oh er</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah but that's precisely it</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0192">I think she just wanted everyone together though didn't she?</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well yes it was</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but as you said that</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1489" who="S0192">it becomes difficult</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0192">I'll probably be back for like I reckon a week over Christmas so</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0192">whichever is easiest for you guys just tell me and I'll kinda split it</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0192">I won't be able to be home much longer than that I have four exams in the first week of <trunc>Jer</trunc>January</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I've got no problem with</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0190">the thing is I'm not being funny it it's lovely for us to see you but what do you do all day?</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0190">we know that you've got work than you can be doing</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0190">it's a waste of your time you know it'd be better to say come up for like a couple of days here and a couple of days there erm with mum and a couple of days with us and then say to us well we can come down to you</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0190">so therefore at least you can study and we can just have the day but you're not having to sit here wasting all your time or trying to work around other people</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0192">hopefully it'll be okay but I am a bit worried they've I have a mid er mid year assessment and it's the first week in January</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0190">do you want the blind down <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0192">erm if it can come down</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0227">it won't that that blind there it's not gonna go down is it really? not gonna</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0190">I can't see which is the blind?</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0227">it's that one</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0192">it's right on the line</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0190">can you bring it down</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0192">if's this one here does that oh this plant yeah yeah no don't worry about it</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0227">no don't worry about that that's fine that can take it erm</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah that's good that's fine okay perfect yeah</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0190">yeah?</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0227">at the end of the day erm erm surely mum would like that but the thing you have to say erm is oh god that damn things taping isn't it?</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1519" who="S0227">you'd better not play that</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0192">nobody else is gonna hear it I mean nobody in our family anyway</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0227" trans="overlap">mum shouldn't always get what mum wants</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0227">are you with me?</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0192">yeah of course</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0227">erm and if he wants to go away she has to think about him what he wants rather than about me me me it it's all good I can show my family blah blah blah we can all integrate and fuse and push all of our families together</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0190">we don't know that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going to be able to accommodate you</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no we <trunc>don</trunc> no no no no one no no</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0190">she might <unclear/> single child</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that's a <trunc>s</trunc> that's a sideshow but if he wants to go there then she says yes</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0190">then she's that's fine</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0227">then she should say okay have a nice Christmas and I'll see you when you get back not saying I want you here because you know I want all my children around me and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0192">I can't really comment can I? I mean when was the last time I was in England for Christmas?</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0227">no you can't you've got erm he's done his stints</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0227">you haven't</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0192">I guess it's just unfortunate that the the year that I'm home he he is talking about going off</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0192">I haven't got a problem with it but</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0192">erm probably would be a bit nicer for me if he was around because I don't really know anyone in the family other than mum and</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0192">kind of know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a little bit now and obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s really the only one that I feel truly close to but</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0192">erm I'm not gonna</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0227">like I said</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0192">tell him not to go cos he doesn't</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0227">because all you'll be doing is serving your own self-interest are you with me? you'll be saying do this for me <trunc>o</trunc><trunc>o</trunc>over what you wanna do for yourself I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be fair is probably quite self-serving and he'll do whatever he wants but it he might it might stop him to think if you are putting erm a bit of a a emotional trip on him thinking oh right <unclear/> blah blah blah but erm at the end of the day that that said erm erm yeah mum would like the pair of you there and she's already well two out of three of you's not bad is it? I mean okay and just quote the I'd just quote the wise old sage Jagger to her you can't always get what you want</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what you want</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0227">exactly</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> wise old sage</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0227">well he is he is old</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he's certainly old</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0227">he may not be wise and he may not be a sage but there is those are his words</u>
<event desc="sound of bird"/>
<u n="1554" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0227">so yeah so I said I'm quite erm as long as I get to see you some er the time erm it's like when I jokingly put I mean you're clever at words so you would have got the little cryptic thing I gave you about the <trunc>Chris</trunc> the birthday the cuckoo and the nest <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1556" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0227">erm I didn't know what you were doing but looking at it from just on face value I thought hold on a second I thought you were coming up to see me</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0227">mum's <trunc>manip</trunc>monopolising this and even then I said well fine whatever I don't cos like I said erm</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0192">yeah I mean she told me ten o'clock and I just went I'll run it by dad and see what he says</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0192">erm you came back with er so I was like I'll just tell her now and</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0192">I said one o'clock to her and she she went yeah one is fine so</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0192">I mean it was a bit cheeky but at the same time I think she was probably thinking I'm seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the day after so</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah she probably doesn't realise it herself I mean or or she does I don't know erm</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0192">nah I'm sure she just thinks</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but I said I I I'm not I don't have the emotional all those emotionals that it that she has that and feel upset and things like that no</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0192">it can be a bit tough for us in the middle though like trying to think I don't wanna you know put off you and I don't wanna put off you so yeah</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah but I'm I she's a much tougher <unclear/> than me cos I'll just say er er okay fine whatever and like I said I put in a thing I put I wanted to emphasise to you that erm what I said was tongue in cheek so I put you a big smiley face on it</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I saw that</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0227">cos to make to cos with when I'm talking to you you can tell by my intonation and my gestures if I'm meaning it or I'm just saying it as I yeah I don't mind well I do mind but and but I'm trying to disguise it and you'll know that but in an email you don't pick up any nuances or nothing like that so I thought if I threw a little diagram in you'll know that what I'm saying is I'm not that you know I'm not that erm I've just recognised it but if you want to go then or or I'll just say okay fine if it makes her happy then do it you know?</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0190">do you know when you'll actually finish uni?</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0192">erm yes I I finish the twelfth of December</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0190">oh right so you've got a fair old time off over</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0192">yeah so erm and as as will <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he'll have more time off than I will cos he won't he might have a mid-year assessment period maybe but</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0192">erm university gives you a fair bit of time off undergraduate</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0190">well yes because the idea is you get a bit of a job if possible doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0190">erm especially at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s age group to sort of help fund some of the things you might need to do</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0192">mm so yeah I'll finish on the twelfth and then I'm just I mean what you were saying is correct about like my studying but I think because it's not coursework because I've just got exams if I came home for a few extra days I think I could study here I might just have to go and lock myself in the room and do it everything should be on my laptop really I should have done everything by that point I just have to study</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0192">I just have to keep reading about it and making sure that I I I follow it so I think I'll be fine <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0192">but he should finish around about mid-December I would say erm it's gonna come round quickly isn't it? really really quick</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes it will do it's ninety days</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's already October next week</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0227">ninety days till Christmas</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0192">oh you're counting down are you? has the has the Coca-Cola advert come on?</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0227" trans="overlap">just do the math boom straight</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0192" trans="overlap">straight answer ninety days</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0227">ninety days erm it erm with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I will speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I see him next Friday I will erm try and stitch him if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s coming home is there any work? cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been left his key fob and everything and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has left a back door he's got I'm hoping he's got a revolving door policy with them</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0192">I mean he should do if he's always got work that needs to be done</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he's got work that is the slight <unclear>break</unclear> for him not to go erm to her</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0227">but the other break <unclear>hole</unclear> kind of be more on system is going good idea if you can afford it but make sure you've done your assignments before you go don't be trying to fit everything in when you get back</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0192">I'm a bit concerned with how he's viewing his finances in general he's given me a very kind of blas</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0192">you know I'm being lent so much money that it doesn't really matter I might as well just spend it and I keep trying to say to him if somebody had told me at the beginning</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0192">take the money don't spend it stick it in an ISA <vocal desc="laugh"/> come out of your degree with more money than you started with or at least only spend a portion of the money</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0192">whereas undergraduates just feel like hey I've got this money where did it come from? like they just spend it</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0192">and then you think oh and I mean I've still got fifteen thousand he's gonna come out with closer to thirty to fifty thousand so</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0192">if he takes the full amount which he keeps talking like that's what he's going to do and I'm like well no take the minimum you don't need to er to take</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0192">I guess if he's never gonna have to pay it back then</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he should he should seek your wise council because there is no substitute for experience I said when I say to him erm about what he's going to and stuff like this it's like with the freshers' week I said I talk as though I've been on this I don't I only know from what I've heard and have a good time blah blah blah you know this is where where you your getting to know people and and the way it works and stuff like that and then you knuckle down erm I said but apart from that I I can't give you any experience er any advice because I've never done this before erm so I'm hoping that he will actually listen to you and seek your council because you've done it you've made the mistakes you know where the where the pitfalls are and you can spare him from doing these sort of things as so so if he wants to go and see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm at Christmas not a problem as long as he makes sure that if he's got any assignments they are all done before he goes not trying to fit them in and just fudge erm erm</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0190">yeah but you'll probably find he won't he he's more chance that he might go early because the flights'll be that much cheaper if he leaves it right on top of Christmas</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0190">it's gonna cost a fortune to go out there</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0192">that's true</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0190">so he might sort of say if he goes soon as he finishes he can perhaps have what? anything like a good ten days out there</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0190">erm and sort of you know come back just as everybody else is going so it doesn't cost him quite as much money</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0192">I think that would be a better idea as soon as he</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0190" trans="overlap">then he can sit down and study</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0192">as soon as the course finishes go out for a week or so come back for Christmas and</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0190">that's it and then you've got some time to finish your studies</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0192">it really depends on his <unclear/></u>
<u n="1628" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it'd keep your mum happy as long as that's when she wants him out there</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0227">she might want him at Christmas are you with me?</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0227">and then he's going to definitely</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0190">but you don't get what you want do you all the time?</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0190">you just have to</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0227">no but</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0190">so wait and see</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0227">I think he if he's going to disappoint me your mother or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think erm your mother and I will be a distant second and third to that I would if I was him and that's the trouble <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's the problem</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1640" who="S0227">so erm yeah so I mean</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0190">yeah but you look at it I'm not being funny he he's had and don't take this the wrong way he's had Christmases that haven't really been anything brilliant for the last two or three years because he's been on his own and an awful lot of that time there at Christmas so if he's got a chance to have a fun Christmas then surely that</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I would go for well</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0190">well you'd go for that wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0192">I feel quite guilty to be honest with you but</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it trumps every time I said the only thing I'd say is if he's going at Christmas make sure that before that you go you've done everything it's it's nothing for you to come home to</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0227">it's all done you're not smart enough to be able to go there and then do this</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> hopefully his workload in the first semester won't be too heavy</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0227">won't be too heavy</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0192">er</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0227">but I mean I fear that science</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0192">it's going to be that I mean the <anon type="place"/> is a top twenty thirty uni same as <anon type="place"/> they're gonna expect more than I had to do at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1653" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0192">so er</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0227">I can't help him</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0227">I gave him some money boom boom that's it erm</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0192">I just hope he uses his money wisely he <trunc>need</trunc> I I know he's got some extra money because he did well in his access course so that's good and he one thing that he can do that I couldn't do which is the whole reason I took a year out I wanted to be self assessed</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0192">I was knowing that you know if you guys are assessed or mum and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were assessed I wasn't gonna get any help</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0192">and I purposefully took a year out but only found out in hindsight that you had to have been living on your own for three years not for one year</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0192">erm and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has been living on his own effectively</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0192">he's okay he's currently been living with mum but as far as apparently they're concerned he's been working so he's a mature student so</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0192">he will get more help because he's been assessed but he also seems to wanna take all of the money and and the impression he's given me is</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0192">just it's free money and I can just kind of spend it</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's not oh it's not free he'll end up having to pay a bit or or erm keep servicing the erm the interest without any of the equity and that could cost him an absolute fortune over over</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I think he'll</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0227">his working life</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0192">I think he'll go travelling over the summer again I think he's got the bug a little bit now</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he's got he's got the bug yeah I just wish I said about the girls and that's easy for me to say but I said focus on the mission girls that will all come later but sometimes people want everything now especially</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0192" trans="overlap">my concern with him travelling he <vocal desc="laugh"/> he spends more than I do travelling</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0227">yes he's not got you <trunc>sk</trunc> he's</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0192">he just he just already has a higher standard than I did at his age so</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah he is I mean like your your mum at her age will happily go camping and stuff like that even at that age now he's going</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0192">do you know how much he he he got with some girl and must have paid about sixty-seventy pounds for a room a a wooden hut on the coast in Thailand it sounds lovely for about sixty-seventy pound really nice mini bar all that kind of stuff I got a very similar one for about eight pounds when I was there you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0192">probably not quite the same standard but it was a beach hut</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0192">on on the beach</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0227">he's got he's got standards</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0190" trans="overlap">you're more far more mature in your attitude</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0190">and have been over the years</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0190">than he ever has been</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0227">yeah and you're</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0192">he seemed to when it was good to see him when he was out there he seemed like or the first time he really seemed like he'd come on a bit when he was out there but</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0190">oh yeah he's he's come on an awful lot</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but then he came home and mum has been like he's gone backwards again he just like didn't come out of his room didn't wanna kind of do anything</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0192">and I guess he was in a bit of limbo at that point</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0227">yeah kind of</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0190">he's been texting <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1704" who="S0192">yes</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0227">even when</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he was so confident out there he was happy to talk to me he really it was nice to spend some good time with him but but yeah I agree I do agree he said to me he feels bad about it and he said you know I felt like I feel I'm behind I feel like I'm younger than other people but I've kind of been in limbo for the last four or five years now I'm kind of catching up I said I don't think it</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0190">yes he <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0227">I think in a way he's</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0192">problem is he's comparing himself to me a little bit</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to him don't compare yourself to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1712" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0192">because he's not the average like you know most people weren't doing this at your age</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0227">no no</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0190">no but on on the other hand what you were doing when he was younger he didn't do</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0190">he was <trunc>ve</trunc> and he can didn't he he was quite sad really one day he came and he sat here at teatime and he says I just feel on my own because all my <trunc>fr</trunc>friends have got girlfriends or something and got something else I don't anything I don't have any <unclear>thing</unclear> to do with anybody else</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0192">how long had <unclear/> with this?</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0190">you know he spent so oh what a good year or more do you remember? we sat at the table</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0227" trans="overlap">before oh it was before his girlfriend erm what's her name now?</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0190">no it wasn't it's been since <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1722" who="S0227">oh since oh yes right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that was her name phew <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1724" who="S0227">when him and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> broke up yeah yeah he did feel</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0190">and he said since then</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0227">I I think everyone every guy or woman will feel sorry for themselves once</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0192">you're not gonna feel good</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0227">it wasn't his <trunc>i</trunc> the erm the disintegration of that relationship wasn't was mostly her not him</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0192">I felt guilty I felt like I abandoned him when he was younger that you guys divorced and I just kind of went off and I didn't spend much time with him and then I went to uni and then I've lived abroad and I felt</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0227">wasn't your place</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0190">you all have to find your own way to cope with it</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0190">I mean you could have stayed here and him still not had any been any different to what you are you know and in fact you might have argued and because you'd have felt you needed to take over dad's place because you saw more of him than dad so you be trying to streamroll him into doing things he could see so it might have spoilt your relationship so there's not I shouldn't feel guilty about it</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah don't beat yourself up</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0192">no I was pleased when he came out to Cambodia</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0192">we felt close I felt close to him but now since I've come home I was at home er mum was our way and I came up here a few times and you know a few weeks ago he didn't spend any time with me at all he I was quite surprised cos we were really tight in Cambodia</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0192">and then we came home I came home and he wouldn't get out of bed until twelve or one</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0192">or something and then he's just</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0227" trans="overlap">like I said he</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0192">I tried to cook with him a bit and stuff</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0192">we did once or twice but I had to push I had to really push</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0227">he needs constant pushing because if he doesn't he slow he slides back into himself I think</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0190">he's so used to spending time on his own and that isn't he?</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0227">I</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0190">he's takes himself to his room and he plays on his computer and he's done that</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0190">for years and years</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0192">he said to me he likes time to himself and I said that's fair</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well that's fine but</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0190"><trunc>lik</trunc> but because he hasn't had a break from that it's a case of come down and play with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone to bed I'll sit and talk to mum</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0190">or something he didn't have the friends to go out with</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0190">and he he so that you can't just keep going to places to try and find somebody as if you're on the <trunc>lo</trunc> but he hadn't even got any male friends because they'd all gone different ways</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0227">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and that had</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to Saint Albans didn't he?</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well their own <trunc>relat</trunc> they've got their own relationships that's that thing is if you see people in couples cos you're couples er although your single friends it it becomes a bit difficult erm</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0192">definitely</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0227">erm because your friend is still in a relationship and he's going well I can see you like every now and again but like I can't be seeing you four or five times a week</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0227">because I'm in a relationship I can't do that I think with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s he has a tendency he realises that he now I think he's categorised his his childhood as not being a very nice one</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0192">yeah he has</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0227">and I think he blames your mum for it</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0192">yeah he does</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0227">now she has to have some put her hands up to some of it and I have to put my hand up to some of it as well</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0192">no I mean</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0227">but it's not all down to that but I think he focuses I think he probably blames her a lot more than he blames me because she is the architect but I still must put my hand up to an extent but so that</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no he was quite brutally honest with me when he was out there and I kinda had to say to him yes obviously as you're saying mum made mistakes</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0192">but you can't say she didn't try to be a good mother she</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0192">may have made lots of mistakes throughout the years but she clearly put effort in to be a good mum it he's kinda yeah what you're saying is just given a blanket impression of how his childhood was</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0192">and I said well prior to this happening you know we had a good time we were pretty happy</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0192">erm and he could have reacted differently</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0192">to the whole thing ah it's difficult because he was young wasn't he? so he he didn't have the option that I did to to get out of the scenario</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah he was ten he was ten</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0192">he was stuck in it and that I feel quite guilty about</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0227">or <trunc>elev</trunc> he was eleven yeah</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0227">but er</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0192">hopefully this'll be yeah but I just hope he gets the degree <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1790" who="S0227">well yeah</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0192">cos it's a lot of money to do</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0227">yes and I hope he doesn't blow a fortune in erm I don't care how much money er the first care is I don't care how much money he blows in its acquisition</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0227">the second care is I hope he acquires it without blowing that much money are you with me?</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0192">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0227">and he doesn't drop out I mean I will not be happy with him after this that he gave up a job that wasn't you know it wasn't the best job in the world but there's a hell of a lot of worse jobs in and it was something that he was good at it was on his doorstep erm and he could have networked into something else rather than I admire him for giving it up and doing this but he must stick through it you know</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0192">I mean if he drops out because he has love interests or he can't be bothered</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh I'd be incandescent with with displeasure</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0192">that's not good if he drops out because it's too difficult</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0192">that's fair I mean</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0192">he's doing a difficult course</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0192">computer science isn't going to be an easy course <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1806" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0192">I can't begin to fathom it so</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah no I don't think it will be like I said erm if that I'll understand that and I'll say well you must now get back into the workplace</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0192">but even if he just gets a C that's better than you know no degree <vocal desc="laugh"/> if you come out you've spent</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0192">twenty thousand pounds but you've got nothing</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well this is this is that's this is where your wise council comes in that you know I I've said to him look you're on a mission now the mission is to get that degree you go from here to here ba ba ba and you get it and this will then enable you to do what you wanna do if you wanna travel well you'd better get a job you'll be able to travel blah blah blah</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0192">I've been trying to get him to think about postgraduate going on to do a masters cos if he does well in his degree</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0227">yeah one step at a time</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0192">I know but</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0227">give him one step at cos otherwise I he might be daunted by</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0192">but it gives him a reason to get that</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0192">if he can see why he needs this to do the next thing</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0192">if he's thinking well what is the next thing? I don't need this then it's a problem so</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well <trunc>ho</trunc>hopefully I'm hoping his work placement might give him a a an experience and a job and cos I think he does have a mission as in what type of job he wants to do if he</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0192">he wants money as well</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0227">he wants he wasn't the <trunc>mone</trunc></u>
<u n="1825" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1826" who="S0227">he wants basically there is</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0192">he wants a comfortable lifestyle</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0227">in relation of you that he wants he's seen you go erm holidaying a lot and travelling and he wants this as well but he needs to have a trouble is your line of work gives you longer holidays</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0227">his line of work will give him four week if he moved to America if he wanted a job in America er most of them get about a week off</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0192">yeah it's terrible isn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0227" trans="overlap">know this so erm erm in the UK he'll get a job that'll give him four or five or even six weeks off but that doesn't give him that range of what you had you know? he could travel in those times but</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0192">well I chose a field because I wanted to travel and it was a combination of travel and work so I found something</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and you're able to ply your trade where you've travelled</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0227">so it's all you know you're at work but you're almost on holiday at the same time cos you this is not the country of your birth you know I am somewhere else</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0192">yeah still feels like travelling</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0227">so</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0192">definitely feels like work though</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0227">it now yes</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it doesn't quite feel like a holiday</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0227">this now feels like more work because you're in the land of your birth and you're working there's okay you're not in <anon type="place"/> that would be a real stretch on your imagination of trying to romanticise it at least with Brighton you can say oh we're by the sea and it's south of England it's not here or like so it's it's it's not as good as being abroad er but it's better than being in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1843" who="S0192">without we wanted to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I really really wanted I think we told you</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0227">yes you did</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0192">we wanted to go to the Netherlands</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0192">or even Scotland</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0192">but cos we want we wanted to be close we wanted to be able to see family this year and have the money that we could you know every month come back home and do that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0192">but it just wouldn't work they there's the myopic that you must have your degree from a native English-speaking country</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0192">even though it's a top one hundred world university even though it's bilingual</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0227">give them what they want cos if it opens more doors that's that's that's what you have to do</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0192">cost a lot more though</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0227">the ends justifies the means</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0192">pretty sure that rule is there because these English-speaking universities have set that rule</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well well</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0192">so that we continue to come to the English-speaking universities yeah</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0192">oh yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0227">yes if you can monopolise something and contain it or control it you that's what you do no one wants to lose control of something that they find precious but I think by the sounds of it</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0192" trans="overlap">how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doing now he's moved in? has he settled?</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0190">he should be here in a few minutes</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0192">oh is he coming over?</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0190">yeah he's going to erm he he's in between he he gave up his job in erm Northampton and went to because he got on really well with erm his immediate boss when he was there and <vocal desc="cough"/> excuse me he left he always wanted to keep going this boss and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> followed him he he kept hounding him and hounding him and that he said come on you've got more chance you're you're like me you want to get on and you want to go up on the scale you don't want to sit at this level so to do that you'll do well but unfortunately when he actually got there and got stuck in what he set out or what he was given to believe didn't come about and they changed everything and he would just have been a door knocker</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0190">literally and said oh I'm not doing that I'm not doing it</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0192">no fair</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0190">but he was very very lucky in the fact that my brother suddenly decided that he could train him up and he'd like it so he's gone to work for my brother</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0192">oh brilliant</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0190">so or he will do he starts on Monday</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0192">fantastic</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0190">erm and what have you so er he's quite looking forward to that I think</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0192">is that the neo</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0190">neo <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0192">neo <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0190">so er</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0192">so is he coming for curry?</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0190">no no no no they've got er something on tonight I said cos well you're welcome to come like I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I said you're more than welcome to come and join in and that but it's a long way erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got some work to get ready hopefully laying her his floor in his kitchen and his conservatory tomorrow so by the time he finishes work he he was in Marseille er when did he go? Thursday morning he had to leave early to fly down to Marseille he then flew back in I think god got home at two o'clock on erm Friday morning he had to be in London for an appointment at eight o'clock erm so by the time he got home last night you know</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0192">he's exhausted</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0190">it's an awful lot erm try and fit everything all in so erm I did say to them</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1884" who="S0190"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1885" who="S0192">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0192">they're they're <trunc>c</trunc> why are they coming this evening? they're just to say hi</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0190">erm well the that was the <unclear/> for the thing erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had to give his car back when he left <anon type="place"/> cos it was a company car</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0192">ah</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0190">so and when he got a company car he sold his car so they have one car between the two of them until he starts work with <anon type="place"/> next week and he will get his own car again</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0192">right</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0190">er well he's got a van this time because of the type of work work he'll be doing so of course he's he wanted the car today his work he's been working for his friend just helping him out erm and that all went pear-shaped today so he came in erm and he's gone he was going over to see my brother so he had to go to to get his friend to drop him off in Wellingborough to get the car from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s work to go to my brothers to sort that out so that he could then come back to pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to come to work and drop <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> off</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0192">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0190">so sharing a car doesn't and then his phone broke so he wasn't a happy bunny</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0192">so it's been a bad day?</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0190">it hasn't do you want er the blind down now?</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0192">no it's this one now it's the door this if I sit forwards I'm alright</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0227">damn sunny</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0192">no it's fine honestly it's not it's not here now</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0227">this one's smaller than my other one</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0190">quantity here</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but how's how's he finding the new house where he's living?</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0190">I think he like it he's had a couple of which what's the word? erm</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0227">setbacks</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0190"><unclear>match</unclear> snags if you like</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0190">that you always think oh yes this looks okay and then</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0227">it gets slimmer</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0192">oh it looks nice</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0227">it's like a it's like a newer version of me isn't it? slimmer</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1912" who="S0190">you're certainly losing it dear you really are I'm getting seriously worrying</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1914" who="S0227">slimmer isn't it? what do you think Miss? I don't think dad I'm a cat</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0190">right well let's hope this one'll be a bit better</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0227">yeah oh so I'll see if I</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0192">what kind of problems have they had then?</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0190">so erm he they've got like a the house was all really nicely done up the only real fault that they had that they could see was the fact that they've got this lounge diner and it's got like a really a really sort of old dated carpet</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0190">through erm and that the chap did apologise in that when he moved out he said I'm sorry I've had them in to clean the carpet <trunc>twi</trunc> it's been down no <unclear/> don't worry it doesn't erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said don't worry because it won't go with suite so and because erm my girlfriend's erm father works here and things</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0190">we get carpet really cheap so look please don't worry about them so they knew they've got to do that and that was getting that sorted but they've got like an old-fashioned corner bath</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0190">it's really nicely set out in the bathroom er and they've got like one <trunc>e</trunc> one end it's like they had in <anon type="place"/> the sort of taps with the shower across the top</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0192">okay yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0190">but it's also got the other end of the bath an overhead shower</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0190">well they don't like bathing they like showers</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0190">but when they went to use this shower to stand in it it wouldn't come the couldn't get any hot water out of it</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0190">so they've now had to pay for a new shower to be put in</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0192">that's no good</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0190">cos rather than try and fix it so all the piping had to be done to put that in properly</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0192">that wasn't cheap</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0227"><unclear/> is much faster sorry guys</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1939" who="S0190">the new toy</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0192">that is that it or have there been more problems?</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that that was it then erm his dad bought him a television table to put his television on cos he bought himself a new TV and the television table was fine but it can't go in the place because the other sofa won't fit in</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0190">so then after that's probably gotta go up in the man cave so he then had to go out and find some other form to do it but he to drill all the wiring cos the wiring had to go so you know it's just little things but</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0192">part of getting your own house isn't it I guess? yeah</u>
<u n="1945" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1946" who="S0190">he's sat last weekend he said come oh come and see the carpets and that mum see how how we're getting on so I said okay then and then you'll see the other stuff we've done so I said right we'll bring your stuff up well they wanted our white garden furniture</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0190">said have than and then loads of bits and pieces golf clubs and his badminton rackets and all these bits and pieces that have been in our garage</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1950" who="S0190">so we loaded the car full and bless him when we got up there he's got open at the back and he's trying to clear all the rubbish up that they've got had left all the old carpet and everything so there's hey don't come and bring any rubbish up here so I said we're not bringing rubbish as far as we're concerned</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0192">it's your stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1952" who="S0190">it's your stuff it's up to you now to decide what you wanna do with it</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's going in your house</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0190">so erm</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0192">so this is a mortgage this place isn't it?</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0190">pardon?</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0192">this is it's mortgaged?</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh yes <unclear/> buying it yeah it's theirs</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah so oh that's a big move isn't it? getting your first mortgage</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0190">it is a big move but like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said if you look at the comparison of what you're paying for a something that is very</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> isn't it? from what I've heard</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0190">yeah I mean it is he he's done very very well he <trunc>ha</trunc> he's taken a very small mortgage to compare to what they offered him</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0190">erm and that so he was doing a lot better off having this mortgage than he did when he rented the place and it's his</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's so much better than money down the drain isn't it?</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh gosh yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0192">every month just nothing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I are just oh I don't know how we'd ever get on the property but er</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0190">well I'm sure you will when if if you get to the stage where you passed all your exams and things there's no reason why you shouldn't have a semi decent job</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0192">no I mean I guess</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0190">so therefore you'll have the money to think about</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I guess if we stop putting the money on education or travel then maybe we could save</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0192">but we haven't really been earning very much although I've been able to save a bit we've only been on about fourteen thousand pounds in South Korea so it's not actually a lot of money it's just that we we</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0227">although your bills are paid aren't they?</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0192">yeah the bills are covered and the rents covered so it kind of and then the cost of living's cheaper so that kind of keeps keeps going up but when you actually take it for what it is to get I mean how much do you have to put down on a mortgage maybe thirty thousand?</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0190" trans="overlap">five percent depends on the property doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0192">yeah it completely varies</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0190">so yeah</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0192">but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I would have to be very settled wouldn't we to be able to do that as well unless you just mortgaged it and then rented it immediately to somebody else I can't see how we'd be able to do it</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well you can</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0192">and I feel a bit bad doing that to somebody else making somebody else pay my mortgage</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0190">why?</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0192">while they live there</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0190">because it gives them a home</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0192">it does but</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0190">give somebody else a home a chance that they probably can't if <unclear/> any other way there just aren't the amount of houses at the moment are there?</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0192">I just feel like that's kind of half the problem with why rent's so high in the UK if people just didn't you know you get one guy that owns twenty houses then he's like well I I own it all so I'll just put the rent up and I just I don't know</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0190">I do well the thing that annoys me more than anything is that if you drive around and have a look in quite there's quite a few places just boarded up where people have bought the property when it was good</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah oh yeah</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0190">and to put sink their money into and now they're well there's people want homes you should only be allowed to hold a house for so long with like living in it or renting it</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0192">yeah I mean there are enough houses for everyone</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0190">there are</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0192">there are there's not a shortage of houses erm I I personally am of the belief this is again slightly ethical issues my own belief I don't think we should be able to own more than two houses I don't I think it would solve quite a few problems it would stop having so many people needing to rent if you just said look why do you need more than your main home and perhaps a summer home somewhere else do you really need to own more than that? I mean I guess most people don't but some some people do</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0190" trans="overlap">but you see if they're property developers and doing this they need to own them to rent them out don't they? to make the money to go on to do the next one</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0192">yeah to do more</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0190">and there's the people that don't do it want to sort of invest money into the property</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0192">I mean I understand for new houses but it gets me when you're talking thinking about an old house that's been paid for twenty times over and yet people are still paying for the same bricks and mortar that were were built a hundred years ago a hundred and fifty years ago</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah but the more that the the older the property the more you're taking on</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0190">because the bills it's like now dad's having to</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0192">the insulations not so good</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0190">that's right that er the roofing is like that the windows the heating</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0192" trans="overlap">things break the maintenance</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0190">the boilers it costs you far more to run an older house than I mean it doesn't cost much my dad as much to run his five-bedroomed house and that as it does to us to run this</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0192">I mean I'm a bit of socialist really I think probably at heart I would say we all own all of the houses you apply to move house and we all put in a little bit of month into a pot that means that your house is maintained by some external company where we don't even need to extend</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no no I I er I don't know</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean that's fine</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0190">I'm so <unclear/> possessions</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0192">and and that's why people that's why it isn't like that cos most people agree</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah but you see it's everybody's got a different outlook haven't they?</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0190">if you think how many <trunc>p</trunc>places that people just trash absolutely trash them</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean effectively it would be yours in this scenario you would be under no pressure to move nobody can force you out it's your house but if you want to move you just er you just look at all the available houses kind of like a house swap do you know what I mean? you just swap houses you don't really oh you can change it you can modify it because it's yours while you're living there but you don't sell it as such it's you don't have the money from it you just move to another house so you apply that's the system that I'm kind of imagining to a certain degree so the house this would still be yours and if you wanted to live here for you know forever you can do that but if you decide well you know I wanna see what it's like in Devon you could go on a website and see who is wanting to move out of Devon and then just kind of swap</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0190" trans="overlap">but you can do that can't you now?</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0192">you can yeah to a certain degree</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I wouldn't I wouldn't wanna leave somebody in my house <unclear/> back</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0192">but I'm talking about an all encompassing system</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0190">for everybody yeah</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0192" trans="overlap">where everyone and then maintenance is kind of more of an external thing you don't need if something breaks in your house if effectively it just comes out of taxes if you're like this is broken then it just you know some company comes round a government agency and fixes it rather than you having to do that yourself cos you get people as well that I had a friend that got a mortgage and he had their house flooded in America and he's just got the house and then the house flooded like there was a freak weather accident in in Nashville or Tennessee and just lumped them with masses and masses of debt just</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0192">they weren't to know that that was going to happen it seemed very unfortunate</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well my friend exactly the same she lives in Wellingborough and erm she's just moved in with her partner now and he daughter's been living in her house that she had that she split with her husband and she managed to get a property of her own and er one day her daughter <unclear>rang</unclear> up mum you're gonna have to come over and sort this water out there's so much water cos think oh yeah with the rain then she goes oh gosh mum if you don't come and sort this out it's going it's nearly up to the conservatory you're having and the long and the short of it is that basically <trunc>some</trunc>somebody has done some work or some building they've erm done it on the er the floodplains</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0190">there's a and then what they've done they've disturbed a spring and so she's having to pay for a pump to pump out the water on to the street</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0192">why's that her responsibility?</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0190">because it's her house and her property</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but someone else yeah but but but ethically should it be? if somebody else has made <unclear/></u>
<u n="2028" who="S0190" trans="overlap">so she just well this is what she said it's not mine I didn't take this or nobody warned me of this</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0190">it was all you know fine when we moved in and I think this somebody has done something to unsettle it and so of course she what can I do? nobody's gonna buy it are they? cos no nobody'll take hands put their hands up and say it's our fault we'll sort it nobody'll do it she's got to do it herself it's gonna cost thousands thousands</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0192">it's no good is it?</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0190">it isn't</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0192">never a problem in <trunc>Chi</trunc> Korea and China is phenomenal how many vacant properties there are I mean they don't build properties like we do there's a lot of high rise buildings but China especially they can't they're not allowed to take large sums of money out of the country so rich people within China are investing in property so they're just building new tower blocks everywhere and it's crazy you go there's just literally hundreds and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of massive tower blocks with nobody in them there's no one there and it really got to me in Mokpo because when I was living in Korea there's so few homeless people really are compared to England there's so few I mean the whole of Mokpo I only ever saw one and it was sadder for me because he's alone he he didn't have a community of homeless people it was just him and I look around and see all these vacant flats and think why can't he just have one you know? why why is he I think he died that winter to tell you <unclear>honestly</unclear> cos I never saw him again after that but</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0192">he was like you know shoes are falling he's got string tied around his shoes and stuff kind of guy just hold his sole on to the bottom of his shoe and like he didn't beg no one gave him money or anything like that he just would just walk around town and like just sit in the corner couldn't they don't really have homeless people so when they do have one or two they just slip through nothing there's nothing there to help them</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0190">so how do they survive?</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0192">I he looked like he'd been on the street for a while maybe he moved on maybe he was a bit of a vagrant and moved on but I don't know I don't know how he survived I saw him quite a lot I felt I really wanted because at the time I felt terrible because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I were allotted an apartment each but we only were using one and I had a whole <trunc>sp</trunc> I was so close to just going to the guy but then I was like I'm responsible for this apartment</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0190">mm once in you can't <unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if he goes in there and destroys it you know I can't you know I'm responsible for that but it pained me to see him every day and to think there are so many places where you could put a roof over your head</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0190">but why was he homeless?</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0192">I don't know</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0190">this is the thing isn't it? you've got to look at the overall picture and think you know some people genuinely need the help to sort themselves out to do this</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0190">and others have put themselves in the position themselves</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0192">I mean it wouldn't be I mean in England we have a problem like people take drugs or something and we think you know you've got there that's your problem you've done it it wouldn't have been that in Korea you don't have access to them they just aren't there so it wouldn't have been drugs could have been alcohol I guess which is a drug erm but he didn't really look like an alcoholic I don't know he struck me as like the type of person who just had no family and they're very family oriented</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0192">and I feel like if you have no family you're just on your own I don't know if you they don't really talk to people you can't really have friends with people that aren't your age either which is very strange so the usually people's best friends are the same age as them and usually the same sex so if he if he just didn't know anyone just had no family <event desc="sound of phone"/> I just I don't know</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
