<text id="SW6K">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:59:07</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-05-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0012 S0013 S0419</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Freelancer's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cars, obsessive compulsive disorders, religion, family, accidents, books, workmates, own space, helping others</topics>
		<activity>Brother visit</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0012">
				<exactage>70</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessey, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mattishal, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0013">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow, Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Childminder (retired)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0419">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessy</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>65 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0419">car passed the MOT</u>
<u n="2" who="S0012">that passed it? oh brilliant</u>
<u n="3" who="S0419">yeah cor that'd have been a nightmare that have I've had I've been doing it since Saturday I think</u>
<u n="4" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0419">yeah and I went even down the old bank holiday Monday and er that was the the what they what we used to call a fan belt and they call an auxiliary erm drive belt</u>
<u n="6" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="7" who="S0419">because that don't just drive well it don't drive the fan any more because</u>
<u n="8" who="S0012">no that doesn't</u>
<u n="9" who="S0419">there's no fan cos er that's an electric fan and that's not driven off the engine</u>
<u n="10" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0419">and erm that go round the air conditioning pump that go round the crank</u>
<u n="12" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh yeah that's right</u>
<u n="13" who="S0419">that go round the power steering and that go <unclear/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0419">and they go and that goes round two one tensioner pulley and then another adjusting pulley</u>
<u n="16" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0419">and that go round in that's a jigsaw puzzle really to figure out and you haven't got the room cos the belt is wider than the gap</u>
<u n="18" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh yeah to get it into</u>
<u n="19" who="S0419">and the side of the inner wing so you have to twist it to get it in and then you got to make sure that run how that supposed to run</u>
<u n="20" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0419">I have to replace it</u>
<u n="22" who="S0012"><unclear>replace</unclear> time chain that run the time</u>
<u n="23" who="S0419">there ain't no time chain there time belt that's the separate one that</u>
<u n="24" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah it's a separate</u>
<u n="25" who="S0419">that's another one inside</u>
<u n="26" who="S0012">that's another one yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0419">but the problem was the belt went and that was getting worse and worse cos that was chafing off and moving over cos they run in them little</u>
<u n="28" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah they do yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0419">thin grooves</u>
<u n="30" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0419">an old groove so I erm what did I do? yeah what happened what caused it was a chip in the <unclear>eyelet</unclear> in the tension pulley there is a chip out of it</u>
<u n="32" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0419">cos they made of some I don't suppose that's plastic similar to plastic material than the actual pulley and that bit of chip came off it and and then that <trunc>go</trunc> cut the belt and as the belt go over it that cuts more and more doesn't it?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0419">so basically you end up with no belt so I had to get another tensioner pulley sixty-one pounds and twenty P and erm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0012">couldn't you get one up the yard?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0419">well</u>
<u n="38" who="S0012">must be <unclear/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0419">you get getting half and if that's any good</u>
<u n="40" who="S0012">that's true that is true if that's no good then</u>
<u n="41" who="S0419">you cos that's a lot of aggravation to go to but that's a nightmare to to fit</u>
<u n="42" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0419">because for the one reason that go that's got a shoulder on on the pulley</u>
<u n="44" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0419">on the bottom of the pulley and then that go in a recess that shoulder</u>
<u n="46" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0419">well what had happened that had seized into the shoulder so you you <trunc>co</trunc> you couldn't normally you can get on the other vehicle the other pulley you've got a square drive on a three inch no a quarter drive innit?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0012">yeah yeah and you</u>
<u n="49" who="S0419">and you can turn that and then that that'll then push the belt that and push that other pulley up and then you can pin it so that hold up in the air</u>
<u n="50" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0419">but because it was seized in the <unclear>housing</unclear> you couldn't loft it up on there</u>
<u n="52" who="S0012">oh crikey</u>
<u n="53" who="S0419">so in the end I had to take the power steering pump off</u>
<u n="54" who="S0012">what?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0419">the alternator off erm what else something else? er alternator power steering pump and then to get to the the bottom the where that go on to the er there's like a spring heavy duty fairly heavy duty spring</u>
<u n="56" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0419">two erm fittings where bolts go fully</u>
<u n="58" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0419">I had to take the whole erm casting off at the engine <trunc>bla</trunc></u>
<u n="60" who="S0012" trans="overlap">all of the all of those off yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0419">yeah take the whole casting what hold everything</u>
<u n="62" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0419">to get this bit because you have to get it off to get through this hole to to undo this</u>
<u n="64" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0419">this thing to get the the spring out to get the</u>
<u n="66" who="S0012">oh god</u>
<u n="67" who="S0419">so that was a cor that was a nightmare cos you ain't got the right <unclear/> you have the right tools for everything</u>
<u n="68" who="S0012">well you do yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0419">so I I tried to make tools up</u>
<u n="70" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0419">didn't finish it till about five o'clock yesterday</u>
<u n="72" who="S0012">didn't you?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0419">no cos erm I had to cancel the MOT cos I'd got to have an MOT yesterday that was booked for quarter past ten yesterday and I had to cancel it</u>
<u n="74" who="S0012">but that passed you did a good job did you?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0419">yeah yeah I welded and everything and that just a <unclear/> on one track an end has a little bit play in it and there was one bulb out on the rear light but that's got two you know double doubles</u>
<u n="76" who="S0012">yeah so you're okay then that passed?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0419">I'm alright for another year</u>
<u n="78" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well <vocal desc="laugh"/> then you just stick a crack rod in next year will you?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0419">yeah I'll do it yeah put em one on and but I reckon I don't know if that will go another year cos I think got the back end that's there's a bit of corrosion getting there and that's really awkward welding cos that's sort of right where the back suspension rod is</u>
<u n="80" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="81" who="S0419">and that's right above that so</u>
<u n="82" who="S0012">is it? oh</u>
<u n="83" who="S0419">I done a fair bit of welding on one side today</u>
<u n="84" who="S0013">right just got to nip off to the</u>
<u n="85" who="S0012">library</u>
<u n="86" who="S0013">library</u>
<u n="87" who="S0419">I've postponed you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0012">no no no</u>
<u n="89" who="S0013">they're overdue so I've got to go</u>
<u n="90" who="S0012">what you're going to take a book back?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0013">it's only walking up the road</u>
<u n="92" who="S0419">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0012">just up the road luckily</u>
<u n="94" who="S0419">oh that's the er mobile library</u>
<u n="95" who="S0012">yeah the mobile library that's handy that is yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0419" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0013">the erm computer doesn't print from</u>
<u n="98" who="S0012">what again?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0013" trans="overlap">computer it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0012">I'll sort that</u>
<u n="101" who="S0419">what's that wireless?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0419">yeah that do play up sometimes don't they?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah that's easy enough to do cos that's she she'll put it print but that won't print by wi-fi so you just got to change that to wi-fi and then it'll print look I don't know why it won't stay on</u>
<u n="105" who="S0419">no that's weird innit? I don't have a lot of trouble with the wi-fi on on the printer but what I do have if anything gets stood on top of the printer</u>
<u n="106" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0419" trans="overlap">you know we'll put like papers and things and then they get taller and taller</u>
<u n="108" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah they do don't they?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0419">and then that put some sort of pressure on the top of the printer and then that that won't go</u>
<u n="110" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="111" who="S0419">that jam the actual cartridge where that run up and down</u>
<u n="112" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0419">that the the printing head is jammed so you got to open it up</u>
<u n="114" who="S0012">yeah these printers they're they're so cheap but the ink the ink is dearer than gold</u>
<u n="115" who="S0419">yeah yeah dearer than gold is it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0012" trans="overlap">what about that hey? yeah for how much they put in</u>
<u n="117" who="S0419">yeah they don't put a lot in do them cartridges do they?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0012" trans="overlap">they don't put a lot in now you buy a new printer and you just get enough to print off the sheet and then you got to fill it up you got to get refills</u>
<u n="119" who="S0419">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0012">they used to put all the refill in the printer you know?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0419">they got <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you know? they don't now they just put a sample in</u>
<u n="123" who="S0419">that's so they can sell em of a bit cheaper but</u>
<u n="124" who="S0012">yeah but the money they must earn</u>
<u n="125" who="S0419">yeah they must earn a lot of money out of the printing ink I used to print and mark stuff but I don't print so much now</u>
<u n="126" who="S0012">no neither do we</u>
<u n="127" who="S0419">cos I don't know I think that's I think for a couple if I get a colour one I think the black and white one is about ten pound and the colour one is about nineteen or something</u>
<u n="128" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0419">yeah about nineteen quid for a</u>
<u n="130" who="S0012">I think ours are twenty-three quid each</u>
<u n="131" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0012">cos there's coloured ones</u>
<u n="133" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0012">there's three different colours you have to buy them</u>
<u n="135" who="S0419">you got to buy yours individually?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0012">and then there's the the photo black</u>
<u n="137" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0012">and then you have to buy the printing black so if you're printing a photo that's got photo black on it instead of printing black</u>
<u n="139" who="S0419">yes oh</u>
<u n="140" who="S0012">ah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0419">I didn't know that I always put did photos just with my ordinary</u>
<u n="142" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0419" trans="overlap">thing they come out alright</u>
<u n="144" who="S0012">yeah they come out good enough don't they?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0012">so as long as they come out good enough</u>
<u n="147" who="S0419">well they stopped making my printer now that's Kodak as well they don't make em any more</u>
<u n="148" who="S0012">I know cos they yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0419">they don't make em any more <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had his go wrong he had a Kodak one he had to get a different make cos they don't make em any more</u>
<u n="150" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah no they're finished they didn't even do printing now do they? Kodak they they they</u>
<u n="151" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="152" who="S0012">they finished</u>
<u n="153" who="S0419">you can still get the cartridges for em though</u>
<u n="154" who="S0012">can you yeah?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0012">until the sold out</u>
<u n="157" who="S0419">until they yeah probably but you know what the Chinese will do then?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0012">well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0419">they'll make more won't they?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0012">I'll just put that in the sun because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has left it in the cold and that'll never thaw out</u>
<u n="161" who="S0419">oh we got to thaw bread out yeah you're don't thaw it out in the microwave then?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0012">no that'll make it go gooey and soft</u>
<u n="163" who="S0419">yeah it do doesn't it yeah?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0012">we got to have a <unclear/> we got to eat</u>
<u n="165" who="S0419">oh dear</u>
<u n="166" who="S0012">so how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0419">he ain't to bad about the same no change where the OCD is anyway?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0012">is he?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0419">no that's a that's an that's how I I told you I done his bathroom</u>
<u n="170" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0419">didn't I? his toilet and that and then put he's got his own washing machine so that give me little more</u>
<u n="172" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0419">freedom in the kitchen and that cos I used to have all the paper everywhere didn't I?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0012">yeah course you did yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0419" trans="overlap">the kitchen roll covering up everything but yeah he's alright but that just that's not changed I go home I'll go home now and and when I go home they'll be paper hanging over the the the light well I got little light what you if you want to read anything you know</u>
<u n="176" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0419">and the paper hanging over that and then he take my phone out of the holder on the wall cos we got two one for him and one for me and he cover that up with paper and he cover the TV remote up with the paper and where I sit with the paper</u>
<u n="178" who="S0012">does he? oh dear</u>
<u n="179" who="S0419">mm god the amount of kitchen roll that's unbelievable yeah that's all good stuff as well</u>
<u n="180" who="S0012">well he never used to be like that did he?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0419">no no</u>
<u n="182" who="S0012">where did he get him from?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0419">I don't know no cos I know when he was about fourteen and that fifteen that didn't start till he was just turning sixteen I don't know whether that has anything to do with when he used to work at McDonald's cos he didn't like the way some of the youngsters there were not very hygienic on their handwashing and when they went to the toilet and that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0419">so that could have had something to do with it yeah erm but yeah that isn't that's not improved but it's not got</u>
<u n="186" who="S0012">worse</u>
<u n="187" who="S0419">too you know</u>
<u n="188" who="S0012">too much worse</u>
<u n="189" who="S0419">the kitchen roll has always been that's always been the same you know? it's just that's moved from all over the house just into the living room now so it ain't quite so bad erm whereas that used to be all in the kitchen and I couldn't I had to wait while he when he using the <trunc>wash</trunc> the washing machine what I use I had to wait for him to finish</u>
<u n="190" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0419">cos if I went home and then I <trunc>wa</trunc>wanted to go through to the other room I couldn't do till he'd got everything out of the washing machine and then took it up to his bedroom and then I could go past then but then all the kitchen was covered up the floor was all covered with kitchen roll</u>
<u n="192" who="S0012">was it?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0419">yeah and er cor yeah everywhere that was like the house made of kitchen roll</u>
<u n="194" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0012">it must cost you something doesn't it?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0419">that don't he pay for it out of his money</u>
<u n="197" who="S0012">does he? is he still seeing anyone about it?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0419">no they they they don't bother any more</u>
<u n="199" who="S0012">they don't?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0419">they used to come round the clinical nurses but he's had a clinical nurse you know <trunc>me</trunc> a psychiatric nurse</u>
<u n="201" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0419">erm a a psychiatrist and a psychologist</u>
<u n="203" who="S0012">has he yeah they can't get through to him?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0419">no no that's er well like I said before that's to do with the serotonin and that in the brain and</u>
<u n="205" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0419">that's a brain that's a thing in the head</u>
<u n="207" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0419">and you know that's no matter how much you you know that's logic to us but to him that's not logic</u>
<u n="209" who="S0012">course it isn't no no</u>
<u n="210" who="S0419">you know and you can tell him and that that don't mean nothing</u>
<u n="211" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="212" who="S0419">you know they</u>
<u n="213" who="S0012">well the thing is that people have gone to in small doses anyway</u>
<u n="214" who="S0419">yes it's all millions of people all over the world</u>
<u n="215" who="S0012" trans="overlap">if I go outside for instance don't matter whether they touch anything or not if I go outside when I come indoors I have to wash my hands</u>
<u n="216" who="S0419">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0012">have to otherwise you know I feel</u>
<u n="218" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0012">dirty if you know what I mean so I can understand everything really <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were quite similar</u>
<u n="220" who="S0419">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would clean up everything and when he came home from work when he was married to er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0012">he was married to her he'd go round and he'd touch stuff and see if that's mucky</u>
<u n="224" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0012">you know he he was a bit like that yeah a bit over the top with her of course they used to smoke then anyway so I can't the sense</u>
<u n="226" who="S0419">no no if you smoke that's</u>
<u n="227" who="S0012">and<anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if you remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she was almost as bad so cos she would I mean if she had to be be ready she'd be she'd be ages and ages in the bathroom and stuff and she'd be and and cleaning up all the time you know so must run in our sort of family</u>
<u n="228" who="S0419" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah yeah mm well that that that's surprising even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his wife go at it as well</u>
<u n="229" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0419">yeah she she she used to be on the way to getting bad but he caught her or he forced her to get it seen to before that went too far you know?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0419">so she she control it a lot more than she used to pull the curtains about so many times and wash her hands till they like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to</u>
<u n="233" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0419">he don't do that he just wear plastic gloves all the time</u>
<u n="235" who="S0012">did he?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0419">yeah he buy boxes of gloves</u>
<u n="237" who="S0012">what latex ones? or</u>
<u n="238" who="S0419">yeah Sainsbury's they have box of gloves he'll buy a couple of boxes of them and then sometimes he run out everything he have to put glove on gloves on for erm but yeah he's er</u>
<u n="239" who="S0012">well it's better than covering stuff up then?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0419">yeah and that's <trunc>be</trunc> well like he still covers stuff up as well</u>
<u n="241" who="S0012">that's better for you though</u>
<u n="242" who="S0419">but he he yeah he used to wash his hands so much they'd all</u>
<u n="243" who="S0012">get sore and</u>
<u n="244" who="S0419">go red they were like red and crack open and that</u>
<u n="245" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0419">but now cos he wear the gloves and that they you don't er they're not quite so bad as they used to be</u>
<u n="247" who="S0012">I couldn't well I mean I do feel awful to him but that must be fairly hard for you to put up with all the time innit?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0419">yeah you work round it people do say that but you get in a system you know you get used to you know erm you just sort of work around him you know you get used to he know he trusts me if his mum come round to see him he don't trust her he watch where she got what she touch and if he thinks she's touched something he'll he'll either not use it again or spend ages cleaning or something</u>
<u n="249" who="S0012">right</u>
<u n="250" who="S0419">but if she come round I try and be there now so</u>
<u n="251" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0419">I make the tea and I got in the kitchen and she all she had to do is if she want to go to the toilet or something she that's it you know he's <trunc>ha</trunc> cos he locks his bedroom I had to put a lock on his bedroom door</u>
<u n="253" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0419">lock on the toilet bathroom door toilet what I done for him lock on that so he makes sure they're all locked up</u>
<u n="255" who="S0012">so no one else uses em</u>
<u n="256" who="S0419">so nobody else can go in there and that and touch his stuff but he trusts me you know you leave his milk in the fridge cos he say he always say I trust dad cos he cos we I know how he works you see? so I work round to keep him happy I don't touch his stuff</u>
<u n="257" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="258" who="S0419">you know and I avoid it and if I'm <trunc>in</trunc> unsure or anything I'll ask him</u>
<u n="259" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0419">you know whereas his mum if she come round she don't think cos she ain't living with it all the time</u>
<u n="261" who="S0012">well course she isn't no</u>
<u n="262" who="S0419">she's just <trunc>nor</trunc> you know just do thing <trunc>no</trunc> how you normally would do</u>
<u n="263" who="S0012">does she know she he's got that does she?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0419">oh yeah she knows yeah she knows he's got it but yeah I just work round it now I just</u>
<u n="265" who="S0012">did she get married yet?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0419">no she's with he's alright this one but she did go off with some weirdy ones didn't she?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0419">you know when she went off with the em that druggy bloke didn't she?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0419">and then I thought they'd took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to a brawl or something but now she's sort of levelled her head out now so she she's you know cos her mum was a bit</u>
<u n="271" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0419">she's been in <anon type="place"/> and and <anon type="place"/> and that and I think that was in in her side of the family and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like that she got like that didn't she?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0419">and that's probably where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> get a little of it from</u>
<u n="275" who="S0012">probably yeah there's no telling is there</u>
<u n="276" who="S0419">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> now she's back to normal</u>
<u n="277" who="S0012">is she?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0419">yeah she yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0012">you see her still do you?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0419">only when she come round to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on a Friday she come round and see him</u>
<u n="281" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0419">yeah she's er the bloke she's with now he's alright</u>
<u n="283" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0419">yeah he's decent sort of you know he ain't one of these</u>
<u n="285" who="S0012">weirdys</u>
<u n="286" who="S0419"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well he yeah he's alright <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but yeah so that's what we do we work round things</u>
<u n="287" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0419">that's all you can do you can't do nothing else can you?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="290" who="S0419">the the <trunc>pe</trunc> the nurses or the the cos he's obsessed with religion as well and he's got an obsessive about religion which he's taught me a lot about religion because you know we're brought up we're <trunc>chr</trunc> brought up Christian religion but and I used to get oh give it a rest <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stop you know cos he went on and on</u>
<u n="291" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0419">but the stuff he's learnt and people don't realise you know all about what's in the how the Bible is written</u>
<u n="293" who="S0012">that's right</u>
<u n="294" who="S0419">he said that's that's an insult to your intelligence cos the god in there god is telling people to kill people</u>
<u n="295" who="S0012">yeah what in <trunc>we</trunc></u>
<u n="296" who="S0419">what people <unclear/> this that and the other and they're supposed to be</u>
<u n="297" who="S0012">all loving</u>
<u n="298" who="S0419">benevolent and and and that and he says for the hypocrisy and er and that's right and some of the stuff he get in his head the words he come out cos him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> get talk talking about it you know and I I keep l keep in the middle you know and er cor he he take in on board and these big words what he come out with what he's learnt all about it he he could he could tie someone up in knots in a in a religious argument about things</u>
<u n="299" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah oh that would be good</u>
<u n="300" who="S0419">because he's got an <trunc>an</trunc> he's got the answers</u>
<u n="301" who="S0012">answers yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0419">he's got the answers cos he talk with people over the internet on his Xbox</u>
<u n="303" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0419">yeah he <trunc>ta</trunc> he don't talk he does instant messages</u>
<u n="305" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="306" who="S0419" trans="overlap">erm and he get people from America and that and some of them are hard line Christians or whatever or whatever religion they are</u>
<u n="307" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0419">they're all got their beliefs and and he he he'll tell em you know they'll say well your god will say do this and then it's give me a reason to why you believe that's okay</u>
<u n="309" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0419">doing this and they can't they can't there's no really you can't give a credible reason why it's okay to to go and kill children and</u>
<u n="311" who="S0012">no you can't I mean this was the whole point about religion that's the only well I should think that's just about the only excuse that people have had to kill each other</u>
<u n="312" who="S0419">yeah that causes world wars than</u>
<u n="313" who="S0012">it's caused more wars than anything else</u>
<u n="314" who="S0419">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0012">I think Jesus he said I mean I'm not religious I'm just quoting</u>
<u n="316" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0012">Jesus said there'd be a war in this <trunc>w</trunc> in this world going on every twenty-five years and that would never stop and there is you get you you look anywhere in the world anywhere</u>
<u n="318" who="S0419">there's always fighting</u>
<u n="319" who="S0012">there's fighting all over the place isn't there?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0419">that's that's mostly other religion</u>
<u n="321" who="S0012">all over religion</u>
<u n="322" who="S0419">or greed</u>
<u n="323" who="S0012">yeah greed</u>
<u n="324" who="S0419" trans="overlap">some some of it is greed in smaller</u>
<u n="325" who="S0012">well if you talk about the yanks that's greed</u>
<u n="326" who="S0419">yeah yeah <event desc="sound of knocking"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0012">god knows who that is</u>
<u n="328" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0012">I'm a coming can't find the key hallo</u>
<u n="330" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0012">oh thank you very much</u>
<u n="332" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">thank you kindly <unclear/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0012">all the best thank oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's had something sent from from China</u>
<u n="334" who="S0419">oh I thought well</u>
<u n="335" who="S0012">that's not for us that's that's a present for her I think</u>
<u n="336" who="S0419">oh right</u>
<u n="337" who="S0012">that's something from China anyway</u>
<u n="338" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0012">well he's late he had to come back</u>
<u n="340" who="S0419">our come round about twenty past eleven usually ten to eleven or something</u>
<u n="341" who="S0012">they yeah they usually come to hear about between ten and eleven</u>
<u n="342" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0012">and he missed it he forgot it</u>
<u n="344" who="S0419">oh so he come back</u>
<u n="345" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he had to come back that's nice of him innit?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0419">yeah I'm lucky cos if we getting anything off Royal Mail that's only <trunc>o</trunc> <unclear/> there around the place</u>
<u n="347" who="S0012">yeah that's it yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0419">he ain't got far to go he'll put the things through the door</u>
<u n="349" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0419">I had some stuff come for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> once some stuff slippers and that so I ordered them off Amazon erm cos he wanted to get some from Next cos he got last lot of slippers he got</u>
<u n="351" who="S0012">oh I see right</u>
<u n="352" who="S0419">the good ones he got was from Next and they were good and they and then he started getting ones from supermarkets and they're useless things they are</u>
<u n="353" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right they all fall to bits in two minutes don't they?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0419">so I said well I haven't got an account with Next but I you know I used Paypal</u>
<u n="355" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0419">and I got Ebay and and Amazon I said I I'll have a look on Amazon Ebay Ebay didn't have nothing then I looked on Amazon and Amazon had Dunlop</u>
<u n="357" who="S0012">oh lovely yeah that's where I got my shoes from</u>
<u n="358" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0012">where I bought my boots</u>
<u n="360" who="S0419">so I thought well that'll be alright wasn't it?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0419">and then there's a pair of trainers he was been looking for for years</u>
<u n="363" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0419">because Amazon's sort of slightly Americanised and</u>
<u n="365" who="S0012">that is yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0419">the trainers what he see on these American things you couldn't</u>
<u n="367" who="S0012">you can't find them here no</u>
<u n="368" who="S0419">see America but they were on Amazon</u>
<u n="369" who="S0012">really? wow</u>
<u n="370" who="S0419">so he's happy he's got them but like I say when they <trunc>del</trunc>deliver we got new neighbours now and they're they're really good quiet</u>
<u n="371" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0419">they <unclear/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0012">cos you've had some real stinkers didn't you?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> yeah we got good ones both sides now</u>
<u n="375" who="S0012">oh that's brilliant</u>
<u n="376" who="S0419"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on the left cos he had erm he had some heart trouble and that and he eventually kept collapsing up he's only a young bloke</u>
<u n="377" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0419">and he's a good neighbour and he kept collapsing and er cos that were there two storey you know a house</u>
<u n="379" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0419">and er he couldn't get up and down the stairs so in the end they give him another place a bungalow</u>
<u n="381" who="S0012">did they? oh</u>
<u n="382" who="S0419">but now we got these other people they're from London or Essex or something they're really nice</u>
<u n="383" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0419">erm they took the parcels in for me yesterday from Amazon cos they just put a ticket through the door saying I've left it with the neighbour</u>
<u n="385" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0419">but yeah they're good neighbours they're quiet</u>
<u n="387" who="S0012">that's nice innit? cos you've had you've had them</u>
<u n="388" who="S0419">cor them ones with the music that went on for years</u>
<u n="389" who="S0012">yeah it did</u>
<u n="390" who="S0419">that just</u>
<u n="391" who="S0012">that drove you nearly mad didn't it?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0419">yeah nearly had a nervous breakdown now even now I can't stand that dum dum dum</u>
<u n="393" who="S0012" trans="overlap">dum dum dum yeah you get that all the time</u>
<u n="394" who="S0419">really annoying</u>
<u n="395" who="S0012">were they there?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0013">yes that was there that bloke who <trunc>re</trunc> used to be with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0012">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0013">yeah they've got a <unclear>chat</unclear> whether there's going to be books in ten years time any books coming out?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0012">well I reckon there might be</u>
<u n="400" who="S0013">the way electronics is going</u>
<u n="401" who="S0419">oh yeah what with e-reading</u>
<u n="402" who="S0013">you can get download on your Kindle</u>
<u n="403" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0013">straight from the library now</u>
<u n="405" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0012">can you?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0419">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0012">oh dear</u>
<u n="410" who="S0013" trans="overlap">for free</u>
<u n="411" who="S0012">oh crikey we'll have to get a Kindle</u>
<u n="412" who="S0013">well it's not the same as looking through the book is it?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0012">no it's not the same as looking at the book</u>
<u n="414" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="416" who="S0012">no you can leave your you can leave your book and then pick it up again in the <trunc>bookma</trunc> where you put the bookmark and read</u>
<u n="417" who="S0419">mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0012">but er I don't know these Kindles you have to go <vocal desc="misc"/> and get back to the page again</u>
<u n="419" who="S0419">oh yeah tech tech is good isn't it? in certain ways</u>
<u n="420" who="S0012">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0419">but then on the other hand tech is messing up cars big time</u>
<u n="422" who="S0012">oh you're telling me yeah they are</u>
<u n="423" who="S0419">tech is messing up cars because I was telling <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> down the garage there I was <unclear/> but I said I'd rather go and buy an old car now and do it up because at least you can work on it</u>
<u n="424" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0419">now you can't work on them</u>
<u n="426" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="427" who="S0419">you can't you can't change nothing you</u>
<u n="428" who="S0012">no I I</u>
<u n="429" who="S0013">stuff is</u>
<u n="430" who="S0419">even even the new ones you got to plug into a laptop and then you got to have the software to</u>
<u n="431" who="S0012">yeah to to</u>
<u n="432" who="S0419">to do anything</u>
<u n="433" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/> with it now when I had a the old Triumph you could jump inside the engine couldn't you?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0419" trans="overlap">the engine bay yeah yeah you could get round</u>
<u n="435" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and do everything everything you wanted to do you could do with that old Triumph</u>
<u n="436" who="S0419">yeah you could get to things you could get to your bolts</u>
<u n="437" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0419">you could but now they they</u>
<u n="439" who="S0012">you can't do nothing on it</u>
<u n="440" who="S0419">they design it on a computer screen</u>
<u n="441" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0419">with the engine out</u>
<u n="443" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0419">and then they lower the body on to the engine and the running gear</u>
<u n="445" who="S0012">that's it yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0419">and they don't think about the people who have to work on it</u>
<u n="447" who="S0012">no no</u>
<u n="448" who="S0419">that the people I think I told you Christmas that when I see them people when I used to go the GES they had that garage out that way near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0012">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0419">and they now only rent vans cos they done a van rental and the vehicle repairs but see now they only rent the vans out now she say because every year they have to upgrade the software for the computer for each <trunc>in</trunc> each individual car</u>
<u n="451" who="S0012" trans="overlap">individual car yeah yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0419">and then you they they're changing the registration you know to every half year aren't they?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0419">and so that when they do that they even do different modifications and change the actual car</u>
<u n="455" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0419">so you you have to be exactly specific when you want the parts</u>
<u n="457" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0419">and that's all that's all a way of getting you to go to the dealership so they get all the work and charge you phenomenal amounts of money</u>
<u n="459" who="S0012" trans="overlap">get all the work yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0419">to to do the job</u>
<u n="461" who="S0012">well I have the well I know why <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keep going but I mean them he he keeps having to upgrade all his stuff all the time</u>
<u n="462" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="464" who="S0419">now it's <unclear/> an Aldi they took at Aldi in there what had it they it it hit something the headlight right?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0419">six hundred pound for the headlight and that's without the special bulbs what go into them</u>
<u n="467" who="S0012">oh god</u>
<u n="468" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="469" who="S0419">and then he said you got to take half the front off the car to to get to replace it and he say you got to do the same if you have to replace the bulb</u>
<u n="470" who="S0012">even with that little one out there I've got you have to take the</u>
<u n="471" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0012">you know that that Astra I've got out there</u>
<u n="473" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0012">you have to take half the thing away to get a bulb into it</u>
<u n="475" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0012">and that takes you ages innit?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's silly isn't it just to replace the bulb</u>
<u n="479" who="S0419">it's it's crazy</u>
<u n="480" who="S0013" trans="overlap">isn't it?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0012">just to fit the bulb I had to have a a run and that a day day time running lamp no I didn't have any of the tools I had to fit anything</u>
<u n="482" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="483" who="S0012">and I <trunc>we</trunc> I had to take it in for them to be able to do it because I had nothing to do it with</u>
<u n="484" who="S0419">cos there's no <trunc>y</trunc> not only you got AF spanners which is the norm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0419">er er or metric er metric spanners</u>
<u n="487" who="S0012" trans="overlap">metric yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0419">which is now the norm you got torques drive you got star drives you got female star drives male star drives female torques male torques</u>
<u n="489" who="S0012" trans="overlap">male star drives yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0012">that's pathetic innit?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0419">why? that's not necessary you the different ones I haven't one that that there er part I took off that framework</u>
<u n="493" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0419">I took off that had Allen screws and and bolts so why? why?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0012">yeah why change it?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0419">why <trunc>ha</trunc> why not have all Allen screws or all bolts?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0419">why</u>
<u n="499" who="S0012">why don't yeah why?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0419">these people are</u>
<u n="501" who="S0012">they just make it awkward that's just like if anything go wrong with with er them they were telling me down there that this is ages ago now they had these motherboards if you like they pull it out and put a new one in and that costs hundreds of pounds</u>
<u n="502" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0012">it's just like a computer motherboard</u>
<u n="504" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0012">you know? they they can't tell what's wrong with the motherboard because something has gone wrong with it and and that don't the the circuits don't work</u>
<u n="506" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0012">well they can find out that the circuits still work but they can't repair it so they had to take the motherboard out fit another motherboard in and then your motor is okay again but that costs hundreds</u>
<u n="508" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0012">just for the stupid little pretty circuit</u>
<u n="510" who="S0419">yeah I said I say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'd rather had a car what used a little more fuel than all this computerised injection system with all these different electronics</u>
<u n="511" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah cos I bet you pay for it in the end don't you?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0419">well yeah well you do you the phenomenal amount of money they they would charge you</u>
<u n="513" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0419">because you can't do it yourself if you work it out you're probably worse off</u>
<u n="515" who="S0012">you are yeah I mean that little one we got out there you open the bonnet up and go better <unclear>hook</unclear> where do you go? where do you go from here? look for a tool you can't fit anything in it</u>
<u n="516" who="S0419">no everything's covered up now as well?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0012">it's all covered up yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0419">they got big cover over the top</u>
<u n="519" who="S0012">even underneath</u>
<u n="520" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0012">you go underneath to to look at any anything underneath that's</u>
<u n="522" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0012">and that's you got to take half the base away to get to anything on the gearbox or the crank shaft or whatever not the crank shaft but what's that called the one that go from the gearbox to the front end thing</u>
<u n="524" who="S0419">drive shaft</u>
<u n="525" who="S0012">drive shaft yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0419">that's the drive shaft on the front or prop shaft on the back</u>
<u n="527" who="S0012" trans="overlap">on the back yeah prop</u>
<u n="528" who="S0419">oh that's my phone it's getting flat</u>
<u n="529" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="530" who="S0419">technology you see?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0012">yeah yeah technology is useless</u>
<u n="532" who="S0419">I think I'll tell you what they how things are going with vehicles if you were if you had the money and you started to make a more basic vehicle for the <trunc>ce</trunc> <trunc>ce</trunc> you know your average handyman</u>
<u n="533" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0419">who likes to do his own car</u>
<u n="535" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0419">I bet you'd be on a winner because</u>
<u n="537" who="S0012">I bet you would yeah yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0419">because you imagine these people they they buy a car don't they? and then they they probably bought it on <trunc>i</trunc> on HP</u>
<u n="539" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0419">didn't they? and then you're paying the HP and then something go wrong and then you got to turn round and pay hell and all to have it repaired</u>
<u n="541" who="S0012">yeah yeah that's pathetic it's pathetic I mean I can't do anything on the Rover</u>
<u n="542" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="543" who="S0012">do you know I can't even take the wheel off</u>
<u n="544" who="S0419">no?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0012">cos cos that's pathetic isn't it? yeah the the wheel nuts are locked on and I got the lock I can lock them though but the jack that they supply you is this little er wind up jack and I can't use that jack you put it in and er</u>
<u n="547" who="S0419">oh that's not geared down properly</u>
<u n="548" who="S0012">that's not geared down you can't jack jack the wheel up I'd had to have the RSC or the AA in to change a puncture I would I I can't do it I tried jacking it up and and that jack you put the jack in there and that jack the whole side up from the front to the back you put the jack in here and that jacks the whole lot up again</u>
<u n="549" who="S0419" trans="overlap">and that do the same thing they don't just jack individual like they used to</u>
<u n="550" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no and of course the wheel is going down all the time because the suspension</u>
<u n="551" who="S0419">you got to <unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0012">yeah and the and the jack they supply is pathetic absolutely pathetic whereas you go up down the <unclear/> and they just reel it underneath pump it up and that or they put it on</u>
<u n="553" who="S0419">on the car lift</u>
<u n="554" who="S0012">on the car lift and that's it innit?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0419">your wheel's free or they that's getting worse</u>
<u n="556" who="S0012">that can't that won't get better I know</u>
<u n="557" who="S0419">that's getting worse vehicles are getting stupid now and and and why are we still messing around with petrol and diesel engines?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0012">well yeah that's true yeah can you remember years ago when they they er</u>
<u n="559" who="S0013">do you like tomato juice?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0419">tomato juice?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0012">well we always have tomato juice with our dinner but you needn't have it it's only a it's only a little drop of juice for you</u>
<u n="562" who="S0419">yeah I'll try some</u>
<u n="563" who="S0012">you'll try some</u>
<u n="564" who="S0013">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0012">if you don't want it I'll drink it</u>
<u n="566" who="S0013">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0419">oh dear it's been a hard few days</u>
<u n="568" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0419">I've spent time making tools up</u>
<u n="570" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0419">welding cutting I sacrificed one of my little short square drive extensions</u>
<u n="572" who="S0012">oh did you?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0419">to make the square drive to get on the <trunc>na</trunc> on the lever to lever the tensioner</u>
<u n="574" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I know what you mean yeah yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0419">done that and then that was either too short or too long cos that just had to be exactly right and then when that did go that that did fit the hole properly cos I tried it in the other one perfect and in the new one <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0012">right I'll get some sauce out</u>
<u n="577" who="S0419">there were some profanities flying around yesterday</u>
<u n="578" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I bet there was</u>
<u n="579" who="S0419">there was</u>
<u n="580" who="S0012">you said oh bugger damn didn't you?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0419">yes I did oh bugger damn <pause dur="short"/> yes ah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0012"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0013">I don't know chutney?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0012">a bit of sauce if you want</u>
<u n="585" who="S0013">shall we have a bit of chutney</u>
<u n="586" who="S0012">chutney I was looking for yeah I may have thrown this in the bin</u>
<u n="587" who="S0013">there's spicy one and there's</u>
<u n="588" who="S0012">do you like this?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0419">erm yeah I don't have it in the in that though I'll just have my tomatoes</u>
<u n="590" who="S0012">I'll have to have that in</u>
<u n="591" who="S0419">do you?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0419">Worcestershire sauce</u>
<u n="594" who="S0012">I love it I think that's one thing I'm addicted to is Worcestershire sauce</u>
<u n="595" who="S0419">yeah? yeah? Worcestershire sauce</u>
<u n="596" who="S0012">especially Lee and Perrins I don't think anyone else make it like that</u>
<u n="597" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah no no you got to have Lee and Perrins <pause dur="short"/> that's alright innit?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0419">how's your kids? the girls?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0012">well it's all we got yeah never mind we got a parcel from China</u>
<u n="601" who="S0013">oh did we?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0012">from Amazon</u>
<u n="603" who="S0013">did it?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0012">that just now come he he went past the first time he come back then I mean how many poor bloke he come all the way back to give us that parcel</u>
<u n="605" who="S0013">from where?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0012">the postman</u>
<u n="607" who="S0013">oh really?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0013">he forgot it?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0012">he said I missed you first time I'm ever so sorry</u>
<u n="611" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="612" who="S0012">are we going to open it or not?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0013">no I don't think it's for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0012">is it? oh I can't remember what she said it was</u>
<u n="615" who="S0013">you said you said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told you</u>
<u n="616" who="S0012">yeah she said there was a parcel coming</u>
<u n="617" who="S0013">was it big? small?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0012">well I put it in there somewhere?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0419">quite a big one weren't it?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well help yourself brother</u>
<u n="621" who="S0013" trans="overlap">heavy isn't it? it's quite heavy</u>
<u n="622" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0419">are they all alright are they?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0013">yes</u>
<u n="625" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0013">yeah <unclear/> little <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0419">oh is that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s little</u>
<u n="628" who="S0012">no that's er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s that one</u>
<u n="629" who="S0013"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0419">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="631" who="S0012">now there's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there</u>
<u n="632" who="S0013" trans="overlap">we haven't got an up to date one of her no here anyway</u>
<u n="633" who="S0012">he's he's only just over a year</u>
<u n="634" who="S0419">oh yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0013">they're coming over in a couple of months time</u>
<u n="636" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0419">are they?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0013">just for a week holiday</u>
<u n="640" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0013">so that'll be good</u>
<u n="642" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="643" who="S0013">cos she runs everywhere now <pause dur="short"/> she's really funny</u>
<u n="644" who="S0012">she was running about when she was ten months old</u>
<u n="645" who="S0419">yeah?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0012">amazing <pause dur="short"/> and the weird thing is she knows when you're going on Skype <unclear/> on Skype she know you wave to you blow you a kiss doesn't she?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0013">yeah water and tea or?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0012">I think I'll have tea now</u>
<u n="650" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="651" who="S0012">want tea or water?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0013">or both?</u>
<u n="653" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="654" who="S0419">that's a silly question innit?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0012">yeah just tea for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0013">okay</u>
<u n="657" who="S0012">I'll have tea just a tea as well <unclear>or else</unclear> I'll be going to the loo all day</u>
<u n="658" who="S0419">that's a new <unclear/> is it? water and tea <unclear/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0012">no we don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0419">you only drink water? no tea?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0012">I get up in the morning and have half a pint of water</u>
<u n="662" who="S0419">mm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0012">then I'll have a cup of tea at ten o'clock <pause dur="short"/> water at dinner cup tea at three o'clock afternoon and then water at tea time</u>
<u n="664" who="S0419">specific reasons?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0012">not really</u>
<u n="666" who="S0419">no?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0012">I just went on the water for some reason why did I go on to water?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0013">erm I think we decided we were drinking too much tea</u>
<u n="669" who="S0419">you don't drink a lot</u>
<u n="670" who="S0013">every time we have a cup of tea we have a biscuit and we still do</u>
<u n="671" who="S0012">that's right we have to have a biscuit with tea</u>
<u n="672" who="S0013">so we cut down on them</u>
<u n="673" who="S0012">we had</u>
<u n="674" who="S0013">no no we found we were we were having we'd have something to eat and then tea and it just got too much stomach</u>
<u n="675" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0013">was a bit bloated decided to cut out that</u>
<u n="677" who="S0419"><unclear/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0012">and this is why we have only our own bread now because of er the additives they put in the bought bread we only have this bread you see cos erm the amount of soya flour and monosodium glutamate that have</u>
<u n="679" who="S0419">yeah?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0013">so I hope you don't mind seeds in it is it alright?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0419">yeah I like it it's yummy it's lovely bread in comparison to what you buy</u>
<u n="682" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0013">think I'm going to have to do some more <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0012">what do you think of the tomato juice then?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0419">that's alright it's nice yeah that's like cold tomato soup</u>
<u n="686" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="688" who="S0419">I've been down <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> roof I was late starting my car</u>
<u n="689" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0419">you know for MOT because normally I'd do it a couple of weeks before that's due but that had run out today</u>
<u n="691" who="S0012">crikey</u>
<u n="692" who="S0419">yes cos I done you know my er I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> done his bathroom roof</u>
<u n="693" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0419">with asphalt</u>
<u n="695" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0419">well he had <trunc>cla</trunc> or <unclear/> so I put some what do they call it fascia</u>
<u n="697" who="S0012">oh yeah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0419">all put round his bungalow <pause dur="short"/> and they put fascia round the bathroom roof</u>
<u n="699" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0419">and remember we used aluminium patch <unclear/> drippers</u>
<u n="701" who="S0012">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0419">they put the fascia up under the drippers level with the drip edge so the water was just running through</u>
<u n="703" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="704" who="S0419">got in into all the erm chipboard</u>
<u n="705" who="S0012">oh no and that just bow it all</u>
<u n="706" who="S0419">and all like that</u>
<u n="707" who="S0013">oh oh</u>
<u n="708" who="S0419">all bow and split apart cos of the sun</u>
<u n="709" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="710" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0419">that split apart and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I say you need if that come in there's a lot of weight on that</u>
<u n="712" who="S0012">there is yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0419">so what am I going to do? I said well I'll do it for you if you want so that's what I had to do get all the asphalt off I had to replace the ends of the joists</u>
<u n="714" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0419">cos they were all</u>
<u n="716" who="S0012">gone</u>
<u n="717" who="S0419">had to cut them and and join bits all along the joists</u>
<u n="718" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0419">and then I filled the asphalt on the roof instead of chipboard cos that's waterproof innit?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0012">yeah that is yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0419">and then just a nice check-up that side got a check-up there double felted it with the torch on and made proper clip edges</u>
<u n="722" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0419">done it all up so that's what got me behind on the car</u>
<u n="724" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="725" who="S0419">so they were they were pleased</u>
<u n="726" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0419">I'm doing more since I've been retired than what I do when I</u>
<u n="728" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0012">that's what we find innit?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0013">I know can't believe it we don't seem to have any spare time</u>
<u n="731" who="S0012">we don't do we?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0013">I know this is kind of spare time isn't it but?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0012">but we always find there's a lot of work out there</u>
<u n="736" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's really strange</u>
<u n="737" who="S0419">you got a lot a lot of work out there haven't you? hell of a lot I'm surprised you haven't got a ride on mower yet</u>
<u n="738" who="S0012">we got this lovely fella er young lad he lives over over <trunc>s</trunc> over the way</u>
<u n="739" who="S0013">he's fifteen</u>
<u n="740" who="S0012">he's sixteen yeah his father asked me if he could keep a load of wood up here so I said yeah he said you can help yourself to it as well so I said fine so because we got the wood out there young <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he comes along with his tractor and his cutter on the back</u>
<u n="741" who="S0419" trans="overlap">oh right I see</u>
<u n="742" who="S0012">and go all round the field</u>
<u n="743" who="S0419">oh brilliant</u>
<u n="744" who="S0013">yeah yeah he does the field and down the bottom</u>
<u n="745" who="S0012">he does the field all the way down the bottom and</u>
<u n="746" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0012">and I just mow the lawn</u>
<u n="748" who="S0419">oh right</u>
<u n="749" who="S0013">just for keeping his wood</u>
<u n="750" who="S0419">that's worth it that isn't it?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0012" trans="overlap">and then <trunc>s</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0013">brilliant deal</u>
<u n="753" who="S0012">mm I used to mow the lawn with my little little</u>
<u n="754" who="S0419" trans="overlap">I know you did</u>
<u n="755" who="S0012">walk up and down</u>
<u n="756" who="S0419">you done it one day when I come knackers you out doesn't it?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0012">yeah totally knackered me</u>
<u n="758" who="S0419">yeah I remember there's a hell of a lot to cut with a</u>
<u n="759" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="760" who="S0012">well it's a forty-two inch cutter you can imagine the field up and down and up and down I think I'd have I'd put a a pacer thing on I think how do you <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="761" who="S0013" trans="overlap">pedometer</u>
<u n="762" who="S0012">pedometer yeah how many did I have to do? how many did I do?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0013">oh I can't remember now</u>
<u n="764" who="S0012">something like two miles I think something like that</u>
<u n="765" who="S0419">that's surprising innit? I've done up you know the little mower what I used to have over at the house to ride on?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0419">I erm that's right I got some new tyres for it</u>
<u n="768" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0419">off Ebay and I took one wheel off come off lovely went to get the other wheel off that had seized on to the axle so I get it and hit it with a hammer didn't I? tried to break it free from the <unclear/> and penetrate and I tried to break it free I was like oh that's going lovely but</u>
<u n="770" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0419">the whole shaft come out the gearbox</u>
<u n="772" who="S0012">I can imagine that I've done that before</u>
<u n="773" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0419">so it was I tried when I got the shaft out I looked at it and it had a <unclear/> around it that was only a circular <unclear/> on the other end where the gear is and I thought well that that should be alright so I in the end I had to put it in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s press and it went with a hell of a bang about a thousand pound pressure went on it and that went with two big bangs when that so you know how badly the</u>
<u n="776" who="S0012" trans="overlap">wow yeah well</u>
<u n="777" who="S0419">that went hell of a bang when that went</u>
<u n="778" who="S0012" trans="overlap">like a gun going off that is</u>
<u n="779" who="S0419" trans="overlap">he he was pumping away there yeah going or not got it all off cleaned all the shaft up cleaned all the gearbox out cos I you know where there's bits of clip or something in there got all that out put it all back together again nice painted wheels and tyres on I ain't used it yet cos like I I'm just I got the bed off now I'm just cleaning the bed up and just sharpen the blades</u>
<u n="780" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0419">or I got out the end cleaned all the engine down cleaned all the magnet thing</u>
<u n="782" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0419">I forget what they call it now that start first time now you used to have to prime it to start it but now that start first time</u>
<u n="784" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="785" who="S0419">oil change I grassed the field but I ain't had a chance to cut it yet cos I've been doing so many other things so hopefully oh I bought a new saw I <trunc>kno</trunc> I told you I bought one saw I showed you the picture of didn't I?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0419">I brought another one a a table saw</u>
<u n="788" who="S0012">oh right? yeah oh they're nice isn't they lead one is it?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0419">big</u>
<u n="790" who="S0012">you got big? you can cut round about what? ten inches with it? ten-inch high blade?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0419">yeah ten-inch blade and and you can cut I was looking at loads of different ones I was looking at and I needed cos of these sweet carts if I had to do any more of them I needed a two foot span you know?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0419">and I got one what extend out the table extend out</u>
<u n="794" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0419">so you that's a bit more than two foot and you can cut plywood and that</u>
<u n="796" who="S0012">oh absolutely yeah so what you got nice nice cut saw have you?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0419">yeah I got two blades I got a multipurpose one and a rip</u>
<u n="798" who="S0012">oh right yeah I got to get I got to get another blade for mine cos that's this erm big tungsten chip blade</u>
<u n="799" who="S0419">oh them ones yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0012">they just rip holes in everything</u>
<u n="801" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0012">you can't cut plywood with it</u>
<u n="803" who="S0419" trans="overlap">you need no you need a sort of fairly like teeth</u>
<u n="804" who="S0012">yeah very fine blade yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0419">you need a sixty-sixty-five tooth <unclear/></u>
<u n="806" who="S0012">that's it yeah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0419">but yeah I was <trunc>look</trunc> thanks I was looking all the different ones and then I thought well I needed to have that sort of a width of cut</u>
<u n="808" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0419">but I also that's beneficial to have to portal isn't it?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0012">yeah really?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0419">so I bought a site saw a Metabo that is</u>
<u n="812" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="813" who="S0419">yeah a Metabo site saw</u>
<u n="814" who="S0012">I ain't heard of one of them</u>
<u n="815" who="S0419">uh?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0012">I ain't heard of them</u>
<u n="817" who="S0419">if you look on Youtube and go on Metabo site saw that'll show you that they go a</u>
<u n="818" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0419">demo on there</u>
<u n="820" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0419"><unclear/> with er the <unclear/> and it has got wheels</u>
<u n="822" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0419">and if you pull everything is all together you pull it all the legs up and everything and then stand it up</u>
<u n="824" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="825" who="S0419">and that has got all extensions on and this that and the other all sorts of things on it</u>
<u n="826" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="827" who="S0419">and erm lovely thing and then I saw wood for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s roof cos I had to saw some on an angle</u>
<u n="828" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0419">with a I had to replace a couple of joists I think and they had to be at on a angle and saw some other bits and pieces on there but bloody hell all the dust and that what come out you know? and so in the end I got an extractor as well to go on it</u>
<u n="830" who="S0012">oh wow</u>
<u n="831" who="S0419">an industrial one</u>
<u n="832" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0419">yeah and er I got a big old big bag a big bag to go underneath it and then there's a big bag on the top and</u>
<u n="834" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0419">that that plug on to the side of the saw bench and that go on to any machine any tools you can fit it to</u>
<u n="836" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="837" who="S0419">that's a hundred and thirty-eight quid that weren't bad</u>
<u n="838" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="839" who="S0419">for that</u>
<u n="840" who="S0012">where did you get that from?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0419">I got that off the internet</u>
<u n="842" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0419">yeah erm what was it called? er that was er that was one the last one they had couldn't get that make but this particular company that was the last one they had in stock</u>
<u n="844" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="845" who="S0419">erm and you had to put it together that come in a box and</u>
<u n="846" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="847" who="S0419">I was the assembler but that's good don't know if I got pictures on my phone on my saw cos I got em on my laptop but</u>
<u n="848" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0419">I haven't got no pictures of it</u>
<u n="850" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0419">but the saw is brilliant that is a lovely bit of <unclear>click</unclear> you know what Germans are like</u>
<u n="852" who="S0012">oh they're the best yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0419" trans="overlap">they're they're best cos the a lot of the saws I looked at they just had pressed steel tops</u>
<u n="854" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0419">you know bent over pressed steel and and powder coated or whatever this is <trunc>hu</trunc> er cast aluminium</u>
<u n="856" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah you you you can only buy good stuff can't you I mean you've got one of them cheaper ones</u>
<u n="857" who="S0419">yeah I looked at loads</u>
<u n="858" who="S0012">Screwfix do the cheap stuff oh they're useless</u>
<u n="859" who="S0419" trans="overlap">ah them no I got I tried to get that other saw from Screwfix you know that er</u>
<u n="860" who="S0012">yeah slide saw wasn't?</u>
<u n="861" who="S0419">yeah a slide saw yeah that's double barrelled as well so it will go both ways</u>
<u n="862" who="S0012">that's it yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="S0419">and he he's an idiot I'd say well I'd say how much you got? he say the only one we got is the one what's on the demo I say well what are you going to do being the demo that got to be cheaper they don't knock any money off</u>
<u n="864" who="S0012">really?</u>
<u n="865" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="866" who="S0012">well <unclear/> they lost they lost</u>
<u n="867" who="S0419">I got it off the internet</u>
<u n="868" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0419">I ordered it in no time that was there the next day</u>
<u n="870" who="S0012">was it?</u>
<u n="871" who="S0419">mm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0012">brilliant sugar there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0419">that had order by eight eight o'clock on six PM you get the product on midday the next day</u>
<u n="874" who="S0012">yeah? wow</u>
<u n="875" who="S0013">clever innit?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0419">yeah and that was there it come at eleven o'clock in the morning</u>
<u n="877" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="878" who="S0419">if you need your big lathe</u>
<u n="879" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0419">you got it here</u>
<u n="881" who="S0012">you can come and have a look</u>
<u n="882" who="S0419">I'll have a look if that's alright</u>
<u n="883" who="S0012">yeah I got my lathe I got my I got the I got the saw the saw is still there but</u>
<u n="884" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="885" who="S0012">yeah I got big blades for them for that cos the the blade I got is the blade I got is er the <trunc>sol</trunc> he's had it years I think but I got the blade I got the saw bench not the saw bench I got the lathe and a bandsaw</u>
<u n="886" who="S0419">oh you got a bandsaw</u>
<u n="887" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0419">mm you're on up on me</u>
<u n="889" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0419">you got a bandsaw</u>
<u n="891" who="S0012">yeah it's a lovely bandsaw innit?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="893" who="S0419">yeah that's the next thing I sort of thinking about cos they're so handy aren't they to</u>
<u n="894" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="895" who="S0419" trans="overlap">cos I use a <unclear/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well this one has got a really thick blade and that's a heavy duty bandsaw and that you put different blades on</u>
<u n="897" who="S0013">yeah you need to get a new blade</u>
<u n="898" who="S0419" trans="overlap">I got a metal bandsaw</u>
<u n="899" who="S0012">have you? yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0419">for metal yeah</u>
<u n="901" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="902" who="S0419">but now but that did that lift up and you put a table on it</u>
<u n="903" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0419">and then that act like a bandsaw</u>
<u n="905" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="906" who="S0419">you take the table off and then that act like a a bandsaw you know for cutting</u>
<u n="907" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah you got one in that big old shed have you?</u>
<u n="908" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="909" who="S0012">I'll have to come down there and have a look</u>
<u n="910" who="S0419">yeah you should come down</u>
<u n="911" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm about time you went and had a look</u>
<u n="912" who="S0419">time you come down</u>
<u n="913" who="S0012">that is</u>
<u n="914" who="S0419">show you my machine tools</u>
<u n="915" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0419">I made erm a postbox for a you know I made that sweet cart</u>
<u n="917" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0419">I made a postbox I can't <unclear/> I think that's on there that's not a good good picture cos I felted it out with felt inside the postbox</u>
<u n="919" who="S0012">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0419">and that bleed out into the picture so that look like there's felt all you know</u>
<u n="921" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="922" who="S0419"><unclear/> you would be able to get the pictures up that's got to be charged <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="923" who="S0012">where did you get your phone from?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0419">off <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="926" who="S0419">I done a day's work for it</u>
<u n="927" who="S0012">have you?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0419">that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> roof look wait have a look there oh no that ain't it that's a that's a marbler a multi-rotor thing</u>
<u n="929" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="930" who="S0419">what I erm <unclear/> ah so that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="931" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="932" who="S0419">that's <unclear/> down there</u>
<u n="933" who="S0012">oh yeah <unclear/> of em</u>
<u n="934" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="935" who="S0419">you can scroll through all the pictures in there</u>
<u n="936" who="S0013">what's that?</u>
<u n="937" who="S0012">this is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house</u>
<u n="938" who="S0013">oh I couldn't work out that's the that's the top innit?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0419">there's all sorts of pictures in there</u>
<u n="941" who="S0012">well that's at the end isn't it?</u>
<u n="942" who="S0419">yeah and you have probably have to open it to find it it's just there's all pictures in there there's nothing nothing untoward in there</u>
<u n="943" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="944" who="S0419">you're quite safe</u>
<u n="945" who="S0013"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="946" who="S0012">ooh that's sexy that is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what's that an old trough?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0419">what's that?</u>
<u n="948" who="S0013">bit of rust rusty erm</u>
<u n="949" who="S0419">that's a roof</u>
<u n="950" who="S0012">that's their roof is it?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0419">that's a roof</u>
<u n="952" who="S0013">wow</u>
<u n="953" who="S0419">I threw half of it out but look I <unclear/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0013">piped up didn't it?</u>
<u n="955" who="S0012">yeah wow</u>
<u n="956" who="S0013">oh you can open it</u>
<u n="957" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh it'll come through as well</u>
<u n="958" who="S0419">mm</u>
<u n="959" who="S0013">what's that?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0012">it's the garden</u>
<u n="961" who="S0013">the garden back garden? is that your garden?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0419"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably</u>
<u n="963" who="S0013">mm?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0419"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s garden I reckon</u>
<u n="965" who="S0012">with his shed in the bottom what's he got two?</u>
<u n="966" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm they look like</u>
<u n="967" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="968" who="S0012">got two fences on that</u>
<u n="969" who="S0419">yeah he's got</u>
<u n="970" who="S0012">and that's his roof is it?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0013">mm oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="972" who="S0012">that's all the roof</u>
<u n="973" who="S0013">I can see it now</u>
<u n="974" who="S0012">that's all the roof he's doing look at that bit took all the bits off how is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="975" who="S0419">he ain't too bad <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> weren't too well this week but <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0012">wow that's a lot of work on the roof wasn't?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="978" who="S0012">whoops</u>
<u n="979" who="S0013">you got a big</u>
<u n="980" who="S0012">oh that's</u>
<u n="981" who="S0013">did you get the <unclear/></u>
<u n="982" who="S0419">I don't know if you can squeeze it</u>
<u n="983" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0419">or open em out think they're meant to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0012">alright <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="987" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="988" who="S0012">that's as far as that go anyway I think oh look there's</u>
<u n="989" who="S0013">oh we're going to look for the postbox</u>
<u n="990" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="long"/> cor he's done a lot of work on that roof there</u>
<u n="991" who="S0013">mm mm did it take you a long time?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0419">er about a week</u>
<u n="993" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="994" who="S0012">all this</u>
<u n="995" who="S0013">oh here comes the roof sheets</u>
<u n="996" who="S0012">he's planted into the sheet before the <unclear/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0419">lead twist into the gutter as well</u>
<u n="999" who="S0013">yeah I saw that yeah and look at that that's the finished finished job there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1000" who="S0013">mm yeah very good</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0419">mm</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0012">it's a nice boot</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0012">nice boot <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0419">oh yeah that's my boot yeah yeah I got to get myself in on the action</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0012">well of course</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0419">it's a selfie</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0012">that's a selfie</u>
<u n="1010" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0013">I don't understand how you take selfies</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0012">you go like that</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0419">you can get a selfie stick what pull what hold the phone</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0013" trans="overlap">turns it round</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0419">yeah you well a selfie you know that</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0013">but people people look at them and say here you are?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0419">yeah but that phone you can take a picture of yourself if you press the one of the icons that will reverse the lens so that take picture you can see yourself and what you're taking</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0012">well you've got your registered he's got his he's got his registered number here look photograph done oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1022" who="S0012">now something's happened again oh here we go what's going on here have I gone wrong up there</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0013">I think it's come to the end innit?</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0013">we didn't find the <trunc>p</trunc>postbox</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0419">yeah well perhaps I</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0013">no go the other way</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0012">that's all at the end <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh no it's something's gone wrong</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no it's not</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0419">that's just run out of juice cos that's getting flat and</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0013">oh no</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0012">oh there we go</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0013">there you go</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0012">we got it again</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0013">auto ready deflection <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0012">ooh</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0013">ladders and all sorts</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0419">oh that's a a scaffold what we've got to use now we're not allowed to use stepladders any more</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0419">we have to use a podium stand</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0419">and that ain't big enough</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0013" trans="overlap">not even by yourself?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0419">no we've got to use we've got to use a podium we're not allowed to use stepladders although we've been using them for six years we're not allowed to use them any more</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0013">my goodness never seen one of them</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0012">what's that there?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0013">that what it is?</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0419">yeah that's the podium <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> modified put them legs on on there what you can adjust he made it all all there</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0012">did he? of well done well done <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0013">that's a podium right?</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0012">that's a lovely ladder though</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0419">that go up in three stages that's the lowest point there I think</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0419">apart from when that's right collapsed flat</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0012">yeah crikey</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0013">how many pictures have you got on here</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0419">I've just taken them <pause dur="long"/> actually now I come to think I think the postbox in on the other phone</u>
<u n="1060" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1061" who="S0012">what's that there?</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you clicked on it</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0419">you can go back don't don't get well that that's the they're the last pictures what you're on that's my window</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0013">is it?</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0419">that's my wind up window thing in the car I had to replace</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0419">I had to order a couple off the internet a couple of them</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0419">I ordered a spare cos they break</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0012">stupid thing oh you got</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0013">you take pictures of everything</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0012">well he's got to know how it works</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0419" trans="overlap">well I take for reference</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0419">for reference sometimes I take photographs of like yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0013" trans="overlap">like we do when we do light fittings</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but anything I take reference of now</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0012">cor we all one of them lights up up there</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0012">what a job they were we took photographs of the</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0419" trans="overlap">lights yeah the wire</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0012">the wire</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah where to put it yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0419">that's so much easier than doing a drawing and writing the colours down and you</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yes that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0419" trans="overlap">just click and away I do that with cars and everything</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0012">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0419">yeah that's not there is that I forgot I got this phone now and that's on the other HTC phone</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0419">I got a new er screen saver to go this they put a glass one before what they call hardened but I ain't put it in yet because of all all the trouble with my eye I couldn't see what to do</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah he got something in his eye and had to go to hospital</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0013">what?</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0012">the only eye he's got he got a load of muck in it</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0013">oh no</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0419">yeah when I was welding the car I had my <trunc>y</trunc> goggles my glasses on</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0419">and that went over the too</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0013">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0419">two bits of it hit and er you could in the casualty he managed to get one bit out but I had to go back in the afternoon to the eye unit</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0013" trans="overlap">when is it this afternoon then?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0419">no no this was</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0419">not last week the week before</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0012">and I sat at casualty for four hours</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0013">have they sorted it now?</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0012">yeah he got it out in and I had to go back the bloke in the morning got one bit out but he couldn't get the other bit he said you'll have to go to the eye clinic and I had to do that</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0419">and that was embedded on well that had burnt onto the eye</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0013">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0419">and so</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0013">that must have been painful</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0419">yeah that were painful but that's more inconvenient cos you can't see where you're going everything's double vision and that</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0419">and er when I cos I left it a couple of days thinking that was going to work out</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0419">and I was watching the TV and then all the white writing was two lots and people had four eyes you know they had another set of eyes underneath</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0419">I ain't hundred per cent yet you know I'm still a bit blurry they've given me a cream and that</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0419">but that's that's better than it was but that chap in the casualty he put that er some more he done put some stuff in to numb it he got one bit out and then he tried to get the other bit he put a different coloured stuff in</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0419">and that was I couldn't even find my way out of the casualty I I had to ask the porter to cos I couldn't even see the what way to go</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0012">oh god</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0012">you drive home?</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0419">yes I did erm I I managed to see</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0013" trans="overlap">gosh you shouldn't have done that</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0419">yeah I knew I didn't have far to go off the off the main road there's only a short bit of main road and then I was on to my little er back of the estate you see where they're all little quiet roads but</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0419">and I was extra really careful anyway I could see but that's like having</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0419">tinted sunglasses on</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0013">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0419">yellow tinted sunglasses</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0419">so it was like looking through yellow tinted sunglasses</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0419">so I could see you know I enough to drive alright but obviously the afternoon I got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to take me up there and</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0419">and pick me up I phoned him up I said can you can you take me up the hospital cos they've got to get the other bit of stuff out yeah course I will</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0419">so he driven me up and drop me off</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0419">and cos that was in emergency he went back home again you see he thought I'd be hanging about but I went in I went to the reception told em and er the nurse come out first she say loads of people in there I go in a nurse come out she said called my name out I went in and er she just done the eye test and asked me this that and the other and she said go outside just sit on the red chairs she say cos they're emergency she said you should be seen soon so I only just sat down and then they come out and called me</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0012">brilliant</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0419">and er and they got it out he just put a couple of lots of numb stuff in it</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0419">and then I and then they got it out just like that and they gave me the well they give me the cream in the <unclear/> and I phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well poor bugger had only just got home</u>
<u n="1157" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1158" who="S0419">he then he then got in the car and walked in and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said oh you got to go back he's he's done</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0012">I bet he</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0419">and I kept</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0012">I can imagine what he said</u>
<u n="1162" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1163" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1164" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1165" who="S0419">and er and I was looking cos that was raining like everything and I was looking out in the lobby to see his car and they were doing roadwork's down the road what lead to the hospital</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0419">and then he made a short cut round that round</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0012">oh god</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0419">about there and the buses can't go and the taxi's so if you're in a taxi and that meters in going and you're ready to go</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0419">and erm I couldn't see his car cos they'd put that stuff in and I stood and then and that was raining outside so I in the end I went outside and stood there under a bit of this thing and I was looking at all these cars were coming down and I couldn't recognise it cos of all the stuff they'd put in my eye and</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0419">then I see he flashed his light cos he could see me standing there and then I thought well that might be flashing to some other people who were standing there so I walked up the path sideways on and I see and he's I got in</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0012" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0013">right yeah</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0419">but oh that reminds me er I got to say hello to you from the lady up the hospital who I see prior to this</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0419">yeah she said oh are you related to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0013">oh was it</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0419">in <anon type="place"/>? I saw yeah</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0013">was she Malaysian?</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0419">yeah she said they used to look after my daughter</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0012">that's it that was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1185" who="S0013"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1186" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1187" who="S0419">yeah she say they used to look after my daughter</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0419">so tell them I said hello when you see him I said I'll probably see them shortly</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0419">I have to go go up the hospital though cos I got a floater in the eye as well</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0012">so have I <pause dur="short"/> in this one</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0419">you think how did you get that one there?</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0012">right right that get in the way sometimes</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0419">do it?</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0012">sometimes that</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0419" trans="overlap">I I'm lucky mine's sort of over the left there but I was a bit concerned cos that I I get up one morning couldn't <unclear/> get up the next day got up one morning <pause dur="short"/> what the hell is that?</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1201" who="S0419">something flying</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0012">mine's a tadpole</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0419">is it? yeah I got two little things there</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they're going to do them are they?</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0419" trans="overlap">no I just went up to get it checked out cos I'm</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0419">like went to the optician first <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said you ought to go to the doctors waste of time they are doctors so I go went to my optician</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0419">and I cos he go he's really thorough</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0419">oh and he say yeah he say but what I'm going to do is write you a letter just being as you only got one eye I'm going to just get them to double check so he says I'll write them a letter he said you give that to your doctor so I only had to give it to the receptionist then I had to wait a few weeks to get an appointment there and that's when I went up to see about that and that's she was the nurse who come out first</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0419">and so yeah she looked you haven't know any people live at <anon type="place"/> have you? I said yeah she said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I said yeah</u>
<u n="1214" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1215" who="S0013">yeah she's she's lovely</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0012">she was a <trunc>lo</trunc> she was a lovely lass</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0419">yes</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0013">she actually bought all the ingredients and came here and cooked</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0419">did she yeah?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0013">cooked us up a Chinese</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0012">a Chinese in in a wok</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0419" trans="overlap">I bet that was good wasn't</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0012">in a wok oh that was brilliant</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah brilliant and to see her do it you know</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0012">yeah to see what she did</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0012">she was wonderful yeah</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0013" trans="overlap">an erm</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0012">yeah lovely woman</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0419" trans="overlap">really nice person innit?</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0012">really lovely person</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0012">she married this bloke he's a scaffolder</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0419">yeah?</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0012">yeah I don't know whether he's still about I don't seen him any more</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0012">he's got his own scaffolding company</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0419">yeah?</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0012">and er they had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1242" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0012">wasn't? was it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1246" who="S0013"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I thought it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1248" who="S0013">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was the boy and</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0013"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was the little girl</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was the girl</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0419">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0013">but she she was a joy to look after she was</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0419">yeah she said you used to look after her</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I can see her now the beaming face all the time</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0013">wasn't she?</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0012">oh that's nice</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0013">yeah that's nice</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0419">yeah she said say say hello to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and<anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when you see them for me?</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I'd love to see them again</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0419">I say alright I will and that now remind me cos I would have forgot if we hadn't have been talking about eyes and hospitals and that by that</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0012" trans="overlap">eyeballs yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0419">and I had to go and <unclear/> but I did mean to I thought of that this morning I thought I must remember that</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0012">I was supposed to go up the hospital Monday well they're shut aren't they?</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0419">what the hospital? they don't close do they?</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well they're not shut but that's <pause dur="short"/> I er mashed my finger in a planer</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0419">no?</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I had my planer on and went to put it away and put my hand right on the planer</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0419">ah</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0012">and that that just</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0013">luckily it had it was was off</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0012">it was off at the time but it was slowing down</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1276" who="S0419">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0012">and that was still going <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1278" who="S0013" trans="overlap">good job it wasn't still going</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0012">put my finger on it then and I put well it mashed it rather than</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah well that would wouldn't it? cos that's not going at the right</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1282" who="S0419">if that had been on full speed that would have just</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0012">that would have just slipped a lump off but this</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0419" trans="overlap">but because that was slowing down</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0013">oh I see yeah <unclear/> think</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that mashed it I couldn't find the bit that because it that</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0013">I think it would be worse if you</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0012" trans="overlap">took the whole skin off and just <trunc>le</trunc> left proud flesh type stuff poking out and you did it up for me didn't you?</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0012">round about like this</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0013">we're lucky it didn't get down to the bone it was only the top</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0012" trans="overlap">wandering about this I was and she was following me</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0419" trans="overlap">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1294" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1295" who="S0013">all your nerves are there aren't they?</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0012">and god the pain the pain was colossal and anyway I come in and I run it for about five minutes under the cold water but that wouldn't stop bleeding would it?</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0013">stand it up didn't you?</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0012">and I held held it up like that well I kneeled on the floor while <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1299" who="S0013">stop him falling over</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0012">while <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did it you see</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1302" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1303" who="S0012">and then she did it all up and that was lovely and that was fine and then I had I thought well Monday or <trunc>Su</trunc> you can't do anything Monday and I'll go all the way to A and E and all of that ah I can't handle all that so</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0013">well we didn't really think it we I</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0012">well</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0013">you weren't sure</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0012">I didn't want to go to hospital anyway I didn't want to do it</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0419">that's a long wait isn't it?</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0012">so I went to the doctor's yesterday was it yesterday?</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0012">yeah yesterday went in to see the nurse cos I asked to see a nurse she took a look why didn't you go to the hospital she said I said well I didn't want didn't want to worry the nurses on a on a bank holiday Monday</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0419" trans="overlap">bank holiday</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0012">that's not fair on 'm oh she said oh dear let's see what we can do with it she took it all off and that was like cos we'd done it right up she said I know what it's going to be like before I even look at it cos</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0419">the air don't get in</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0012">the air don't get to it she said that'll be all mashy and horrible</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0012">and when she took the dressing off it was all mashy and horrible that was</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0012">and er this is a breathable one I got to go up again Friday innit?</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0012">Friday</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0012">to have it done again</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0012">but talk about pain</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0419">mm</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0012">that was I mean right in your index finger</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0419">well you're sensitive there aren't you in your fingers</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0012" trans="overlap">really sensitive in your fingers aren't you?</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0419">I cut my finger off there</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0419">that one didn't I?</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0012">yeah you did yeah</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0419">cut that one off that was <trunc>sc</trunc> I did scream like a <unclear/> on my engine</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0013" trans="overlap">did you have it stitched?</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0419">yeah that this bit this bit here that hung down here at a right angle</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh dear ah</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0419">cos I dropped the tail board I I when I was using a lathe</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0419">and and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a step on his pick up and that had a razor-sharp edge</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0419">and and I had this mattress on the back of the tailboard and that was pressed up against the tailboard well I released one of the butterflies and I had my hand down there like that</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0419">and I released the other one and table went</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0012" trans="overlap">bang</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0419">bang</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0419">and then I picked it up and my finger was hanging down there just on a little</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0419">but you you can see where the nail's grown funny look</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0013">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0419">it's different size to that one</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0013">oh it is totally</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1359" who="S0419">and they and and the <trunc>beau</trunc> best part of it was you'd go I'd get in the ambulance and I phone <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> first I said take take us up the hospital and he wanted to call a bleeding ambulance for that cos I was holding it together and he phoned and ambulance didn't he? and they come didn't they?</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0419">and er I say oh you I go oh <unclear/> like that I was like you shouldn't have phoned that's alright that's alright don't worry he said they so he said let's have a look so he he oh yeah that's quite bad</u>
<u n="1362" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1363" who="S0419">yes and then and then I got up the hospital didn't I? and then you see nurse don't you? and she said oh we'll just have a look</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0013">er</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0419">she said oh yeah that's quite nasty isn't it? what she say I bet you swallowed it? and I said well there was one or two one or two words coming and then put it back again and then a doctor come says we'll just have a look again and he put that back he said I'll just better see plastics and get that right</u>
<u n="1366" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1367" who="S0012">we'll just have a look as well</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0419">and then he come and then in the end the plastic surgeon you should be alright to <trunc>da</trunc> stitch clean it and stitch it all up but so he said I'll I'll give you an injection well they inject into the meat</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0419">they gone into the bare meat</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0012">oh god</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0419">they don't go into the side they go where the they open it up and they inject it in there and they got an emergency in</u>
<u n="1373" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1374" who="S0419">and off he go and I sit there waiting and waiting and ages I think that must have been over an hour</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0419">yeah sitting there waiting and waiting when he come back the numbness had gone hadn't it?</u>
<u n="1378" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1379" who="S0419">and I thought well I ain't going to wait here and so I had to use a little bit of mind over matter I was looking at the curtains what were around the thing and sort of getting in your head with your patterns on the curtain a</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah getting</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0419">he say is it still numb yeah and he he's stitching it up and you feel every one</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh I say</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0419">and you you sort of just keep concentrating on these thing but he stitched it up and then I had to keep going back and then get it dressed and that</u>
<u n="1384" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1385" who="S0419">I remember when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> chopped his finger off on that trailer</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0419">off the jack and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there I went and got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bit of finger off and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1388" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1389" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1390" who="S0012">yeah of dear yeah I remember jumping off the asphalt off the back of the asphalt lorry and catching my ring underneath the</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0419">ah crack</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0012">I used to have a signet ring on and caught it underneath you know one of the hooks and that I just ah and I just managed to touch the floor</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0419">oh god</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0012">otherwise that'd have pulled my finger off</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0012">I never wore a ring since</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0419">yeah no I don't</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0012">never ever wore a ring since</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0419">I don't wear anything I don't wear watches and that</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0012">no I neither do I</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0419">no they're too they are a hazard aren't they?</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0012">they are when you're working aren't you yeah?</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0419" trans="overlap">especially if you're working yeah it'd be a hazard but yeah cor</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0419">all the things we have done in the time</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0012">yeah I remember once</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0419" trans="overlap">accidents you've had</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0012">I remember when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> smacked you on the head with a</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0419">hammer</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0012">hammer god he did he he smacked him right across with a sledgehammer</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0419">yeah a big fourteen pound I was holding the bar in the mixer when he was chipping the mixer out</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0419">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stood on top of it so I stood on the walk platform</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0012">yeah holding the bar high for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to hit it</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0419" trans="overlap">holding like that and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> missed the bar and hit me in the eye</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0012">well he said when I nod my head hit it so then he did</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1420" who="S0419">I managed to climb down the little ladder and I hear <vocal desc="misc"/> and then there were the there were little stars you do see them</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0012">yeah yeah right</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0419" trans="overlap">flashing everywhere they are and then the sight went when I was in the car and <trunc>lu</trunc> I think I told you when we got up to the top of <anon type="place"/> lane along <anon type="place"/> lane?</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0012">yeah <anon type="place"/> lane</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0419">yeah top of there where the lights are that was holiday time as well loads of traffic down there</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0419">and you know what dad sat in the front I sat in the back I said I can't see cos that went right black you see I was sort of semi-conscious</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0012">yeah well you yeah you'd got concussion hadn't you?</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0419">yeah and then and er as luck would have it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was pulling up and he this car come up on the cop point <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> shouted I hit my mate with a hammer</u>
<u n="1431" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0419">he said I got to get to the A and E well he put his blues up follow me he put his blue light on we went right down the middle of the road right to the that was I think that was the old hospital in <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0012">the old hospital in <anon type="place"/> yeah right up on <anon type="place"/> wasn't?</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah up <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0013">horrible to get to</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0419">yeah he took us right in there he did right up to the</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0419">the A and E there yeah and they and then I layed in there for ages</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0419">cos they didn't even scan they didn't have scans and stuff</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0012">no they didn't have anything did they?</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0419">they didn't have scans that was just you lay there</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0012">look in my eyes open your eyes looking up with the</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0419">stare at the pupils and</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0012">yeah dilated or whatever but they didn't have <unclear/> now they put you on a scan don't they?</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0419">they do yeah and they can see any bleeds or anything happening they have amazing gear</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0013">it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0013">we are really lucky aren't we?</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0419">we're lucky yeah to have that sort of stuff available</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0013">now</u>
<u n="1452" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1453" who="S0012">cor oh we've had some scrapes haven't we?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0012">what with er I was talking to somebody yesterday up cos I went up the quacks and I sat there and he come from <anon type="place"/> so I said do you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? he said yeah I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well he used we used to he used to work with with us he fell in the mixer didn't he?</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0419">yeah he did didn't he? yes good job the agitators weren't turning</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0012">good job the agitators because we had these great big agitators going round and they had great big er paddles weren't they</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah big arrow like paddles</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0012">big arrow like paddles and if er they'd been turning</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0419">that'd have put him in</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0012">he'd have gone and we'd have never seen him we'd be laying him the next day</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0419">that would have ground him up because the aggregate was in the asphalt</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0419">and with that constantly turning the the heat cos that's four fifty Fahrenheit the material</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0012">yeah yeah four hundred and fifty Fahrenheit</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0419">you get the heat and that would have just burnt everything away evaporated everything basically</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we wouldn't ever seen him again</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0419" trans="overlap">and the aggregate and the the things would just grind up the bones and everything</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0419">and we would have layer him and we wouldn't even well if we</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well you have to have it running that will burn on</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0419">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> where is he?</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> where is he?</u>
<u n="1475" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1476" who="S0013">blimey</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0012">what's that a blokes teeth in there</u>
<u n="1478" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1479" who="S0419" trans="overlap">but then</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0012">that'd have been awful well oh dear</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0419">when you when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when we were doing that er brewery down <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1482" who="S0012">yeah yeah we made this big huge floor didn't we?</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0419">yeah when we done the brewery and the <trunc>no</trunc> and the jubilee clip weren't done up enough on his gas gun was it?</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0419">and and he was torching the joints with the gas gun cos he was like a griller wasn't he? really really <unclear>chesting</unclear> everything</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he was</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0419">and the pipe come off the end of the gas gun</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0419">and that was it was a big ball of flames</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it went boom yeah</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0419">and and his chest cos he was dark skinned wasn't he?</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0012">yeah he was dark skinned</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0419">cos he's sort of Italian origin and his chest was red wasn't it? it took all the hairs all his eyebrows eyelashes everything</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0012">yeah and half his hair</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0013">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0419">yeah and he still laid the asphalt</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0012">he did didn't he?</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0419">in all that heat</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0013" trans="overlap">really</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0419">and so too did he when</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0013">so he didn't?</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0419">no he didn't bother then</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0012">no he didn't he bother no</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0419">cor he was hard as nails he was</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0012">hard as nails <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1507" who="S0419">he he even continued laying asphalt that time we was doing a roof and and he only had one strap on his feet pad instead of two</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah he did yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0419">and and the knee pad flopped forward</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0419">and we tipped the asphalt and he and the asphalt run into his knee pad and he knelt into it didn't he? and a <vocal desc="misc"/> big huge blister come up with it</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0012">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0419">he still keep going</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0012">god that was awful though</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0013" trans="overlap">gosh</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0419">he still he still kept going didn't he?</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0012">he did didn't he?</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0013">wow</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0419">cor he was hard as nails weren't he?</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0012">hard as nails poor old <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1521" who="S0419">he he fell off the asphalt didn't he?</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he right yeah</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0419">off the truck off the trailer we had a trailer</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we were break we were breaking up the blocks or moving the blocks and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was on the side and he went over and he <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he says where you going <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0419">he went all backwards all on the asphalt blocks</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he fell he fell</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0419">that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1528" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he lay there like that</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0012">we called a doctor didn't he?</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0419">never walk again he said?</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0419">didn't he? he said you won't walk again he discharged himself out of hospital the same day</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0012">same day yeah</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0013">really? you</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0012">and then he that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that his wife wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0012">bloody fool she says he come home</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1540" who="S0419">hard as nails that bloke</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0013">god</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0419">he was only short wasn't he?</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0012">yeah course but he he was big</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0419">he was all stocky wasn't he?</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0012">yeah he was a lovely bloke</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0012">really lovely bloke</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0419">old <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0012">old <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0013">sounds more like robot</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0012">yeah he was he was like a robot</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0419">monkey we used to call him</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0012">yeah we used to call him</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0419">you did name him monkey <unclear/></u>
<u n="1557" who="S0012">I did <unclear/></u>
<u n="1558" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1559" who="S0012">he used to take his shirt off and you couldn't tell him from a monkey you really couldn't</u>
<u n="1560" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1561" who="S0012">cos he was all brown and and</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0013">hairy front and back</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0012">hairy front and back yeah you couldn't tell him from a monkey I called him monkey</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0419">he used to go around and call him monkey when he first start when he first come with us that was brilliant wasn't? cos we'd be laying and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1565" who="S0012">oh and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0419">and poor old <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's sort of tried to lay asphalt as you you know sort of like not really the best way of laying it</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0012">that's it</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0419">and it had to be the right temperature so you'd push it all the time</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0419">instead of using gravity well not gravity but movement</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0419">if you heat the stuff up to the right temperature and you continually pour it back on that'll that'll always run forward</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0012" trans="overlap">always keep running forward</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0419">and so you</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0012" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0419">need the least amount of work to level it then</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0012">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to go shh shh like that and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'d go <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1580" who="S0419">really really no disrespect to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but we used to be a day didn't we?</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0419">to do maybe one and a half two bungalows</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0419">we finished two by dinner time with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't we?</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0012">yeah we did</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0419"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is that alright didn't he? when he went no that no good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you got to heat that a lot more than that</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0012">and when he heat it up it run like water</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0419">yeah that's that's better</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to lay it all three quarters of an inch thick and that was supposed to be only half an inch thick</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0012">so we usually use</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0419">more stuff</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0012">more stuff more blocks and what have you</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0012">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to do that and you'd run it out and it would almost run flat wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0012">and he'd just go shh like that and</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0419">and he had a float a huge great banana float</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> onto it</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0419">he had arms didn't he?</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0012">he had arms like a gorilla he did</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0419">yeah well he was a gorilla really</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0012">I think he I think he was a gorilla once</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0419">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I never forget that first time we couldn't believe it could we?</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0419">we were home at dinner time</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0419">well on the way</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0012">on the way home</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0013" trans="overlap">just because he did it so quickly</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0012">so quickly yeah</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0419">yeah cos we've always been used to to er to how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1613" who="S0012">to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s swearing and cursing didn't he?</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0012">cor he used to swear a lot <vocal desc="laugh"/> you had a <unclear/> with him didn't you?</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0419">yeah oh you had a fight didn't you?</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0012">we had a fight to cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0013" trans="overlap">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0012">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to lose his temper something awful and er threaten everyone that he was going to beat em up or do em up I remember when we were in a cafe one day</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0419">ooh yeah</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0012">we were on we were on the pinball machines</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0419">yes</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0012">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to love winning you see and he used to swear at you if you if you weren't winning didn't he? and this here bloke come over there and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said hello stalky cor just a load of who are you calling stalky <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that really scares me</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0419">I thought I knew <unclear/></u>
<u n="1625" who="S0012">I don't <unclear/> me I don't want to know you he says</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0012">cor that that was really</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0419">yeah cos he er a bit of a handful that bloke</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0012">he was a bit of a handful god</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0419">cor dear the <unclear/> we had <unclear/> didn't we?</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0012">yeah I I always laugh about you bringing the tea over to us</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0419">oh what when I stood in that <trunc>pa</trunc> puddle what was a hole wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0012">a hole you know like like that girl on on Vicar of Dibley she jumped in the in the pot holes and then she disappear he walk walking along with our lunch as well</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0419">all the sandwiches and that</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0012">all the sandwiches and everything</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0419">oh god in a crate when we had our communal crate without the bits in that you know what <unclear/> just a crate and everyone's sandwiches were in it</u>
<u n="1639" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1640" who="S0012">cos</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0419">and I go to cross the site the building site and <unclear/> and there was these puddles weren't there they were just puddles</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0419">but one of the puddles weren't weren't a puddle</u>
<u n="1644" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1645" who="S0419">and all the sandwiches <trunc>we</trunc>went in the water didn't they?</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0012">yeah god and the tea</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0419">and all the tea gear yeah all the tea gear everything went in the water</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah we had a separate</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0013" trans="overlap">so you disappeared?</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0419">hey?</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0013">you disappeared down</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0012" trans="overlap">he went right down he he went down a fair way didn't you? and then come out again</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah now now nowadays they</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0012">that wouldn't be allowed</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0419">wouldn't be allowed you wouldn't be allowed they wouldn't have a site like they used to</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0012">we couldn't get some some of the sites we couldn't get anywhere near the bungalow or the house</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0419">no we had to run on deal boards cos that's so muddy and everything wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0419">but nowadays all the roads have to be in now or it's</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0012">yeah the</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0419">part of the surface you know they're</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0012" trans="overlap">hard put a hard surface on these</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0419" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1666" who="S0012">there's three quarter of er tarmac on them</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0419">yeah just to so everything</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0012">so everything can get there</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0419">cor yeah that saying that was erm you used to spend I remember when we used to tile with mixer and we used to go and do the job get a JCB to tow the mixer on to the site</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0419">and then sometimes if they want a JCB you'd get as far as you could and that would go down to the axle</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0012">that's it</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0419">and then we'd do the job from a distance and then add the jack</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0012" trans="overlap">jack it up again</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0419">jack it up and block it up to get</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0013" trans="overlap">woo gosh</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0419"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1679" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it was hard work it was was hard work and on days where it was really really really hot</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0419">yeah oh yeah</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0012">that was</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0419">there was one time we did have to finish we couldn't do it</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we couldn't do it we were</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0419">it was too hot</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0012">it was so hot we couldn't do it</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0419">and you can't er drink you can't drink too much in one hit cos that'll knock you out</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0419">cos that cool your blood down too quick</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0419">cos you're in four hundred and fifty degrees of heat inside</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0013">yeah oh</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0012">inside the house was four hundred and fifty <trunc>de</trunc>degrees oh that was hard wasn't?</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0419">well yeah</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0012">kept us fit though innit?</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0419">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0012">I mean we wouldn't be like we are now if we hadn't done that</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0419">no no way</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0419">no that did er we used to run like nothing</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0012" trans="overlap">run run the bucket over</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0419" trans="overlap">half on the <unclear/> piece and holding them like that when the</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0012" trans="overlap">probably why my shoulder's are gone for</u>
<u n="1704" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1705" who="S0419">we used to run them down to the</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0012">run like mad</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0419">up ladders</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0419">well and before they we used to pull em up on the thingy</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0419">cos we didn't have them like they do now we didn't have all the gear now to lift stuff up don't they?</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0012">that's it</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0419">we had to manually <unclear/> and that was towards the end we did have these er pack hoists</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0012">we did yeah</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0419">yeah and but I remember one of them I brought it up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come to help me cos there was only we was three hands at that time I think it was on <anon type="place"/> library</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0012">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0419">we were only three handed and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come over to help me with the buckets cos I was getting them down here and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was sending them up or I was operating the hoist on top of the roof bringing them up and I let it down to quick and the hook went in the asphalt and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come over and I quickly whipped it up and the hook come up</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0013">ooh</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0419">cos he always had his shirt off didn't he?</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0012">shirt off</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0419">and that went right on on his chest</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0012">really?</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0419">with all hot asphalt on</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="1725" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1726" who="S0012">he went through the mill</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0419">poor old <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did didn't he?</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0012">yeah I remember when we were on <unclear/> roof that er when we were doing the</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0419">the er oh the EDP?</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0012" trans="overlap">the <unclear/> yeah it was the EDP</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0419" trans="overlap">was it the EDP one?</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0012">and they were we were asphalting the aerials in the</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0012">that was when I first realised that I had vertigo and I and the roof was flat and it felt like that and I couldn't go near the edge at all that was it that nearly done my head in that did</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0419">it's a <unclear/> you up the ladder</u>
<u n="1736" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1737" who="S0012">yeah I used to go up the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1738" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1739" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had to come and <trunc>re</trunc>rescue me once</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I remember</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0419">well you good job you didn't come with me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to look at look at that one at <anon type="place"/> for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he say he used to cart all the cars on his transport we had a job to price up at <anon type="place"/> up <anon type="place"/> there and that was a big on a big high rise things</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0419">and er we went up first of all we went up in the a lift I think and then we went on to a balcony and then we went up a three tier ladder</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0419">onto the top of a three day ladder off the balcony and the wind cos you're up that high aren't you?</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0419">on this big high rises the wind was blowing there and there's no parapet round it</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0419">imagine working up there</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0419">cos you couldn't we we couldn't you had a to price it high because you couldn't do it when it the time the stuff got up there got up there that would be too too cold to use</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0419">you'd you'd have to the only way you'd do that is to have pots on the roof wouldn't you? you'd have to do that with pots on</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0012">when they built that EDP er place on the top of it they had that that big office <trunc>b</trunc> office block didn't they?</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0012">and it was a it was you know an office that you could move</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0012">and er they offered it to us for nothing they offered it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for nothing</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0419">oh yeah if we could get it down</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0012" trans="overlap">if you if you can get that down you can have it</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0419">no you can have it yeah if you pay for the</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0012">for the <trunc>cr</trunc>crane which was a hundred pound off</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0012">you can have that</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0013">nice</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0012">I don't know whether they got it down do you? they had to get it down</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0419">I reckon they had a deal I reckon someone probably with it who had to accompany you on these cranes and that probably had it for the you know I mean it</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0419">for if you want to take it down you can have the building sort of thing</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0012">lovely wasn't?</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0419">lovely building</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0012" trans="overlap">lovely building yeah oh lovely building like</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0419">was fitted out with everything</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0012">yeah electric the lot</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0419">everything</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0012">yeah water electric that had innit? fantastic</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0419">yeah that was beautiful</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0012">we could have had it down the field here <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that would've been lovely</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0012">a holiday home</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0012">a holiday home yeah</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0419">yeah that's the <unclear/> got some holiday lets down there?</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0012">oh he should have shouldn't we?</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0013">I'd quite like a a chalet</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0419">a lot of people a lot of people are doing the countryside</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0013">but who would want to stay here?</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0419">hey?</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0013">who would want to come and stay here?</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0419">cor yeah where we go out with the buses work and that there's lots of places in the country what have got a little holiday lets</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0419">cos people like to walk around the they like these old villages and that</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0012">yeah they do yeah</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0419">and if they got a car they they just drive into places like <anon type="place"/> cos that's quite historical isn't it?</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0012">yeah well</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0419">and all these little villages had people who are interested in not everyone like the seaside because it's busy</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0012">no no they don't</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0419">like there's loads of people like erm</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0012">well we're right next to the bedded way really aren't we?</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0013">nobody walks around here do they really?</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0012">not really no</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0013">I mean there are footpaths but I mean I suppose what what you're used to is not exciting is it</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0012">no that's true</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0419">but you yeah you take it for granted don't you?</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0012">you do yeah</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0419">you know I always say to people like they got there even if they've just got a little bungalow or something like that I said you don't really realise how lucky you are to be able to drive in your own driveway</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0419">without anyone</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0419">next door to you</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0012">that's right</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0419">cos you're forever worrying about noise issues</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0419">and also like mine I've got like you can't have look out any window where's there's someone not looking back at you</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0012">that's true yeah</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0419">your totally surrounded</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0419">you can't and people they've just been brought up with their little bungalows and that ain't they?</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0419">and they don't they just don't realise</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0419">how that's just nice to be have your own space</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0419">you know cos I go home and I'm they'll be someone parked in my place</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0419">and then you end up having to park over in the corner somewhere you know</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0012">yeah that's true yeah</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0419">but</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0012">in someone else's place</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0419">yeah in somebody else's place</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0419">you know <pause dur="short"/> but that's erm that's the annoying thing about it like what you were saying at least we got some good neighbours now the new ones then they moved in their they're really</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0012">yeah you had some rough ones times didn't you?</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0419">I was saying yesterday you know I haven't really seen them that's the first time I see her yesterday and she's nice but I see him a while back cos I went and asked him if he mind if I cut his bit of grass at the front of the house</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0419">you see cos I've got a plug socket outside</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0419">I said cos you you think to yourself well you think well you think if that was me I'd think well he could have just cut my bit if he's</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that's right yeah so</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0419">that <trunc>no</trunc>nothing that's hardly any size that's a stupid little bit you know and that's just a <unclear/> go on just a bit further over</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0419">so I knocked on the door and said I'm your neighbour oh hi he say I'm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I I'm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said I just come round to <trunc>s</trunc>see whether you'd be okay with me cutting your bit of grass oh yeah yeah we ain't got a lawn mower yet he said</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0012">oh</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0419">yeah he say that'd be great if you would so and then they took the them parcels in for me yesterday</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0012">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0419" trans="overlap">and then he said I'm a chippie you know he say I'm a carpenter he say if you ever want anything done he say I'll help you he say no charge</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0012">brilliant yeah</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0013">that's what you want isn't it?</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0012">yeah now that's how that's how it used to be years ago innit?</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I I think they just moved from London and because that's getting so crowded up there and that</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0419">I think they <trunc>do</trunc> they they they just appreciate the more peaceful atmosphere</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0419">you know</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0419">but yeah that's that's good that's nice and quiet both sides</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0012">yeah that's brilliant</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0419">the other neighbours are good</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0419">they're quiet</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0012">cos they when they built them places they didn't build it with neighbours in mind</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0012">they just built the houses didn't they?</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0419">yeah that's typical council they just think you're rabble if if you're a council tenant like anything'll do for a council tenant</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0012">yeah that's it yeah</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0419">you know? you you you're not in there in these council's eyes you're just you know</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0419">peasants really</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0419">and anything'll do for the peasants</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0012">although years ago they that weren't like that council houses were built for the people</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0419">yes that was the early ones weren't they? yeah</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0419">but these are built in nineteen eighty these ones</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0419" trans="overlap">and they you can hear them through the walls you can hear them talking</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0419">you when they pull the toilet or you know flush the toilet you can hear that you can hear them talking</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0419">in the night</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0012">well that's just one <trunc>bri</trunc> one brick innit?</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0419">yeah building regs now they won't <unclear/></u>
<u n="1891" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1892" who="S0419">no that's got to be quiet you're you're not supposed to hear any noise or anything what's going on but then they just they just didn't care</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0012">that house we had in <anon type="place"/> there that council house that was a lovely house weren't it?</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0013">yes it was weren't it?</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0012">we had some lovely neighbours</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0419">and you had a good size gardens</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0012">and the garden was massive yeah</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0012">and there was enough room to park the car inside as well</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0013">yeah it was nice</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0012">that was really but the first time I parked my van up there I got a ticket sixteen quid that cost</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0419">did you?</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0012">for parking it the wrong way round</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0419">hey?</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0013">cos there weren't any street lights</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0419">oh no street lights yeah</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0013">we didn't know about that did we?</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0012">and we had that was that was about four o'clock in the afternoon it was getting dark and I was unloading the van</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0419">oh</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0012">right from from where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was in er</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0012">in <anon type="place"/> in er <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1917" who="S0013">it was we had a car wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0012">well that was a van</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0013">was it?</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0012">I've I've only every owned vans</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0013">no it was a purple car</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0012">purple car yeah</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0419">oh the Zephyr</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0012">yeah the Zephyr yeah</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0419">yeah the Ford Zephyr weren't it?</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0012">I don't think that was the Zephyr I'm sure that was the van</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0419">was it?</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0012">yeah yeah anyhow he village copper got friendly with him in the end</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0419"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1931" who="S0012">but erm</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0419">did you ask for you sixteen quid back?</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0013">it was the <trunc>fir</trunc> first time</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0012">it was the first time being in <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0419" trans="overlap">well that's the wrong way to get started</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> good with the</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0012">after four o'clock here on his bike or whatever he was on</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0013">we didn't know about it till the next morning did we?</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0012">there it was ticket on it</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0419">he probably thought oh I didn't get a lot of action out this way so</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0012">bit of money here</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0419">bit of cash here cor dear</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0012">and do you know I used to get stopped</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0419">loads in that white van</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0419">in the minivan <trunc>ev</trunc> loads and loads of time</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0012" trans="overlap">loads of times I got stopped</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0012">and I used to go down to the beat cos it they they give tickets to do and see the raffle</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0419">straight in</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0012">yeah but I used to go down to have you I said well we got a copper in the village I can go down to him he said yeah and I said well he said not again what are they doing to you?</u>
<u n="1954" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1955" who="S0419">you could call that victimisation now couldn't you?</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0013">never like that white van did they?</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0419">you could have em done now for constantly</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you could yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0419">puling you up because that's the</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0012">pulled me up one day coming home in the in the snow that was snowing like hell and of course they'd salted the roads and there was slush all over the road and that splattered up everywhere when a car went passed you they'd splatter you and splatter you going along er little old blue light behind me oh god what have I done now? and he come up he says you come past us I couldn't see your number plates so I said oh well I'll clean them off oh he say no you'll have to have a ticket for that I said but look that's snowing you know I can't see yours either you know that sort of thing you know but he did let me off he didn't give me a ticket but darn well tried</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0419">yeah I had this <unclear/> when you come out the thicket once didn't you?</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0419">cos that was all muddy and that</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0419">I remember that one as well</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0012">yeah they pulled me in for that they did</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0419">oh dear oh dear</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0012">it's all they have to do now</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0419">yeah there's there's nothing much to do</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0012">I had a a my little er what was that called? that little red car we had from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1971" who="S0013">Saab</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0012">a Saab red Saab</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0013">very old Saab</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0012">and that was when I had long hair down to here you see I was going on the road and er oh stopped me got out keep me in the car <unclear/></u>
<u n="1975" who="S0419">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0012">and funnily enough that stopped right outside I think it was <unclear/> or someone's and they were taking the mick</u>
<u n="1977" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1978" who="S0012">I said they're my mates over there look oh he says oh well I thought you belonged to the travellers group up the road there was a load of travellers up the road</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0012">and he was he had it in for them you see</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0419">ah</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0013">it it was a really old car wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0012">it was a really old car yeah</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0013">and when you when you applied for like insurance they said what what year is the car and you say J reg and they say oh quite a new one no J from before</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0419">yeah from the old days seventy-two wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0012">seventy-two yeah</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0419">seventy-two yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0013">yeah I think that was it J but it was funny really isn't it?</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0012">well the best best one I had was old van the old tiny van I had though and er I've welded that up so much that look like a tank</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0419">I remember yeah</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0419">loads and loads of work</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0012">I done no end of work on that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1996" who="S0013">it was good</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0012">that really didn't that really earned its pay that did</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0012">there was more people more people in <anon type="place"/> were there?</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0012">yeah all for nothing mind mind you I did get</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0013">fined once</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0012">yeah I did get a fine but that was an all day job</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0013">it was an all day job and when you got to the other place they weren't there</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they were down the pub</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0013">down the pub ah</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0012">yeah and they hadn't even told us</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0013">and he'd been going backwards and forwards fetching more stuff and they they just disappeared and out to the pub</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0012">they went to the pub and I had to unload all the stuff</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0013">oh makes you mad doesn't it? when people do that</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0419">oh what?</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0013">I mean you don't mind helping people out</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0419">no</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0013">when they're that's taking the mickey</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0419">that's rubbing your nose in it that is yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0013">you weren't very happy with that were you?</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0012">I weren't very</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0013">well you didn't know then you were only going to get a fiver</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0013">and he'd worked all day</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0419">of course</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0013">oh here you are</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I'd worked all day backwards and forwards from <anon type="place"/> lane in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2025" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0012">down to <anon type="place"/> at the back there you know</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0013">fiver and a drink</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0012">fiver and a drink not even asked down to the pub or anything</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0013">no yeah</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0419">there's funny people aren't there?</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0013">and all they think is oh well we're not going see you again so</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2034" who="S0012">that really upset me that did</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0013">that did yeah</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0012">all that for nothing</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0013">it's a shame cos when people do that then you're kind of a bit wary of doing it for someone else aren't you?</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0012">there was a little old lady across the road I I moved her all her stuff in and she was going to give me I don't know what she was going to give me no I don't want anything you know that's how you do it innit?</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0013">yeah it's different innit?</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I don't want you <unclear/> I don't want anything you're okay you know I don't mind helping you out</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0013">yeah people appreciate it</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0012">cos she was so nice and we were neighbours going to be neighbours anyway</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0013">mm yeah</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0012">and er you know I just helped her out and that was fine cos that weren't far I didn't have to move it far did I?</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0013">no you didn't</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0012">just move out all her stuff and course they they had all the old stuff out like aunt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to have you know that sort of old really old furniture which was not worth a penny anyway</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0013">but you don't you don't need money for things you just</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0012">no you don't need money</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0013">appreciate it don't you?</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0419">yeah someone just say thank you and show appreciation that go a long way doesn't it?</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0419">but you get some people they don't even show no appreciation or thank you or they just as though they take it for granted</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no no yeah</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0013">that's right</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0012">yeah there are horrible people about</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0419">used to get people like that when I used to do the DM then you get other people totally different you know?</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0419">come out there they couldn't thank you enough and this that and the other</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0012">well when we used to do er asphalting</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0012">for for people in council houses right? you'd get cups of tea and biscuits and</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0012">lovely bits and pieces</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0012">then you'd go to some rich bod up the road like that bloke who laid on his</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0419"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2073" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2074" who="S0419"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2075" who="S0012">MP he was</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0419">he was an MP conservative MP</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0012">he laid in the middle of his his</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0419">pool didn't he?</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0012">swimming pool with</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0419">glass of</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0012">glass of champers</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0419">or whatever he was drinking</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0012" trans="overlap">or whatever he was drinking</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0419">we was sweating like anything</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we were sweating</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0419">and they didn't even offer us a glass of juice or water or anything</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0012" trans="overlap">water or anything</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0419">he just lay there while we were</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0012">cor we grafted for that idiot didn't we hey?</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0419" trans="overlap">sweating and grafting yeah</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0012">I'd have like to have</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0419">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2095" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0419">conservative nineteen seventies area era was it the seventies?</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah something like that must must have been late seventies yeah</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0419">he was Maggie in Maggie Thatcher's government wasn't he?</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0012">yeah that's right he was with Maggie's</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0419">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> laying on his airbed in the middle of the pool</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0012" trans="overlap">in the middle of the pool</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0419">with his drink in his hand</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0012">cor dear</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0419" trans="overlap">and we were running round weren't we?</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0419">doing his extension</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0012">yeah and now what about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when we did up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2113" who="S0419">oh that posh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s yeah</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0012">yeah she come out she says oh thank you very much boys lined us all up</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0012">and give us four chocolates each</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0419">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2118" who="S0012">and we were supposed to go like oh thank you very much Mrs you know?</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0419">like in the olden days</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0012">and the blokes from <anon type="place"/> went <unclear/></u>
<u n="2121" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2122" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0012">they were swearing and cursing who the hell does she think she is <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2124" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2125" who="S0012">and that was when that was a a factory</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0012"><anon type="place"/> factory up the the road there wasn't?</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0419">do you remember when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> weed on the banker</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2131" who="S0419">on the back of it there we'd just emptied the hot asphalt what we had left on the back of the <trunc>artic</trunc> trailer we put</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0419">boards all round and sand and that and we used to empty that on the back</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0012">so we could use it again</u>
<u n="2135" who="S0419" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and we we finishing off in the kitchen of this place and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there weren't nowhere for him to have a wee in this place</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0419">so he weed on the banker and the smell coming round</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2139" who="S0419">the corner and the posh <trunc>de</trunc> oh whatever's that smell is is it that asphalt that smells like that that's rather nasty</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="2141" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2142" who="S0013">cor</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0012">oh we had some laughs we did have some laughs didn't we?</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0419">yeah it was good it was hard work but we come across a lot of funny</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it could be <unclear/></u>
<u n="2146" who="S0419">yeah we come a lot across of a lot of funny characters</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0012">we did come up against a lot of funny characters</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0419">cos you meet all sorts don't you?</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0013">there you are you could write a book</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0013">guys in the asphalt</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0419" trans="overlap">you can always you can guarantee if you got in one of these little villages and you wanted to know the way</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0012">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0419">you'd always pick the wrong person</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0419">to tell you the way</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0012">we had one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stopped well I probably told you this before he stopped outside and he says where's <anon type="place"/> and the bloke went down there and that was it</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0012">we got up the other end of the village or or up right up the road and we saw another bloke sitting there swinging his legs on the side of the road he shouted where's <anon type="place"/> and the bloke went down there</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2163" who="S0012">and that was it we'd gone through <anon type="place"/> which was about three houses or something I can't remember</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah a tiny little place we were at actually in it</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0012">we were actually in it</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="2167" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0419">cor yes some places we went to didn't we?</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0012">we did and some are and when you think about it there was no <trunc>nav</trunc>navigation was there? we didn't have any</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0419">no we had to find it didn't we?</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we had to find these places</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0419" trans="overlap">we didn't have satnav then did we?</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0012">we didn't have satnav</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knew <anon type="place"/> like the back of his hand anyway</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0419" trans="overlap">yeah he knew everywhere didn't he? yeah</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2179" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0419">yeah we used to we used to go quite a way away sometimes</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0012">we did we did</u>
<u n="2182" who="S0419"><anon type="place"/> we went to once</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0012">yeah yes all the way to <anon type="place"/> didn't we?</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0012">ha <pause dur="long"/> and the old mixer the pulling that mixer behind that was a horrible one when it got when we go the old load holder</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0419">on the <unclear/> that was lovely that</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0012">that was lovely on the load holder we had a plug for the kettle didn't we?</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0419">yeah electric starter to start the engine</u>
<u n="2189" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0419">and everything all mod cons then weren't they?</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0012">well that cost three thousand pounds</u>
<u n="2192" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0012">that mixer</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0419">that's a lot of money that</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0012">that was lot of money then there thousand pounds I remember mum saying I don't know where we're going to get the money for that but we had to have it cos the bottom kept dropping out of the other mixer didn't it?</u>
<u n="2196" who="S0419">yeah we used to come home and weld the bottom of it every night</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0419">pretty much</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0419">you go one one day's work and then you had to go back cos that that was always heated up and moving and expanding and retracting</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0012">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0419">we had to put another patch on it</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0012">and then we took it down <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to have it done didn't we?</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0419">yeah and made a whole new</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0012">a whole new bottom for it</u>
<u n="2206" who="S0419" trans="overlap"><unclear/> mark</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0012">yeah they did yeah but that had to be boiler steel on you see</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0012">not ordinary mild steel it had to be boiler steel</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0012">so that that could stand it</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0013">wouldn't melt yeah</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0012">stand all the hot because that was hot wasn't it?</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0012">and then the the burners used to burn out didn't they? the the</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0419">big long tubes</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0012" trans="overlap">big tube</u>
<u n="2218" who="S0419">yeah they got hot</u>
<u n="2219" who="S0012" trans="overlap">they had loads and loads of holes in all the way up</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0419" trans="overlap">they were all stainless steel and</u>
<u n="2221" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0419">and they'd last so long and then they'd start to collapse wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="2223" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0419">and then they'd gradually fall to pieces</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2226" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2227" who="S0012">we had to have new ones and then god that was a lot of work in that weren't they?</u>
<u n="2228" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0419">yeah old crane wheels on the old one</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2231" who="S0419">if they weren't crane you had to buy the pair didn't you?</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="2233" who="S0419">cos they match</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you had to buy the pair the worm and the wing</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0419" trans="overlap">and the ground wheel</u>
<u n="2236" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="2237" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2238" who="S0419">we converted it with a <trunc>du</trunc> we had a gearbox on it</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0012">that's it yeah we put a gearbox on</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0419">we had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come down and work all the configuration out for the to drop the RPM</u>
<u n="2241" who="S0012" trans="overlap">the RPM</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0419">or the revolution per minute</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0012">that's it yeah we did didn't we?</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0419">and they dropped that down to I don't know what was it sixty to one reduction something like that</u>
<u n="2245" who="S0012">yeah something like that yeah</u>
<u n="2246" who="S0419">and they <unclear/> they worked it on we had chains and pulleys didn't we?</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0012">yeah we did</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0419"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2249" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2250" who="S0419">put it in gear and ease the clutch up and that worked</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah that worked yeah</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2254" who="S0419">oh the things we used to do</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0012">all that all that <unclear/> we did</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0419">yeah</u>
<u n="2257" who="S0012">just to keep going</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0419">yeah just to earn a <unclear/> back</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0012">and mum used to say well you home already?</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0419">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2261" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2262" who="S0013">haven't you done anything?</u>
<u n="2263" who="S0419" trans="overlap">but she she cos because she was old school and they were always brought up to do like an eight hour and eight-hour day at least</u>
<u n="2264" who="S0012" trans="overlap">eight hours at least</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2266" who="S0419">but the what she didn't take into consideration was the fact</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
