<text id="SW98">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:02:30</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0002 S0018</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A university café,  Birmingham </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Rented accommodation, travel, studying, driving, working abroad, buying a house</topics>
		<activity>Friends catching up while having a coffee.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0002">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Japanese -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<event desc="sound of background"/>
<u n="1" who="S0018">so are you living still with the the housemate that you found back in October?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0002">yes <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately <pause dur="short"/> I mean fortunately</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What what but why is it I thought you said it was a lovely place?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0002">er oh</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">you remember when you went to see it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0002">did I say that?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">you remember when we saw those hovels?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0002">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's just a lesser hovel</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> but it's only the other it's only one flatmate?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0002">two flatmates <pause dur="short"/> but they're quite quiet <pause dur="short"/> they're <trunc>t</trunc> third year undergrads <pause dur="short"/> so they're about to finish and they've got tons of exams and assignments <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">but wasn't it er just living with one woman?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">or is that a different place?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0002">mm <pause dur="short"/> that was a different place</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0002">which I probably should've taken <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But I didn't <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018">I was under the impression that you'd</u>
<u n="18" who="S0002">oh</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">gone with that</u>
<u n="20" who="S0002">the nice one</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">one you see</u>
<u n="22" who="S0002">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> not in the end</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">I thought it was all swish <pause dur="short"/> and you had a big room <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="24" who="S0002">no <pause dur="short"/> oh that <pause dur="short"/> oh God I'd totally forgotten about that</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">so was it cheaper? This other place?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0002">this place is cheaper but I've got I've been locked into a contract until the end of June <pause dur="short"/> and I'm now I'm trying to find someone to replace me <pause dur="short"/> but I'm it's been I've been advertising it for two months and I haven't found anyone <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="28" who="S0002">probably I have to pay until June</u>
<u n="29" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0018">how much is it?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0002">three hundred no yeah including bills and internet and everything it's three hundred and ten per month</u>
<u n="32" who="S0018">that's not too bad with bills and stuff</u>
<u n="33" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just like <trunc>t</trunc> two minutes down the road</u>
<u n="34" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="35" who="S0002">so it's really close</u>
<u n="36" who="S0018">perfect</u>
<u n="37" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sort of roll out of the bed and go to the school in the morning</u>
<u n="38" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And is it a small place? It's er what what was it that about the other place that you didn't like? Or was it just the price?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0002">do you you know where <anon type="place"/> is?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0002">it's it was there</u>
<u n="42" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="43" who="S0002">um and that considering it was five hundred and fifty per month</u>
<u n="44" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="45" who="S0002">um</u>
<u n="46" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="47" who="S0002"><trunc>Othe</trunc></u>
<u n="48" who="S0018">that was a lot more expensive</u>
<u n="49" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was a lot of money <pause dur="short"/> but she was quite flexible about when I could so I she said I could um leave after three months</u>
<u n="50" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0002">which would've been better <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so I probably should've done that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0018">what happens if you break your contract? Have you given them a deposit?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0002">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they've got a deposit</u>
<u n="54" who="S0018">I mean that's</u>
<u n="55" who="S0002">I don't actually know <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't it says that you have to complete the full contract <pause dur="short"/> I believe there's no like get-out clause <pause dur="short"/> like give one month's notice and you can leave <pause dur="short"/> as far as I can see <pause dur="short"/> they told me at the beginning if I can find someone else to replace me then I can break the contract</u>
<u n="56" who="S0018">SE hmm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0002">but that's quite hard</u>
<u n="58" who="S0018">and how many months er rent do they have from you for <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="59" who="S0002">one month's</u>
<u n="60" who="S0018">as a deposit?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0002">deposit <pause dur="short"/> but actually um huh we're thinking of pushing legal action against the landlord because er for the last three months we haven't had any well not we haven't had any but we've had major problems with the boiler</u>
<u n="62" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0002">so we've been days sometimes weeks without hot water and heating <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I've been going home to my mum and dad's for showers</u>
<u n="64" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="65" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> and every time we say every time well we must they we must have had British Gas come round about fifteen times this year</u>
<u n="66" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="67" who="S0002">and they're still not replacing the boiler <pause dur="short"/> and that's just one of the problems <pause dur="short"/> there's been tons of problems <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="68" who="S0018">why don't you just refuse to pay your rent until he sorts it out?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0002">so we've that's what we've now said that we're gonna do <pause dur="short"/> but it has to be all of us <pause dur="short"/> we have to all do the same thing <pause dur="short"/> if we don't then it's yeah we don't want them to er huh the thing is we get yelled at every time we say look we're not paying until until it's all fixed <pause dur="short"/> they make us feel like we're completely unreasonable <pause dur="short"/> which I know we shouldn't get talked round in er these things but</u>
<u n="70" who="S0018">is it a private landlord? Or?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0002">no it's <trunc>ra</trunc> it's through an agency</u>
<u n="72" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0002">and the agency won't hear of us not paying <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018">yeah but I mean at the end of the day if they're not it could be a way of getting out of your contract</u>
<u n="75" who="S0002">that's this so in January when it was really bad over Christmas <pause dur="short"/> actually I got really ill because</u>
<u n="76" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="77" who="S0002">there was a week that there was cold water <pause dur="short"/> and it was cold at Christmas <pause dur="short"/> and um I went I came to the university <pause dur="short"/> first I went to my faculty kind of adviser and said look I'm having these problems <pause dur="short"/> I wanna know if I can break the contract <pause dur="short"/> because I don't see why I should be paying considering it's <trunc>unliv</trunc> it's like uninhabitable literally <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018">it was so cold as well wasn't it</u>
<u n="79" who="S0002">it was freezing <pause dur="short"/> um and they said that there's nothing they can do <pause dur="short"/> so then I went to the university housing <pause dur="short"/> they also said there's nothing they can do <pause dur="short"/> so now we now we've gone through the Citizens Advice Bureau and we've applied for legal aid</u>
<u n="80" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="81" who="S0002">and only one of the girls in the house qualifies for legal aid being free because if you earn over a if you have a certain amount in savings you can't get free legal aid</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="83" who="S0002">so it's all up to her <pause dur="short"/> if she's willing to push <pause dur="short"/> otherwise we can be done for not paying rent</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0002">it has to be done properly <pause dur="short"/> which is such a pain in the arse <pause dur="short"/> the whole thing</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">and have you  have you  got any er is there not a legal adviser in the university housing association?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0002">no</u>
<u n="88" who="S0018">Cos can you is there not?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0002">no <pause dur="short"/> I've taken my contract</u>
<u n="90" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0002">and they've just kind of gone well we can't do anything <pause dur="short"/> they're pretty useless <pause dur="short"/> shouldn't really be saying this on a recording should I</u>
<u n="92" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Why don't? Oh</u>
<u n="93" who="S0002">um I <trunc>mea</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't <trunc>kno</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a standard agreement <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't even understand why we're in such a difficult position to it's er so something will break and then someone will come round and it'll be fixed for like a few days and then it'll break again <pause dur="short"/> so it's not like they're not reacting <pause dur="short"/> every time we complain they do come round like pretty quickly <pause dur="short"/> but it's just the point that if they dont' replace it or if they don't give us a proper solution <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="94" who="S0018">well they're obviously fixing trying to fix something that can't be fixed <pause dur="short"/> needs replacing</u>
<u n="95" who="S0002">basically <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0018">and in your contract does it say that the that they are responsible for upkeeping the I don't know what they'd call it the</u>
<u n="97" who="S0002">there's a yeah the like</u>
<u n="98" who="S0018">fixtures and fittings</u>
<u n="99" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0018">and</u>
<u n="101" who="S0002">I mean like it's one of those contracts which is like thirty statements long <pause dur="short"/> and one statement says the house will be kept in a reputable <trunc>whatev</trunc> I can't remember the exact wording <pause dur="short"/> but there is one clause that says that they but it doesn't define what it means by <trunc>inh</trunc> inhabitable</u>
<u n="102" who="S0018">well if there's no hot water</u>
<u n="103" who="S0002">hot water</u>
<u n="104" who="S0018">and no heating that's hardly habitable is it?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0002">they keep saying to us oh summer's coming soon <pause dur="short"/> and we're like and we'll still want a hot shower <pause dur="short"/> your point is really not valid at all <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="106" who="S0018">well why don't you just try and get a lawyer to just get advice to say look they've broken the contract in that they haven't kept the house habitable um I want to write them a letter saying <trunc>vie</trunc> er</u>
<u n="107" who="S0002">Don't I have to pay for that?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0018">in consideration <pause dur="short"/> well I dunno <pause dur="short"/> try and find a</u>
<u n="109" who="S0002">that's why we're trying to go through the legal aid thing</u>
<u n="110" who="S0018">or just ask er ask the question <pause dur="short"/> if I write this letter saying that they've broken this contract and this there has been no hot water and no heating since November?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0002">it's been intermittent since December</u>
<u n="112" who="S0018">then that's you know that's not they're breaking the contract <pause dur="short"/> that's not what you signed up for</u>
<u n="113" who="S0002">I think we talked to the landlord recently <pause dur="short"/> apparently they've been trying to get hold of him and he won't answer the calls <pause dur="short"/> and then finally the estate agent gave us cos one of the girls was yelling at him on the phone and she he gave us the landlord's number <pause dur="short"/> and he the landlord phoned back and he sweet-talked her <pause dur="short"/> I was just watching her on the phone just going</u>
<u n="114" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="115" who="S0002">she started off really angry and then she sort of calmed down <pause dur="short"/> and then by the end of it she was simpering on the phone <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like</u>
<u n="116" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh no</u>
<u n="117" who="S0002">come on woman <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But um it sounded like he said he wasn't aware of the problem <pause dur="short"/> yeah right <pause dur="short"/> I don't believe you <pause dur="short"/> um and that he was gonna get someone round <pause dur="short"/> some of his own people to check it <pause dur="short"/> and if it needs changing he's willing to change it <pause dur="short"/> but it's just been going on forever <pause dur="short"/> like and I think if we do threaten not to pay they probably will just fix it <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I won't be able to break the contract</u>
<u n="118" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0002">which is kind of the idea</u>
<u n="120" who="S0018">well that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> just don't threaten <pause dur="short"/> just say look for the past four months it's been uninhabitable <pause dur="short"/> we've been repeatedly telling you <pause dur="short"/> it has not been fixed <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I cannot continue I'm in  I'm in  full-time education <pause dur="short"/> I have a lot of work to do <pause dur="short"/> blah blah blah blah blah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we've we've said</u>
<u n="122" who="S0018">this is</u>
<u n="123" who="S0002">all of this</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018">compromising my ability to concentrate <pause dur="short"/> it's um making it extremely inconvenient for me on a day-to-day basis because I have to go and have showers</u>
<u n="125" who="S0002">at home</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018">twenty miles <vocal desc="laugh"/> away</u>
<u n="127" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> for this</u>
<u n="129" who="S0002">but</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018">reason I would like to dissolve the contract based on the fact that you haven't respected</u>
<u n="131" who="S0002">I er that's actually I think pretty much been said <pause dur="short"/> and the answer just is you can't <pause dur="short"/> so without some legal intervention somewhere</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018">can you not? SE What about the Citizens Advice Bureau?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0002">that's yeah that's why we're going <trunc>throu</trunc> we've been to them and they said we need to go through legal aid</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="135" who="S0002">which takes time and I mean they're booking us an appointment and the girl has to go in and see them <pause dur="short"/> and we can't all go because we can't all be represented <pause dur="short"/> blah blah blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> it's just like typical really <pause dur="short"/> but to be honest I'm I just wanna forget it <pause dur="short"/> as in I'll just keep paying the rent just for an easy life in a way</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0002">and I can just go home whenever <trunc>anyw</trunc> I'm lucky I have that option <pause dur="short"/> the other girls don't <pause dur="short"/> their family's down in London so</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018">hm <pause dur="short"/> have they joined the gym? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0002">yeah I know I I don't know what I think one of them goes to her boyfriend's and the other one probably goes to a friend's but <pause dur="short"/> or they've just been having cold showers <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">it's not typical <pause dur="short"/> I E it's not typical <pause dur="short"/> it's not <vocal desc="laugh"/> what am I talking about?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0002"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0018">it's not er oh what's the word? It's not an ideal situation</u>
<u n="143" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018">there you go</u>
<u n="145" who="S0002"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0018">not an ideal situation when you</u>
<u n="147" who="S0002">I'm like what are you trying to say? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0018">I don't know what I'm <vocal desc="laugh"/> trying to say <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="149" who="S0002">no it's not an ideal situation</u>
<u n="150" who="S0018">especially when you've got so much else to deal with <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="151" who="S0002">huh <pause dur="short"/> so I'm going away for a month next week</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">oh yeah? Where?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0002">Japan</u>
<u n="154" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="155" who="S0002">um <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna be writing up my two term papers</u>
<u n="156" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0002">from there</u>
<u n="158" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0002">but I really wanted to get some done before I left <pause dur="short"/> but it's just been so not and the thing is I can't even show someone around without feeling like I'm cheating them</u>
<u n="160" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0002">do you know what I mean? Cos I'm trying to get them to move into this hell hole</u>
<u n="162" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0002">I mean <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but yeah I'm flying out next Friday <pause dur="short"/> so I get a month away from the slug palace <pause dur="short"/> yay</u>
<u n="164" who="S0018">the slug palace <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And how was Morocco?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0002">Morocco was interesting <pause dur="short"/> it was good I suppose <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018">how long did you go for?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0002">four days</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018">oh it was a quick quick trip</u>
<u n="169" who="S0002">it was a very quick trip <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> we left we drove to Heathrow on like a Thursday night <pause dur="short"/> and then  and then  we took a <trunc>f</trunc> plane at like six in the morning on a Friday <pause dur="short"/> arrived there at ten or something <pause dur="short"/> and then on the way back we were exceptionally stupid <pause dur="short"/> we our flight was at eight P M from Morocco <pause dur="short"/> and we arrived here at <trunc>mi</trunc> we arrived in <trunc>Lon</trunc> at <trunc>Lon</trunc> in London</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0002">woah prepositions um in London at midnight <pause dur="short"/> then we slept for like a few hours and then we drove up <pause dur="short"/> and then my friend who lives in <anon type="place"/> didn't wanna drive to <anon type="place"/> so she dumped me at a station at like eight in the morning <pause dur="short"/> and I ended up missing all of my classes</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0002">and I was just like oh mate I'm gonna kill you <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018">and how was the Morocco part of the journey? SE <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0002">I was kind of surprised <pause dur="short"/> I expected it to be more not as <trunc>r</trunc> er how can I put this? I expected it to be a more modern city</u>
<u n="176" who="S0018">really? Where were you?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0002">marrakesh</u>
<u n="178" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="179" who="S0002">um <pause dur="short"/> and it wasn't at all <pause dur="short"/> it was pretty much like Pakistan or <trunc>s</trunc> like Cambodia or yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was  it was  up there with <trunc>s</trunc> some of the most sort of dodgy trips that I've done</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0002">in terms of <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean they had sort of running hot water and things like that so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0018">well it's better than what you've got at the moment <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0002">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm living in a third world country right now <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="184" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">little republic of third world</u>
<u n="186" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0002">yes <pause dur="short"/> that's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="188" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">and did you see anything nice? Or buy anything nice?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0002">oh my friend wanted to go <pause dur="short"/> sE The whole reason she wanted to go was to go shopping</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="192" who="S0002">in the souqs and the markets <pause dur="short"/> have you ever been?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> I planned a trip to go but um I planned a trip to go with my best friend who I um was working at the same place with <pause dur="short"/> and at the last moment they told us that we weren't allowed to take holiday at the same time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0002">what?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">I know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0002">oh that sucks</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">we'd already got the tickets</u>
<u n="198" who="S0002">huh</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">and everything <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0002">that's really bad <pause dur="short"/> where were you gonna go?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">we were going to do we were going to I think arrive in Fes</u>
<u n="202" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">and then travel down the east coast <pause dur="short"/> go to <trunc>Ous</trunc> <trunc>Ouasidi</trunc> er Oualidia? mm <pause dur="short"/> can't remember <pause dur="short"/> it was like twelve years ago <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0002">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I dunno about travelling there <pause dur="short"/> I went with a female friend and we just <pause dur="short"/> she didn't get hassled for some strange reason <pause dur="short"/> I got hassled <pause dur="short"/> but it was not I mean like my friend who I went with has been to Tunisia and said that that's much worse <pause dur="short"/> so I get I understand that what I went through was not that bad compared to other countries but I still don't wanna go through it again so <pause dur="short"/> they were pretty rude man <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">I find that that um like the kind of TE Maghrebins in France are just so rude</u>
<u n="206" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0018">and there's like there's no barriers <pause dur="short"/> there's no they'll <trunc>st</trunc> like they won't stop think that it's just not polite or not socially acceptable to come and sit next to you in a bar</u>
<u n="208" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0018">and just not chat you up even <pause dur="short"/> just <trunc>l</trunc> blatantly leer at you</u>
<u n="210" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> that's horrible</u>
<u n="211" who="S0018">it's disgusting</u>
<u n="212" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I noticed that <pause dur="short"/> I mean there are places in Europe where it happens actually <pause dur="short"/> I mean I remember when I was travelling</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018">it's weird though <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't happen in Spain</u>
<u n="214" who="S0002">it doesn't happen in Spain <pause dur="short"/> but that's cos they're all an amorous bunch aren't they <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="215" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0002">I mean I got followed once or twice in Spain <pause dur="short"/> and I had like random things happen <pause dur="short"/> like a guy on the subway in Barcelona got down on one knee in front of me and sung me a song with his guitar <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like oh please go away <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0018">are you sure his best mate wasn't trying to rob you from behind? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0002">um</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">Pick pocket</u>
<u n="220" who="S0002">probably <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="221" who="S0018">it was probably a diversion tactic <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0002">yeah it probably was <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're right <pause dur="short"/> well that's normally the thing in Spain though <pause dur="short"/> they have their own problems</u>
<u n="223" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0002">different ones <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But yeah <pause dur="short"/> no in France it was a bit dodgy <pause dur="short"/> and in some parts of Eastern Europe it was a little bit <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> no er Morocco was just I don't know why <pause dur="short"/> er they thought I was local <pause dur="short"/> which surprised me <pause dur="short"/> because</u>
<u n="225" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="226" who="S0002">I thought if they thought I was local they would treat me with a little bit more respect <pause dur="short"/> I mean I was dressed like a local <pause dur="short"/> pretty much <pause dur="short"/> like I don't think I stood out blaringly obvious <pause dur="short"/>SE I'm a tourist <pause dur="short"/> but er they just were so rude <pause dur="short"/> and the things they would say I just like I wish I didn't understand French</u>
<u n="227" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh no</u>
<u n="228" who="S0002">Cos I don't wanna know what you're saying <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0018">so like lecherous things</u>
<u n="230" who="S0002">just nasty <pause dur="short"/> they just comment on your body and what they wanna do <pause dur="short"/> and you're just like I'm gonna keep walking and ignore you <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna pretend you don't exist <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's like</u>
<u n="231" who="S0018">just say you can think it but just don't vocalize it <pause dur="short"/> alright?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0002">just don't even  don't even  look at me <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It was pretty nasty actually</u>
<u n="233" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0002">and</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">I'm sorry</u>
<u n="236" who="S0002">well it was an experience <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realize it would be that bad <pause dur="short"/> like I have bruises on my arm where someone grabbed me <pause dur="short"/> I was like</u>
<u n="237" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="238" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0018">crikey <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0002">and my mate was like why don't you just hit them? Or like shout at them? And I was like we're in a Muslim country <pause dur="short"/> you can't do that</u>
<u n="241" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0002">like the men it's all men <pause dur="short"/> there's no women around</u>
<u n="243" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0002">no one's gonna save you <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0002">they're all gonna stick up for each other <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">oh well</u>
<u n="248" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">you know</u>
<u n="250" who="S0002">so I'm not going back there</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0002">but apart from that</u>
<u n="253" who="S0018">and I saw that you said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that you've got friends in Thailand where she's going <pause dur="short"/> how did have you visited have you  have you  travelled to Thailand too?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0002">I have been to Thailand <pause dur="short"/> I went a few years ago <pause dur="short"/> I did like a big six week trip backpacking around</u>
<u n="255" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0002">Thailand Cambodia and Vietnam</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> so that's how you got everything in <pause dur="short"/> it's like  it's like  Katie said you you've been everywhere</u>
<u n="258" who="S0002">I haven't been everywhere</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">you know people everywhere <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0002">I haven't been everywhere <pause dur="short"/> I haven't been to enough places <pause dur="short"/> I worked it out the other day <pause dur="short"/> I've been to twenty-six or twenty-seven countries <pause dur="short"/> and there is like another fifteen that I really <vocal desc="laugh"/> want to go to</u>
<u n="261" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0002">I was like oh maybe one a year is my</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0002">aim at the moment <pause dur="short"/> to tick a new country off</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018">oh my friend's just been to Burma and it looks amazing</u>
<u n="266" who="S0002">amazing</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">she had such a fantastic time <pause dur="short"/> she really made an effort to meet <trunc>peop</trunc> meet locals and</u>
<u n="268" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018">and do local things</u>
<u n="270" who="S0002">things</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">as opposed to touristy stuff</u>
<u n="272" who="S0002">how did she do that? Cos I always wonder <pause dur="short"/> like what's the best way to sort of get a real experience when you go somewhere? It's hard <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018">I think she's just got such a that</u>
<u n="274" who="S0002"><trunc>Pers</trunc> personality</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018">kind of personality <pause dur="short"/> she really  she really</u>
<u n="276" who="S0002">that's pretty awesome</u>
<u n="277" who="S0018">takes risks in chatting with people</u>
<u n="278" who="S0002">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0018">and because she's so eager and she's very I dunno she's very um engaging</u>
<u n="280" who="S0002">yes <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I can understand</u>
<u n="281" who="S0018">I think she picks her  she picks her  victims well</u>
<u n="282" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0002">charming</u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">but yeah she was chatting she she travelled with a another girl who she met in a a backpacking place</u>
<u n="285" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0018">en en route <pause dur="short"/> and I think the fact that there were the two of them together gave them confidence</u>
<u n="287" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> to</u>
<u n="288" who="S0018">to maybe</u>
<u n="289" who="S0002">to sort of</u>
<u n="290" who="S0018">chat with people <pause dur="short"/> um but they got invited back to families' houses and</u>
<u n="291" who="S0002">nice</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">had a few whispered political discussions and</u>
<u n="293" who="S0002">blimey</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">went and stayed at er temples and stuff like that</u>
<u n="295" who="S0002">my mum's one of those <pause dur="short"/> she's really good at sort of TE wheedling her way into <trunc>situatio</trunc></u>
<u n="296" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0002">I mean a long time ago they came to visit me in Japan <pause dur="short"/> and I would come home from work and my mum and dad would be sitting there and my dad would be going don't tell her  don't tell her  And I'm like don't tell me what?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0002">and every day they had some story of how</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0002">they'd had a tour in a police van <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0002">someone had driven them home <pause dur="short"/> or this woman had invited them into their house <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like you're in Japan people don't even do that</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0002">but you're just like working your way round the countryside <pause dur="short"/> like it was pretty funny <pause dur="short"/> er they had a really good time</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">that's good</u>
<u n="307" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0018">whenever my parents used to come to visit me I felt I just felt that they they abandoned all abilities to make any decisions at the airport</u>
<u n="309" who="S0002">oh and <trunc>e</trunc> expected you to do everything?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="311" who="S0002">oh</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018">I mean I can <trunc>un</trunc></u>
<u n="313" who="S0002">oh I just leave my parents to it</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">I can understand <pause dur="short"/> cos you know they don't speak the language they're a bit</u>
<u n="315" who="S0002">is this in Spain?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but also France actually</u>
<u n="317" who="S0002">yeah?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">when I was in living in France as well <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> though <trunc>w</trunc> I have friends who do that</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0002">they come visit you and they're just like you're gonna look after me right? And I'm like um my language skills are just as bad as yours <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="322" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0002">Don't be deceived by the fact that I've been living here for three months <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Like it doesn't mean anything <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So where's the next country on your list?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0002">to go new place? Or to go? New I really wanna go to China <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I'm sort of hoping while I'm in Japan cos I'm going for quite a long time that we can manage like a week trip <pause dur="short"/> I have a friend that lives in Shanghai with his girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> and they have a big apartment <pause dur="short"/> and they've said that we can go stay with them <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">cool</u>
<u n="327" who="S0002">I'm sort of hoping that it might happen <pause dur="short"/> but it's very hard to sort out the visa</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because you need a visa to go to China <pause dur="short"/> and they need to know your concrete travel plans <pause dur="short"/> so I can't apply for it here</u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0002">because I want to buy the ticket in Japan <pause dur="short"/> so that means I'd have to apply for the visa in Japan <pause dur="short"/> dunno how long it takes</u>
<u n="332" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0002">so I'm not sure if it's even possible</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018">that's a shame</u>
<u n="335" who="S0002">it is <pause dur="short"/> I wish I could just get up and go but</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018">er go to Taiwan instead <pause dur="short"/> I don't think you need a visa to <trunc>g</trunc> get into there</u>
<u n="337" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> can you go from Taiwan? I know you can go from Hong Kong into China quite easily</u>
<u n="338" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="339" who="S0002">I dunno about Taiwan</u>
<u n="340" who="S0018">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I've no idea <pause dur="short"/> and so did you were you trying to get um teaching work in China?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0002">before?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know the the whole pre-sessional thing</u>
<u n="343" who="S0002">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to <pause dur="short"/> but I I kept umming and erring which was my demise because</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="345" who="S0002">it would be from May to June <pause dur="short"/> and I have to hand in my first full draft by the end of June <pause dur="short"/> so to do both at the same time was probably a bad idea <pause dur="short"/> but I am overlapping one <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>mon</trunc> six weeks of pre-sessional with the end of my dissertation</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">how many weeks have you got to do your dissertation?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0002">I've got from May to <trunc>Septem</trunc> beginning of September <pause dur="short"/> so May June July August <pause dur="short"/> four months</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0002">so I'm hoping that I'll be pretty much done by the end of July <pause dur="short"/> then I can do corrections in August and work at the same time for the six weeks and that's the plan <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's gonna happen</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> has um has your tutor been quite supportive and helpful in <trunc>di</trunc> er your proposals? Your <trunc>d</trunc> for your dissertation? Or? You know it sounds like you're just giving her ideas and she's</u>
<u n="351" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just say I've thought about this and she tells me yes you can do it no you can't do it you can do that for a PhD love <pause dur="short"/> and I'm like I don't wanna do a PhD</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0002">I just wanna get through this <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're alright <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's better here than it was at my previous university <pause dur="short"/> when I was an undergrad I felt like I didn't know anyone</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0002">but here it's quite a small department <pause dur="short"/> but the problem is is they won't give you ideas <pause dur="short"/> and if you're really stuck then you're really stuck</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0002">like if you don't know what to do <pause dur="short"/> cos I really can't think of er a plan B <pause dur="short"/> which I probably might need</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">what what are other your fellow students doing?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0002">most people are not doing teaching related projects</u>
<u n="360" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="361" who="S0002">because there's actually only five applied linguistics people <pause dur="short"/> there's a huge number of critical discourse in communication like my friend that you met earlier <pause dur="short"/> um and there's quite a lot of TEFL people <pause dur="short"/> but they're doing very TEFLy things</u>
<u n="362" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0002">like how does this affect a classroom? Or I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I don't really wanna do anything too TEFLy <pause dur="short"/> cos I didn't I did half of my courses very linguistic and half TEFL <pause dur="short"/> so I tried to make a balance <pause dur="short"/> but it might have been my undoing in some <vocal desc="laugh"/> ways <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">what kind of TEFL stuff did you cover?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0002">I did teacher training</u>
<u n="366" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0002">um <pause dur="short"/> english for academic purposes <pause dur="short"/> and that's it actually <pause dur="short"/> and everything else has been linguistics</u>
<u n="368" who="S0018">and did they actually provide modules lectures and stuff on those subjects?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0002">yes</u>
<u n="370" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="371" who="S0002">but that's part of the TEFL course that I kind of</u>
<u n="372" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="373" who="S0002">transferred over to a little bit</u>
<u n="374" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="375" who="S0002">but the other stuff I've done is corpus linguistics <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="376" who="S0018">aha <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0002">discourse yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um discourse analysis <pause dur="short"/> and social <trunc>socio</trunc> sociolinguistics and psycholinguistics</u>
<u n="378" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="379" who="S0002">and yeah kind of</u>
<u n="380" who="S0018">have you had to cover like structural linguistics and stuff like that?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0002">we had a choice <pause dur="short"/> I didn't cos</u>
<u n="382" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> good choice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0002">we all did do a bit of functional grammar <pause dur="short"/> which was not fun</u>
<u n="384" who="S0018">urgh</u>
<u n="385" who="S0002">urgh <pause dur="short"/> I ended up writing my assignment on we had a choice between functional grammar analysis and <trunc>f</trunc> um something to do with lexis <pause dur="short"/> and I went down the lexis road <pause dur="short"/> which was probably the best decision I've ever made</u>
<u n="386" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0002">because I would've failed the grammar <pause dur="short"/> a lot of people failed apparently</u>
<u n="388" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="389" who="S0002">I think like cos we spent three lessons three ninety minute lessons analyzing one sentence</u>
<u n="390" who="S0018">oh my Lord <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0002">so most of us were not really prepared to go in and do a full analysis by ourself <pause dur="short"/> and I think about more than half of the people that submitted that paper failed it <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was a good idea not to do it</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">how long are papers?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0002">four thousand words</u>
<u n="394" who="S0018">huh <pause dur="short"/> four thousand words? Crikey <pause dur="short"/> it's all</u>
<u n="395" who="S0002">our dissertation's only twelve thousand</u>
<u n="396" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/>SE That's not actually much</u>
<u n="397" who="S0002">it's not <pause dur="short"/> its actually probably not enough <pause dur="short"/> cos I have a</u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">especially</u>
<u n="399" who="S0002">problem with TE wittering</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">especially for a research project</u>
<u n="401" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0018">as well <pause dur="short"/> were the papers just like essays? Or were they research?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0002">we have one research paper this term <pause dur="short"/> and everything else is just essays</u>
<u n="404" who="S0018">so how many have there been in total? Apart from the dissertation</u>
<u n="405" who="S0002">not that many you know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why I spend all my time complaining <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="406" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0002">I've done three already <pause dur="short"/> I have three more now <pause dur="short"/> and then I have my dissertation <pause dur="short"/> so six papers plus a dissertation</u>
<u n="408" who="S0018">still quite heavy going</u>
<u n="409" who="S0002">it's</u>
<u n="410" who="S0018">especially when you have to read so much</u>
<u n="411" who="S0002">I know</u>
<u n="412" who="S0018">before you <pause dur="short"/> I I my problem was that I couldn't  I couldn't  get out of that stage of reading and taking notes</u>
<u n="413" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0018">I had to always force myself into starting to write things <pause dur="short"/> I just</u>
<u n="415" who="S0002">because you were still reading and taking notes</u>
<u n="416" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I feel I just feel really uninspired <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="419" who="S0002">so I'm just like it's not interesting <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't wanna write about it <pause dur="short"/> that's a problem</u>
<u n="420" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0002">like you have to be interested otherwise <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="422" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0002">well you don't have to be interested <pause dur="short"/> but it sure does help <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="424" who="S0018">and it what what do you think the masters level is like? Cos I was you know the course I was doing was er um at a masters level <pause dur="short"/> but I thought that it was graded <pause dur="short"/> I mean huh I read some of the papers that the research projects that um some of my fellow school mates <vocal desc="laugh"/> classmates whatever you call it</u>
<u n="425" who="S0002">mhm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0018">er had written <pause dur="short"/> cos they asked me to proofread them</u>
<u n="427" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> not only was the language awful but the actual content was awful as well</u>
<u n="429" who="S0002">but did they do well?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0018">well they passed</u>
<u n="431" who="S0002">they passed?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0018">they passed a masters level assignment</u>
<u n="433" who="S0002">I think passing well I don't know to be honest because I proofread <trunc>s</trunc> one of my friend's papers and she failed two papers <pause dur="short"/> and when I started reading it I thought why has she failed? It's not that bad <pause dur="short"/> but when I got into it structurally</u>
<u n="434" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0002">and content wise she didn't have a clear understanding of what she was doing</u>
<u n="436" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="437" who="S0002">so I did understand why</u>
<u n="438" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0002">but I think I mean you know I don't know many people that are getting firsts to be honest <pause dur="short"/> like it seems pretty hard to do well</u>
<u n="440" who="S0018">well I got</u>
<u n="441" who="S0002">it seems fairly</u>
<u n="442" who="S0018">I got two distinctions</u>
<u n="443" who="S0002">oo <pause dur="short"/> get you</u>
<u n="444" who="S0018">and I was just absolutely floored cos it's</u>
<u n="445" who="S0002">why? You've so much experience you're</u>
<u n="446" who="S0018">because it just</u>
<u n="447" who="S0002">bringing to the table <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="448" who="S0018">yeah but it just felt like it was the <trunc>re</trunc> the research was completely Mickey Mouse</u>
<u n="449" who="S0002">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="450" who="S0018">whereas I was thinking oo masters level research it's going to be really heavy and</u>
<u n="451" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0018">it's gonna be statistical analysis <pause dur="short"/> and it's gonna be</u>
<u n="453" who="S0002">no I don't think it is that bad</u>
<u n="454" who="S0018">and lots of different variables <pause dur="short"/> and it wasn't <pause dur="short"/> it was just basically</u>
<u n="455" who="S0002">common sense</u>
<u n="456" who="S0018">Mickey Mouse</u>
<u n="457" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0002">how many papers have you already submitted?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0018">three <pause dur="short"/> and I'd have to do three more</u>
<u n="460" who="S0002">okay <pause dur="short"/> and then dissertation?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0018">no there is no dissertation</u>
<u n="462" who="S0002">there's no dissertation?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0018">Cos it's it's so practical based</u>
<u n="464" who="S0002">and how long are the papers?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0018">three thousand words</u>
<u n="466" who="S0002">okay</u>
<u n="467" who="S0018">which is a nightmare because it's so difficult <pause dur="short"/> because you have so many things that you have to do <pause dur="short"/> the requirements of the</u>
<u n="468" who="S0002">so keeping it short and concise</u>
<u n="469" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0002">and</u>
<u n="471" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0002">yep <pause dur="short"/> that's hard</u>
<u n="473" who="S0018">it was difficult <pause dur="short"/> like so you had to write an introduction <pause dur="short"/> review the government documentation <pause dur="short"/> then review the literature <pause dur="short"/> then describe your rationale behind choosing the research methods that you did</u>
<u n="474" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0018">and then describe the research methods</u>
<u n="476" who="S0002">that's a lot</u>
<u n="477" who="S0018">and then TE analyse the research methods and TE analyse how if they worked <pause dur="short"/> did I just say that? Can't remember</u>
<u n="478" who="S0002">no</u>
<u n="479" who="S0018">see I'm getting confused just telling you about it</u>
<u n="480" who="S0002">well the I mean if it if you have to do that much it's literally what? A paragraph for each thing?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0018">more or less</u>
<u n="482" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean er</u>
<u n="483" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously you have to do the critical analysis with it <pause dur="short"/> I the yeah the <trunc>crit</trunc> the review of the literature</u>
<u n="484" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0018">was more or less two sides</u>
<u n="486" who="S0002">sides</u>
<u n="487" who="S0018">and then the evaluation and of your findings and criticizing your research methods was about two sides <pause dur="short"/> but I <trunc>d</trunc> I dunno I just felt that it was really</u>
<u n="488" who="S0002">Mickey Mouse?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0018">Mickey Mouse <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Squeak</u>
<u n="490" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0018">but I guess you don't find that <pause dur="short"/> maybe cos on my course it was more practical</u>
<u n="492" who="S0002">I'm finding well I mean I don't I I didn't know at the beginning what a good level was <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? Like what is what was a distinction? You have no idea until you've actually submitted something and got it back <pause dur="short"/> and for my first paper I got a distinction</u>
<u n="493" who="S0018">all As</u>
<u n="494" who="S0002">and then after that I didn't do so well <pause dur="short"/> I got two merits <pause dur="short"/> but low merits <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought I couldn't see the difference <vocal desc="laugh"/> between what I had done in the first and the other two <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like okay <pause dur="short"/> you set me up on a high but I still don't understand how to get up there now</u>
<u n="495" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0002">like it's er the the things last term cos it was all new <pause dur="short"/> I mean linguistics I don't really have a background in it <pause dur="short"/> I didn't really know <pause dur="short"/> it was all brand new <pause dur="short"/> they that all felt quite hard <pause dur="short"/> but this term the two TEFL papers <pause dur="short"/> they don't seem hard <pause dur="short"/> it's not challenging <pause dur="short"/> it's just trying to put it all together in a good way</u>
<u n="497" who="S0018"><unclear/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0002">in fact I might show you one of my papers in a bit <pause dur="short"/> and go</u>
<u n="501" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no problem</u>
<u n="502" who="S0002">what do you think of this rubbish</u>
<u n="503" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0002">oh</u>
<u n="505" who="S0018">it sounds so difficult having to choose your dissertation topic with no hardly any support though</u>
<u n="506" who="S0002">but I guess that's the way it is</u>
<u n="507" who="S0018">so what's your driving instructor like?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0002">I thought no more complaining</u>
<u n="509" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0002">he's alright <pause dur="short"/> he shouts a lot</u>
<u n="511" who="S0018">why?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0002">but apart from that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I thought that was normal <pause dur="short"/> why? What's your driving instructor like?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0018">really chilled <pause dur="short"/> he's such a nice guy <pause dur="short"/> he's really er er er his instructions are really clear <pause dur="short"/> and they come at exactly the right moment <pause dur="short"/> and he chats around them as well to keep me really calm <pause dur="short"/> and it's it's as if like everything's really natural <pause dur="short"/> I felt</u>
<u n="514" who="S0002">mine has a lisp <pause dur="short"/> and I can't figure out what he's saying half the time</u>
<u n="515" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0002">which is not helpful <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then he thinks I'm not listening <pause dur="short"/> and he shouts at me <pause dur="short"/> and I'm like <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know what you're saying <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="518" who="S0002">but I mean I like him <pause dur="short"/> and he I feel like he pushes me <pause dur="short"/> but he's quite critical if I mess up <pause dur="short"/> I mean how many lessons have you had?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0018">three</u>
<u n="520" who="S0002">oh you're ever?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0018">yeah in my life</u>
<u n="522" who="S0002">oh okay</u>
<u n="523" who="S0018">this is my third one <pause dur="short"/> I had two this week <pause dur="short"/> and one last week <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0002">blimey <pause dur="short"/> and you're enjoying it though?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> actually while I'm actually in the lesson with him it comes quite naturally <pause dur="short"/> and it's not as</u>
<u n="526" who="S0002">do you get worked up before the lessons?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> quite a little bit</u>
<u n="528" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I do too</u>
<u n="529" who="S0018">he told me that I was gonna be driving on the <anon type="place"/> the day before yesterday <pause dur="short"/> he told me right tomorrow I'm taking you out on the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you'll be doing forty miles an hour in fourth gear or something <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh my life</u>
<u n="530" who="S0002">already? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0018">crikey</u>
<u n="532" who="S0002">and it was alright?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was fine <pause dur="short"/> there weren't many cars on the road <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't rush hour <pause dur="short"/> but <vocal desc="cough"/> he said next  he said next  lesson if your neck's okay because in my second lesson he took me around quite a quiet er residential area that had loads of speed bumps</u>
<u n="534" who="S0002">oh yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0018">and you know I've got problems with my neck?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0018">well oh the day after I was like</u>
<u n="538" who="S0002">ff</u>
<u n="539" who="S0018">like today we're gonna do emergency stops <pause dur="short"/> I was like no no no</u>
<u n="540" who="S0002">already?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0018">no I can't do it <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna</u>
<u n="542" who="S0002">already?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>pu</trunc> he pushes me</u>
<u n="544" who="S0002">that's really quick</u>
<u n="545" who="S0018">he pushes me quite quickly</u>
<u n="546" who="S0002">okay <pause dur="short"/> maybe I need to change instructors</u>
<u n="547" who="S0018">well I was thinking if you're getting er you're travelling over to your parents to have this <unclear/> guy?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0018">well why don't you just catch the number one bus <pause dur="short"/> get off in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and he'll pick you up in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos I can't</u>
<u n="550" who="S0002">Don't they normally pick you up from most places though?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> well he only works the south of <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> he wouldn't  he wouldn't  travel</u>
<u n="552" who="S0002">the thing is that I'm I've been driving around the test centre roads near my parents' house <pause dur="short"/> and it's got a higher pass rate than the ones near here <pause dur="short"/> because it's quiet it's a quiet very very quiet area</u>
<u n="553" who="S0018">I don't understand <pause dur="short"/> higher what?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0002">um so um different test centres have different pass rates <pause dur="short"/> and I've been practising around the roads around the test centre that I would go do my test at</u>
<u n="555" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0002">so I wanna stay in that area <pause dur="short"/> because I know it <pause dur="short"/> otherwise I'll have to learn a whole new area for the test</u>
<u n="557" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="558" who="S0002">so I've had like sixteen lessons <pause dur="short"/> so I'm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> quite advanced</u>
<u n="560" who="S0002">probably about ten lessons away from taking my test I'd say</u>
<u n="561" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0002">I haven't done many manoeuvres <pause dur="short"/> I haven't done an emergency stop <pause dur="short"/> I've only done bay park like <trunc>para</trunc> reversing back parking <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know what that's called <pause dur="short"/> which is not a good thing</u>
<u n="563" who="S0018">gosh <pause dur="short"/> I've not even yeah no I haven't even done a reverse <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0002">I didn't do that until like my tenth lesson or so</u>
<u n="565" who="S0018">what were you doing for your first three or four lessons?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0002">driving driving driving <pause dur="short"/> getting used to the car <pause dur="short"/> getting it all sort of automatic in my head</u>
<u n="567" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you see I <trunc>ha</trunc> I don't feel that I've had enough of that <pause dur="short"/> I don't feel automatic enough when I'm changing gear and</u>
<u n="568" who="S0002">oh I'm only there now <pause dur="short"/> and it's seventeen lessons later <pause dur="short"/> and now I feel it's quite natural to do everything <pause dur="short"/> I'm not thinking about it <pause dur="short"/> I'm not looking at the gear stick <pause dur="short"/> I'm not looking at my speed <pause dur="short"/> it's all <trunc>co</trunc> sort of just</u>
<u n="569" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="570" who="S0002">but it's taken a long time</u>
<u n="571" who="S0018">and how much do you pay per lessons?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0002">ninety-two quid for five lessons <pause dur="short"/> five hours</u>
<u n="573" who="S0018">so that's eighteen quid an hour</u>
<u n="574" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm paying about seventeen <pause dur="short"/> I pay a hundred and seventy for ten lessons <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0002">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's alright</u>
<u n="577" who="S0018">oo <pause dur="short"/> and have you started revising your Highway Code? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0002">I've passed my theory</u>
<u n="579" who="S0018">oh have you?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I passed it um in January</u>
<u n="581" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0002">but I'm taking a big long break now <pause dur="short"/> so I don't</u>
<u n="583" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="584" who="S0002">I'm gonna have to come back and sort of get back onto it <pause dur="short"/> I really just wanna get it out the way</u>
<u n="585" who="S0018">when how do you do the theory then? Do you just apply to do it?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0002">you just apply online and pay online <pause dur="short"/> and you can reserve any date <pause dur="short"/> and there's a test centre in the middle of town</u>
<u n="587" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="588" who="S0002">near Argos</u>
<u n="589" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="590" who="S0002">and you just go in and do it <pause dur="short"/> and yeah it was alright <pause dur="short"/> I er literally kinda read the Highway Code the day before</u>
<u n="591" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and didn't I didn't think I was gonna pass</u>
<u n="593" who="S0018">but did had you learnt a lot from the driving that you'd done?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0002">no <pause dur="short"/> and I'm one of these people that actually has no common sense sometimes <pause dur="short"/> and don't understand the <trunc>ba</trunc> like my friends er most of my friends drive and passed their test when they were like eighteen <pause dur="short"/> and they're all like testing me a while ago <pause dur="short"/> and they were like how do you not know this? It's common sense <pause dur="short"/> and I was like I just don't know <pause dur="short"/> I never paid any attentions when I was in a car with anyone <pause dur="short"/> like I don't really care about <trunc>driv</trunc> I didn't really care about driving <pause dur="short"/> never really wanted to pass <pause dur="short"/> so I wasn't really interested <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't I think I was lucky and my test was not a hard one</u>
<u n="595" who="S0018">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> what kind of</u>
<u n="596" who="S0002">it depends on what you get</u>
<u n="597" who="S0018">what kind of questions came up?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0002">the usual <pause dur="short"/> like what's this sign mean? What's this speed limit? The the <trunc>har</trunc> the worst part is the hazard perception part <pause dur="short"/> which is you watch the video and then you have to click when you see a hazard <pause dur="short"/> and it only marks you on two <pause dur="short"/> and if you have to click within a second to get the full points <pause dur="short"/> so if you click a little bit too late you lose all those points <pause dur="short"/> and that's quite difficult <pause dur="short"/> when I did all the practices for that I failed it every single time <pause dur="short"/> but somehow in the actual test I passed it</u>
<u n="599" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh right <pause dur="short"/> and what kind of hazards come up?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0002">just for example if so you're watching a video and your car's travelling down a road and you're looking out for people stepping onto the road or something that might <pause dur="short"/> the thing is there are lots of things that can develop into a hazard</u>
<u n="601" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0002">like someone who's walking along the pavement might suddenly step onto the road <pause dur="short"/> but you don't get  you don't get  marked on seeing a potential hazard <pause dur="short"/> you get marked on seeing a hazard when it occurs</u>
<u n="603" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="604" who="S0002">so I'm just like click click</u>
<u n="605" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0002">click click</u>
<u n="607" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0002">click click click click like <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just yeah <pause dur="short"/> um and the best hint that somebody gave me for the hazard  for the hazard  perception is you see a hazard <pause dur="short"/> click <pause dur="short"/> wait two seconds <pause dur="short"/> click again <pause dur="short"/> because if you didn't if you clicked it too quickly you'd lose the points</u>
<u n="609" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="610" who="S0002">so make sure you do it twice at least when you see the hazard <pause dur="short"/> and then you've got a better chance of getting some points for it <pause dur="short"/> rather than just</u>
<u n="611" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="612" who="S0002">doing it once <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="613" who="S0018">didn't the theory test used to be just a few questions asked by the <trunc>ins</trunc> by the tester? When you were doing your</u>
<u n="614" who="S0002">you still have some questions asked by the <trunc>exa</trunc> by the driving instructor on your <trunc>dri</trunc></u>
<u n="615" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's more about the car</u>
<u n="617" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="618" who="S0002">like you have to lift up the bonnet and say what's what <pause dur="short"/> and stuff like yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="620" who="S0002">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> just little  just little  Just like three or four questions</u>
<u n="621" who="S0018">oh my life</u>
<u n="622" who="S0002">nothing major <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> it feels like a very high hill to climb to pass</u>
<u n="623" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0002">I mean cos they say like on average you take as many lessons as your age <pause dur="short"/> that's a lot of er lessons and a lot of money</u>
<u n="625" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh crikey</u>
<u n="626" who="S0002">and I'm just like uh</u>
<u n="627" who="S0018">I've never heard that one <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0002">God <pause dur="short"/> cos like most of my friends keep going oh I passed in like twenty lessons <pause dur="short"/> which is actually probably a big lie</u>
<u n="629" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0002">I would say <pause dur="short"/> I don't think most people could pass in <trunc>twent</trunc> er not unless they're driving someone else's car all the time <pause dur="short"/> but you don't even do manoeuvres until like</u>
<u n="631" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I'm not having any practice outside of the lessons</u>
<u n="632" who="S0002">I neither am I <pause dur="short"/> so it's just the lessons <pause dur="short"/> and that's quite a big ask</u>
<u n="633" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0002">so</u>
<u n="635" who="S0018">how old are you?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0002">twenty-eight</u>
<u n="637" who="S0018">how many lessons have you had?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0002">seventeen</u>
<u n="639" who="S0018">oh well eleven more</u>
<u n="640" who="S0002">I think I'll need a few more to be honest</u>
<u n="641" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll see <pause dur="short"/> I'm just happy to be er</u>
<u n="642" who="S0002">doing it</u>
<u n="643" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've dreamt about it so many times <pause dur="short"/> that I've been driving</u>
<u n="644" who="S0002">wow</u>
<u n="645" who="S0018">and it's always been such a huge thing er when I wake up I'm like oh my  oh my  gosh I was driving in my sleep <pause dur="short"/> I'm like</u>
<u n="646" who="S0002">how quickly do you wanna do it?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0018">um I've</u>
<u n="648" who="S0002">not bothered</u>
<u n="649" who="S0018">I'm er not rushed <pause dur="short"/> I'm not I don't need a car <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to have a car even</u>
<u n="650" who="S0002">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0018">I'd prefer to live in a nice little city that's got good public transport</u>
<u n="652" who="S0002">me too <pause dur="short"/> I don't want a car at all</u>
<u n="653" who="S0018">but I just thought it would it's a good idea to</u>
<u n="654" who="S0002">it's good to have it <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="655" who="S0018">take advantage of this time</u>
<u n="656" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's the same</u>
<u n="657" who="S0018">also if there's any jobs that come up that require</u>
<u n="658" who="S0002">that you need to drive</u>
<u n="659" who="S0018">a driving licence</u>
<u n="660" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this is what I thought <pause dur="short"/> it was just like it's just something it's <pause dur="short"/> one of my friends broke her leg in Japan and I was just thinking neither me or my boyfriend can drive <pause dur="short"/> if one of us could drive we could help her out</u>
<u n="661" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0002">and it's just such a shame when you're like okay we can't help anyone <pause dur="short"/> can't do anything</u>
<u n="663" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0002">and it would just be useful to to be able to hire a car sometimes to sort something out</u>
<u n="665" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0002">and so <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah kind of just wanna get it out of the way <pause dur="short"/> and it was supposed to be a competition between me and my boyfriend who would do it first <pause dur="short"/> but he hasn't even started his lessons</u>
<u n="667" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0002">he seems to think he can do it in a month <pause dur="short"/> I've been driving since last October <pause dur="short"/> I'm like really? Good luck mate</u>
<u n="669" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0002">and in Japan they don't let you practise on the road</u>
<u n="671" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="672" who="S0002">they practise in a little grid area in the back of a test centre</u>
<u n="673" who="S0018">actually do you know what? I think I'd prefer to do that for the first</u>
<u n="674" who="S0002">for the first one or two</u>
<u n="675" who="S0018">first few lessons <pause dur="short"/> just to get confident to know what you're dealing with mechanically in the car</u>
<u n="676" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0018">not I mean tut not bonnet and explain what's going on but what you have to do in order to change gear <pause dur="short"/> what you have to do in order to stop at a junction and <pause dur="short"/> it would be a lot easier to do that without a lot easier to get automatic without with that without worrying about</u>
<u n="678" who="S0002">without worrying about the road</u>
<u n="679" who="S0018">oh there's someone following me <pause dur="short"/> I bet they're thinking bloody learner driver <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0002">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've developed this like my er driving instructor calls it a mouse sound</u>
<u n="681" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0002">instead of swearing when I'm driving I always just go eek eek</u>
<u n="683" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0002">and he's just like stop it  stop it  <vocal desc="laugh"/> And I'm like you don't understand how much I would be swearing if I wasn't doing that though</u>
<u n="685" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I said I think I said bloody</u>
<u n="686" who="S0002"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0018">and then I said oh excuse my French <pause dur="short"/> and he said don't worry I used to be a builder</u>
<u n="688" who="S0002"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0018">there used to never</u>
<u n="690" who="S0002">heard it all</u>
<u n="691" who="S0018">be a sentence without a swear word <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he said my driving instructor was like I would prefer that you just swore instead of made that stupid noise <pause dur="short"/> and I was like okay <pause dur="short"/> actually last week we went out with my dad in the back <pause dur="short"/> cos my parents just bought a new car and they put me on the insurance <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't driven it yet because I'm terrified <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a new car</u>
<u n="693" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0002">and I don't wanna just drive it into a wall <pause dur="short"/> and then my driving instructor was like I'll take you out and your dad can sit in the back so he can see how much instruction you still need <pause dur="short"/> and he can er</u>
<u n="695" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="696" who="S0002">so I mean I drove it fine <pause dur="short"/> it no major incident <pause dur="short"/> but I just kept squeaking</u>
<u n="697" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0002">because like the clutch and everything is so different on a different car</u>
<u n="699" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0002">and it was I was just like couldn't <trunc>f</trunc> feel the bite properly and just really jerky and slow coming out of corners <pause dur="short"/> and my dad was just like you're very safe just like your mother</u>
<u n="701" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0002">you're very safe and slow just like your mother</u>
<u n="703" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="704" who="S0002">and my driving instructor got all defensive for me <pause dur="short"/> he was like no she's doing really well <pause dur="short"/> you should praise her more <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like oh God I feel like I'm</u>
<u n="705" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="706" who="S0002">twelve in the middle like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="707" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> well at least he sounds like he's got some nice words for you as well <pause dur="short"/> I thought he was</u>
<u n="708" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's</u>
<u n="709" who="S0018">just shouted at you all the time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="710" who="S0002">not all the time <pause dur="short"/> eighty percent of the time</u>
<u n="711" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0018">I mean I'd just jump if he shouted at me</u>
<u n="714" who="S0002">I cried once in the car <pause dur="short"/> and I think he sort of came off it a little bit</u>
<u n="715" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0002">after that</u>
<u n="717" who="S0018">why? What happened?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0002">he just was yelling <pause dur="short"/> and I was already really upset cos I think I'd come out of the the house after a fight with my mum and I was already like just tired and <pause dur="short"/> and I and he was like you're a danger on the road</u>
<u n="719" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="720" who="S0002">and then he was like pull over <pause dur="short"/> and then I just was like I'm trying really hard <pause dur="short"/> and he was just like okay</u>
<u n="721" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="722" who="S0002">and he sort of stopped a little bit after that <pause dur="short"/> he's not as bad anymore</u>
<u n="723" who="S0018">that's the whole thing about learner drivers <pause dur="short"/> they're <trunc>l</trunc> they're learning how not to be a danger on the road</u>
<u n="724" who="S0002">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0018">like yeah <pause dur="short"/> call a spade a spade why don't you?</u>
<u n="726" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0002">I know <pause dur="short"/> er the thing is I've been looking for another instructor cos I just you know I wanna see if it's different with a different driving instructor</u>
<u n="728" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="729" who="S0002">but it seems really hard to find someone good</u>
<u n="730" who="S0018">well why don't you just have like a few lessons with my  with my  instructor? Cos honestly he's so he puts you at your ease</u>
<u n="731" who="S0002">but it's just the whole</u>
<u n="732" who="S0018">I can't believe I'm confident</u>
<u n="733" who="S0002">I don't I really don't wanna take my test somewhere else</u>
<u n="734" who="S0018">but you won't wouldn't have to <pause dur="short"/> just have a few lessons</u>
<u n="735" who="S0002">but you have to have that driver's car</u>
<u n="736" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="737" who="S0002">and that instructor</u>
<u n="738" who="S0018">but you could go back  you could go back  to your instructor</u>
<u n="739" who="S0002">oh right <pause dur="short"/> to do my test?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just I think</u>
<u n="741" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0018">it might be  it might be  a good thing just to have experience with someone else in the car <pause dur="short"/> just to <trunc>prep</trunc> prepare you for your test as well</u>
<u n="743" who="S0002">that's true actually <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've actually got a Groupon voucher <pause dur="short"/> six three lessons for six quid <pause dur="short"/> which has been sitting on my table for ages <pause dur="short"/> I should probably just phone them up and use it</u>
<u n="744" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you see I was I there was  there was  le le le le there are quite a few driving schools in my area that do <trunc>le</trunc> er lessons</u>
<u n="745" who="S0002">stuff like that</u>
<u n="746" who="S0018">for eight pounds and stuff and I'm thinking mm do I want to go with a driving instructor who is working as part of a franchise and probably gets paid</u>
<u n="747" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0018">ten P an hour?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0018">is he gonna be happy in his job? No <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="751" who="S0002">that's true</u>
<u n="752" who="S0018">I'd prefer to go with the guy who's got his own business and he's relaxed and</u>
<u n="753" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> these guys have their own business <pause dur="short"/> I found them on Groupon actually</u>
<u n="754" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they were <trunc>pre</trunc> they were pretty they've got a good pass rate <pause dur="short"/> but that's probably just cos they whip their students</u>
<u n="756" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="757" who="S0002">until they pass the damn thing <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="758" who="S0018">you will pass your test</u>
<u n="759" who="S0002"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0018">you will bring shame onto our driving school if you don't</u>
<u n="761" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0002">it seems like that</u>
<u n="763" who="S0018">gosh</u>
<u n="764" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> I probably should try a few others</u>
<u n="765" who="S0018">and just out of interest how much extra did it cost your parents to put you on their?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0002">three hundred</u>
<u n="767" who="S0018">three hundred quid?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0002">for a year</u>
<u n="769" who="S0018">pff</u>
<u n="770" who="S0002">for a brand new Fiesta</u>
<u n="771" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="772" who="S0002">it's not that bad</u>
<u n="773" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="774" who="S0002">it sounds a lot <pause dur="short"/> but most people are like only three hundred?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0002">when I tell them <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0018">you see tut</u>
<u n="778" who="S0002">that sounds like a huge amount of money though</u>
<u n="779" who="S0018">that's like a bus pass for the whole year <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="780" who="S0002">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> no you're right <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> and I've driven it like twice <pause dur="short"/> and it's not I need to drive it more to really sort of get some money's worth <pause dur="short"/> but I'm terrified <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a new car</u>
<u n="781" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0002">like I had all these lessons and then I got I went in the car in the new car with my dad and the driving instructor last week and I was er literally shaking</u>
<u n="783" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="784" who="S0002">and my driving instructor was just like what's wrong with you? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Like</u>
<u n="785" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="786" who="S0002">you're not normally like this <pause dur="short"/> and I was like I just don't wanna ruin the car <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="788" who="S0002">but they're not really my it was supposed to be for my mum the car <pause dur="short"/> but my mum doesn't drive very much anymore <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>sh</trunc> in fact she didn't even wanna drive it at the beginning because she couldn't get used to it</u>
<u n="789" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0002">so I'm just like well should've somebody should really drive this car like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0018">did your dad choose it? Or did your mum choose it?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0002">my dad chose it</u>
<u n="793" who="S0018">why didn't he let your mum choose it? Cos surely</u>
<u n="794" who="S0002">Cos he's a numpty</u>
<u n="795" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0002">wonder how often that'll come up in a corpus search</u>
<u n="797" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="798" who="S0018">he's a numpty</u>
<u n="799" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="800" who="S0018">hm <pause dur="short"/> yeah my my mum had to go and er my dad was complaining about it actually she he said she had to go and sit in about fifty different seats and test the cars and</u>
<u n="801" who="S0002">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> you should find a car that you're <trunc>comf</trunc> my dad bought the first car he saw</u>
<u n="802" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0002">that's not clever at all <pause dur="short"/> but um yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice car <pause dur="short"/> it's it's a poser car a little bit <pause dur="short"/> it's bright red</u>
<u n="804" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="805" who="S0002">I know</u>
<u n="806" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's just like having a</u>
<u n="807" who="S0002">it's like hello I'm here <pause dur="short"/> and like</u>
<u n="808" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like having a big finger pointing at you</u>
<u n="809" who="S0002">basically</u>
<u n="810" who="S0018">all the time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="811" who="S0002">but in a way it's good because I used to never be able to find them in a parking lot because they have a silver car and there's so many silver cars</u>
<u n="812" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0002">and now it's just like there they are</u>
<u n="814" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0002">like I can see them a mile away <pause dur="short"/> it's so bright</u>
<u n="816" who="S0018">what kind of car is it?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0002">it's a Fiesta <pause dur="short"/> it's like a new Fiesta Titanium thing <pause dur="short"/> they're really nice <pause dur="short"/> but the one thing I don't like about it is the dashboard <pause dur="short"/> it comes <trunc>rea</trunc> like basically the front of the car is really small <pause dur="short"/> and the engine is built into the dashboard and the front</u>
<u n="818" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="819" who="S0002">so the dashboard comes really far down in front of you <pause dur="short"/> so you feel a little bit cramped in the front <pause dur="short"/> which is not really great <pause dur="short"/> and it's so like every mod con <pause dur="short"/> like voice activated <pause dur="short"/> it talks back at you</u>
<u n="820" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's like KITT car <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0002">it is basically <pause dur="short"/> and I'm just like do you really need all of this? My dad's like oh we'll learn how to use it <pause dur="short"/> he hasn't even opened the manual <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="822" who="S0018">so what what can you command it to do by voice?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0002">so it's all auto <pause dur="short"/> like all the lights <pause dur="short"/> it will  it will  dim and <unclear/> the lights <pause dur="short"/> and the windscreen wipers are auto <pause dur="short"/> and you can tell it like I'd like the car to be this temperature and it will set the temperature for you <pause dur="short"/> what else can you make it do? You can make it do quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> you can make it phone people like er you know</u>
<u n="824" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0002">er you can make it you can put it onto auto like cruise er through voice activation <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of weird actually <pause dur="short"/> it's like</u>
<u n="826" who="S0018">no wonder  no wonder  the dashboard comes up to your face</u>
<u n="827" who="S0002">I know</u>
<u n="828" who="S0018">it's it needs a brain</u>
<u n="829" who="S0002">it's like a rocket</u>
<u n="830" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0018">and have you tried night driving?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0002">um <pause dur="short"/> I had one lesson at night <pause dur="short"/> two lessons at night</u>
<u n="833" who="S0018">is that a lot different from driving during the day?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0002">it's not that bad actually</u>
<u n="835" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0002">um <pause dur="short"/> I thought it would be terrifying <pause dur="short"/> but it was pretty just pretty much the same <pause dur="short"/> just you can see</u>
<u n="837" who="S0018">Cos I don't know whether my eyes are sensitive to light but you know those um headlights</u>
<u n="838" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="839" who="S0018">that are really kind of like</u>
<u n="840" who="S0002">bright</u>
<u n="841" who="S0018">bright blue</u>
<u n="842" who="S0002">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0018">white? They they leave such a trace on my vision</u>
<u n="844" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="845" who="S0018">that er but but it doesn't seem to be so intense for other people <pause dur="short"/> I'm just wondering whether I've got particularly sensitive eyes</u>
<u n="846" who="S0002">have you ever had it checked?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've had my eyesight <trunc>che</trunc> I've never had any problems with my eyesight <pause dur="short"/> apart from being er maybe a bit light sensitive</u>
<u n="848" who="S0002">are there special things glasses you can wear for that?</u>
<u n="849" who="S0018">yeah I'll just look really cool all the time</u>
<u n="850" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0018">with my sunglasses and</u>
<u n="852" who="S0002">with my shades in the night</u>
<u n="853" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0002">that's proper Knight Rider <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="855" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm too cool</u>
<u n="856" who="S0002"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="857" who="S0018">I dunno</u>
<u n="858" who="S0002"></u>
<u n="859" who="S0018">I'd like to end up in a little city and be able to walk to work or catch a bus</u>
<u n="860" who="S0002">you wanna stay in the UK?</u>
<u n="861" who="S0018">if it's cold <pause dur="short"/> do I want to? No <pause dur="short"/> not particularly <pause dur="short"/> if there was Mediterranean weather here? Yes</u>
<u n="862" who="S0002">so er</u>
<u n="863" who="S0018">but <trunc>a</trunc> at the moment all I want is you know a bit of stability</u>
<u n="864" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0018">and a stable income</u>
<u n="866" who="S0002">but when you say I want to end up does that mean that could be anywhere? You're open to ending up anywhere? Or are you <trunc>r</trunc> kind of <trunc>f</trunc>?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0018">I'm open to ending up anywhere as long as there's a way of er supporting myself</u>
<u n="868" who="S0002">stability</u>
<u n="869" who="S0018">and financial independence</u>
<u n="870" who="S0002">stable job</u>
<u n="871" who="S0018">Cos that was the worst thing about Spain <pause dur="short"/> you never knew when they were</u>
<u n="872" who="S0002">how much you were gonna earn <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0018">going yeah well you never knew how much you were gonna get earn month to month <pause dur="short"/> you never knew when they were going to turn around and tell you that your contract had been terminated</u>
<u n="874" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0018">just because they wanted to save a bit of money <pause dur="short"/> but you could still carry on working there <pause dur="short"/> it's just you wouldn't be working with a contract</u>
<u n="876" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="877" who="S0018">and so that means no</u>
<u n="878" who="S0002"><trunc>S</trunc> Spain is</u>
<u n="879" who="S0018">healthcare</u>
<u n="880" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="881" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="882" who="S0002">I understand</u>
<u n="883" who="S0018">unemployment benefit in case you lose your job <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="884" who="S0002">that's what I was like in Japan <pause dur="short"/> but I was self-employed so I brought that upon myself <pause dur="short"/> but getting a good job that has a proper full-time contract <pause dur="short"/> actually I was working for the British Council before I came out here came back here not out here <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="885" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="886" who="S0002">and um recently they contacted me and said Oh we've got full-time jobs and I worked for them for quite a long time hoping and praying that the day would come that they would say we have full-time jobs <pause dur="short"/> cos it's the kind of place that no one will ever leave</u>
<u n="887" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0002">and suddenly they came up with four full-time jobs <pause dur="short"/>SE And I was just like</u>
<u n="889" who="S0018">in Japan?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0002">yes <pause dur="short"/> I was really angry</u>
<u n="891" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0002">but then I looked at the conditions and I was like nah <pause dur="short"/> I earnt more when I was self-employed <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="893" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="894" who="S0002">and I had more flexibility <pause dur="short"/> could do what I wanted <pause dur="short"/> take a holiday when I wanted <pause dur="short"/> it just depends what you want I suppose</u>
<u n="895" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> well that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I've done the whole</u>
<u n="896" who="S0002">flexible</u>
<u n="897" who="S0018">being flexible <pause dur="short"/> earning very little money but still having a great life</u>
<u n="898" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="899" who="S0018">but living with the restrictions of not knowing when you're gonna have holiday <pause dur="short"/> not knowing when you're gonna be able to afford to buy the thing</u>
<u n="900" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="901" who="S0018">if the fridge breaks down</u>
<u n="902" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> then you're screwed</u>
<u n="903" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="904" who="S0002">the <trunc>proble</trunc> the thing was that I was er part of a two income household and</u>
<u n="905" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="906" who="S0002">it was even my boyfriend's job was not a hundred percent stable <pause dur="short"/> but between the two of us or even one of us could cover the rent if the other one went out of work <pause dur="short"/> so we had we have that to help so that makes it better for me <pause dur="short"/> because I I ideally want to go back to work part-time and self-employed when I have kids <pause dur="short"/> so it kind of suits me in a way <pause dur="short"/> but if it wasn't in that <trunc>situa</trunc> but even then even when I was single I was quite happy working part-time</u>
<u n="907" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0002">I dunno</u>
<u n="909" who="S0018">it would be great to be able to earn full earn part-time wages and be able to live off them <pause dur="short"/> but I just think the price of the</u>
<u n="910" who="S0002">I think in Spain that's very hard</u>
<u n="911" who="S0018">oh it's impossible <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the price of life</u>
<u n="912" who="S0002">in Japan</u>
<u n="913" who="S0018">is just horrendous <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="914" who="S0002">I used to make for one lesson er so I worked for a little I worked for British Council and I worked for a little college</u>
<u n="915" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="916" who="S0002">and they would term employ you per term <pause dur="short"/> but if you did one term you were fairly guaranteed to get the next term <pause dur="short"/> and in fact they'll keep you for as long as you want <pause dur="short"/> but the their whole thing was that they wouldn't employ anyone with enough classes for them to rely on that</u>
<u n="917" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="918" who="S0002">on them</u>
<u n="919" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="920" who="S0002">so they had a maximum of eight classes <pause dur="short"/> but if you did eight classes during the day so decent working hours that was two hundred  two hundred  thousand yen <pause dur="short"/> which is like</u>
<u n="921" who="S0018">and how much was your rent? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="922" who="S0002">my rent between two thirty thousand each</u>
<u n="923" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> two hundred I'm trying to <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="924" who="S0002">it's about coming up to two thousand eight hundred a month</u>
<u n="925" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="926" who="S0002">which is as much as most people make full-time</u>
<u n="927" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="928" who="S0002">sometimes <pause dur="short"/> so even that was enough to sort of keep me ticking over <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc> the average rent in Tokyo is about eighty to ninety thousand</u>
<u n="929" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="930" who="S0002">but a hundred thousand a month will quite happily clothe feed party whatever you wanna do</u>
<u n="931" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0002">it's quite a decent amount of money <pause dur="short"/> but like you said <pause dur="short"/> if anything happens</u>
<u n="933" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="S0002">you need to go home or something breaks down then yeah it's a problem</u>
<u n="935" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="936" who="S0002">but yeah</u>
<u n="937" who="S0018">but it just seems here even um the one of the newly qualified teachers at my er at the school I was in before December she was struggling on a teaching salary <pause dur="short"/> okay she'd started off on the the lowest</u>
<u n="938" who="S0002">what is the lowest? Eighteen?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0018">twenty-two eight hundred?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0002">I think the cost of living in the UK is extortionate</u>
<u n="941" who="S0018">it has gone up so much</u>
<u n="942" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="943" who="S0018">but it's the same in Spain <pause dur="short"/> it's it's comparable in Spain now <pause dur="short"/> but salaries are so much lower</u>
<u n="944" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0018">but here it's yeah the fuel bills supermarket bills</u>
<u n="946" who="S0002">just things like council tax and stuff</u>
<u n="947" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="948" who="S0002">is so expensive</u>
<u n="949" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0002">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it's expensive everywhere <pause dur="short"/> the only thing in Japan that's not expensive is food</u>
<u n="951" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="952" who="S0002">everything else is <vocal desc="laugh"/> expensive <pause dur="short"/> but food is important <pause dur="short"/> food eats up a lot of your bills to be honest <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="953" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0002">I always feel like I spend a fortune here on food</u>
<u n="955" who="S0018">you're supposed to eat it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> me too <pause dur="short"/> I used to go to the markets and stuff <pause dur="short"/> you could get like like your whole rolly bag trolley</u>
<u n="956" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> full</u>
<u n="957" who="S0018">filled</u>
<u n="958" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0018">with fruit and vegetable for pff ten Euros</u>
<u n="960" who="S0002">ten quid <pause dur="short"/> ten yeah yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0018">that would last you more than a week</u>
<u n="962" who="S0002">not here</u>
<u n="963" who="S0018">well I can't believe it <pause dur="short"/> it's like oo slap a price on it <pause dur="short"/> what shall we say? A quid <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> one pound for a tiny little bag of spinach</u>
<u n="964" who="S0002">it's really expensive</u>
<u n="965" who="S0018">it is <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="966" who="S0002">if you wanna eat well it's really expensive</u>
<u n="967" who="S0018">stupid <pause dur="short"/> which is why you need a job that pays at least  at least  thirty grand I think <pause dur="short"/> to be able to have</u>
<u n="968" who="S0002">there are not many jobs that pay thirty <vocal desc="laugh"/> grand</u>
<u n="969" who="S0018">I know</u>
<u n="970" who="S0002">I don't know if I even wanna live in this country to be honest <pause dur="short"/> I don't not I dunno I wouldn't mm not convinced about the quality of life here to be honest</u>
<u n="971" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> me either <pause dur="short"/> I just think that from what compared to you know I'd like to live in Spain again but compared to Spain it's just there is no possibility of earning a living wage there</u>
<u n="972" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="973" who="S0018">and there is an a possibility of doing that here so</u>
<u n="974" who="S0002">here <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="975" who="S0018">but obviously cos you</u>
<u n="976" who="S0002">you wanna stay in Europe?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0018">um</u>
<u n="978" who="S0002">would you ever look further afield?</u>
<u n="979" who="S0018">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> because I I moved to France and lived in France and then I moved to Spain and lived in Spain <pause dur="short"/> I've in my adult life I've always lived abroad</u>
<u n="980" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="981" who="S0018">and knowing what tut knowing how much effort it takes <pause dur="short"/> not just effort but how much time it takes to <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> feel like you've settled into a new culture and</u>
<u n="982" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I understand</u>
<u n="983" who="S0018">a new language and to a new way of doing things <pause dur="short"/> I think maybe I'm I'm too not too old but I'm too</u>
<u n="984" who="S0002">just exhausted by the whole thing</u>
<u n="985" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I get that too</u>
<u n="987" who="S0018">it's comforting in a way being back in the country where you know I speak the language <pause dur="short"/> um you know</u>
<u n="988" who="S0002">everything <pause dur="short"/> you can function in every single way</u>
<u n="989" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0002">there is no limitation</u>
<u n="991" who="S0018">exactly</u>
<u n="992" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I understand that</u>
<u n="993" who="S0018">but no I wouldn't um rule out living in another country <pause dur="short"/> but I think when when you're in your thirties you start thinking a lot more in terms of your family and</u>
<u n="994" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="995" who="S0018">putting down roots and and if you can't do that <pause dur="short"/> and surviving basically <pause dur="short"/> being able</u>
<u n="996" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0018">to support yourself <pause dur="short"/> and if if you can't do that that's when you start getting anxious and uh I just want it <pause dur="short"/> I just want a quiet life</u>
<u n="998" who="S0002"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="999" who="S0018">I don't wanna earn too much money <pause dur="short"/> I don't wanna earn</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0002">just wanna be comfortable without worrying about money</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0018">definitely <pause dur="short"/> like one little summer holiday a year <pause dur="short"/> and just enough to pay your rent or oo a mortgage <pause dur="short"/> now that would be see most of the you know you can't get a mortgage on a single</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0018">person's salary</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0002">that's true</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0018">unless you're earning over thirty grand <pause dur="short"/> and even earning over thirty grand you'll have problems getting a mortgage</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0002">I just think the housing crisis is disgusting here</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0002">like I mean pff it's so expensive</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0002">I was in <anon type="place"/> teaching on Monday and</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0002">the the family that I the <trunc>t</trunc> the woman that I teach is a housewife but her husband's doing an MBA here <pause dur="short"/> they're Japanese <pause dur="short"/> and um they're renting a very nice townhouse flat</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0002">and I was just curious <pause dur="short"/> cos I was like oh this is somewhere that I can imagine that me and my boyfriend might end up living at some point <pause dur="short"/> so I looked it up and I looked up the <trunc>pri</trunc> oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> if you wanted to buy one of the flats it was two hundred and seventy-five thousand</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0002">and I'm like they're not they're nice <pause dur="short"/> they're new <pause dur="short"/> but it's a flat <pause dur="short"/> and it's small</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0002">and it's far away</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0018">but it's <trunc>al</trunc></u>
<u n="1020" who="S0002">from the city centre</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0018">but it's also <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0002">I know <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/>'s expensive</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0002">but that's just insanely expensive</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0018">it is  it is</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0002">A one bedroom flat for two hundred and seventy-five</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0018">crazy <pause dur="short"/> but for example my friends are looking to buy <pause dur="short"/> they're living in <anon type="place"/> renting at the moment <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="place"/>'s too expensive for them to buy in <pause dur="short"/> and they're looking at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> which is right you know five minute drive down the road <pause dur="short"/> and the comparison price difference is</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0002">is so</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0018">enormous</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0002">different</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0018">I mean they're looking at um two bedroomed house <pause dur="short"/> er semi-detached or terraced or <pause dur="short"/> and in <anon type="place"/> you're looking at um two hundred and forty-two hundred and fifty thousand <pause dur="short"/> and in <anon type="place"/> you're looking at one hundred and sixty</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0002">oh okay</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0018">one hundred and seventy</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0002">there's a big difference then</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0018">really big difference <pause dur="short"/> so I imagine in Harborne it's the same</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0002">but I mean er we were looking at buying um before we rented we recently moved to a new flat in Tokyo <pause dur="short"/> and before we rented that place we were looking at houses <pause dur="short"/> we were looking at buying <pause dur="short"/> and you can buy a brand new house in Tokyo <pause dur="short"/> have it developed to how you want it <pause dur="short"/> the thing that's expensive is land <pause dur="short"/> but probably all in for a two three bedroom three three level house probably about three hundred thousand pounds <pause dur="short"/> but we're talking in the middle of a metropolitan city</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0002">and that's not bad</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0018">especially when salaries sound to be better</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0002">yeah they are a bit better <pause dur="short"/> so we were like well it would make a lot of sense but we don't know where we're gonna end up</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0018">so where why do you say that you don't know if you wanna live in Japan? Cos I <trunc>th</trunc> I thought you seemed quite enamoured by it all</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0002">no I mean I like it <pause dur="short"/> but I don't the idea of spending a long time there doesn't appeal</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0018">is that in light of what happened last year with the earthquake? And the nuclear?</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0002">it's a little bit about that <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> a little bit about the earthquake <pause dur="short"/> a little bit just about bringing up a family there</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0002">um <pause dur="short"/> and being away from my family</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0002">I want like I the thing that fills me with terror which is me getting way ahead of myself of course but I don't wanna have a child and be away from my mum</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0002">and not only be away but be an ocean</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1052" who="S0002">a thirteen-hour plane ride away</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0018">exactly <pause dur="short"/> it is so far isn't it</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0002">it's really far <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think that his family are gonna really be that involved in our lives</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0002">so I just  I just  want a support network as I get older</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0002">and as they get older <pause dur="short"/> I'm worried about my parents too</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> that was one of the deciding factors in me er in my coming home as well</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0002">yeah</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0018">especially with all the injuries I had <pause dur="short"/> it was just so much easier having being able to rely on people in case</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0002">mm</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0018">all of a sudden you've you can't</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can't</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0018">rely on your body or something</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0002">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the other thing is there is still quite a big language barrier <pause dur="short"/> I mean I would have <trunc>t</trunc> I feel like if I made a commitment to going back I would have to go back to language school</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0002">just to improve my spoken <pause dur="short"/> but I'm always gonna be have the huge barrier of reading and writing</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0002">because that is not something you can make up <pause dur="short"/> that's like prr ten years I would say to become</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0002">get to a point where you can sort of get by</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0002">so that's a huge thing is feeling like I live on a periphery of a society <pause dur="short"/> and I've that's okay when you're just <trunc>visi</trunc> not visiting but</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0002">it's temporary <pause dur="short"/> but if that was to somehow become permanent I don't know how well I would do with that <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0018">it does leave you feeling slightly marginalized doesn't it</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0002">and yeah er I'm not the brightest when it comes to languages <pause dur="short"/> they're pretty hard <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Like</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0002">especially Japanese</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0018">such a difficult language though <pause dur="short"/> surely <pause dur="short"/> there's different alphabet</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0002">school's expensive too <pause dur="short"/> it's like a hundred and sixty thousand for three months</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0018">oo ff</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0002">that's like three four <trunc>hou</trunc> four hours tuition a day <pause dur="short"/> and I was doing that and working eight hours a day at the same time <pause dur="short"/> so I probably didn't get as much of it as out of it as I should've</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0002">but it was just so expensive <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how people afford it <pause dur="short"/> and everyone else there was a full-time student <pause dur="short"/> there was me like beavering away at work and doing homework and doing classes <pause dur="short"/> and just like huh can't do this <pause dur="short"/> it's exhausting <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0002">it's fun but it's exhausting <pause dur="short"/> like and like why did you fail the test? Cos I <vocal desc="laugh"/> didn't have time to <trunc>w</trunc> study like</u>
<u n="1089" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1090" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think teachers are the best students</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0002">students</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0018">either <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1093" who="S0002">no <pause dur="short"/> definitely not</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0018">I hate</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0002">learning that on this degree <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I hate studying <pause dur="short"/> and I hate having homework to do <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind working late <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind in a job doing a lot of work</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0002">but actually studying</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0018">but actually <trunc>stu</trunc> oh and exams and urgh</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0002">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty brutal <pause dur="short"/> I had tests every week when I was on that course <pause dur="short"/> I had tests almost every day actually for the characters</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0002">and it was just like I couldn't get them into my head</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0002">and it was just you know it was really hard <pause dur="short"/> I just can't imagine getting to the point where I can say you know what? I can manage now <pause dur="short"/> I know enough Japanese to really get by <pause dur="short"/> I can't imagine ever getting to that point <pause dur="short"/> and I don't want my kids to be running circles round me like linguistically</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1105" who="S0002">like that would be not good <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
</body>
</text>
