<text id="SWBG">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0251 S0252</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living room in Malton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Recent family gathering</topics>
		<activity>Anniversary party</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0251">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>North Ferriby, East Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>GCSE Maths Examiner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0252">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>York</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0251">I think yesterday went quite well don't you? the ruby wedding party that we went to</u>
<u n="2" who="S0252">yes it did <pause dur="short"/> and I think everyone had a good time</u>
<u n="3" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="4" who="S0252" trans="overlap">and er it's nice to have a chat to er extended members of the family that I have not seen for some time</u>
<u n="5" who="S0251">that's right mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0252" trans="overlap">to what extent do you think it was a surprise?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0251">well she said it was a surprise I asked her and she said she hadn't got any idea whether it was a good idea or not I don't know because a few weeks before the party she'd said if anybody gives me a surprise party I'd really hate that</u>
<u n="8" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0251">so I don't know and er also they'd only just come back from holidays the day before so I think they could have been a bit tired</u>
<u n="10" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="11" who="S0251">and the other thing is I think if she'd have known it was a party she'd have probably got dressed up a bit more</u>
<u n="12" who="S0252">mm yes</u>
<u n="13" who="S0251">also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might have made a better and longer speech if he'd have had a bit more time to consider what to say</u>
<u n="14" who="S0252" trans="overlap">is that an advantage or a disadvantage?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0251" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it depends whether you like listening to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s speeches or not really</u>
<u n="16" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0251">I think we the journey went quite well we got there easily didn't we?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes I think one advantage was er not having to drive in as many er urban areas</u>
<u n="19" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="20" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I think the erm A18 managed to mm to some extent provide a bit of a ring road between the <anon type="place"/> and the venue</u>
<u n="21" who="S0251">yes it's a spectacular bridge the <anon type="place"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0252">it is yes</u>
<u n="23" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it's quite stunning is that mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes it was er erm <unclear>out</unclear> on on the landscape for at least about a fifteen to twenty mile radius from</u>
<u n="25" who="S0251">definitely yes it is it's stunning</u>
<u n="26" who="S0252" trans="overlap"><unclear/> itself</u>
<u n="27" who="S0251">and it was a nice bright day as well</u>
<u n="28" who="S0252">yes I got</u>
<u n="29" who="S0251" trans="overlap">shown to the best advantage</u>
<u n="30" who="S0252">with a nice view of the <anon type="place"/> and we could see</u>
<u n="31" who="S0251" trans="overlap">we did it was all a sparkle</u>
<u n="32" who="S0252" trans="overlap">the sandbanks</u>
<u n="33" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="34" who="S0252" trans="overlap">and yachts and</u>
<u n="35" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="36" who="S0252">pleasure boats</u>
<u n="37" who="S0251">yes it was lovely</u>
<u n="38" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="39" who="S0251">mm you operated the satnav very efficiently didn't you?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0251">and it took us straight to the venue</u>
<u n="42" who="S0252">it did</u>
<u n="43" who="S0251">so as grandad says it's not the driving but the parking that's the problem but another problem can be the navigation can't it?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0252" trans="overlap">indeed it can</u>
<u n="45" who="S0251">but the satnav does take some of the guesswork out of it doesn't it?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it does although erm admittedly sometimes it does take you on a rather obscure route</u>
<u n="47" who="S0251">true</u>
<u n="48" who="S0252">such as when we were on erm our holiday we were</u>
<u n="49" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0252">going down some almost single tracks</u>
<u n="51" who="S0251">yes the good thing about it though is if you want to go a certain way it does recalculate it doesn't it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="53" who="S0251" trans="overlap">if you want to take a particular route</u>
<u n="54" who="S0252">mm it also lets you know whether you are happy that the road is a toll road or not</u>
<u n="55" who="S0251">oh right yes actually I thought the toll on the bridge was less this time than when we've been before</u>
<u n="56" who="S0252">so did I I</u>
<u n="57" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I thought it had gone down</u>
<u n="58" who="S0252">yes <pause dur="short"/> I think they seem to be doing some refurbishment to the toll booths</u>
<u n="59" who="S0251">oh</u>
<u n="60" who="S0252">I think they're trying to make it into some sort of plaza complex</u>
<u n="61" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh why is that then?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0252">well it is part of the refurbishment programme</u>
<u n="63" who="S0251">oh right it's mm we really need to find the charger for that satnav because I don't think it's got much battery left now has it?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0252">it has not you can recharge it via the plug erm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0251" trans="overlap">in the car?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0252">no from a a three pin socket in the house</u>
<u n="67" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh right yes</u>
<u n="68" who="S0252">we've got the charger at the <unclear>back</unclear></u>
<u n="69" who="S0251">right</u>
<u n="70" who="S0252">but we don't have the in-car charger which</u>
<u n="71" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="72" who="S0252">is just means that if you're doing a journey of more than ninety minutes</u>
<u n="73" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="74" who="S0252">erm you are not really able to use the satnav</u>
<u n="75" who="S0251">yes oh right and I had my first selfie at the party</u>
<u n="76" who="S0252">you did you've had it even before I have</u>
<u n="77" who="S0251">of all the original bridesmaids on that day forty years ago</u>
<u n="78" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0251">I don't know what I think to selfies really they look a bit <pause dur="short"/> funny sometimes really like you have to group in so tightly you <trunc>lo</trunc> look like you're in one of those photo booths don't you?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="81" who="S0251">which er is a big strange and it's amazing how things have changed really my parents had their wedding photographs taken on glass plates</u>
<u n="82" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="83" who="S0251">it's amazing what's happened in a generation</u>
<u n="84" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it is and from my point of view if I was shown that photograph erm without knowing what occasion it was was</u>
<u n="85" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="86" who="S0252">wedding photograph I I think I would have failed to have recognised a er the people in it if I had just come it across it by an off chance</u>
<u n="87" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0252">the the people have changed so much since then</u>
<u n="89" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="90" who="S0252">also it highlights the different fashions <trunc>th</trunc> blonde hair and</u>
<u n="91" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it did didn't it?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0252">aubergine jackets and</u>
<u n="93" who="S0251">yes it</u>
<u n="94" who="S0252" trans="overlap">er rather sturdy boots for the occasion and</u>
<u n="95" who="S0251" trans="overlap">well it was the seventies it's called the decade that fashion forgot sometimes</u>
<u n="96" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="97" who="S0251">yes and we also got given from one of my other cousins a digitalised DVD of an old cine film</u>
<u n="98" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0251">which I'm hoping to watch apparently</u>
<u n="100" who="S0252" trans="overlap">that's</u>
<u n="101" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it's of Christmas 1961</u>
<u n="102" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0251">of my cousins opening their Christmas presents</u>
<u n="104" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0251">so that'll be interesting to see</u>
<u n="106" who="S0252">it will</u>
<u n="107" who="S0251">I think it'll be colour</u>
<u n="108" who="S0252">oh will it?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="110" who="S0252">right I don't it might be about the time the transition time</u>
<u n="111" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I would have thought</u>
<u n="113" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it was on the television <pause dur="short"/> yeah and then we had a photograph taken of all the people that were present on that wedding day forty years ago</u>
<u n="114" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="115" who="S0251">I'm afraid we're dwindling in number</u>
<u n="116" who="S0252">we are but also <unclear/> percentage of the people who attended the party</u>
<u n="117" who="S0251">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm were there yes so it kind of filled me with a bit of nostalgia really</u>
<u n="118" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="119" who="S0251">which is a longing for something that you can't have the past <pause dur="short"/> but there again</u>
<u n="120" who="S0252">at least you've captured the moment</u>
<u n="121" who="S0251">yes if it was the past then I wouldn't have you would I?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0252">mm no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0251">and I wouldn't want to miss out on that <pause dur="short"/> and er we got back safely took the same route didn't we?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes we did</u>
<u n="125" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I was pretty tired though when we got back</u>
<u n="126" who="S0252" trans="overlap">we did yes</u>
<u n="127" who="S0251">so how long did it take us that journey?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0252">I think it was approximately a hundred minutes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0251">yes and how far was that?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0252">er how far? erm well I think it's was about twenty-nine miles from the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="132" who="S0252">and then I think it's thirty-four from the <anon type="place"/> to the house</u>
<u n="133" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="134" who="S0252">so I think it was possibly about sixty-two miles in total</u>
<u n="135" who="S0251">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's a lot quicker than when we used to go when we were young and of course the <anon type="place"/> wasn't there</u>
<u n="136" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0251">we had to go round via <anon type="place"/> which took us hours and hours</u>
<u n="138" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0251">that was really a tortuous route</u>
<u n="140" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="141" who="S0251" trans="overlap">going out of your way the wrong direction before you could turn round to come back</u>
<u n="142" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0251">you couldn't cross the river in those days</u>
<u n="144" who="S0252" trans="overlap">but er disadvantage of using the erm boat at the time was that the</u>
<u n="145" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no the ferry yes</u>
<u n="146" who="S0252" trans="overlap">the er sandbanks that accumulated in the over the <anon type="place"/> erm meant that sometimes you would be stranded on a sandbank</u>
<u n="147" who="S0251" trans="overlap">well that <trunc>occa</trunc>occasionally happened it never happened when I was on it but and it was quite good fun on the ferry anyway</u>
<u n="148" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="149" who="S0251">we used to get lemonade and crisps and be looking out it was quite nice really</u>
<u n="150" who="S0252">yes so long did did that take?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0251">I can't remember I'd only be quite small I don't know not very long would it?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0252">no maybe a quarter of an hour</u>
<u n="153" who="S0251" trans="overlap">maybe <trunc>tw</trunc> yeah I was going to say twenty minutes yes</u>
<u n="154" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0251">yeah one thing was loading up getting the cars on and</u>
<u n="156" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="157" who="S0251">all the people and that sort of thing</u>
<u n="158" who="S0252">that would take er quite a bit of time</u>
<u n="159" who="S0251">mm it did yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0252">it's erm amazing the erm suspension bridge that is currently in place</u>
<u n="161" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="162" who="S0252">erm that er did used to be one of the world's longest suspension bridges</u>
<u n="163" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it was for at time yes I think it's been superseded now hasn't it? with</u>
<u n="164" who="S0252">yes er I think it it's a bridge in China but I'm not sure</u>
<u n="165" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes I think you're right mm yeah I don't think they've got the record any more</u>
<u n="166" who="S0252">no but the Chinese have been erm building significant er infrastructure projects with their</u>
<u n="167" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0252">the erm Three Gorges Dam</u>
<u n="169" who="S0251">right</u>
<u n="170" who="S0252">and lots of suspension bridges had erm lots of railway projects</u>
<u n="171" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0252" trans="overlap">high speed rail they've really spent a lot of money</u>
<u n="173" who="S0251">mm investments</u>
<u n="174" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0251">mm <pause dur="short"/> and er they got some nice presents didn't they?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0252">they did yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0251">somebody got them that rose that's called Ruby Wedding</u>
<u n="178" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="179" who="S0251">we nearly got that didn't we?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0252" trans="overlap">we did</u>
<u n="181" who="S0251">but I thought somebody else might get it so</u>
<u n="182" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="183" who="S0251">I decided not to</u>
<u n="184" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="185" who="S0251">I think they got some theatre vouchers</u>
<u n="186" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="187" who="S0251">quite a good present</u>
<u n="188" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0251">erm got er some sort of candelabra</u>
<u n="190" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0251">I didn't see what anybody else had bought did you?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="193" who="S0251">that was what I saw</u>
<u n="194" who="S0252">mm did you think the er I suppose a book of memories that was presented</u>
<u n="195" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="196" who="S0252" trans="overlap">was a good idea?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0251">it was lovely I I was surprised that the book was made of wood wasn't it?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0251">and it had little erm hearts carved out of it didn't it?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0252">it did</u>
<u n="201" who="S0251" trans="overlap">so it was very attractive haven't seen one like that anywhere else</u>
<u n="202" who="S0252" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="203" who="S0251">and er a lot of old photographs and that I hadn't seen before</u>
<u n="204" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0251">quite interesting to look at</u>
<u n="206" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="207" who="S0251">and er <pause dur="short"/> there's the er place was nicely decorated with balloons and</u>
<u n="208" who="S0252">it was</u>
<u n="209" who="S0251">rose petals and bunting thought that the girls had done a good job</u>
<u n="210" who="S0252">yes I was not expecting to help out actually <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0251">no well it was a good job we were a bit early because I I don't think they would have been ready is we hadn't turned up actually</u>
<u n="212" who="S0252">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="213" who="S0251">there was still quite a bit to do wasn't there laying the tables and</u>
<u n="214" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="215" who="S0251">getting all the food out setting up the glasses and cups and saucers</u>
<u n="216" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0251">I thought they'd er done well to get it all ready and think they'd obviously stayed up late making the cake and decorating it</u>
<u n="218" who="S0252">ah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0251">and putting the vases of flowers and the candles for the table decorations</u>
<u n="220" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="221" who="S0251">they'd been very busy</u>
<u n="222" who="S0252">I in some ways I mm don't like pinning things up when I have to stand on a chair because</u>
<u n="223" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I know it's a bit dangerous isn't it?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0252">I I was nervous that I might fall or especially when the they had to particularly overhang the</u>
<u n="225" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="226" who="S0252" trans="overlap">cups and saucers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah oh yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I never thought I who I must admit am not a very athletic person</u>
<u n="228" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0251">would ever hold one of the Olympic torches</u>
<u n="230" who="S0252">I know absolutely</u>
<u n="231" who="S0251">but er but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s husband had been one of the</u>
<u n="232" who="S0252">torch bearers</u>
<u n="233" who="S0251">yeah torch bearers as the the relay went around the country didn't it?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="235" who="S0251" trans="overlap">and he had er got the torch which was quite big what</u>
<u n="236" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0251" trans="overlap">would you say? how long do you <trunc>th</trunc> I'd say it was about a metre wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm er yes it was</u>
<u n="239" who="S0251">maybe not yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0251" trans="overlap">about that</u>
<u n="242" who="S0252">erm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0251" trans="overlap">fairly heavy I thought</u>
<u n="244" who="S0252" trans="overlap">the thing that surprised me is I thought it was quite top-heavy</u>
<u n="245" who="S0251">it was top-heavy wasn't it?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0252" trans="overlap">cos just when I first held it I held it at a <trunc>sl</trunc> a slant because I was expecting the weight to be evenly distributed</u>
<u n="247" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes it wasn't was it? I think because there must be the burner in the top end</u>
<u n="248" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="249" who="S0251">it's made it heavy but at the pointy end it was quite light wasn't it?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="251" who="S0251">so you needed to hold it higher up didn't you?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0252">you did</u>
<u n="253" who="S0251">yes that was unexpected pleasure</u>
<u n="254" who="S0252">it was</u>
<u n="255" who="S0251">yeah another one for the album there</u>
<u n="256" who="S0252">yes er but perhaps a an unusual one</u>
<u n="257" who="S0251">er very yes not many people can say they've held the Olympic torch can they?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0252" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="259" who="S0251">so he did well to get chosen didn't he?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="261" who="S0251">surprising <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="262" who="S0252">well I suppose he does have a lot possibly has a bit to do with sport and athletics</u>
<u n="263" who="S0251">he's interested in it</u>
<u n="264" who="S0252" trans="overlap">in the community</u>
<u n="265" who="S0251" trans="overlap">does he still does he still play rugby?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0252">erm I think so</u>
<u n="267" who="S0251">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0252">rugby is not really a a sport that I er would like to do really any more I think it's a little bit on the rough side</u>
<u n="269" who="S0251">it's a bit dangerous really isn't it?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="271" who="S0251">it can be very physical <pause dur="short"/> I think you've tried it but you didn't especially like it did you?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0252" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="273" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it didn't really appeal</u>
<u n="274" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="275" who="S0251">no and I'm not too sorry really because it's not much fun standing on the touchlines on</u>
<u n="276" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0251">cold rainy Sunday mornings</u>
<u n="278" who="S0252">one of the things I I don't particularly like er sort of getting soil all over my clothes and</u>
<u n="279" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh no you get dirty definitely</u>
<u n="280" who="S0252" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> legs et cetera</u>
<u n="281" who="S0251">oh yes and you need a good bath after that don't you?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yeah I know yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I think it's er well that is when I'm trying to do tennis it's er that shouldn't happen <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0251"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no yes it's that's more of a summer game though isn't it?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes I no it is having said that that is a more of a summer game rather than</u>
<u n="285" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="286" who="S0252">a winter game</u>
<u n="287" who="S0251">it is isn't it and we saw <anon type="place"/> airport</u>
<u n="288" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="289" who="S0251">as we were coming back</u>
<u n="290" who="S0252">we did</u>
<u n="291" who="S0251">but we didn't see many aircraft there though what</u>
<u n="292" who="S0252" trans="overlap">no it's it's dwindled a lot since the start of the recession the original airports such as <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> have really seen a massive reduction in air travel I think <anon type="place"/> have seen the lowest level for about fifteen twenty years</u>
<u n="293" who="S0251">why's that? because there aren't the number of people going on foreign holidays or</u>
<u n="294" who="S0252" trans="overlap">well erm airlines have pulled out erm certain airlines have closed down erm have they've just <pause dur="short"/> er they have not been able to keep it up</u>
<u n="295" who="S0251">so it restricts consumer choice really because it means you've got to go to the bigger airports like Manchester</u>
<u n="296" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="297" who="S0251">or London</u>
<u n="298" who="S0252">yes I think one issue is is that <pause dur="short"/> many airlines tend to operate like to operate the same class of aircraft so that they erm all operate within say the A320 group or</u>
<u n="299" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="300" who="S0252">Boeing seven three seven group because that means lower maintenance costs</u>
<u n="301" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0252">so those aircraft are at least a hundred and twenty possibly up to two hundred and twenty depending exactly what <unclear>they're in</unclear> and just simply will not be the demand for that er</u>
<u n="303" who="S0251" trans="overlap">two hundred and twenty what?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0252">people</u>
<u n="305" who="S0251">oh right passengers</u>
<u n="306" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="307" who="S0251" trans="overlap">passengers that they can have yes</u>
<u n="308" who="S0252">mm whereas really you want to be using smaller aircraft with maybe fifty to seventy seats</u>
<u n="309" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0252">which erm would would be a commercially viable option but it's just not what airlines like to do</u>
<u n="311" who="S0251">because you think you could fill them up easier?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="313" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="314" who="S0252">there was er one commercial aircraft at the airport when we came back</u>
<u n="315" who="S0251">which one was that?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0252">it was an Eastern Airways BAE Jetstream thirty-one</u>
<u n="317" who="S0251">oh right</u>
<u n="318" who="S0252">it's only a small little aircraft with thirty-one seats</u>
<u n="319" who="S0251">oh that is very small isn't it?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0252">it is</u>
<u n="321" who="S0251">and there was a couple of <trunc>helicopt</trunc></u>
<u n="322" who="S0252">yes well I think they get quite a lot of trade from North Sea oil rigs</u>
<u n="323" who="S0251">oh I see</u>
<u n="324" who="S0252">yes I think that is a a significant erm source of revenue for the airport <pause dur="long"/> erm I'm not sure what the future is going to be like <pause dur="short"/> erm I think <pause dur="short"/> there's an element of change from er aircraft use to more high-speed rail I think er cos Eurostar is putting er more pressure on routes such as Paris and Brussels and <unclear>Viale</unclear> and obviously you can connect there to as far as Spain and Italy and Germany and erm northern Europe so that is a new source of competition that has really erm started to take over domestic routes domestic and short haul routes</u>
<u n="325" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0252">er from the UK</u>
<u n="327" who="S0251">I actually prefer going on the Eurostar because I find it less stressful than having to go through all the checks that you have to go through for the airport it seems much more relaxed and I think the the ride is more pleasant it's more airy</u>
<u n="328" who="S0252">it is</u>
<u n="329" who="S0251" trans="overlap">and you can get about and er go down to the buffet car and things</u>
<u n="330" who="S0252">you can</u>
<u n="331" who="S0251">there aren't as many restrictions on your luggage are there?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="333" who="S0251">you can more or less take on as much as you can carry and as much as</u>
<u n="334" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="335" who="S0251">you can manage so I think it's more relaxed</u>
<u n="336" who="S0252">it is</u>
<u n="337" who="S0251">and it's a very smooth ride isn't it?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0252">it is well I think they are welded tracks</u>
<u n="339" who="S0251">oh right</u>
<u n="340" who="S0252">yes it's a special erm type of track for that sort of speed</u>
<u n="341" who="S0251">mm yeah I've enjoyed it</u>
<u n="342" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="343" who="S0251">and er and you can see the countryside</u>
<u n="344" who="S0252" trans="overlap">you can that's lovely some of it yes</u>
<u n="345" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it's much more interesting isn't it especially when we've er been through France</u>
<u n="346" who="S0252">yes yes yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0251" trans="overlap">they're quite rural areas aren't they?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0252" trans="overlap">all there are village churches and</u>
<u n="349" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes they're quite attractive aren't they?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0252" trans="overlap">er sometimes harvesting the crops</u>
<u n="351" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="352" who="S0252" trans="overlap">and sowing them yes what I think er would be a good boost except I think in some ways er the Italian railway operator Trenitalia is erm buying some trains that erm are able to recognise and receive all the types of signals and power across Europe</u>
<u n="353" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0252">because each country has different voltages and signalling systems</u>
<u n="355" who="S0251">oh right</u>
<u n="356" who="S0252">so it should allow er more flexibility in</u>
<u n="357" who="S0251">yes it would</u>
<u n="358" who="S0252">erm international rail services</u>
<u n="359" who="S0251">yes mm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0252">furthermore they are erm opening a new railway line between Turin and Marseilles</u>
<u n="361" who="S0251">oh</u>
<u n="362" who="S0252">erm which will almost halve the journey time between Paris and Milan so from seven hours to about three and a half</u>
<u n="363" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="364" who="S0252" trans="overlap">so halved</u>
<u n="365" who="S0251">gosh that would be an achievement that wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0252">it would but it's will take quite a bit of time because they're having to drill under the Alps</u>
<u n="367" who="S0251">oh wow so there's quite some technical challenges</u>
<u n="368" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="369" who="S0251" trans="overlap">by the sound it of</u>
<u n="370" who="S0252">yes but I think it would definitely be well worth going on I think it will definitely mean that the mid and southern part of Italy is reachable from the north of England in a day</u>
<u n="371" who="S0251">good heavens mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0252">it would mean you can just about get to Milan in a day</u>
<u n="373" who="S0251" trans="overlap">well <event desc="unintelligible"/> yes</u>
<u n="374" who="S0252">but mm you can't get to erm Rome or</u>
<u n="375" who="S0251">no so that's</u>
<u n="376" who="S0252" trans="overlap">er Sicily or</u>
<u n="377" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0252">anywhere like that in a day</u>
<u n="379" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no yeah that's still good though</u>
<u n="380" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="381" who="S0251">yes and you you could have a different sort of holiday you could have</u>
<u n="382" who="S0252">stop off</u>
<u n="383" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah stop off have different centres that you visit and as you make your progress to the furthest destination couldn't you?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0252">you could yes</u>
<u n="385" who="S0251">I think that would be quite an interesting way to do it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0252">it would it would it would require some very effective organisation because</u>
<u n="387" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0252">those sort of high-speed trains if you buy the ticket on the day it will cost</u>
<u n="389" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0252">er a fortune</u>
<u n="391" who="S0251">yes there'll be a penalty</u>
<u n="392" who="S0252" trans="overlap">so if you you have to book it you know at least for a few months in advance to to get the</u>
<u n="393" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah so it would have to be well planned</u>
<u n="394" who="S0252">the well-priced tickets</u>
<u n="395" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="396" who="S0252">because if you did book on the erm not that far in advance</u>
<u n="397" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="398" who="S0252">it would probably be more expensive than flying</u>
<u n="399" who="S0251">right mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0252">which is a shame because I think with the European Union going from one extreme to banning Hoovers that are too er powerful</u>
<u n="401" who="S0251"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0252">they don't think about well what is a significant cause of pollution? how that would be an easy fix to have</u>
<u n="403" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0252">electric railways</u>
<u n="405" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="406" who="S0252">going at high speed</u>
<u n="407" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="408" who="S0252" trans="overlap">compared to doing something as I don't know that's not going to make as much difference like banning</u>
<u n="409" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0252">Hoover size</u>
<u n="411" who="S0251">no yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they're trying to make it competitively priced really</u>
<u n="412" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="413" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0252">I think the issue is banning Hoovers is an easy target and building a lot of railways is a big organisation</u>
<u n="415" who="S0251" trans="overlap">that's more difficult isn't it definitely</u>
<u n="416" who="S0252" trans="overlap">and costs a lot more money</u>
<u n="417" who="S0251">it does</u>
<u n="418" who="S0252">but erm I think it is starting to come together I think they are getting erm new railways built and</u>
<u n="419" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0252">obviously trains that can run in most of Europe it should help to</u>
<u n="421" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah that's very versatile isn't it?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0252" trans="overlap">erm connect Europe better</u>
<u n="423" who="S0251">yes it'll be good</u>
<u n="424" who="S0252">good would you be tempted to go on that? or</u>
<u n="425" who="S0251">yes definitely it sounds er quite an adventure doesn't it?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0252">yes I think one place which we have gone on holiday is Greece and I I think</u>
<u n="427" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="428" who="S0252">that would be quite tricky to do by rail because erm you're going through countries that don't really have a really impressive rail system</u>
<u n="429" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I mean Greece doesn't have such an impressive railway system</u>
<u n="431" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="432" who="S0252">and Bulgaria and</u>
<u n="433" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0252">er that sort of area but</u>
<u n="435" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0252">er just a bit</u>
<u n="437" who="S0251">needs more development</u>
<u n="438" who="S0252">most of the some of the rolling stock is sort of from the former Soviet Union so it's a bit</u>
<u n="439" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh it is <pause dur="short"/> bit older</u>
<u n="440" who="S0252">yes it's a bit older</u>
<u n="441" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0252">but apparently it can be done in three days</u>
<u n="443" who="S0251">to where?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0252">to Athens from London</u>
<u n="445" who="S0251">oh right three days</u>
<u n="446" who="S0252">yeah yes</u>
<u n="447" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0252">it's a bit of time that</u>
<u n="449" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="450" who="S0252">but it should improve because there's a a new line between <unclear>Thessaloniki</unclear> and Athens which should speed things up a bit</u>
<u n="451" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="452" who="S0252">I think they're trying to erm invest in er public spending projects in order to help the deficit in Greece</u>
<u n="453" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh the planning yes</u>
<u n="454" who="S0252" trans="overlap">to try and get people erm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0251" trans="overlap">in more work</u>
<u n="456" who="S0252" trans="overlap">back to work</u>
<u n="457" who="S0251">yes yes</u>
<u n="458" who="S0252">yes so the</u>
<u n="459" who="S0251">that'll be good</u>
<u n="460" who="S0252">it would having said that they are making improvements to the Greek rail system because they are erm are now online you can book tickets online now which you</u>
<u n="461" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="462" who="S0252">I couldn't do</u>
<u n="463" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="464" who="S0252"><trunc>ver</trunc> very long</u>
<u n="465" who="S0251">very forward looking yes</u>
<u n="466" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes so I think that would help them because</u>
<u n="467" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0252">they have made some big losses erm in the past</u>
<u n="469" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm you</u>
<u n="470" who="S0252" trans="overlap">years</u>
<u n="471" who="S0251">mm <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that she wasn't really interested on going on any more flights because she finds it too tiring now that she's getting a bit older but er they've just got one holiday left that's already booked which is flying and they're going to Israel</u>
<u n="472" who="S0252">oh</u>
<u n="473" who="S0251">so <trunc>tha</trunc> she's just a little bit</u>
<u n="474" who="S0252">anxious</u>
<u n="475" who="S0251">concerned yes about how safe that is going to be</u>
<u n="476" who="S0252">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0251">they're going to fly and they're going for six days</u>
<u n="478" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="479" who="S0251">but they really want to go and look at Bethlehem</u>
<u n="480" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="481" who="S0251">in particular erm but she doesn't know whether she's going to be disappointed when she sees it because I think you possibly have a preconceived idea that it's going to look something like a Christmas card and if it er is a situation that is a little bit tense in that country it might spoil your idea of what it looks like and what it should be there potentially be a bit of a mismatch</u>
<u n="482" who="S0252">mm I think in some ways they've picked the wrong time to go really because I think in the past few years the tensions between Gaza and Israel have not as been as heightened</u>
<u n="483" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0252" trans="overlap">as they have in the last</u>
<u n="485" who="S0251">well yes</u>
<u n="486" who="S0252">six months</u>
<u n="487" who="S0251">yes I suppose they've been waiting until they've got retired and they've picked one or two other holidays they recently wanted to go to Crete erm because that's where their father was fighting during the war</u>
<u n="488" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="489" who="S0251">and what with the anniversary of the First World War coming up they thought it would probably be appropriate to go and walk in the footsteps of where he was in Crete and er <pause dur="short"/> well not see what he had to contend with but just look at the countryside and they didn't tell us too much about what they actually found there did they?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="491" who="S0251">no they</u>
<u n="492" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I think he did survive so</u>
<u n="493" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes he did survive yes he did get back</u>
<u n="494" who="S0252" trans="overlap">erm there wouldn't have been a a grave or anything to see</u>
<u n="495" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no no but there could have been some other landmarks or museums and</u>
<u n="496" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes yes <pause dur="short"/> I think in some ways it would have been very emotional for them to think</u>
<u n="497" who="S0251" trans="overlap">it could yes</u>
<u n="498" who="S0252">that erm a hundred years ago the</u>
<u n="499" who="S0251" trans="overlap">well it wasn't the first oh yes it was the Second World War that he was fighting in though wasn't it?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0252" trans="overlap">oh was it?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="502" who="S0252">oh right so that would have been</u>
<u n="503" who="S0251">the thirty-nine forty-five war</u>
<u n="504" who="S0252">the then it wouldn't be a hundred years</u>
<u n="505" who="S0251">no I think it's the hundred years anniversary that just prompted them to think about it I think</u>
<u n="506" who="S0252">I see oh</u>
<u n="507" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0252">yeah I <trunc>sup</trunc> it must be a surprise to think that that would have been the case</u>
<u n="509" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="510" who="S0252">but obviously er I think they'd have had a rather more enjoyable experience <vocal desc="laugh"/> than the</u>
<u n="511" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I hope so definitely</u>
<u n="512" who="S0252" trans="overlap">her father</u>
<u n="513" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0252">er I don't suppose I suppose er on a the slightly positive side of it it <trunc>cer</trunc> I don't think it would have been as bad as the Somme and that lot</u>
<u n="515" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="516" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I think it will have still have been very er emotional and er</u>
<u n="517" who="S0251">definitely</u>
<u n="518" who="S0252" trans="overlap">a horrific experience</u>
<u n="519" who="S0251" trans="overlap">traumatic definitely</u>
<u n="520" who="S0252">but so which erm area did he fight in? is it army and navy or air force or?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0251">army I presumed I think yes army I think</u>
<u n="522" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="523" who="S0251">yeah do you remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? so you remember seeing him do you remember seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="525" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="526" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="527" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="528" who="S0252">no I do not</u>
<u n="529" who="S0251">you may be a bit young to remember him</u>
<u n="530" who="S0252">yes <pause dur="short"/> but in some ways it's a a little shame that they didn't go when he was er alive</u>
<u n="531" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm to take him back yeah to see him to see the place in a better light <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0252">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0252">yes also he would have been able to tell them that that</u>
<u n="535" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="536" who="S0252" trans="overlap">that footsteps</u>
<u n="537" who="S0251" trans="overlap">to point out the venues and that yeah you're right</u>
<u n="538" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="539" who="S0251">I think he was probably just glad to get away from it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0252">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
