<text id="SWHR">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:12:10</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0365 S0366 S0420</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Computers, technology</topics>
		<activity>Family discussing new technology</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0365">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London (Essex)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Edinburgh</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Scotland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Basic</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0366">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Oxford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Scotland</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scottish twang</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Edinburgh</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Scotland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur></hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>scotland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>scotland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>scotland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Psychotherapist/Nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0420">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Scotish</nat>
				<birthplace>Edinburgh</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Scotland</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Edinburgh</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Edinburgh</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Scotland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>scotland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>scotland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>scotland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Director of Studies</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0420">so you got a new laptop?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0366">yeah I'm really pleased about this laptop cos I've never had one before</u>
<u n="3" who="S0420">what a laptop?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0366">no I've never owned a laptop only had a static computer</u>
<u n="5" who="S0420">oh like a desktop</u>
<u n="6" who="S0366">mm mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0420">and the so what what what prompted you?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0366" trans="overlap">well it's <pause dur="short"/> erm well er my friend's partner erm you know I was asking him about getting a laptop and he said he well he had one that he wasn't using</u>
<u n="9" who="S0420">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0366">that was only a year old so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0365">but you first came round to wanting a laptop cos you had a purpose you were trying to get a presentation ready</u>
<u n="12" who="S0420">ah ah yeah that's</u>
<u n="13" who="S0366" trans="overlap">yes yes for the talk</u>
<u n="14" who="S0420">after doing the presentation yeah so</u>
<u n="15" who="S0366">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0420">you found you couldn't live without it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0366" trans="overlap">well now I'm yeah I want I decided erm well I I'm trying to write and I find writing on the laptop once I've formulated a few ideas rather than just writing longhand I find it really good to just to to</u>
<u n="18" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah cos you can go back and edit stuff and <unclear/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0366" trans="overlap">yeah dead easy it's dead easy erm so <pause dur="short"/> so er yeah that was <unclear/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0420" trans="overlap">still it's not as difficult to use as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="21" who="S0366">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s is going back tonight</u>
<u n="22" who="S0420"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0366">I've got to just get the fingerprints off it and sort of tidy it up a bit and but it's not that was very difficult</u>
<u n="24" who="S0420">yeah yeah I think you just I think he wished he hadn't bought it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0366">yeah he does</u>
<u n="26" who="S0420">oh well and you're still plugging away with the Linux one?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0365">I am yeah yeah I like er using Linux cos it's erm a bit different and erm it's not Microsoft</u>
<u n="28" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0365">which is a <unclear/> bonus</u>
<u n="30" who="S0420">you're not losing any money to Bill Gates or Steve Jobs or</u>
<u n="31" who="S0365" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0420">and of these</u>
<u n="33" who="S0365">and what I found with these er new laptops and er Windows is that they are trying to extract information from you all the time if you notice that erm <pause dur="short"/> computers constantly engaging with the internet so</u>
<u n="34" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0365">they're taking information off you that's why I don't like so</u>
<u n="36" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah I get the same with my phone</u>
<u n="37" who="S0365"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0420">it's always saying you know data will be <trunc>trans</trunc> you know data will be shared with this and that and the other</u>
<u n="39" who="S0366" trans="overlap">yes I don't like that</u>
<u n="40" who="S0420">it is a bit worrying but I I think you can there's a lot of things you can click so it's not doing that I think that you just actually need to spend the time but yeah since I've started using that Linux laptop I'm very happy</u>
<u n="41" who="S0365">right right</u>
<u n="42" who="S0420">the only problem is</u>
<u n="43" who="S0365"><unclear>so</unclear> you're using Open Office?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0420">er <trunc>Lib</trunc>Libra</u>
<u n="45" who="S0365">yes</u>
<u n="46" who="S0420">and er it's just the one that came with that</u>
<u n="47" who="S0366">is that similar to Open Office?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0365">it is an Open Office programme yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah they're all a much of a muchness really</u>
<u n="50" who="S0365">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0420">erm but it's definitely good cos now and again you get something that you can't do that perhaps a a normal laptop could do but there's not much</u>
<u n="52" who="S0365">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0420">and if you spend a bit of time finding out about it it's not bad</u>
<u n="54" who="S0365">the other thing about Linux is if you erm need to fix something it is a lot harder than <unclear>Windows</unclear></u>
<u n="55" who="S0420" trans="overlap">there is a greatest sense of achievement isn't there?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0365">there is yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0420"><unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0366">why's it harder?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0365">er sometimes er well it's not so good at automatically installing things</u>
<u n="60" who="S0420">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0365">so you have to find a programme install it and find the right place to install it it's getting better erm the other thing is that sometimes if you need to fix things you actually have to enter lines of code so remember on my computer the brightness control doesn't work automatically</u>
<u n="62" who="S0366">mm mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0365">I have to put in a small line of code I had to find on the internet cos</u>
<u n="64" who="S0366" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="65" who="S0365">I can't code in Unix so</u>
<u n="66" who="S0366">in Unix?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0365">Unix is</u>
<u n="68" who="S0420" trans="overlap">the language of the operating system</u>
<u n="69" who="S0365">the language of the operating system yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0420">but it's nice that you get there's a sense of achievement it's like being able to change the oil in your car or something like that</u>
<u n="71" who="S0365" trans="overlap">yeah that's right mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0420">if you can do it erm it's kind of <unclear/> about but so the new one is brand shiny and</u>
<u n="73" who="S0366" trans="overlap">well what happened was he the house got broken into and</u>
<u n="74" who="S0365" trans="overlap">your friend's house</u>
<u n="75" who="S0366">a friend's house about a year and a half ago</u>
<u n="76" who="S0420" trans="overlap">and you've got a laptop from them</u>
<u n="77" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0420">right okay it all becomes clear</u>
<u n="79" who="S0366">and erm the insurance paid for a you know a replacement</u>
<u n="80" who="S0420">ah yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0366">and erm so I was just saying I didn't want a computer with Windows eight on it like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s one so I wanted I didn't need a and I didn't want a touch screen you know the new one's I just wanted one maybe year or two old</u>
<u n="82" who="S0420">yes</u>
<u n="83" who="S0366">and erm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said ah I think I might have something you're interested in he said you know what were you thinking of spending? and I said well you know not more than about two fifty and he and he said well would you like this for one fifty? and it's erm basically it's about a year old he's hardly used it and so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then looked it up on the web and at the very least it was six hundred wasn't it?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0420" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="85" who="S0365">yes yes</u>
<u n="86" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><unclear>wow</unclear> that's a bargain</u>
<u n="87" who="S0366">yeah oh it's fantastic er it's really fast</u>
<u n="88" who="S0365" trans="overlap">and the reviews are really good yeah five star reviews</u>
<u n="89" who="S0420" trans="overlap">what brand is it?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0366">it's Samsung</u>
<u n="91" who="S0420"><trunc>Sams</trunc> okay</u>
<u n="92" who="S0366"><trunc>cro</trunc>cromo</u>
<u n="93" who="S0420"><unclear/> so it's a recognised brand isn't it?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0366">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0420">good</u>
<u n="96" who="S0366">and it's so after using <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s er when you're using the <trunc>p</trunc> er what do you call it? the curser</u>
<u n="97" who="S0420" trans="overlap">the touchpad</u>
<u n="98" who="S0366">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s was so difficult</u>
<u n="99" who="S0420">yeah it had that bumpy kind of</u>
<u n="100" who="S0366" trans="overlap">and this one is so smooth</u>
<u n="101" who="S0365" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0366">and</u>
<u n="103" who="S0420" trans="overlap">it's very unnatural</u>
<u n="104" who="S0366">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0365" trans="overlap">yeah it's</u>
<u n="106" who="S0366">whereas this one is so smooth it's it's fantastic</u>
<u n="107" who="S0420">good</u>
<u n="108" who="S0366">erm so going to buy <unclear/> tomorrow</u>
<u n="109" who="S0420">mm I need to yeah I need to think about getting my old laptop I've got a big one as well that little Linux the white one I've got is good but I've got a big laptop sitting there and that's only a year year and a bit old and that's the one that got broken the hard disk</u>
<u n="110" who="S0365">ah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0420">it's dead so it would need a new hard disc hard drive? hard disc? is it the same thing?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0365">I think it's the same thing</u>
<u n="113" who="S0420">yeah I need a new one fitted a brand new one fitted and an operating system put on it again so that would probably cost about a hundred and fifty pounds so</u>
<u n="114" who="S0365" trans="overlap">it's getting to the realms now where it's almost as easy to buy a new one isn't it?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0420">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0365">erm like my computer if I was to replace it it would cost about two hundred pounds so there's almost no point me er <unclear>fixing it</unclear></u>
<u n="117" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><trunc>re</trunc>repairs unless there's unless there's stuff on the machine itself or it was an expensive machine to begin with if it was a thousand pound machine and there's only a small problem they probably would fix it because you've already spent that money for a reason</u>
<u n="118" who="S0365">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0420">you know for <trunc>capat</trunc> the capabilities of the computer but I don't know I don't</u>
<u n="120" who="S0365" trans="overlap">what brought you to Linux then?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0366">he doesn't use it do you use Linux?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0420" trans="overlap">it's free <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0365">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0366">I didn't realise you used Linux</u>
<u n="125" who="S0420">yeah yeah on that little white laptop we've got</u>
<u n="126" who="S0366">oh right</u>
<u n="127" who="S0420">erm because that had Windows on it when I bought it from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm about four or five years ago now <pause dur="short"/> erm and then I I got hold of a disc which so I put a newer Windows on it but it couldn't really cope with it</u>
<u n="128" who="S0365">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0420">and then I had it as a <unclear/> when I was in Tunisia erm after <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was born I went back to Tunisia after being back in China for a couple of weeks I put I put I took that with me and left <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the big laptop and I put it with a double boot system so it could do Windows or Linux and it didn't work very well a lot of the stuff like you said adjusting the the brightness and things like that there erm were certain things that didn't work and the one I'm using now Linux Mint work very well</u>
<u n="130" who="S0365">ah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0420">erm there's nothing that it doesn't do that I want it to do</u>
<u n="132" who="S0365">really?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0366">do you know Linux do you know what Linux <trunc>me</trunc> is?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0365">I don't no I use <unclear>Ubuntu</unclear> and</u>
<u n="136" who="S0420">I I just like the name <vocal desc="laugh"/> and and and</u>
<u n="137" who="S0366" trans="overlap">sounds cool</u>
<u n="138" who="S0420">yeah Linux</u>
<u n="139" who="S0365" trans="overlap"><trunc>sou</trunc>sounds more like Windows which is erm although they call it kind of plug and play</u>
<u n="140" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah some some things not everything but I don't know it's good and it's it's you know</u>
<u n="141" who="S0365" trans="overlap">and the thing about it is that it is erm an older it's based on an older operating system but it was coded properly from the beginning and like you say your computer was struggling with the latest version</u>
<u n="142" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0365">of Windows but this operating system which is more sophisticated because it is more efficient it actually works better</u>
<u n="144" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0365">uhu even on a <unclear/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0420" trans="overlap">I've not had any problems with it it's not frozen or crashed or anything like that I did try to install an update and it wasn't happy with that so I just went back and uninstalled it and it was happy again so I I don't know enough about them and I don't have enough I don't care enough about them <vocal desc="laugh"/> to want to learn about it</u>
<u n="147" who="S0366">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0420">so you just want it to work erm <pause dur="short"/> but when I get my first pay cheque from my new job</u>
<u n="149" who="S0365">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0420">I'm gonna buy a new Ipad so</u>
<u n="151" who="S0365"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0366">oh yeah when do you start your job?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0420">I have</u>
<u n="154" who="S0366">oh you have started?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0420">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0366">oh right</u>
<u n="157" who="S0420" trans="overlap">well I've I've been</u>
<u n="158" who="S0366" trans="overlap">oh yes you would have by now</u>
<u n="159" who="S0420">well no I've been going in in the afternoons when I don't when I've not been teaching</u>
<u n="160" who="S0366">mm mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0420">just to kind of get up to speed and also cos my boss had a lot to run through with me <pause dur="short"/> he erm <pause dur="short"/> he's away on holiday for two weeks from Tuesday</u>
<u n="162" who="S0366">right</u>
<u n="163" who="S0420">so he wanted to get me up to speed</u>
<u n="164" who="S0366">uhu</u>
<u n="165" who="S0420">before that so erm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0366" trans="overlap">oh so is it looking positive?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0420">yeah yeah hard work but positive</u>
<u n="168" who="S0366">right good</u>
<u n="169" who="S0420">tried to recruit a trying to recruit a few teachers at the moment but one one she's perfect she <unclear>looked</unclear> like a really good teacher erm <pause dur="short"/> she was easy on the eye which'll go down well with the Italians and the Spanish students coming across <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0366"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0420">and of course what happens? she got poached by another school and we offered her a more permanent contract</u>
<u n="172" who="S0365" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="173" who="S0420">but erm ah these things happen</u>
<u n="174" who="S0366">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0365">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0420">but er no going back to your computer erm you've got no excuse now not to use <unclear>Prezi</unclear></u>
<u n="177" who="S0366">yes ah right</u>
<u n="178" who="S0365">what's Prezi?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0366">Prezi is this erm er I've only see a week bit erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> showed me but it's instead of Powerpoint so instead of us sort of</u>
<u n="180" who="S0365" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0366">from what I gather a sort of linear slide presentation it's a bit like going into some kind of memory board or something</u>
<u n="182" who="S0365" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="183" who="S0420" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0366">and being able to go into different bits it's more three dimensional</u>
<u n="185" who="S0420">yeah but more dynamic than than erm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0366" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0420">than Powerpoint</u>
<u n="188" who="S0366" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0365">and is that erm a <unclear/> software?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0420">no the <pause dur="short"/> there's two <trunc>th</trunc>there's a free version and there's a sort of premium version</u>
<u n="191" who="S0365" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0420" trans="overlap">and I think the free version you can do almost anything with it erm I used it given I mean I did workshops in China for for teachers and <trunc>gen</trunc> it caught people's attention which was nice erm rather than saying well I'm gonna put the PP you know the Powerpoint on now and most people go oh god really? erm but I think it it does it's like more and more like a memory board you've got more it's more flexible as you're using it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0366">mm mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0420">which is nice and because it <trunc>work</trunc></u>
<u n="195" who="S0365" trans="overlap">does it work on the Windows?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0420">it works on all the platforms I think</u>
<u n="197" who="S0365" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0420">erm cos it's web based</u>
<u n="199" who="S0365">oh I see</u>
<u n="200" who="S0420">erm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0365" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="202" who="S0420">but you can pay for it and have it locally</u>
<u n="203" who="S0365" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="204" who="S0420">erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't I I really like it I just</u>
<u n="205" who="S0365">so if it's web based where do you store your presentation?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0420">on on on in the cloud</u>
<u n="207" who="S0366">in the cloud</u>
<u n="208" who="S0365" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="209" who="S0420">in the cloud sounds so threatening doesn't it? but erm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0365">so it's a bit like a Dropbox system? where you can store your stuff</u>
<u n="211" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0365">er on another server</u>
<u n="213" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah more or less I think <trunc>y</trunc> as a free user you can download so many before you</u>
<u n="214" who="S0365" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0420">before they sort of cap it</u>
<u n="216" who="S0365">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0366">right</u>
<u n="218" who="S0420" trans="overlap">erm and for things like phones and Ipads there's actually a <pause dur="short"/> an app and I think you can download all your Prezis so erm <pause dur="short"/> but because it's more more memory board's a good way of describing it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you tend not to put as much text on</u>
<u n="219" who="S0365">mm mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0420">so you it's more visually oriented</u>
<u n="221" who="S0366">mm mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0420">which I think presentations should be cos the</u>
<u n="223" who="S0366" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0420">you know the if they're gonna be sitting reading something it's a bit of a waste of time isn't it?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0366" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0365" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0420">to be to be presenting it so we'll see</u>
<u n="228" who="S0366">oh yeah if you wanna come I'm giving a talk on the first of March</u>
<u n="229" who="S0420">first of March what day is that?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0366">Sunday</u>
<u n="231" who="S0420">Sunday?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0366" trans="overlap">Sunday afternoon</u>
<u n="233" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0366">if you wanna come <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know if anyone's gonna come yet but that's another topic</u>
<u n="235" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I'll be there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0366"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0420">yeah that'll be good then you've got your new laptop now</u>
<u n="238" who="S0366"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0420" trans="overlap">so you can do it was confidence</u>
<u n="240" who="S0366">absolutely</u>
<u n="241" who="S0420">sounds good</u>
<u n="242" who="S0366"><unclear>I hope so</unclear></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
