<text id="SWLR">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:46:35</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0391 S0393</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Navigation, aviation, schedule, weddings, weather, technology, wildlife, food and drink, music, poetry, ceilidhs, driving, injury, work, property, crafts, wool, politics, places, history, sport, people, equipment, retail, satnavs, culture, local area, </topics>
		<activity>Journey to Gig</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0391">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Darlington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>British</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>County Durham</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0393">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kendal</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern/RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bagby near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Writer</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0393">just as long as we get there in time</u>
<u n="2" who="S0391">that's why er I think we'll go the fast way <pause dur="short"/> see I haven't got anywhere and it's nearly ten past ten</u>
<u n="3" who="S0393">which way's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0391">he's going the way he knows past <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <trunc>p</trunc>past the <trunc>airp</trunc> you know where we were the other night? for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0393">he said he said <anon type="place"/> airfield is that what he means when he says the airfield? does he? <pause dur="short"/> is that what they used to call the airport?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0391">no I think that's there as well</u>
<u n="7" who="S0393">the main thing is just to relax because er <pause dur="short"/> we don't start playing till one o'clock</u>
<u n="8" who="S0391">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they could even hold it up couldn't they?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0393" trans="overlap">it <trunc>w</trunc> it <trunc>w</trunc> it would literally take five minutes</u>
<u n="10" who="S0391">right</u>
<u n="11" who="S0393">to get the those two amps up the stairs right?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0391" trans="overlap">ah right it's just like playing for mass?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0393">it is really they do a tuning up and stuff like that</u>
<u n="14" who="S0391">well the thing is they can easily wait it's not like you've got a registry office spot is it? it's less pressure</u>
<u n="15" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0391">cos they are already married there's no registrar there <pause dur="short"/> there's no <trunc>si</trunc></u>
<u n="17" who="S0393" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0391">there's no signing in of the register</u>
<u n="19" who="S0393">oh I see right</u>
<u n="20" who="S0391">they just went and did that on their own and this is their wedding celebration</u>
<u n="21" who="S0393" trans="overlap">so what's this then? they're just doing their vows?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0391">this er they they they only went for a small official service to the registry office just before we met them they'd done it two weeks before that or something</u>
<u n="23" who="S0393">right</u>
<u n="24" who="S0391">so that they didn't wanna be bothered with all the official stuff at their wedding</u>
<u n="25" who="S0393">okay</u>
<u n="26" who="S0391">they <trunc>w</trunc> do you see what I mean? they've planned this wedding day themselves sort of celebration <pause dur="short"/> that was today</u>
<u n="27" who="S0393">er so there there won't be a minister or a <unclear/></u>
<event desc="sound of sat nav"/>
<u n="28" who="S0391">no that might fall</u>
<u n="29" who="S0393">yeah that's <unclear>due to fair up</unclear> anyway isn't it?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0391">I thought the rain would be worse <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of sat nav"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0393"><unclear>I</unclear></u>
<u n="32" who="S0391">see how clear that is? I'd rather follow that than try a different route</u>
<u n="33" who="S0393">the sat nav?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0391">I'd rather follow the sat nav than try a different route even if the other route was gonna be shorter what would you rather do?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0393">I <trunc>w</trunc> I must admit I would've looked into it beforehand and and found the the quickest route</u>
<u n="36" who="S0391">but you're a navigator</u>
<u n="37" who="S0393">no I'm the guitarist</u>
<u n="38" who="S0391">no you're the navigator as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0393">well do you want me to have a look on the atlas?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0391">no cos we know the two routes it's just which one do we take? the easy one following the sat nav</u>
<u n="41" who="S0393">if if you kept on going right? and disobeyed the sat nav</u>
<u n="42" who="S0391" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0393">and went to <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> would the sat nav pick you up and start directing you?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <trunc>y</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0393">the only thing is</u>
<u n="46" who="S0391" trans="overlap">it would take longer</u>
<u n="47" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah as I that's what I'm saying</u>
<u n="48" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0393">because er often people who take as I have done in the past it doesn't end up being shorter does it?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0391">no</u>
<u n="51" who="S0393" trans="overlap">just take shorter in miles but longer in time</u>
<u n="52" who="S0391">yeah well that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he said this way is shorter in miles but longer in time <pause dur="short"/> so for the purpose of this journey I think we should just go the easy longer <unclear>proper</unclear> route</u>
<u n="53" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's a kestrel <unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0391">evidently it flares up the further south you get</u>
<u n="55" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0391">so</u>
<u n="57" who="S0393">I mean I <pause dur="short"/> we must remember to see if they want some slow airs in the</u>
<u n="58" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh at the end of the service? yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0393" trans="overlap">you know when they're signing the book or</u>
<u n="60" who="S0391">no there's no book to sign</u>
<u n="61" who="S0393" trans="overlap">oh well whatever they do</u>
<u n="62" who="S0391">I think they will want music even</u>
<u n="63" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0393" trans="overlap">we've got the music it's not a problem</u>
<u n="66" who="S0391" trans="overlap">they they've designed their own service so they must be creative</u>
<u n="67" who="S0393">they are aren't they?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0391">yes they're quite</u>
<u n="69" who="S0393" trans="overlap">I tell you I know what we'll do</u>
<u n="70" who="S0391">have you brought the Thomas Hardy?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0393">I've got all the poems and stuff yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0391">have you got the Thomas Hardy though? cos he wants literature and he liked that <unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0393" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> but listen I've driven it from my mind</u>
<u n="74" who="S0391"><unclear>mm</unclear>?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0393">oh yeah I know what we'll do we'll tell them I'll just start inventing</u>
<u n="76" who="S0391">oh yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0393">the origins of these dances cos no one knows you know waulking songs?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0393" trans="overlap">W A U L K I N G</u>
<u n="80" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0393">in Scotland they did them everywhere like <unclear/> you know tunes for for er <trunc>sp</trunc>specific tasks</u>
<u n="82" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0393">one of the main ones was when they dyed yarn and all of that in urine</u>
<u n="84" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0393">to preserve it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0393">so I'll say this is reciprocating the</u>
<u n="88" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0393">yeah do you want some of this can before I have a go?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0391">no thanks yeah <pause dur="long"/> that's a good idea to make it specific to this one</u>
<u n="91" who="S0393">I mean they sounded</u>
<u n="92" who="S0391" trans="overlap">it's really good if you can do those poems cos it just lets me find the next dance get the <unclear>moves</unclear> into my head</u>
<u n="93" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0391">gives <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a break cos it's quite</u>
<u n="95" who="S0393" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0391">physically demanding for him</u>
<u n="97" who="S0393">I've got one by Pablo Neruda</u>
<u n="98" who="S0391">oh good idea yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0393">I've got one by er John Agard it's quite nice</u>
<u n="100" who="S0391">what's that one?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0393">it's er something like let your love be a river you know that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="102" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="103" who="S0393">there was a Guardian thing where it had they asked modern poets to er write verses about <trunc>w</trunc> for weddings</u>
<u n="104" who="S0391">they've probably I bet there's one they've chosen at least from yours <vocal desc="laugh"/> we'll have to listen to the service</u>
<u n="105" who="S0393" trans="overlap">no cos I avoided the search Google search for wedding</u>
<u n="106" who="S0391" trans="overlap">ah very clever</u>
<u n="107" who="S0393">I went into another one just</u>
<u n="108" who="S0391">very clever</u>
<u n="109" who="S0393" trans="overlap">I knew that would be a bit</u>
<u n="110" who="S0391">having said that</u>
<u n="111" who="S0393">there's a heron</u>
<u n="112" who="S0391">having said that oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> having said that you can't beat the ones at the <anon type="place"/> though you know where they came right down?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0393">that was amazing wasn't it?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0391">having said that I think they would quite like the ones they've chosen for the evening guests <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a different group coming tonight to dance</u>
<u n="115" who="S0393" trans="overlap">do we know how many guests there are?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0391">no they weren't sure at the time were they?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0393">are we dealing in what? a hundred? or two hundred?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0391">I <trunc>thi</trunc> I think he I think he said there was enough for people to go upstairs and downstairs so he envisaged them swapping so probably about seventy or eighty upstairs seventy or eighty downstairs</u>
<u n="119" who="S0393">right yeah it's a lot isn't it?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0391">yeah it is quite a lot <unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0393" trans="overlap">how many were at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s do?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0391">er about that</u>
<u n="123" who="S0393">hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="124" who="S0391">about that yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0393">right</u>
<u n="126" who="S0391">but a lot of hers have just come to sit down haven't they? <pause dur="short"/> I'm guessing they'll have <unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0393">do you want <unclear>that little bit</unclear> of seven up?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0391">no thanks I'm guessing they'll have <pause dur="short"/> upstairs erm <pause dur="short"/> with a buffet and downstairs with the ceilidh if people don't want to dance or listen to the music they can go and sit upstairs</u>
<u n="129" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0391">but for the very start it would be nice cos I think there'll be a lot of people for the first dance that's why I'm thinking if we get them into the middle for Circassian Circle we can even have a circle round a circle round a circle we could fit everybody in if they were careful when they go into the middle</u>
<u n="131" who="S0393" trans="overlap">what is that dance? is it quite simple?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0391">that's the simplest</u>
<u n="133" who="S0393">ah good idea to start with it then</u>
<u n="134" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0393">I was thinking maybe why not get them in the circle to start off with?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0391">oh right yeah cos <unclear/> <unclear>gather round in</unclear></u>
<u n="137" who="S0393" trans="overlap">do you without telling them that er just gather round the couple you know</u>
<u n="138" who="S0391" trans="overlap">gather round</u>
<u n="139" who="S0393"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0391">they might be anyway</u>
<u n="141" who="S0393" trans="overlap">cos do you remember the chimney sweep used to say?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0393">he didn't you know you'll never walk alone with everyone in the middle</u>
<u n="144" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah I remember</u>
<u n="145" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0391">they're not quite <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I think they're a more a different bunch <pause dur="short"/> she said she'd carefully looked at the other ones on the website and she thought this looked like more their thing <unclear>with the</unclear> explanations about the <anon type="place"/> music</u>
<u n="147" who="S0393">say it again?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0391"><unclear/> I'm trying to drive <pause dur="short"/> she chose us because we were different to the others</u>
<u n="149" who="S0393">right</u>
<u n="150" who="S0391">because we offered readings and she liked the aspect of it being <anon type="place"/> as well to explain to the <anon type="place"/> crowd</u>
<u n="151" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0391">about the <anon type="place"/> music <pause dur="long"/> is that the Strip the Willow one?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0393">which one?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0391">the <anon type="place"/> music one</u>
<u n="155" who="S0393">er I don't know it's about</u>
<event desc="sound of sat nav"/>
<u n="156" who="S0391">I thought it was keep right up here <unclear/> the other day <pause dur="short"/> when I <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0393" trans="overlap">so you put this you put this venue into that sat nav?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0391" trans="overlap">hang on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this is it's er bad visibility <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of sat nav"/> what did she say?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0393">bear in the right lane I think you have to be</u>
<u n="160" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0393" trans="overlap">oh we're alright we're in the south yeah no that's alright yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh <unclear>it's</unclear> alright <pause dur="short"/> I've still gotta overtake this is it a caravan?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0391">it's supposed to be brighter it's darker down here look at it</u>
<u n="165" who="S0393" trans="overlap">there's a copper don't be speeding</u>
<u n="166" who="S0391">I'm not speeding I'm not even up to seventy <pause dur="short"/> get into trouble for not doing seventy sometimes in this lane</u>
<u n="167" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0393">I'd love to do one of these events where people aren't panicking all the time</u>
<u n="169" who="S0391">who's panicking?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0393">well about getting there on time or about erm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah that's why the <anon type="place"/> ones'll be lovely absolute bliss cos you know if you've forgotten something you can just pop home we've got two of those haven't we?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0393">we have indeed</u>
<u n="173" who="S0391">that'll be fantastic</u>
<u n="174" who="S0393">my only thing about the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s one is er if someone falls down like they did last time flat on their face they'd crack their head open</u>
<u n="175" who="S0391" trans="overlap">this'll be a hard this'll be a hard floor as well do I get over in the other lane? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0393">yeah you join it <pause dur="long"/> I don't know about the floor cos er <pause dur="short"/> when I worked at the <anon type="place"/> the upper floors were wooden but I suppose that's like a hazard these days is it?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0391">I don't know what you mean</u>
<u n="178" who="S0393">well you said a hard floor it might be there might be wooden floors but the ceiling's laced with</u>
<u n="179" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="180" who="S0393">ceilings'll be laced with asbestos</u>
<u n="181" who="S0391">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> well they'll have to be careful and look for hazards I didn't like it when she said I don't want the dancing on the first floor</u>
<u n="182" who="S0393">well</u>
<u n="183" who="S0391"><unclear>did you</unclear>?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0393">that's obviously why</u>
<u n="185" who="S0391">no she thought we'd cave in</u>
<u n="186" who="S0393">yeah <pause dur="long"/> god the visibility's terrible</u>
<u n="187" who="S0391">poor isn't it? I think it is brightening up though I thought it was getting darker but</u>
<u n="188" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0391">it is brightening up a bit <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> it's supposed to <unclear>get er nicer</unclear> this afternoon isn't it?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0393">yeah I wonder if I should write a poem for them</u>
<u n="191" who="S0391">oh that would be nice <pause dur="short"/> maybe you need to see the mill <pause dur="long"/> what do you reckon?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0391">aren't they leaving the mill behind? <pause dur="short"/> I'm just guessing the venue'll feature in it</u>
<u n="194" who="S0393">they are leaving the mill behind just <unclear>they'll</unclear> have the lease</u>
<u n="195" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0393">her dad leased it before</u>
<u n="197" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0393">so this is probably a bit of a wrench isn't it? in that respect</u>
<u n="199" who="S0391">yeah they obviously want to have one last celebration in it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0393">I should've just taken the those poems <unclear>that I</unclear> used to do for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and people like that</u>
<u n="201" who="S0391">have you still got them?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0393">they're quite sort of simple aren't they? really</u>
<u n="203" who="S0391" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got hers in a frame on the wall in her house with erm she's got the poem and the bouquet <pause dur="short"/> or part of the dried flowers with the poem</u>
<u n="204" who="S0393">découpage</u>
<u n="205" who="S0391">did you keep it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0393">no</u>
<u n="207" who="S0391">oh that's alright then <vocal desc="laugh"/> won't repeat it would you like to reread it?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0393">no</u>
<u n="209" who="S0391">I bet it's lovely <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0393">do they what kind of <trunc>te</trunc> <trunc>d</trunc> is it a wool mill? are they into woollen products?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0391">yarns</u>
<u n="212" who="S0393">is a yarn wool?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0391">I think they've got threads and <unclear/> to me the website <unclear>looked more like</unclear> threads <pause dur="short"/> crafts <pause dur="long"/> I'm not sure there might be wool as well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0391">keep keep looking for me</u>
<u n="216" who="S0393">I am love is like the life of wool <pause dur="short"/> it begins amongst mist and drizzle with the sheep in the moors</u>
<u n="217" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh that's nice</u>
<u n="218" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0393">it's it begins in mystery how about that?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0391">love begins in mystery</u>
<u n="221" who="S0393">love is like the life of wool</u>
<u n="222" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0393">it begins far away</u>
<u n="224" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they'll love this</u>
<u n="225" who="S0393">in mystery</u>
<u n="226" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0393">sheep <pause dur="short"/> er sheep startled on the moors how about that?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0391">yeah cos they're they're erm they're just near the moors aren't they?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0393">sheep startled on the moors leave a fibre of life on the brambles <unclear>is</unclear> it too much? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0391">the beginning was nice just tone it down a bit</u>
<u n="231" who="S0393" trans="overlap">love is like the life of wool it begins far away in mystery sheep</u>
<u n="232" who="S0391" trans="overlap">mist and mystery might be nice cos there was</u>
<u n="233" who="S0393" trans="overlap">well hold on sheep</u>
<u n="234" who="S0391"><unclear>maybe</unclear> those misty moors that's where they live</u>
<u n="235" who="S0393">sheep startled on the misty moors <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> no it's no good</u>
<u n="236" who="S0391">ah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0393">far away in mystery sheep startled on the misty moors <pause dur="short"/> how about walkers startled sheep on the misty moors?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0393">a startle of sheep on the misty moors leaves behind right</u>
<u n="240" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0393">a startle of sheep <pause dur="short"/> on the misty moors leaves behind a garment in embryo</u>
<u n="242" who="S0391">yeah?</u>
<u n="243" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0393">leaves behind the dream of a garment</u>
<u n="245" who="S0391">oh yes that's better much better you don't wanna be talking about embryos</u>
<u n="246" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0393">leaves behind the dream of a garment erm <pause dur="short"/> fleeces accrue <pause dur="short"/> what's the next process in woollen making? urine</u>
<u n="248" who="S0391">no you put it on the erm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0393">ah a carder</u>
<u n="250" who="S0391">is that what they call it?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so love is like the life of wool it begins far away <pause dur="short"/> from town times er in mystery a startle of sheep on the misty no it's it's too</u>
<u n="252" who="S0391">you've got the right ideas</u>
<u n="253" who="S0393">yeah that sort of thing</u>
<u n="254" who="S0391">just get the ideas down for now</u>
<u n="255" who="S0393" trans="overlap">I'll do er I'll do it later when we're</u>
<u n="256" who="S0391" trans="overlap">well why don't you write some <trunc>idea</trunc> cos all your ideas are good it's just putting them together</u>
<u n="257" who="S0393">well it's just gonna be the</u>
<u n="258" who="S0391" trans="overlap">the journey of the wool</u>
<u n="259" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0391">so that's what I'm thinking so what do they do with the yarn on that erm?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0393" trans="overlap">they card it that's why you get wool carder bees</u>
<u n="262" who="S0391">yes yes</u>
<u n="263" who="S0393">carding then you preserve it in urine but we'll leave that bit out</u>
<u n="264" who="S0391">leave that bit out</u>
<u n="265" who="S0393">carding tenterhooks</u>
<u n="266" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0393">isn't that when they stretch it? leaves you on</u>
<u n="268" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah stretching on tenterhooks</u>
<u n="269" who="S0393">love can leave you on tenterhooks</u>
<u n="270" who="S0391" trans="overlap">ah <unclear/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0393">well</u>
<u n="272" who="S0391">oh I told you it would drop off there</u>
<u n="273" who="S0393">no er I moved it</u>
<u n="274" who="S0391">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0393">that's really loud yeah er tenterhooks I'll just do something really simple if I can get it down then it'll be a nice touch just to hand it to them</u>
<u n="276" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah journey in wool well after that the stretching can you remember the ladies in the <anon type="place"/> museum?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0393">eh</u>
<u n="278" who="S0391">weaving <unclear>the yarn just</unclear></u>
<u n="279" who="S0393">weaving <pause dur="short"/> then wearing weaving then wearing weaving dreams</u>
<u n="280" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0393">in each in each garment</u>
<u n="282" who="S0391"><unclear>copy a bit of Yeats</unclear></u>
<u n="283" who="S0393">yeah that's the trouble isn't it?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> still it's good</u>
<u n="285" who="S0393"><unclear/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> eh</u>
<u n="287" who="S0393"><unclear/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0391">we're going all the way to the M62</u>
<u n="289" who="S0393">so <trunc>w</trunc> how how long is that?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0391">if you look at that it'll tell you</u>
<u n="291" who="S0393">what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are we following <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s briefing sheet?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0393">when are we gonna find out about Jeremy Corbyn?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0391">eleven o'clock</u>
<u n="295" who="S0393">oh god it's gonna be amazing isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> hello today's the wedding of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0393">and it's taking place <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> it's advised to go by the <anon type="place"/> and the A1 is that what we're on?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0391">we're on the A1 now</u>
<u n="299" who="S0393">right we should follow this one for two</u>
<u n="300" who="S0391" trans="overlap">for how long?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0393">thirty-four point two miles into the journey</u>
<u n="302" who="S0391">see if you were going to <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> you'd come off here</u>
<u n="303" who="S0393">that's the way <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have gone isn't it?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0391" trans="overlap">they're going that way but I think we'll carry on</u>
<u n="305" who="S0393">can't we get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to take us in the little horsebox?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0391">yeah that would be better <pause dur="short"/> we're going down to the M62</u>
<u n="307" who="S0393">right so</u>
<u n="308" who="S0391" trans="overlap">if you if you if I know the next step of each bit it helps</u>
<u n="309" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah okay we keep right to the fork onto the M1</u>
<u n="310" who="S0391">oh just go back a bit</u>
<u n="311" who="S0393" trans="overlap">following the sign</u>
<u n="312" who="S0391">just go back a bit just I'm on the A1 now</u>
<u n="313" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah you should follow the A1M</u>
<u n="314" who="S0391">to for how long?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0393">three thirty-four point two miles</u>
<u n="316" who="S0391">how long do you think I've been on it?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0393">oh not long not that long</u>
<u n="318" who="S0391">ten miles? twenty miles?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0393">twenty miles</u>
<u n="320" who="S0391">have I?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0393" trans="overlap">then then you follow the A1 then you keep right to the fork onto the M1 you follow the sign for M1 <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0391">right that'll do for now and then</u>
<u n="323" who="S0393" trans="overlap">there will have been similar ones before to get you ready</u>
<u n="324" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0393">do you remember? like there's two or three miles of them</u>
<u n="326" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0393">yeah is this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? or?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0391">that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0393">then we're on that for ten miles</u>
<u n="330" who="S0391"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> what does it say?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0393">then you come off at junction forty-two for <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0393">er can you believe <anon type="place"/>'s so near?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0391">yeah cos do you remember when we went to that Ikea? it was nearly in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0393">I didn't go</u>
<u n="336" who="S0391">you did just <unclear/> what? fifteen years ago</u>
<u n="337" who="S0393">so you could get to <anon type="place"/> in an hour and a half couldn't you? two hours</u>
<u n="338" who="S0391">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0393">but who would in their right mind go to <anon type="place"/>? <pause dur="long"/> it is a good er briefing sheet this one</u>
<u n="340" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0393" trans="overlap">I like the picture of <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0391">pictures pictures of the road signs</u>
<u n="343" who="S0393">the pictures</u>
<u n="344" who="S0391" trans="overlap">how's he got those? <pause dur="short"/> can you get those on a map? er a picture of the actual road sign? or has he has he gone onto Google Maps as well as?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0393">I don't know</u>
<u n="346" who="S0391">whatever that is RAC or AA</u>
<u n="347" who="S0393">I don't know how much to go on about you know we usually say these are the dances that people living round here would've had? you could spin a story about</u>
<u n="348" who="S0391">spin spinning's a good word spinning</u>
<u n="349" who="S0393">about how the people probably left places like er <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0393" trans="overlap">and with their dances and ended up in this mill like working with their children</u>
<u n="352" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh yes I'm sure they did I'm sure they had dances in the mill yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0393">I I just don't know what the politics of the mill <trunc>own</trunc> the current mill owners are though do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0391">what's that got to do with <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0393" trans="overlap">well if you're up if they're like rank Tories they don't wanna be reminded of er</u>
<u n="356" who="S0391">no er you're just reminding me of the Thomas Hardy <unclear>sort of way</unclear></u>
<u n="357" who="S0393" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="358" who="S0391">the people who would've loved you know to celebrate it</u>
<u n="359" who="S0393">you mean this was all that remained of the fresh air</u>
<u n="360" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0393">gusting through their hair <pause dur="short"/> this string of melodic notes</u>
<u n="362" who="S0391">to be honest I think they're just like er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> doing their own business online with</u>
<u n="363" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0391">crafts and yarns and stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0393">yeah I mean they must be quite entrepreneurial to make it work cos it sounds</u>
<u n="366" who="S0391" trans="overlap"><unclear>choosing</unclear> arts and crafts makes me think they're quite creative like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they buy stuff like that</u>
<u n="367" who="S0393">arts and crafts you know is a massive market isn't it?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0391">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is</u>
<u n="369" who="S0393">people like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do it</u>
<u n="370" who="S0391">does she?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0393">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well have you not seen all the egg cups in her house?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0391">that's not arts and crafts she just collects egg cups</u>
<u n="373" who="S0393">it's similar</u>
<u n="374" who="S0391">no it's not</u>
<u n="375" who="S0393">it's it's the same sort of like</u>
<u n="376" who="S0391">no</u>
<u n="377" who="S0393">department in the store</u>
<u n="378" who="S0391">no no no no not at all <pause dur="short"/> these are the raw materials to make things to <unclear/> to do it</u>
<u n="379" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah if you've got a bunny rabbit egg cup then you're playing on the same team as people who make like</u>
<u n="380" who="S0391" trans="overlap">no not at all</u>
<u n="381" who="S0393">cottages out of wool don't you think?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0391">no some are collectors and some create things from the raw materials <pause dur="short"/> it's totally different</u>
<u n="383" who="S0393">so remember we're looking for er</u>
<u n="384" who="S0391">M1</u>
<u n="385" who="S0393">the sign for M1 onto the M1 you follow the sign for M1 <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0391">glad it <unclear>fairs</unclear> up for the journey back <pause dur="short"/> oh is it getting lighter?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0393">it is a bit yeah are we still not out of <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0391"><anon type="place"/>? oh no that's <anon type="place"/> over there</u>
<u n="389" who="S0393">is it? that says <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0391"><unclear>I take</unclear> <unclear/> the left lane <unclear/> do you think I can <unclear/> then come back out? or do you think my right lane's coming up?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0393">I think you get loads of loads of reminders <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0391"><unclear>might as well cross then</unclear></u>
<u n="393" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0391"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> seems to know it I think he knows <anon type="place"/> quite well see if we got there early what would be er heaven would be we've got set up for tonight or we can all go to an Indian restaurant <unclear/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0393" trans="overlap">what? at four o'clock?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0391">really leisurely meal well anytime I would love to go to a <anon type="place"/> Indian wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0393">well they're supposed to be the best aren't they? obviously it's the capital</u>
<u n="398" who="S0391" trans="overlap">I remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he evidently makes them really well but he said <anon type="place"/>'s the only place you can go for one better <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he knows a couple of good ones</u>
<u n="399" who="S0393">talking about him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="place"/> have had a disaster</u>
<u n="400" who="S0391">have they?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0393">they're not even in the Super League</u>
<u n="402" who="S0391"><unclear>oh dear</unclear> oh look it's bright I can see now that's better <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0393">what do you think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are <trunc>tal</trunc> chatting about?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0391" trans="overlap">I would love <pause dur="short"/> I would love <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0391">to get set up <unclear/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0393" trans="overlap">twenty-four hour Greggs</u>
<u n="408" who="S0391">and just chill <unclear>with beer</unclear></u>
<u n="409" who="S0393">I think we can do that <pause dur="short"/> don't you think we get a bit quicker each time?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0391">well I've found some jobs that I can do and I think it's always good if you pack the cars the same way and do the same jobs <pause dur="short"/> for example I can I know how to put batteries in microphones and screw the tops on and I can do that in reverse at the end of the night and that's quite fiddly and time consuming</u>
<u n="411" who="S0393">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I could lift everything and er <pause dur="short"/> match <unclear/> match leads up with</u>
<u n="412" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0393">before you get into this business you have no idea how much of a pain it is</u>
<u n="414" who="S0391">well that's er</u>
<u n="415" who="S0393" trans="overlap">with the equipment</u>
<u n="416" who="S0391">yeah it's the roadie side isn't it?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0391">the the the problem is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> loves that that's his thing it's just</u>
<u n="419" who="S0393">he likes driving I don't know</u>
<u n="420" who="S0391" trans="overlap">no he likes being part of it</u>
<u n="421" who="S0393">well where is he today?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0391"><unclear>with his crew at home</unclear> they changed their fixtures thought he was free I think it was something to do with the England match or something <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure but <unclear>he may just be at home</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0393">yeah <pause dur="long"/> we've been on the road for like er twenty-eight minutes we're making good time</u>
<u n="424" who="S0391">oh so we might be near our thirty mile thing</u>
<u n="425" who="S0393">yeah I think so yeah not far off it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0391"><anon type="place"/> thirteen <pause dur="short"/> we're not far from <anon type="place"/> are we?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0393"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he's gonna send us a text when the Corbyn result comes in</u>
<u n="428" who="S0391">oh right are we switching the er thing off and putting the radio on at eleven or what?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0393">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you won't be able to hear the radio though will you? in the micro bus in the golf cart</u>
<u n="430" who="S0391"><unclear>I always listen to it</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> I must admit I liked it when I saw that erm it says finish around nine o'clock</u>
<u n="431" who="S0393">that would be that would be lovely wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0391">that would be fantastic that's why it'd be good to get half seven start is it half seven <unclear>to</unclear> quarter past eight?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0391">and then quarter past eight till nine o'clock <pause dur="short"/> where we might have a tiny break <trunc>quar</trunc> at quarter past nine</u>
<u n="435" who="S0393">yeah but</u>
<u n="436" who="S0391">so that's just the usual</u>
<u n="437" who="S0393" trans="overlap">they probably won't wanna stay up all night themselves</u>
<u n="438" who="S0391" trans="overlap">they'll be tired</u>
<u n="439" who="S0393">she said she's got some sort of basic system upstairs where they can put music through</u>
<u n="440" who="S0391">yes just normal microphones upstairs <pause dur="short"/> I hope that's after us and not in competition</u>
<u n="441" who="S0393" trans="overlap">you you got the first one yeah? A1 follow the A1</u>
<u n="442" who="S0391" trans="overlap"><unclear>can't be that this one it's this wide one</unclear></u>
<u n="443" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0393">follow the sign for M1 <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0391">yes I'm in the right lane aren't I?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0391">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saying you get <trunc>lo</trunc>loads of notice</u>
<u n="449" who="S0393">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0391">why is that sat nav not talking to me?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0393">I don't know</u>
<u n="452" who="S0391">you keep your eye on that bit of paper there</u>
<u n="453" who="S0393">she should be shouldn't she?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0393">did we switch her off when we put the volume up?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0391">no <pause dur="short"/> maybe cos I'm still going straight</u>
<u n="457" who="S0393">it might pipe up in a minute or so</u>
<u n="458" who="S0391">I thought she'd say continue on the blah blah blah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah you'd expect her to <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0391">I might need to get a little sat nav to put on my</u>
<u n="461" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah why don't you?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0391">cos you can see the map as well can't you? <pause dur="short"/> are they under fifty quid yet?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0393">no idea</u>
<u n="464" who="S0391">it's just er I always thought I'd wait till they were under fifty quid</u>
<u n="465" who="S0393">I think they are yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0391">I saw one for sixty-eight not paying that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0393">aye <pause dur="long"/> right</u>
<u n="468" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0393" trans="overlap">I'm gonna er</u>
<u n="470" who="S0391">I don't really want one for my birthday because I'd rather have clothes</u>
<u n="471" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0391">that I need for school</u>
<u n="473" who="S0393">well let's hope the Marks and Sparks scenario plays out</u>
<u n="474" who="S0391">that's what I was wondering if we knew that was definitely happening <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0393" trans="overlap">can't rely on it</u>
<u n="476" who="S0391">can't rely on it can you? <pause dur="short"/> oh that is so lovely isn't it?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0393">I think once we've started a precedent it'd be cruel</u>
<u n="478" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> oh but then when you weren't working for them how awful would that be? right am I in the wrong lane? or is this lane part of it?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0393">yeah er</u>
<u n="480" who="S0391">she's gone to sleep</u>
<u n="481" who="S0393">what should I do?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0391" trans="overlap">have er have a look <pause dur="short"/> unless she hasn't because we're still going straight that way</u>
<u n="483" who="S0393" trans="overlap">it says one point eight miles until you change</u>
<u n="484" who="S0391">oh right well just keep your eye on it <unclear>she's gone to sleep</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0393">don't know sat navs might be a bit of a mixed blessing <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> never uses one does he?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0391">well he's been on the UK roads for decades hasn't he? <pause dur="short"/> he knows the way he wants to go <pause dur="short"/> the thing I like them for is if they can tell you <unclear/> ahead</u>
<u n="487" who="S0393">this one's silent</u>
<u n="488" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this one's rubbish <pause dur="short"/> I probably <unclear>knocked her off</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0393" trans="overlap"><unclear/> six</u>
<u n="490" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0393">shall I try and get the volume back?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0391">yeah you might as well but don't get the picture off cos at least you can look at it <pause dur="short"/> is it near the bottom? <pause dur="short"/> is there a symbol along the bottom <unclear/>? <pause dur="short"/> down the bottom somewhere I <unclear/> erm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0393">no I don't know</u>
<u n="494" who="S0391">do we look as if we're still alright?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of sat nav"/>
<u n="496" who="S0391">oh</u>
<u n="497" who="S0393">keep right</u>
<u n="498" who="S0391">ah she just tells you literally just before</u>
<u n="499" who="S0393">in half a mile well that's plenty of time isn't it?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0391" trans="overlap">that's alright yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0393">couldn't you get like someone</u>
<u n="502" who="S0391" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0393">couldn't I was just thinking it'd be great to have <trunc>s</trunc> another voice doing</u>
<event desc="sound of sat nav"/>
<u n="504" who="S0391">what did she say?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0393">keep right</u>
<u n="506" who="S0391">oh well that that <unclear/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0393" trans="overlap">that's it <pause dur="short"/> oh it was wasn't it?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0393">right okay</u>
<u n="510" who="S0391">still <unclear/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0393" trans="overlap">nine minutes to junction forty-two that's the one we're coming off at</u>
<u n="514" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0393" trans="overlap">well it'll be signed <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0391">so I just follow <anon type="place"/> signs on the M62?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0393">you follow the M1 this one for ten minutes until at junction forty-two you exit onto the M62 following signs for <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0391">right</u>
<u n="519" who="S0393">then you're on that one for ten miles</u>
<u n="520" who="S0391">right <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0393">I think it's the one everyone gets off at</u>
<u n="522" who="S0391">yes I know but it's whether you go east or west I I go as you get to it it's which way do you go on it?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0393"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0391">what?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0393"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> can you get like different people doing the sat nav voice?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0393">who who is it?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0391" trans="overlap">when we got a taxi once he said who would you like? we got erm Basil Fawlty</u>
<u n="529" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0391">that was funny</u>
<u n="531" who="S0393">did you not get Elvis or anything like that?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0391">well he was dead he couldn't do them could he?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0393" trans="overlap">no but there's a bloke in Memphis who sounds exactly like him</u>
<u n="534" who="S0391">oh an impersonator?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0393">well not an impersonator just by some chance he's got the same vocal chords and everything</u>
<u n="536" who="S0391">oh well he should offer to do it put your pound in a jar</u>
<u n="537" who="S0393">I think I have haven't I? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0391">loads of people would buy that</u>
<u n="539" who="S0393">god you're right <pause dur="short"/> you're definitely right there</u>
<u n="540" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0393">cos it was an internet thing people saying have you heard this guy? <unclear/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0391">well if even if he can't sing you've got him a job <unclear/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0393" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0391">is that speaking? or singing? or what?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0393" trans="overlap">speaking <pause dur="short"/> except he's quite he had a stutter and was quite hesitant so might not be the best</u>
<u n="546" who="S0391">what number was it? forty-two?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0391">the junction?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0393">yeah junction number forty-two</u>
<u n="550" who="S0391">what number's this one?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0393">forty-six</u>
<u n="552" who="S0391">oh oh we'll take this <unclear/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0393"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> waste solutions</u>
<u n="554" who="S0391" trans="overlap">are we getting paid for petrol?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0391">are we?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0393">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's funny that waste solutions <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0391">is the cheque payable to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0393">cash I've asked for</u>
<u n="560" who="S0391">he can earn loads can't he?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0393">oh I've just heard it's been cancelled didn't happen <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0391">I bet the result comes on the radio soon</u>
<u n="563" who="S0393">shall I er?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0391">how much have we got to go?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0393">erm the <trunc>l</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s last birthday was er she was thirty-seven</u>
<u n="566" who="S0391">oh right</u>
<u n="567" who="S0393"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0391">do you know how old <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is next year?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0393">forty-five</u>
<u n="570" who="S0391">fifty</u>
<u n="571" who="S0393">is she?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0393">you would never of I would never of thought that</u>
<u n="574" who="S0391">no I didn't realise</u>
<u n="575" who="S0393">mind you poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> she's worn to the bone isn't she?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0391">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> she is</u>
<u n="577" who="S0393">she's just</u>
<u n="578" who="S0391">she's <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>her own worst enemy</unclear></u>
<u n="579" who="S0393" trans="overlap">worries about everything</u>
<u n="580" who="S0391">she does <pause dur="long"/> is this a new road?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0393">don't know</u>
<u n="582" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0393">yeah it's awful isn't it?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0391">horrible it's like <unclear/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0393">this is the <pause dur="short"/> they've resurfaced the motorway in <anon type="place"/> you know cos of the din</u>
<u n="586" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0393">you hear you can hear this four or five miles away</u>
<u n="588" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh you will</u>
<u n="589" who="S0393">on a quiet day</u>
<u n="590" who="S0391">here we are M62 <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0391"><unclear/> to <anon type="place"/> not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="593" who="S0393">you don't want <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but junction</u>
<u n="594" who="S0391" trans="overlap"><unclear/> east <unclear/> west</u>
<u n="595" who="S0393" trans="overlap">it's junction forty-two</u>
<u n="596" who="S0391">is that right?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0393">yeah <anon type="place"/> is very east</u>
<u n="598" who="S0391">right so which way's east and which way's west?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0393"><anon type="place"/> is west</u>
<u n="600" who="S0391" trans="overlap">west is over there so I'm gonna go <unclear>erm that way</unclear> is that right?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0393">I don't know</u>
<u n="602" who="S0391">no south west east <unclear/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0393" trans="overlap">well I don't know where the magnetic north is from here</u>
<u n="604" who="S0391" trans="overlap">well we're heading south aren't we?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0393">are we?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0391">yeah yeah <unclear/> we're heading south <pause dur="long"/> so it's gonna be over there isn't it? <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0393">right <pause dur="short"/> I bet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets there early</u>
<u n="608" who="S0391">oh he will <pause dur="long"/> am I okay in this lane do you think?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0391">oh yeah er it's a slip road off that's alright <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0393">you've still got three point nine miles three point eight miles</u>
<u n="612" who="S0391">that was number forty-five</u>
<u n="613" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0391">next junction <unclear/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0393">what? <pause dur="short"/> I thought <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was about forty</u>
<u n="616" who="S0391">oh right I seem to remember her having her fortieth <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise it was that er <unclear>just to</unclear> <anon type="place"/> <trunc>w</trunc>we wouldn't come to <anon type="place"/> this way</u>
<u n="617" who="S0393">no <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> only if you were a lunatic</u>
<u n="618" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you see even coming back tonight I might still prefer this road</u>
<u n="619" who="S0393">yeah?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0391">than can you remember when we came back from <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/>? <pause dur="short"/> it still seemed long didn't it?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0393">but this is beginning to seem long as well</u>
<u n="622" who="S0391">I remember that one seemed very long</u>
<u n="623" who="S0393">this one's quicker just in terms of</u>
<u n="624" who="S0391" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0393">speed and less stress is it?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0391">it's easier to see</u>
<u n="627" who="S0393">is it easier to drive it?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0391">I think it is <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> we'll see</u>
<u n="629" who="S0393" trans="overlap">I just could never drive you know thinking about it I just dunno how you do it</u>
<u n="630" who="S0391"><unclear>I'm glad you appreciate</unclear> me</u>
<u n="631" who="S0393">always</u>
<u n="632" who="S0391">good <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0393">I'd just been thinking <unclear>now with like</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> two seconds away from death all the time</u>
<u n="634" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but you could be <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0393">well yeah that's the trouble it would be stressful</u>
<u n="636" who="S0391">it is it is in bad weather I must admit <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of sat nav"/> oh thank you she's telling me a bit sooner now</u>
<u n="637" who="S0393">and there's the <anon type="place"/> headquarters you know <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0391">it's what?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0393"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> milk <anon type="place"/> you know they've got it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="640" who="S0391" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0393">well they've got stuff in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="642" who="S0391"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> is this it <unclear>then</unclear>?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0393">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> well done</u>
<u n="644" who="S0391"><unclear/> got to head for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="645" who="S0393">junction forty-two exit onto the M62 following signs for <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0391">at least I'm in the right lane anyway</u>
<u n="647" who="S0393">so when we come to that junction forty-two</u>
<u n="648" who="S0391">it'll be like loads of cars meeting at this point</u>
<u n="649" who="S0393">this is the one</u>
<u n="650" who="S0391">yeah this is it</u>
<u n="651" who="S0393">five hundred and fifty yards</u>
<u n="652" who="S0391">which way did I say was west? that way?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0393">I don't know</u>
<u n="654" who="S0391">north south no that way I'm trying to guess which direction <unclear>I'll</unclear> be</u>
<u n="655" who="S0393" trans="overlap">no you won't be able to</u>
<u n="656" who="S0391"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0393">we're joining another sewer outflow of traffic</u>
<u n="658" who="S0391">this <trunc>l</trunc> this is a massive one if I remember rightly</u>
<u n="659" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0391">coming from all over the place <unclear/> that's where north south meets</u>
<u n="661" who="S0393" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> you're in the right one that's it</u>
<u n="662" who="S0391">it's where north south meets west east isn't it?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0393"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> seven miles twelve minutes <pause dur="short"/> that's not now though</u>
<u n="664" who="S0391">that says roadworks</u>
<u n="665" who="S0393">it's not now</u>
<u n="666" who="S0391">that said roadworks</u>
<u n="667" who="S0393">yeah with a date</u>
<u n="668" who="S0391">just keep your eye on the signs <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> hooray <pause dur="short"/> I love it when I see a <anon type="place"/> sign</u>
<u n="669" who="S0393">oh god welcome to our work zone you don't want that sort of sign though do you?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0391">no <event desc="sound of sat nav"/> <pause dur="short"/> right at the fork that's what I said</u>
<u n="671" who="S0393">right at what?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0391">the fork she's she's very good telling me in advance <pause dur="short"/> I want to be up to the right <pause dur="short"/> thank you lady</u>
<u n="673" who="S0393">oh <event desc="sound of sat nav"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0391">see how she keeps telling me?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0393">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0391">I am right at the fork <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0393">that's it <trunc>ma</trunc> not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0391">that's it that's all I was worried about getting on the wrong one</u>
<event desc="sound of sat nav"/>
<u n="679" who="S0393">ten miles</u>
<u n="680" who="S0391">ten miles <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0393">it's eleven thirty the Corbyn thing though isn't it? not eleven</u>
<u n="682" who="S0391">I thought it was eleven</u>
<u n="683" who="S0393"><unclear/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0391">just try and let me concentrate <unclear>till</unclear> I get on the right road cos I'm not quite sure <unclear>I</unclear> get over here <pause dur="short"/> I just feel as if I'm going in the right direction now</u>
<u n="685" who="S0393" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0393">this reminds me of <anon type="place"/> you know erm when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> took us to the domes</u>
<u n="688" who="S0391">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0393">a huge tunnel yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was a lovely spot though wasn't it?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0393">absolutely beautiful</u>
<u n="692" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0393" trans="overlap">who would've thought it would place like that would exist</u>
<u n="694" who="S0391" trans="overlap"><unclear>this is</unclear> M62 let's concentrate</u>
<u n="695" who="S0393" trans="overlap">in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> right you're staying on this for ten miles</u>
<u n="696" who="S0391">that won't be long <pause dur="short"/> and then what?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0393">er then the signs you follow this time are for <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> junction twenty-six take the exit</u>
<u n="698" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0393">oh you should've</u>
<u n="700" who="S0391">talk about <unclear/> someone's way oh am I in the wrong lane? <vocal desc="gasp"/> gosh <unclear/> don't I? or do they let me further on? <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> here <pause dur="long"/> we'll be near erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="701" who="S0393">right</u>
<u n="702" who="S0391"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0393" trans="overlap">signs you follow this time <pause dur="short"/> at junction twenty-six take the exit for <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="704" who="S0391"><unclear>then</unclear> that'll be easier like <pause dur="long"/> twenty-six</u>
<u n="705" who="S0393">it's quite tricky</u>
<u n="706" who="S0391">she'll that's why I want the <unclear/> for that <unclear>point</unclear></u>
<u n="707" who="S0393">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0391"><unclear/> once you get near a place <pause dur="short"/> it's hard to find the exact location</u>
<u n="709" who="S0393">that's right <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="place"/> mill</u>
<u n="710" who="S0391">mm?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0393"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> golf <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>it's very</unclear> I might switch this off now and do it later</u>
<u n="712" who="S0391">oh put Corbyn on yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
