<text id="SWRQ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:24:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-11-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0320 S0443</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>0320's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Family life, Shopping, Discussing a wedding</topics>
		<activity>Mother and daughter talking about family life over a cup of tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0320">
				<exactage>34</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Torquay</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Totnes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>TEFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- advanced; French -- intermediate; German -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0443">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cardiff</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Great Britain (UK)</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Classic BBC English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Totnes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultancy and training (freelance)</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- A-level standard</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0320">okay hi</u>
<u n="2" who="S0443">hi how are you?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0320">I'm alright</u>
<u n="4" who="S0443">what have you been doing today then?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0320">I went to the park</u>
<u n="6" who="S0443">the park? what did you go to the park for?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0320">I took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to go and play in the park</u>
<u n="8" who="S0443">oh right is he going on the swings yet</u>
<u n="9" who="S0320">nope still doesn't like them</u>
<u n="10" who="S0443">ah perhaps they make him feel a bit like sick like a bit of vertigo</u>
<u n="11" who="S0320">I don't think so he doesn't generally like swinging he likes climbing</u>
<u n="12" who="S0443">oh right so what did he climb on?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0320">the slide the everything really</u>
<u n="14" who="S0443">have they got a climbing frame there?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0320">mm not really they've kind of got erm like no erm more climbing wall type thing so sort of rounded slopes with erm climbing wall holds bolted on to them</u>
<u n="16" who="S0443">that's a bit sophisticated down at erm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0320">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> it is</u>
<u n="18" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0320">it's not as sophisticated as I'm explaining it it's not as complicated as I'm making it sound</u>
<u n="20" who="S0443">have they got like a cargo rope that you climb up?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0320">er what like a spider web one?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0320">yes</u>
<u n="24" who="S0443">oh right</u>
<u n="25" who="S0320">but he's too little for that</u>
<u n="26" who="S0443" trans="overlap">that's quite yeah that is quite high down at erm <anon type="place"/> park they've got like a wooden framed one which is really solid it's goes very high so it's about</u>
<u n="27" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0443">twelve feet high</u>
<u n="29" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0443">or ten feet high</u>
<u n="31" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0443">but there's definitely a climbing frame</u>
<u n="33" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yeah by the swimming pool?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0443">yeah by the paddling the paddling pool</u>
<u n="35" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0443">I can't wait to take him bouldering</u>
<u n="37" who="S0320">mm you?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0443">yeah why not?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh don't I don't know I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will probably take him</u>
<u n="40" who="S0443">no you'll have to wait forever I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will probably take him</u>
<u n="41" who="S0320">I'm going to take him to the erm play group in the climbing wall when it's <trunc>da</trunc> when it's raining so probably next week</u>
<u n="42" who="S0443">which climbing wall?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0320" trans="overlap">maybe this week</u>
<u n="44" who="S0443">at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0320">no it's in erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0443">yeah that's the one I'm thinking of</u>
<u n="47" who="S0320">it's a bouldering wall</u>
<u n="48" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0320">yes</u>
<u n="50" who="S0443">that's the one I'm talking about</u>
<u n="51" who="S0320">yeah I think it's <trunc>Mon</trunc> I think it's Tuesday Wednesday Thursday I can't remember I have to check the days</u>
<u n="52" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0320">so I think I'm going to take him there</u>
<u n="54" who="S0443">oh right? you might have a go a climbing yourself</u>
<u n="55" who="S0320">it's bouldering so probably not it means you just have to get across and it's really hard rather than up</u>
<u n="56" who="S0443">what like for an eighteen-month-old can do it but you can't?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0320">they have soft play stuff for them and it doesn't necessarily mean they have to climb up the wall</u>
<u n="58" who="S0443"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it sounds like a good good chance for you to to have a go</u>
<u n="59" who="S0320">I probably won't</u>
<u n="60" who="S0443">oh</u>
<u n="61" who="S0320">I'll just take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0443">oh it's cold today there was nearly all frost this morning</u>
<u n="63" who="S0320" trans="overlap">I know I know</u>
<u n="64" who="S0443" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes round saying he's cold he's hold he's cold I'm going to <anon type="place"/> tomorrow so I can get some woolly socks</u>
<u n="65" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/> where are you going to get your woolly socks from?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0443">I don't know a woolly sock shop there are so many outdoor shops in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0443">but I won't be able to wear them with my <unclear>tigger</unclear> shoes</u>
<u n="69" who="S0320"><unclear>tigger</unclear>shoes what those?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0443">yeah my new Gore-Tex trainers</u>
<u n="71" who="S0320"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is erm or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <trunc>ru</trunc> one of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s rucksacks arrived in the post today</u>
<u n="72" who="S0443">one? how many has he got?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0320">erm oh yeah maybe it's only one <trunc>wh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s rucksack arrived in the post this morning</u>
<u n="74" who="S0443">oh right is it a full on outdoor one or just a little <unclear/> one?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it's it's quite small it's sort of in between they don't seem to like to carry much erm so it's bigger than a day pack but not a big backpack</u>
<u n="76" who="S0443">oh right</u>
<u n="77" who="S0320">for travelling</u>
<u n="78" who="S0443">so not like the marines</u>
<u n="79" who="S0320" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it's better than his well they're both really small</u>
<u n="80" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so they've both got fairly small and I don't think they carry much or take much</u>
<u n="82" who="S0443">oh okay just a lot of chocolate</u>
<u n="83" who="S0320">maybe I don't know I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has to take like hammers and stuff so he can hammer rocks</u>
<u n="84" who="S0443">I thought he was doing mechanical engineering?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0320">I think he's going something to do with geology actually</u>
<u n="86" who="S0443">that's a bit different</u>
<u n="87" who="S0320">it's to do it's also engineering as well it might be geological engineering <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0443">ah sounds a bit odd that's all computerised now cos your cousin <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does it and earns a fortune working in <anon type="place"/> with his master's in geology</u>
<u n="89" who="S0320" trans="overlap">maybe not maybe that's what he wants to do next I'm not sure I can't remember he did tell me but I can't remember</u>
<u n="90" who="S0443" trans="overlap">cos it it's mostly computer generated graphics to to interpret it to find out where the oil is</u>
<u n="91" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0443">nothing to do with bits and hammers</u>
<u n="93" who="S0320">well then maybe he's doing something different I don't know</u>
<u n="94" who="S0443">mm oh right what else are you getting for him?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0320">I dunno <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is doing it trousers boots all sorts mostly shoes I think for outdoor shoes for all of them</u>
<u n="96" who="S0443">that's really funny cos you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a new pair of shoes</u>
<u n="97" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0443">and it was only last minute he found out they was made from yak skin</u>
<u n="99" who="S0320">yes</u>
<u n="100" who="S0443">which is hilarious</u>
<u n="101" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0443">so they're obviously from actually they're probably from what is now China so it would have been Tibet Mongolia</u>
<u n="103" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0443">that kind of region you get the yaks</u>
<u n="105" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0443">but also we're having a lecture about the last in the shoe</u>
<u n="107" who="S0320">oh</u>
<u n="108" who="S0443">the last is the bit that gives the support to the archway way through</u>
<u n="109" who="S0320">oh okay</u>
<u n="110" who="S0443">and one of them had a last that was a triple last split in three and the other was a steel which was plastic and the other had a a single steel last that goes through the shoe</u>
<u n="111" who="S0320">in the shoe?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0443">yeah every shoe has a last</u>
<u n="113" who="S0320">made of steel?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0443">or is made of a last yeah they're very expensive</u>
<u n="115" who="S0320">I don't think every shoe has them the shoes I have got haven't got any of that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0443">well they're not shoes they're just slippers</u>
<u n="117" who="S0320">no yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0443">when I tried on my new shoes I wanted to throw my old shoes away cos there was just no support in them whatsoever</u>
<u n="119" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0443">but I didn't</u>
<u n="121" who="S0320">no I wear my walking boots quite a lot they're very good</u>
<u n="122" who="S0443">oh they'll be handy for when you go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding</u>
<u n="123" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0443">a nice dress and walking boots</u>
<u n="125" who="S0320">I must find some <trunc>we</trunc> no I was thinking wellies or flip-flops I must find some wellies not you can't have walking boots with a dress don't be silly</u>
<u n="126" who="S0443"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0320">I still need to find some wellies I tried some on in Mountain Warehouse and they're horrible</u>
<u n="128" who="S0443">yeah everything in Mountain Warehouse is horrible I don't know how they exist</u>
<u n="129" who="S0320">something's <unclear/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0443" trans="overlap">Go Outdoors in the place</u>
<u n="131" who="S0320"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got his waterproof suit from Mountain Warehouse which is nice</u>
<u n="132" who="S0443">oh yeah they're nice for kiddies but not for adults Go Outdoors is the place for wellies</u>
<u n="133" who="S0320">right</u>
<u n="134" who="S0443">they have Cath Kidston look-alikes I don't think they've got Hunter's they haven't got top of the range</u>
<u n="135" who="S0320">oh Hunter's don't fit me anyway</u>
<u n="136" who="S0443">Hunter's are just so faffy it's what every posh person wears to a festival</u>
<u n="137" who="S0320">yes they do and in cities</u>
<u n="138" who="S0443">well doesn't rain that much in cities</u>
<u n="139" who="S0320">no I suppose not</u>
<u n="140" who="S0443">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0320">is that the plan for the wedding then?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0443">yeah shall I tell you about it?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0443">what's happening there?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0443">as much as I can remember anyway so it's a nine acre site</u>
<u n="147" who="S0320">is it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0320">what's the equivalent to then?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0443" trans="overlap">in West Wales</u>
<u n="151" who="S0320">nine acres</u>
<u n="152" who="S0443">don't know</u>
<u n="153" who="S0320">how big is your field down there?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0443">er that's three acres I think</u>
<u n="155" who="S0320">oh okay</u>
<u n="156" who="S0443">erm I don't know how many tennis courts you can get in an acre</u>
<u n="157" who="S0320">how many what?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0443">tennis courts</u>
<u n="159" who="S0320">I can work with acre</u>
<u n="160" who="S0443" trans="overlap">or football</u>
<u n="161" who="S0320">I</u>
<u n="162" who="S0443">how many football pitches can you get in an acre?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0320" trans="overlap">I don't know no idea</u>
<u n="164" who="S0443">there's probably two football pitches to an acre so this is nine acres so it's pretty huge it's massive</u>
<u n="165" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0443">and it's in West Wales which is an interesting location cos you got the coast on one side and then there's this long flat plane and then you've got the <anon type="place"/> and the mountains in the distance which is going to <anon type="place"/> so it's a bit of a rain belt I think</u>
<u n="167" who="S0320">no really?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0443">mm cos when we got there it was absolutely pouring from rain and you could see the weather clearing from the mountain so it's in between the mountains and the coast</u>
<u n="169" who="S0320" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="170" who="S0443">yeah yeah so it's very wet</u>
<u n="171" who="S0320" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="172" who="S0443">and it has a lake going through the middle of it</u>
<u n="173" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0443">erm and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the chap that owns the land was telling me it's actually quite an ancient thing they use to use it as a waterway and then further up here</u>
<u n="175" who="S0320" trans="overlap">did they? before it was a lake then?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0443">before it was private land further up here they've got otters</u>
<u n="177" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="178" who="S0443">not not on their land but it's the same amount of water</u>
<u n="179" who="S0320">but it's a lake it's a lake not a river then?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0443" trans="overlap">I can't remember mm it's now a lake</u>
<u n="181" who="S0320" trans="overlap">so how did they use it as a waterway?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0443">yeah it used to be it used to go all the way down to the coast obviously from the mountains to the coast</u>
<u n="183" who="S0320" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="184" who="S0443">I think I can't remember a lot about about it but all I've got this aerial view you know a sort of Google birth map erm so the site's right next to the main road</u>
<u n="185" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0443">which has got a fifty mile an hour limit</u>
<u n="187" who="S0320">has it?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0320">oh dear</u>
<u n="190" who="S0443">and then there's just this really small turning in there erm and there's only parking for ten cars maximum</u>
<u n="191" who="S0320" trans="overlap">mm yeah okay</u>
<u n="192" who="S0443">so we're going to get everyone to park in <anon type="place"/> which is at the coast</u>
<u n="193" who="S0320" trans="overlap">mm oh okay</u>
<u n="194" who="S0443">and it's free parking</u>
<u n="195" who="S0320">is it?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0443">we don't have any free parking in <anon type="place"/> yeah so we did a recce of the car parks so we went and had a look at all the car parks around and it's right by the Co-op so I reckon people will buy beer</u>
<u n="197" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0443">at the Co-op</u>
<u n="199" who="S0320">yeah they might run out</u>
<u n="200" who="S0443">well I doubt it but erm so there isn't parking on site so that's a bit of a disadvantage so we might there'll be local taxi drivers or a shuttle bus possibly I don't know I think it'll be local taxi drivers doing it</u>
<u n="201" who="S0320">okay it's not a working farm then?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0443">it's not a farm at all</u>
<u n="203" who="S0320">not a farm at all looks a bit like a farm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0443" trans="overlap">no no no no animals</u>
<u n="205" who="S0320">mm mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0443">a couple of swans on the lake</u>
<u n="207" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0443">who are quite territorial if you go over their bridge they're not so keen on it all</u>
<u n="209" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0443">so it's sandwiched between the road and then you've got fields and then you've got the lake and then you've got the far side which won't be used</u>
<u n="211" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="212" who="S0443">so I think it's about that far side is about four and a half acres so this is about four and a half acres</u>
<u n="213" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0443">so there it is</u>
<u n="215" who="S0320">okay and where are they going to do the ceremony?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0443">erm here</u>
<u n="217" who="S0320">by the house?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0320">okay and so what's the blue field for?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0443">chill-out zone</u>
<u n="221" who="S0320">and the red field?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0443">er marquee</u>
<u n="223" who="S0320">okay why is it why why is the blue field a chill-out zone in between the ceremony and the marquee?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0443">why not?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0320">what's going to happen in there then?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0443">everyone's going to chill out</u>
<u n="227" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0320">we might not need to chill out</u>
<u n="229" who="S0443">it's a wedding of course you need to chill <trunc>ou</trunc> chill out yeah now see what the red field's for</u>
<u n="230" who="S0320">I did I said what are the red fields for?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0443">no this one</u>
<u n="232" who="S0320">there's two red fields</u>
<u n="233" who="S0443">yeah this one</u>
<u n="234" who="S0320">that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s field isn't it?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0443">no</u>
<u n="236" who="S0320">what's that for then?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0443">that's the camping field</u>
<u n="238" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0443">and then there's a secret location over here</u>
<u n="240" who="S0320">oh okay</u>
<u n="241" who="S0443">and then you go round on the other side of the lake which is where the generator will be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is actually doing a lot of erm wedding specing today actually</u>
<u n="242" who="S0320">how is the generator going to be all the way over there then?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0443">that's</u>
<u n="244" who="S0320">what's it gonna be powering?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0443">what do you think?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0320">the stuff in the marquee?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0443">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0320">have all the cables got to come over the bridge then?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0320">have they?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="253" who="S0443">the generator's pretty noisy</u>
<u n="254" who="S0320">mm it's a big site though</u>
<u n="255" who="S0443" trans="overlap">and it's probably safer</u>
<u n="256" who="S0320">oh okay what to have it over the water?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0443">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0320">oh okay</u>
<u n="259" who="S0443">and there might be some fireworks over there if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gets her own way</u>
<u n="260" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0443">which she usually does but I think fireworks you might as well just burn a twenty pound note burn two hundred quid</u>
<u n="262" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0443">I think fireworks is a bit of a waste of money maybe we could all have sparklers maybe you are chief bridesmaid</u>
<u n="264" who="S0320">I'm not chief bridesmaid</u>
<u n="265" who="S0443">as a bridesmaid can say why don't we just all have sparklers?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0320">no my involvement in the wedding tends to be yes that sounds great? would you like this bridesmaid's dress yeah why not? that's that's generally as far as it goes just going yeah alright then</u>
<u n="267" who="S0443">have you got one?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0320">no I haven't got any yet just lots of different ideas erm but no I'm just going yes okay lovely</u>
<u n="269" who="S0443">what would you like what would you like?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0320">I don't really mind as long as I can as long as it's got straps I don't want anything strapless</u>
<u n="271" who="S0443">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0320">I really don't mind long short whatever just <trunc>a</trunc> the only thing I want is that it's got straps I'm not bothered otherwise</u>
<u n="273" who="S0443">oh okay</u>
<u n="274" who="S0320">it's not I can't really it yeah no it's not <trunc>re</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got all of her friends and her cousin and her sister to tell her what they want I'll just go yeah okay yeah that's fine she doesn't need me going no I don't want that as well</u>
<u n="275" who="S0443">oh okay</u>
<u n="276" who="S0320">so I just keep saying yeah fine yeah lovely that looks nice why not? why don't you buy this? it's really cheap that's generally what I say look at this it's really cheap it's only twenty pounds why don't you buy these? you can buy seven on them and she'll go mm I don't want to</u>
<u n="277" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0320">and she very politely goes maybe and then ignores me</u>
<u n="279" who="S0443"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanted <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to have a role</u>
<u n="280" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did what did you say to that?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0443">I said oh he's a bit little yet</u>
<u n="282" who="S0320">I think my words would be he's a bit stubborn he probably won't do anything that anybody wants</u>
<u n="283" who="S0443">oh she just though he's so good-looking he'd look really sweet which is sweet</u>
<u n="284" who="S0320">mm but he'll probably just run off and be on his own all the time <trunc>he</trunc> he I don't I I don't</u>
<u n="285" who="S0443">well he can't well he's got nine acres</u>
<u n="286" who="S0320">exactly that's what I mean <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0443">he can't there's too much water</u>
<u n="288" who="S0320">not run off and be on his own but he'll just run away from the other people like he always does</u>
<u n="289" who="S0443">he might not</u>
<u n="290" who="S0320">mm maybe he'll probably quite like it there'll be lots of kids</u>
<u n="291" who="S0443">will there?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0320">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying there's about twenty-five kids so far</u>
<u n="293" who="S0443">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0320">I think they were going to do a tent for kids</u>
<u n="295" who="S0443">yeah it's in this field</u>
<u n="296" who="S0320">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0443">the kid zone</u>
<u n="298" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0443">it's here</u>
<u n="300" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0443">I think it should be in the chill-out zone</u>
<u n="302" who="S0320">er I don't because if it's if there's if the marquee is here and the kid zone is here that means that you've got to walk all the way across here to come back and find the kids no I think it I think they're right I think it should be nearer the marquee at least in the same field</u>
<u n="303" who="S0443">marquee is going here</u>
<u n="304" who="S0320">yeah I think it I don't yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0443">and there's a little bridge over here and then that's a muddy track over there</u>
<u n="306" who="S0320">there is a lot of water isn't there?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0443">it's huge it's like it's a nature conservation site really</u>
<u n="308" who="S0320">I hope the kids section is going to be enclosed</u>
<u n="309" who="S0443">course it's not</u>
<u n="310" who="S0320">oh god</u>
<u n="311" who="S0443">why would it be enclosed?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0320">I don't know it might be like <trunc>in</trunc>inside a marquee and all closed up</u>
<u n="313" who="S0443">no</u>
<u n="314" who="S0320">there's this amazing slide that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s made</u>
<u n="315" who="S0443">oh yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0320">it looks very nineteen fifties it probably wouldn't be in a modern park it's very tall</u>
<u n="317" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0443">it's like fifteen feet tall made of stainless steel and quite steep and that will be in the kid's zone</u>
<u n="319" who="S0320" trans="overlap">mm that sounds good</u>
<u n="320" who="S0443">yeah so yeah it's a really lovely site actually it's just it's just a festival really is the thing</u>
<u n="321" who="S0320">yeah that's fair enough</u>
<u n="322" who="S0443">so this is where the ceremony is going to be cos there's trees here and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanted it there and I had to negotiate with them all because they said look if you stand there and look through the trees to the <trunc>bl</trunc> the <anon type="place"/> mountains over there</u>
<u n="323" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0443">erm it'll work and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said okay only if we can have hay bales</u>
<u n="325" who="S0320">oh okay</u>
<u n="326" who="S0443">so there's going to be hay bales for a hundred people there</u>
<u n="327" who="S0320">really?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0320">gosh that's a lot</u>
<u n="330" who="S0443">what of people or hay bales?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0320">both <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0443">I've got quite a few erm I've bought another couple of sheets to go on the hay bales cos they're going to be quite prickly</u>
<u n="333" who="S0320" trans="overlap"><unclear/> to do yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0443">erm the other day so I got quite a few of those <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> of course wants to just go and buy a a bolt of calico</u>
<u n="335" who="S0320">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really liked the ones that you bought</u>
<u n="336" who="S0443">I said oh it depends what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes I can see what he means it'll all but look very weddingy but calico is beige</u>
<u n="337" who="S0320" trans="overlap">she doesn't want really want it to look weddingy does she?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0443">calico is beige</u>
<u n="339" who="S0320">I don't really know what calico is</u>
<u n="340" who="S0443">er it's just <trunc>be</trunc> you know the covering on the heater for the clothes?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0443">that</u>
<u n="343" who="S0320">oh well that's alright</u>
<u n="344" who="S0443">that kind of thing</u>
<u n="345" who="S0320">it's very thick</u>
<u n="346" who="S0443">yeah it is quite thick and it's that colour</u>
<u n="347" who="S0320" trans="overlap">you wouldn't get you wouldn't <trunc>e</trunc> you wouldn't get prickled from the hay bales</u>
<u n="348" who="S0443">but then what's the point of having hay bales?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0443">straw bales cos apparently straw bales are cheaper</u>
<u n="351" who="S0320" trans="overlap">straw yeah I was going to say straw bales are better</u>
<u n="352" who="S0443">if you can't see the straw</u>
<u n="353" who="S0320">I don't know</u>
<u n="354" who="S0443">so that's going to start there</u>
<u n="355" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0443">and then you've got to process into the chill-out zone</u>
<u n="357" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="358" who="S0443">and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm who is an expert welder is making a birdcage he calls it</u>
<u n="359" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="360" who="S0443">it's like a pavilion that you get a bandstand</u>
<u n="361" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="362" who="S0443">and there's going to be a fire pit in it apparently</u>
<u n="363" who="S0320">oh cool</u>
<u n="364" who="S0443">and lots of cushions and lots of cushions round here and then a marquee there with serving Pimms erm and a drink and some you know aperitifs and stuff there</u>
<u n="365" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0443">and then acoustic music here</u>
<u n="367" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="368" who="S0443">and I don't think there's that's why I wanted the kids in there I don't think there's enough in the chill-out zone</u>
<u n="369" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="370" who="S0443">but you have that so it was ceremony at two o'clock and then nibbles and drinks there</u>
<u n="371" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0443">and then you can either go across the rickety bridge which is just like the one in the Three Billy Goats Gruff</u>
<u n="373" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0443">or you can go across here and</u>
<u n="375" who="S0320">oh okay</u>
<u n="376" who="S0443">and again I argued for that cos of the kids but that is the way the tractor will be going</u>
<u n="377" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0443">cos this is not a stable bridge</u>
<u n="379" who="S0320">no</u>
<u n="380" who="S0443">it's a beautiful but it's not very stable</u>
<u n="381" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0443">and it's not very safe and then the main marquee is going to be here</u>
<u n="383" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0443">so the food is going to be tapas in the main marquee at about half past three</u>
<u n="385" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="386" who="S0443">so the main marquee is there loos are going to be over here kid's zone is going to be here</u>
<u n="387" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0443">erm hog roast is going to be about here this is huge this field</u>
<u n="389" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0443">it must be at least three acres but it's flat unlike the orchard</u>
<u n="391" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="392" who="S0443">and then they're going to run erm erm a tap down here and this is going to be the camping area</u>
<u n="393" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0443">not quite sure how it's going to work out with the cars et cetera but then if you go to a festival you don't take your car do you? you just trudge trudge across a muddy field</u>
<u n="395" who="S0320">I think people do take their cars</u>
<u n="396" who="S0443">yeah but they <trunc>u</trunc> if you think of Glastonbury</u>
<u n="397" who="S0320">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="398" who="S0443">if you take your car you've still got to walk three miles to the site</u>
<u n="399" who="S0320">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0443">with and carry all your stuff</u>
<u n="401" who="S0320">but then equally you get you can have a shower in Glastonbury</u>
<u n="402" who="S0443">yeah I think the loos will have showers</u>
<u n="403" who="S0320" trans="overlap">if you turn up well that's good cos if you turn up and lug carry all your stuff and put all your tent up and then want to go to the wedding</u>
<u n="404" who="S0443">no they'd come Friday unless they were coming only for the evening thing I don't think they'd be doing that</u>
<u n="405" who="S0320">oh okay</u>
<u n="406" who="S0443">so yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0320">you're not camping then?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0443">no we're too grown up to camp</u>
<u n="409" who="S0320">where are you staying?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0443" trans="overlap">are you camping?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0320">I really don't know <pause dur="short"/> ideally I'd like <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to go here you are we've found somebody to babysit for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> while you can go and have a have a nice time in the evening and work it out that way but I don't know if that's going to happen or not</u>
<u n="412" who="S0443">which evening?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0320">well the evening of the wedding</u>
<u n="414" who="S0443">well there'll be no one for him to</u>
<u n="415" who="S0320" trans="overlap">they can have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for</u>
<u n="416" who="S0443">babysit no that's not gonna happen</u>
<u n="417" who="S0320">no I know it's not going to happen that's what I'd like to happen someone to go yeah of course</u>
<u n="418" who="S0443" trans="overlap">cos all the <unclear/> are the guests oh right</u>
<u n="419" who="S0320">no not for the whole evening just anyway I don't know erm I don't know if we'll camp or not maybe probably</u>
<u n="420" who="S0443">I think you'll like</u>
<u n="421" who="S0320">it's cheaper <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0443">the <anon type="place"/> country park</u>
<u n="423" who="S0320" trans="overlap">oh yeah that's is that across the road?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0443">it's down down the road and off to the right it's very flat and by the beach</u>
<u n="425" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it also depends how long we</u>
<u n="426" who="S0443">and it's got lots of little play parks for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to climb on</u>
<u n="427" who="S0320" trans="overlap">oh that sounds better</u>
<u n="428" who="S0443">mm and it's got much more facilities</u>
<u n="429" who="S0320">and then I suppose if we'd have to take a taxi back</u>
<u n="430" who="S0443">yeah everyone's going to be getting taxi's yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0320" trans="overlap">from there to the apart from the people who are camping who are going to be staying the whole time</u>
<u n="432" who="S0443" trans="overlap">cos the house itself is out of bounds it's actually quite a small house it's just a bungalow with a bit added on</u>
<u n="433" who="S0320" trans="overlap">oh is it? yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0443">so the house itself is out of bounds</u>
<u n="435" who="S0320">yeah then maybe we'll do that</u>
<u n="436" who="S0443">yeah I think you'll like country park I think it'd be better if you had a the ideal would be if you're able to hire and camper van in country park</u>
<u n="437" who="S0320">yes that would be nice actually</u>
<u n="438" who="S0443">but erm I don't know</u>
<u n="439" who="S0320" trans="overlap">that would make life a lot easier</u>
<u n="440" who="S0443" trans="overlap">we found this yeah we found this big house <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> found the big house that's set about eight or ten people and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> shall we book it? for you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and the girls and you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but erm cos it's August she has to wait for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to tell her what she can do so the last thing was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was thinking of booking it for his merry men for the night before</u>
<u n="441" who="S0320">yeah? it sounds like <unclear>someone</unclear></u>
<u n="442" who="S0443" trans="overlap">which might be a great idea</u>
<u n="443" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0443">cos it's not very far away it's in <anon type="place"/> and it sleeps loads of people it's a really really big house</u>
<u n="445" who="S0320">well that sounds like a good idea</u>
<u n="446" who="S0443">yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says there's little cottages just down the road and</u>
<u n="447" who="S0320">oh really?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0443">and places you can rent but yeah cos it's the holidays so</u>
<u n="449" who="S0320">oh it's August</u>
<u n="450" who="S0443" trans="overlap">I think we'll be going for a week we'll go for a week</u>
<u n="451" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yeah I don't think we'll be able to cos I'll be right in the middle of summer school</u>
<u n="452" who="S0443">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0320">and they'll they yeah I'll be in the middle of summer school and it finishes starts July oh it'll be coming towards the end actually they start the end of June and go for six weeks so they'll be finishing they must be finishing around the fifteenth of August</u>
<u n="454" who="S0443">oh right well that's not so bad then</u>
<u n="455" who="S0320" trans="overlap">so I'll be coming towards the end I won't be in the middle of them</u>
<u n="456" who="S0443">and you won't be at the very end oh that sounds alright then</u>
<u n="457" who="S0320">yeah it'll be towards the end it'll be the last couple of weeks I think but it should be fine I'm I'm sure I can work around taking a few days off</u>
<u n="458" who="S0443" trans="overlap">right oh right</u>
<u n="459" who="S0320">especially if I'm only working part time it won't really matter</u>
<u n="460" who="S0443">yeah if you've built up your hours</u>
<u n="461" who="S0320">well it's not</u>
<u n="462" who="S0443" trans="overlap">although you're working right through aren't you?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0320">yeah no it should be fine cos I think I don't know what'll happen but we'll probably have alternate weeks to go and visit the school so it should be fine I just work around it it won't be a problem</u>
<u n="464" who="S0443">oh okay</u>
<u n="465" who="S0320">so I can go go out for a few days</u>
<u n="466" who="S0443">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0320">yeah a camper van in the country park sounds good</u>
<u n="468" who="S0443">it does I don't know if you can hire a camper van <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s sister is staying in her camper van</u>
<u n="469" who="S0320">you can hire camper van's they're fairly expensive</u>
<u n="470" who="S0443">no I meant on the park</u>
<u n="471" who="S0320">oh just what like a <trunc>car</trunc></u>
<u n="472" who="S0443" trans="overlap">what would be handy yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0320">do they have caravans then?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0443">I don't know I think everyone's takes their own it's a massive site</u>
<u n="475" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0443">and it's got beautiful bit by the erm beach</u>
<u n="477" who="S0320">mm sounds great</u>
<u n="478" who="S0443">and it's quite flat and yeah it's massive but I don't know it's not kind of mega trendy</u>
<u n="479" who="S0320">no sounds good though nice from the picture's I saw</u>
<u n="480" who="S0443" trans="overlap">yeah I think that would suit you a lot</u>
<u n="481" who="S0320">yeah lovely</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
