<text id="SWZA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:23:59</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0687 S0688 S0689 S0690</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Car, Istria, Croatia</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Art, Plants, Sons of Anarchy-TV series, Driving, Music festivals, Cars, Drinks, Markets, Istria and, Croatia, Restaurants, Where to visit, Olive oil, Wine, Caravans, Camping, Center parks</topics>
		<activity>A family conversation during a car journey</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0687">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bolton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- A-level</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0688">
				<exactage>53</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bolton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>53 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Midwife</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0689">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bolton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>16 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0690">
				<exactage>53</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>mixed southern English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bolton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Management Consultant</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0688">I think you could have it on in the background</u>
<u n="2" who="S0689">no I on on some of the last recordings it's like it's quite loud so</u>
<u n="3" who="S0690">Buje there was er there was a market there but not this not today I don't think</u>
<u n="4" who="S0687">you wanting to go to that <trunc>Grozn</trunc>Groznjan as well</u>
<u n="5" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah is that up there?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0687">yeah that's that way</u>
<u n="7" who="S0690">you <trunc>di</trunc> you didn't wanna go there now did you?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0688">I don't know where now or whatever <pause dur="short"/> I wonder what that one is up on the hill there</u>
<u n="9" who="S0687">yeah <vocal desc="yawn"/> <unclear>it looks small</unclear></u>
<u n="10" who="S0688">maybe that's it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0687">I think it's a little way up there</u>
<u n="12" who="S0688">what Rovinj?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0687">Rovinj yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0690">well what's there? is that another hotel is it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0688">yeah I think so isn't that where <unclear/> is? no?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0690">no</u>
<u n="17" who="S0687"><unclear/> past Buzet</u>
<u n="18" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0689">so if like if pieces of art are worth like like from people we haven't heard of are worth like four grand now it's well er it's a bit of a silly question I was gonna say how much are like the Mona Lisa and The Scream and all the famous art?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0689">I mean really <pause dur="long"/> see how do you how do you like you know why are they worth millions? that's a very very nice car erm why they're worth millions but you know it's all that?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I suppose the more famous the artist is the bigger the figure for his work but I don't know how I mean Banksy's work how do you is it not just the how he operates that that increases the value of his work?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0689">probably</u>
<u n="24" who="S0688">you know the fact that no one knows who he is and</u>
<u n="25" who="S0689">I can't believe <trunc>nob</trunc> but like nobody's ever</u>
<u n="26" who="S0687">he has an agent <pause dur="short"/> who he works through</u>
<u n="27" who="S0688">how did he first come to sort of say I'm Banksy but I'm staying anonymous?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0687">don't know</u>
<u n="29" who="S0689">so I'm sure his agent must know who he is</u>
<u n="30" who="S0688">must do</u>
<u n="31" who="S0689">let's hope they never fall out cos that's a</u>
<u n="32" who="S0688">yeah I'm sure he's got clauses written into er <pause dur="short"/> his contract</u>
<u n="33" who="S0687"><unclear/> you should overtake <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0689">see all those like little watchtowers?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0688">what's that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0689">there's a little wooden thing there</u>
<u n="37" who="S0688">by the side of the road?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0690" trans="overlap">yeah I've seen a few of those</u>
<u n="39" who="S0687">in the fields yeah it's we er it look it look like the ones you know that are like when you see in films around concentration camps?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0688">did you see those that's what I was the word I was thinking of those little <unclear>store</unclear> pots do they call them <unclear>cops</unclear>?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0687">no idea what store pots?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0688">that we saw in the fields <unclear/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0687" trans="overlap">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0688">where d'you get that from?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0690">I think they're shepherds' huts aren't they some of them?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0687">that's what I thought they would be <pause dur="short"/> hey I'm really tired now</u>
<u n="48" who="S0688">close your eyes love <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0689">what does that sign mean with the little <pause dur="short"/> arrow?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0690" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0689">was it across?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0690" trans="overlap">the road left and right there <unclear/> road</u>
<u n="53" who="S0689">oh <pause dur="short"/> suppose you never really see that in the UK do you? you can never be well I suppose <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0688">there's a river just up there to the left</u>
<u n="55" who="S0690">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0688">what's that? there's a cycle path there <pause dur="long"/> they have made hay er haven't they?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0689">why when do they usually do it in the UK?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0688">it's usually a lot later on in the summer whoops</u>
<u n="59" who="S0689">like when?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0688">like August</u>
<u n="61" who="S0689">August?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0689">like I said though it's probably <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was gonna say all the you know even when you were talking about that plant earlier it's probably genetically different to the plants we have</u>
<u n="64" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0689">you know it's still a lavender plant but it's genetically different</u>
<u n="66" who="S0688">but mine don't survive</u>
<u n="67" who="S0689">yeah cos I mean it makes sense that erm a lavender plant that er that's a pretty cool</u>
<u n="68" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0689">erm that a lavender that is grown in Croatia has to survive hotter summers than it does in the UK which makes it harder wearing and then gradually over time and like natural selection the lavender plants just you know</u>
<u n="70" who="S0688">evolves</u>
<u n="71" who="S0689">yeah almost I mean if you think about it if you if you think about how natural selection works the strongest survive while the rest die and then the strong pass on their genes to the next thing so you know say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got the gene that allows him to survive an extra day without water and I've not got that gene and I'm gonna die first meaning <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then can <trunc>s</trunc> do you know the little pollinating thing? you know that you know what plants do don't you?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0689">and then the you're everybody else has got that gene and it takes thousands and thousands of years but</u>
<u n="74" who="S0688">they look exactly the same don't they?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0689">I know but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know that's the only that was the only explanation I can think of <pause dur="long"/> wanna watch Sons of Anarchy as well when I get home that was a good series enjoyed that</u>
<u n="76" who="S0688">I can't think what that's about</u>
<u n="77" who="S0689">biker gang in California</u>
<u n="78" who="S0688">have you watched the whole thing?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0689">I watched the first like <trunc>s</trunc> two seasons I think <pause dur="short"/> it was really really good <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0688"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh that is a straight road</u>
<u n="81" who="S0689">yeah <pause dur="long"/> bit like America that isn't it? they have really straight roads</u>
<u n="82" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah but do you know I was thinking that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? Route 66</u>
<u n="83" who="S0689">it said it in that book and I remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> telling me you know in like the southern states? erm so like school stops like a month early to just for the harvest basically cos children have to work on the ranches and you know the farms?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0688">oh</u>
<u n="85" who="S0689">and erm er you can get a driving licence as young as like I think it was fifteen? or maybe fourteen I can't remember it might have been fourteen erm <trunc>be</trunc> and it's called like an early licence or something and basically it means if you have if you are driving and you have farm related material in the back of your trunk you're allowed to drive on your own so if you have a lamb in your back or some feed you're allowed to drive anywhere so basically so long as you have something farm related in your trunk then you're absolutely fine which means you can legally drive by the age of fourteen or fifteen I can't remember which one it is</u>
<u n="86" who="S0688">wow</u>
<u n="87" who="S0689">which is <trunc>pr</trunc> like pretty pretty crazy when you think about it isn't it? well <trunc>s</trunc> it</u>
<u n="88" who="S0688" trans="overlap">it is really</u>
<u n="89" who="S0689">it is especially crazy seeing as what? you can't drink until you're twenty-one but you can drive a car when you're fourteen fifteen</u>
<u n="90" who="S0688">and how old do you have to be to have <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0689">er <pause dur="short"/> again I <trunc>b</trunc> I bet it varies by state by state but I don't I don't know about that one I'd guess eighteen but <pause dur="short"/> you know if you're doing farm work then <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0688"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s asleep</u>
<u n="93" who="S0689">is she? there's another <unclear>winery</unclear> there <foreign lang="hrv">kolo</foreign> was it?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0688">no I dunno but it said <unclear>camping</unclear></u>
<u n="95" who="S0689">no it said <foreign lang="hrv">kolo</foreign></u>
<u n="96" who="S0688">okay</u>
<u n="97" who="S0689">K O L O <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0688">I think I'm sure that worked then this is where we're going to is that <trunc>str</trunc>? <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0689">do quite like the Audi SUVs</u>
<u n="100" who="S0688">HGVs?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0689">Audi SUVs</u>
<u n="102" who="S0688">oh okay <pause dur="long"/> so it doesn't look like they need to wait a long time all them trees before you get the crop on it</u>
<u n="103" who="S0690">no well I thought they had to mature <pause dur="long"/> but I couldn't see any growing on those trees opposite us</u>
<u n="104" who="S0688" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> maybe <unclear/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0690">and that I dunno what sort of crop you get off every tree like I suppose it depends how old it is how big it is but <pause dur="short"/> well it must be enough to make it worth his while <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0689">you're a very noisy breather <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="long"/> sorry?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0688">it's got <unclear>pizza</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0689">sorry what was that?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0688">someone had pizza <unclear/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0689">that's pretty cool <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> there's a house for sale well an apartment for sale there</u>
<u n="111" who="S0688">I wonder where the guys live</u>
<u n="112" who="S0689">god knows <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0688">I've got heat rash</u>
<u n="114" who="S0689">I would quite like you know like one of those like choppers like do you not remember <trunc>th</trunc>there used to be a TV programme about you know the like chopper motorbikes where it's like really high handlebars and you're like low to the ground?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0690">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0689">I quite like the look of them <pause dur="short"/> I'd <trunc>ne</trunc> I'd never be able to like <pause dur="short"/> get myself to ride a motorbike but I'd love to have one</u>
<u n="117" who="S0690">it's come from Italy this one then is that a Harley is it? sounded it didn't it? <pause dur="short"/> so I think it should be</u>
<u n="118" who="S0688" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="119" who="S0690">this way <pause dur="short"/> I think <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0689">no</u>
<u n="121" who="S0690" trans="overlap">no cos we have to go over this erm <pause dur="short"/> looks like a pontoon or whatever don't it? a causeway <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0689">Harley-Davidsons are really expensive aren't they?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0688">I think they are I think it's their reputation really I don't <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="124" who="S0689">no that's the only like motorbike company I know of though innit? like <pause dur="short"/> I suppose like Kawasaki <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> oh excuse me park fest music festival in no maybe that's that <trunc>mus</trunc> fest I don't even know what it is Glastonbury's kicked off tomorrow? today? I don't even know</u>
<u n="125" who="S0688">probably yesterday er was it? I thought it usually went on over like a bank holiday weekend</u>
<u n="126" who="S0689"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0690">er I er well I this weekend for sure I dunno really <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0689">I well I saw people like piling in a couple of days ago like even before the music had started and it looked like absolute chaos</u>
<u n="129" who="S0690">it was all very wet and muddy weren't it?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0688">which day was that?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0689">I can't remember I remember seeing like videos on Facebook of people like <pause dur="short"/> pushing like suitcases it looked like really just like in the mud <pause dur="long"/> yeah it didn't look very pleasant <pause dur="short"/> plus I told you some bloke died before it even opened didn't I? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0690">I would like to go as long as it didn't rain</u>
<u n="133" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0690">would you not come with me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0689">no <pause dur="short"/> if I got a waterproof tent I would but <pause dur="short"/> I just couldn't imagine anything worse than being cold at like</u>
<u n="136" who="S0690" trans="overlap">oh this looks like a causeway anyway we've got this bit right for this <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0688">I think we didn't come this way before</u>
<u n="138" who="S0690">don't think so <pause dur="short"/> I dunno how we got past this cos I thought we went down the coast from Novigrad but anyway <pause dur="short"/> we certainly didn't come across here</u>
<u n="139" who="S0689">water looks very greeny can you see?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0690" trans="overlap">oh there's a big road bridge up there perhaps we went across that one <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0689">see like how could oh I suppose they're just going down to the seabed aren't they? I was gonna say how would you like structure this so it's not just you know?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0690">just really built it up on rocks and stuff haven't they? just a causeway <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0689"><vocal desc="yawn"/> excuse me</u>
<u n="144" who="S0690">was that you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0688">what do you mean was it me?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0690">I was wondering if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s awake</u>
<u n="147" who="S0688"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s asleep <pause dur="short"/> that looks like the holiday place up there doesn't it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0689">yeah looks like a bit like a campsite</u>
<u n="149" who="S0688">is that the really long road bridge then there?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0690">no</u>
<u n="151" who="S0689">I'd say er</u>
<u n="152" who="S0690">no I think it was about half a mile up here and then a road off to the left I think <pause dur="short"/> it's this cheese and winery place or something is it?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0688">this is er it says this is the way to Rovinj I'm not sure why</u>
<u n="154" who="S0690" trans="overlap">it is yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0688">I suppose there's more than one way isn't there?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0690">well you just follow the coast round don't you? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0689">is it this <unclear/> that we're going to? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0690">erm <pause dur="long"/> blooming hell now this car's got two roof boxes <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear>mean bus</unclear></u>
<u n="159" who="S0689"><unclear>only</unclear> two</u>
<u n="160" who="S0690">dunno all his stuff in there I suppose</u>
<u n="161" who="S0689">I would have thought he'd just get one big one but</u>
<u n="162" who="S0690">oh hang on</u>
<u n="163" who="S0689">what's it called? a roof</u>
<u n="164" who="S0690" trans="overlap">roof box</u>
<u n="165" who="S0689" trans="overlap">roof box</u>
<u n="166" who="S0690">we used to have one didn't we?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0689">can't remember</u>
<u n="169" who="S0688" trans="overlap">we still have oh no you sold it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0690" trans="overlap">no we sold it when we sold it to make some space I think <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0689">I don't like those windows when they only like open a little bit cos you don't get any air you're just like <pause dur="short"/> sweltering</u>
<u n="172" who="S0688">I think there's a key for there's like er at the top of the window that you only open it like a centimetre er you can turn the handle then and it stays <trunc>clo</trunc> you can't just <unclear>open</unclear> the window and just close it</u>
<u n="173" who="S0689">sorry I'm confused what you mean</u>
<u n="174" who="S0688">I thought you said you've just seen a window but you didn't like it cos it didn't open</u>
<u n="175" who="S0689">mum my ears are going funny I <trunc>c</trunc> I really can't hear what you're saying</u>
<u n="176" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I think it that er</u>
<u n="177" who="S0690" trans="overlap">is that it?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0690"><unclear/> is that it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0688">I think so</u>
<u n="181" who="S0690">yeah okay</u>
<u n="182" who="S0688">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0690"><unclear/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0688" trans="overlap"><unclear/> had an alternate that's where she said</u>
<u n="185" who="S0689"><trunc>mu</trunc> er my ears are <trunc>rea</trunc> I <trunc>c</trunc> I can't hear what you're saying</u>
<u n="186" who="S0688">oh I was talking to dad then</u>
<u n="187" who="S0689" trans="overlap">oh right sorry <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0688">weird how stop's in English isn't it? what's that up there to the right?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0690">this <unclear/> village or something <pause dur="short"/> dunno</u>
<u n="190" who="S0689">can I turn the air con down a little bit how are you in the back?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0688">little bit not a huge amount</u>
<u n="192" who="S0689">I only turned it down two notches</u>
<u n="193" who="S0690">it's off now I think</u>
<u n="194" who="S0689">it's not it's still</u>
<u n="195" who="S0690">oh</u>
<u n="196" who="S0689">blowing through</u>
<u n="197" who="S0688">you're having trouble with this clutch aren't you?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0690" trans="overlap">I don't like no it's the handbrake I don't like said automatic handbrakes on the manual</u>
<u n="199" who="S0689">isn't it the auto hold?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0690">yeah but dunno can't <unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0689" trans="overlap">what even what even is an auto hold?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0690">to stop you rolling back I think don't er don't go forward <pause dur="short"/> felt like a bigger road than this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but anyway we'll give it a try</u>
<u n="203" who="S0687">said it was a dirt road</u>
<u n="204" who="S0690">oh do they? oh we can have a try then <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0689">sorry what is this?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0688">she said it's a road like er our road</u>
<u n="207" who="S0687"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's too hot here gonna have to</u>
<u n="208" who="S0689" trans="overlap">it's not off but okay</u>
<u n="209" who="S0687">why don't you turn your fans down?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0689">well it's fine <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0687">went really sleepy then <pause dur="short"/> my leg's hurting me</u>
<u n="212" who="S0688">I thought these headrests were quite well that one's comfy <unclear/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0687">still not comfy for sleeping <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="214" who="S0689">why did you stop?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0687">what was that? was there an animal?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0688">bump in the road I think</u>
<u n="217" who="S0689">bit of a dodge road isn't it?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0687" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0689">there's a lot of abandoned homes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0688">there are aren't there? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0687"><vocal desc="yawn"/> oh deary lord</u>
<u n="222" who="S0688">they know this place like the back of their hand don't they?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0687">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0689">it's the middle of nowhere <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="225" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah I don't know how anyone would find it that live lives here</u>
<u n="226" who="S0688">look at these pinky flowers haven't seen those <pause dur="short"/> people do</u>
<u n="227" who="S0689">people obviously do</u>
<u n="228" who="S0688" trans="overlap">maybe it's listed in er the better guides</u>
<u n="229" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0688">yeah than we have</u>
<u n="231" who="S0689">so what is this?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0687">there's a park for you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0689">buzzing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0690">it's all happening here</u>
<u n="236" who="S0687">over there</u>
<u n="237" who="S0689">so are are we getting out?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="239" who="S0690"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0687">right shall we decide where we're going then?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0687">where do you want to go?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0688">er well there's the map</u>
<u n="244" who="S0687">I know this map's literally just <unclear/> though</u>
<u n="245" who="S0688">dad said that was the better one</u>
<u n="246" who="S0687">I know but this just this doesn't tell you places to go mum we need to know where to go</u>
<u n="247" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I know but I know but I haven't got the book</u>
<u n="248" who="S0687">right well I can't read it</u>
<u n="249" who="S0690" trans="overlap">this book?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0687">whilst we're going around</u>
<u n="251" who="S0689">I need a drink</u>
<u n="252" who="S0688" trans="overlap">get that up full pelt <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> please</u>
<u n="253" who="S0687">yeah ta yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0690" trans="overlap">I think it's a bit odd to go to the beach if there's no shade don't you?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0688">no we were gonna go there at teatime</u>
<u n="256" who="S0690">okay</u>
<u n="257" who="S0689">can we stop at a gas station and get like a Fanta lemon or something? I'm like</u>
<u n="258" who="S0690" trans="overlap">course we can</u>
<u n="259" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0687">we've got to go to <unclear/> go back to Groznjan right back towards where the house is</u>
<u n="261" who="S0688">where's Tar?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0687">we are kind of here and Tar's just like a little bit further on this main road I think dad</u>
<u n="263" who="S0690">okay what's there?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0687">I don't know</u>
<u n="265" who="S0690">okay</u>
<u n="266" who="S0687"><unclear>I don't know I think maybe look in this book</unclear></u>
<u n="267" who="S0689">I'm wearing your socks today <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they're very comfy I must say</u>
<u n="268" who="S0690" trans="overlap">are you? that's a shame cos I've I've I've only washed them and I've only got two pairs</u>
<u n="269" who="S0687"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0690">thinking oh will I have to wash them again before we go home?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0687" trans="overlap"><unclear/> for you</u>
<u n="272" who="S0690">I've only I've only got two pairs of them full stop <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0689">I've got some funky socks if you wanna wear them</u>
<u n="274" who="S0690">er okay <pause dur="short"/> er so the I washed a pair of yours as well when I did mine nice of me I thought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll be in the same boat</u>
<u n="275" who="S0689">I've got plenty of socks left</u>
<u n="276" who="S0690">oh right why have got?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0687" trans="overlap">so you've just decided to wear <unclear/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0690" trans="overlap">why have you got why have you gotta wear mine then?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0688">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0690">why have you gotta wear my sweaty ones?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0687">right dad we wanna decide what we're gonna go</u>
<u n="282" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0690">so what happens at the end then turn left is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0690">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0687">you could like have that for <unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0688">I think so <unclear/> careful</u>
<u n="288" who="S0687">jesus</u>
<u n="289" who="S0689">I wonder if we were cats how many lives we'd have lost</u>
<u n="290" who="S0687">all of them <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0688"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she talked about that</u>
<u n="292" who="S0687">what was that? what happened?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0688"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0687"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0688">it's just all the signs up that say I think it's what we drove through <unclear/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0690">Tar here <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0689">god the sun reflecting off them cars isn't pleasant</u>
<u n="298" who="S0690">someone's blooming overtaking down there <pause dur="short"/> that'll be the end of the</u>
<u n="299" who="S0688"><unclear>what?</unclear></u>
<u n="300" who="S0687">this idiot overtaking him <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0689">he looks about ten <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0690">sorry? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0687">I don't know you just said she was talking about it</u>
<u n="306" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0689">there's a nice house actually on the double garage double garage I'm telling you I need a double garage <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0687"><vocal desc="yawn"/> lordy lord</u>
<u n="311" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0689">why have you been bitten?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0688" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0689">are you still taking those pills for your swelling up thing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0688">she <unclear/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0687">does she?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0688">I was gonna tell her this is nice here <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0687">that's the <unclear/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0689">you what?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0689"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0688">I never tried <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0689">there's a market there dad oh no it's closed</u>
<u n="325" who="S0687"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0688">oh there's little places down the back <pause dur="short"/> looks like a school</u>
<u n="327" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0688">it's just a little town isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> we'll sit and have a glass of wine <pause dur="short"/> or a drink</u>
<u n="329" who="S0690">do reckon we're there?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0690" trans="overlap">that's why we're close to the</u>
<u n="333" who="S0687">isn't it?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0690">there's on a Saturday yeah looks like it's down to the beach now then let's have a look</u>
<u n="335" who="S0687">let's have a look</u>
<u n="336" who="S0689">fish marked</u>
<u n="337" who="S0690">fish market <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0689">I know but it says fish mark</u>
<u n="339" who="S0690">no it's fish market is that open <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0689">dunno have a look</u>
<u n="341" who="S0690">oh closed?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0688">I think it's an aquarium isn't it?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0689">no it's a it says fish marked</u>
<u n="344" who="S0688">well you know like where you could buy fish like tropical fish?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0687">no it's eaty fish</u>
<u n="346" who="S0689">I think it was eaty fish yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0690">eaty fish?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0689">can I turn these this air con down a little bit? it's really</u>
<u n="350" who="S0688">a little bit that's alright</u>
<u n="351" who="S0689">oh right I guess I'm I'm in the front but I</u>
<u n="352" who="S0687" trans="overlap">no but you two have got your fans blowing off so you can turn yours down</u>
<u n="353" who="S0688" trans="overlap">oh look there's a nice church there to the left</u>
<u n="354" who="S0689">where?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0687"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0689">thanks for that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0689">oh</u>
<u n="359" who="S0690" trans="overlap">oh apartments and whatnot aren't they? yeah there's one could do with that <unclear/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0690" trans="overlap">one for sale</u>
<u n="362" who="S0687" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0687"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I think that's it for the town</u>
<u n="365" who="S0688">go back in it looks like we've lost it</u>
<u n="366" who="S0689">go back into where? the town?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0687">to town <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0689">the <unclear/> guy</u>
<u n="370" who="S0687"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> can't stop to twiddling these bits <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> these are quite nice I'll have one of them <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0689">there's a German flag down there</u>
<u n="372" who="S0687" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0689">I know but it had it had a German flag outside</u>
<u n="374" who="S0687">oh right well it's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0689">no I'm not saying that I'm just</u>
<u n="376" who="S0687" trans="overlap">that would have to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0688">which one? there's</u>
<u n="378" who="S0687">this one</u>
<u n="379" who="S0689">I'd say these are holiday though</u>
<u n="380" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0689">I wanted to turn it down but you wouldn't let me</u>
<u n="382" who="S0687">you're meant to keep it cool I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0690">nice <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0688">sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is that the church?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0690" whoConfidence="low">which one?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0688">looks like a tower isn't it?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0689">oh it'll probably be a church won't it?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0687">why's that looking like <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0690">wanna go there then do you?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0688"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0687">I dunno if it's all like a matter of perspective but kind of like the things that we do and <unclear/> we're like be things to do so it was kind of a bit like that <unclear/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0688">well why was? <trunc>th</trunc>that was a nice place if you were going for something to eat</u>
<u n="401" who="S0689">yeah I can't see there being much huge events</u>
<u n="402" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0687">boring</u>
<u n="405" who="S0690">I thought we'd be closer to the sea</u>
<u n="406" who="S0687">what here?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0690">yeah can't be far away can we?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0687">no a couple of miles</u>
<u n="409" who="S0688">shall we not just take some more inland</u>
<u n="410" who="S0690">inland?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0687">what today?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0688">yeah you know just</u>
<u n="413" who="S0687">we can go to Groznjan cos that's on the way back to the house <pause dur="short"/> or I don't know what <unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0688">here</u>
<u n="415" who="S0687">it's on the <unclear/> closer up to erm very close to the border with Slovenia</u>
<u n="416" who="S0688">that's a long way isn't it?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0687">no probably cos we're here <unclear/>'s there and so we're there</u>
<u n="418" who="S0689">sorry what what's what's there to do in <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0687">hang on <unclear/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0688">where was it that map? <unclear/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0687">er it was the well the first time we drove through I don't know which way I don't know where we are now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0687">I don't know <unclear/> cos I don't think it was down here</u>
<u n="424" who="S0690">no I'm trying to retrace my steps we'll find it this'll take us back past the church won't it?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0688">they're all pretty houses aren't they? <pause dur="long"/> shall we say did you hear her saying that the house they looked at it they were looking at an apartment and then but you weren't getting so much for your money?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0690">right</u>
<u n="427" who="S0688">er and then they saw this house and then they thought about it and while they were thinking about it they came back and had another look and it had dropped in price</u>
<u n="428" who="S0690">right</u>
<u n="429" who="S0688">er so she said four years ago house prices were higher than they are now cos it got this reputation for being the Tuscany of Istria</u>
<u n="430" who="S0690">right</u>
<u n="431" who="S0687">of Croatia</u>
<u n="432" who="S0688">she said Istria</u>
<u n="433" who="S0687">oh</u>
<u n="434" who="S0689">so why has house prices fallen?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0687">someone's feet smell keep getting I can really smell feet</u>
<u n="436" who="S0688">I don't know whether it's just that come to fruition you know whether it's not taken off like</u>
<u n="437" who="S0687">what hasn't? <unclear/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0690">this was <unclear/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0689" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="441" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0690">do you wanna go in this one?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0687">why not? <unclear/> Mlvazija that was it what she said</u>
<u n="444" who="S0688">was it?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0687" trans="overlap">we can try yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's just <unclear/> to buy it's already <unclear/> drink it</u>
<u n="446" who="S0690">dunno well there's no bottles outside so let's do it right?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0687">this is definitely homemade</u>
<u n="448" who="S0690">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0688"><unclear/> actually</u>
<u n="450" who="S0687">yeah there's a big sign</u>
<u n="451" who="S0690">find out there's a big sign on the road so we're not coming for a</u>
<u n="452" who="S0687">cup of tea</u>
<u n="453" who="S0690">cup of tea</u>
<u n="454" who="S0689">yeah that's very true</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="455" who="S0688">so people can pop here from the restaurants can't they? and buy</u>
<u n="456" who="S0687">yeah I think that that guy</u>
<u n="457" who="S0689" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0690">I'm sure</u>
<u n="459" who="S0687">was yeah with a bit of a</u>
<u n="460" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0690"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0688"><unclear/> would I do it again though?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0690">there's nothing behind me is there? okay?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0689">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="467" who="S0688" trans="overlap">it's free</u>
<u n="468" who="S0690"><unclear/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0689">I didn't know why it had to have chemicals in to be exported <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0688">oh look at these what are these <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? are they <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0690">it's <unclear/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> oh gosh this is a dangerous country <pause dur="short"/> christ that's dangerous just jump out from <unclear/> come out here and literally there's a blind corner</u>
<u n="472" who="S0688">should have a <unclear/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0690">they should yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we're going back to back up to the road are we? the main road <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> going back towards Novograd or are we going?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0687">what do you wanna do? it's up to you guys <pause dur="short"/> decide what you wanna do and I'll tell you where to go</u>
<u n="475" who="S0688">well where did you say shall we go to that Grovinj? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0687">you want to go to Groznjan? I need to see the map then where's the map gone guys?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0690">how far inland is that?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0688">it's here</u>
<u n="479" who="S0687">closer back towards home</u>
<u n="480" who="S0688">it's here</u>
<u n="481" who="S0687" trans="overlap">where's the map dad? I had it before <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0688">did we take it in?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0687">have I sat on it? I didn't take it in there we'd know</u>
<u n="484" who="S0688">have you got hold of it?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0689">sorry have I got hold of what?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0687" trans="overlap">has anybody got the map in the front guys?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0690">don't believe so if you had it in the back back before it'll still be there <unclear/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0688" trans="overlap">oh it's there darling</u>
<u n="489" who="S0687">do you want to go to <trunc>Grov</trunc>Grovnjan? <pause dur="short"/> yes?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0688">yeah <pause dur="long"/> oh gosh they have <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0687">so you're basically gonna go back the way you want for home but turn off at Grovnjan dad</u>
<u n="492" who="S0690">okay</u>
<u n="493" who="S0688">what we're near to Porec now aren't we?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0687">yeah bit further south</u>
<u n="495" who="S0688">Porec is I can't remember what it looked like what what</u>
<u n="496" who="S0687">it was the one that we didn't like we went on the first day and it was dead touristy do you remember?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0688">we went on the first day?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0687">do you remember? that's</u>
<u n="499" who="S0690" trans="overlap">I thought it was quite nice it wasn't as nice as the one further south</u>
<u n="500" who="S0687">no it wasn't it was the one that we sat in that café where dad was moaning about the carpark and we all said it was <trunc>disa</trunc> it was a disappointment</u>
<u n="501" who="S0688">I can't remember</u>
<u n="502" who="S0687">can't remember? we sat in the</u>
<u n="503" who="S0689" trans="overlap">do you not <trunc>re</trunc>?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0687">the</u>
<u n="505" who="S0689" trans="overlap">do you not <trunc>re</trunc>remember the one where that woman took like four hundred <unclear>ticks</unclear> off the?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0687">yeah she took like what we paid for our bill as a tip</u>
<u n="507" who="S0689">oh yeah well it was alright <pause dur="short"/> but it was touristy <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0688">shall we try that pizzeria tonight that was near home?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0687">can do</u>
<u n="510" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0690">what was that?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0687">Alto I thought you wanted to go to the truffly place on our way back tonight</u>
<u n="513" who="S0688">is that? I'm I'm lost with where she said things were</u>
<u n="514" who="S0687">where we get to the main road you go straight across there's a big truffle banner</u>
<u n="515" who="S0688">oh is there? I thought she was telling us about</u>
<u n="516" who="S0687" trans="overlap">that's what she was telling us about <trunc>Dobo</trunc>Dobolli or whatever</u>
<u n="517" who="S0688">where the lady cooks her homemade</u>
<u n="518" who="S0689" trans="overlap"><unclear/> again</u>
<u n="519" who="S0688">pasta?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0688">okay</u>
<u n="522" who="S0687">erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0689">anyone seen a sign for one of them <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0688">that was back down there wasn't it?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0689" trans="overlap">oh was it?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0688">cos we went on from there didn't we? to where we got the pork butty</u>
<u n="527" who="S0687">where did we get the pork butty?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0689" trans="overlap">sorry I don't understand what you mean mum</u>
<u n="529" who="S0688">from Porec didn't we carry on up the coast of Fortuna and get the?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0687">no from Porec we went to Rovinj</u>
<u n="531" who="S0688">yeah but on the way</u>
<u n="532" who="S0690">Fortuna was that big erm <unclear>hotel</unclear> up there</u>
<u n="533" who="S0688">yeah but with that is where we stopped going up the hill isn't it? erm where they had the pork the pig butties that <unclear>weren't</unclear> pig butties</u>
<u n="534" who="S0690" trans="overlap">yeah pig butties that <unclear>weren't</unclear> pig butties <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0689"><unclear/> have like spray paint on</u>
<u n="536" who="S0688">yeah I'm not sure why <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0687">I can <trunc>f</trunc> I've got a headache coming on</u>
<u n="538" who="S0688">have you?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0689">do you want <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0688" trans="overlap">well you didn't drink any wine did you?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0687">I've drunk loads of water I just feel dead tired I don't think I'd slept well last night cos I was just too hot</u>
<u n="542" who="S0688">what does that say on there?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0687">I were <unclear/> you were asleep <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I woke up at three o'clock I couldn't read it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0689">well I woke up once when you were turning off the air con</u>
<u n="545" who="S0687">turning it off yeah it was before then I woke up again at three and put it back on</u>
<u n="546" who="S0689">I got woken a couple of times with you moving about but</u>
<u n="547" who="S0687">I was drenched in sweat my hair was wet</u>
<u n="548" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0690">could be anywhere down there then</u>
<u n="550" who="S0688" trans="overlap">you could drive down there let's have a little look</u>
<u n="551" who="S0687">careful this car's doing something</u>
<u n="552" who="S0690" trans="overlap">where are you going mate?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0688">is it just like a fishing place do you think? like a little harbour</u>
<u n="554" who="S0687" trans="overlap">I think so the water's scummy</u>
<u n="555" who="S0690" trans="overlap">thereabouts there yeah it's full of scum <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0689">can you purify any water by boiling it? could you get that water boil it and then it would be safe to drink?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0688">sea water?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0690">they can do pretty amazing things to water can't they? they have have these used things you can buy that sort of you suck water through this <unclear/> fancy filter or whatever and it</u>
<u n="559" who="S0688">change it into drinking water</u>
<u n="560" who="S0690"><unclear/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0689">no but I mean just straight boiling</u>
<u n="562" who="S0688">no</u>
<u n="563" who="S0690">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0688" trans="overlap">you wouldn't get rid of all the salt would you?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0689">no I mean like say like the lake that had a bit of scum in it was a bit horrible could you not just <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah if it's fresh water couldn't sea water though</u>
<u n="567" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0688" trans="overlap">so is is the we keep saying that whenever we're in this car er</u>
<u n="570" who="S0687"><unclear/> it's not the kind of place you would like sit and sunbathe is it?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0688">not really</u>
<u n="572" who="S0687">not very picturesque really</u>
<u n="573" who="S0688">erm <pause dur="short"/> the beach</u>
<u n="574" who="S0689" trans="overlap">oh look at that dog</u>
<u n="575" who="S0688">in the water?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0688">the beach that she said they go to is that further that's the Novigrad?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0687">it's north of Novigrad</u>
<u n="579" who="S0688">oh okay so kind of the direction we're going in</u>
<u n="580" who="S0687">mm not if we're going to Grovnjan</u>
<u n="581" who="S0690" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0688">sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0690">we can have a look at that if you want</u>
<u n="584" who="S0687">it's it's like if we go to Groznjan and then back to there we'll be like doing</u>
<u n="585" who="S0689">well let's have a look at it now then</u>
<u n="586" who="S0690">it's all boats</u>
<u n="587" who="S0688">there's nowt here</u>
<u n="588" who="S0690">not much to look at looks quite nice from the opposite side don't know</u>
<u n="589" who="S0688">I'll get a <unclear/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0690"><unclear/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0689">that was a gate but it's locked <pause dur="long"/> that obviously leads up to something doesn't it?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0690">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0688">bet it says you can only walk though</u>
<u n="594" who="S0690">up the hill?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0688">yeah it doesn't tell you what's up there</u>
<u n="596" who="S0690">no it's er so it's if evacuation in case of fire</u>
<u n="597" who="S0688">jump in the water <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0687">what you chatting on about you?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0688" trans="overlap">see I saw lots of these that's unusual I saw those when erm let me have a look at it up close that plant <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I saw lots of it</u>
<u n="600" who="S0687" trans="overlap">it looks like dodgy cotton wool</u>
<u n="601" who="S0688">yeah that's</u>
<u n="602" who="S0689" trans="overlap">yeah it does</u>
<u n="603" who="S0688">I saw it when what's he called was driving us here</u>
<u n="604" who="S0690">dodgy cotton wool</u>
<u n="605" who="S0689">it does look like stained cotton wool I must say</u>
<u n="606" who="S0687">mum you're letting the warm in</u>
<u n="607" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0687" trans="overlap">on no mum uh <pause dur="short"/> what's she doing?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0689">I don't know er checking out the dodgy cotton wool</u>
<u n="610" who="S0687"><vocal desc="sigh"/> can we leave her?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0689">yeah that's a good shout can we leave her? leave her with <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0687"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and she'd poo herself then</u>
<u n="613" who="S0689"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0687">she's giving me daggers for no reason it was you trying to run her over</u>
<u n="615" who="S0688">it looks like it's gonna be soft from here but when you get close up to it it's not at all</u>
<u n="616" who="S0689">really?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0687">dad</u>
<u n="618" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0687" trans="overlap">I'm glad we've learnt that</u>
<u n="620" who="S0689">yeah me too</u>
<u n="621" who="S0687"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0689">have you got any more <unclear/> mum or are you alright? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0687">yeah where there's loads of cars here you'd think there'd be something here to see</u>
<u n="624" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0688">maybe people have got boats and gone out or but</u>
<u n="626" who="S0687" trans="overlap">no these like they're packing up for the beach</u>
<u n="627" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0690">no I was <trunc>b</trunc> I haven't seen anything as picturesquey as those any of those beaches in Catalonia like</u>
<u n="629" who="S0687">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0690">see a really really nice beach</u>
<u n="631" who="S0689">that's quite a nice boat</u>
<u n="632" who="S0690">quite a nice boat</u>
<u n="633" who="S0689">oh</u>
<u n="634" who="S0688">what was that?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0689">what?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0688">looks like a quarry doesn't it?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0689" trans="overlap">I was just about to say that <pause dur="short"/> unless there's just been a rockslide</u>
<u n="638" who="S0687"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0688">someone swimming out there</u>
<u n="640" who="S0689">where?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0687">swimming? <pause dur="short"/> oh this bloody seatbelt</u>
<u n="642" who="S0689">is it <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0687">it's kicking up a right fuss</u>
<u n="644" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="645" who="S0687">she's bloody claimed it <unclear/> like you could go on that</u>
<u n="646" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0687" trans="overlap">this one's got her boobies out</u>
<u n="648" who="S0689">what?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0687" trans="overlap">that's what I said she's a naturist <pause dur="short"/> ain't nobody need to see that</u>
<u n="650" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0687">ignore it</u>
<u n="652" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0687">well there isn't is there? keep it to yourself there's a reason Adam and Eve had fig leaves</u>
<u n="654" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0687">oh bloody hell here's camper van Joe <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0689">watch his wing mirrors that stick out like <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0688">I don't wanna get my finger in it</u>
<u n="658" who="S0687">well</u>
<u n="659" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I'd rather if you'd have pull it out</u>
<u n="660" who="S0687">just put your lips in it <pause dur="short"/> where are you taking us here?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0689">yeah right</u>
<u n="662" who="S0690">just taking us back to that big road I think</u>
<u n="663" who="S0688">oh <pause dur="short"/> hat <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0687">evening watch the sunset from the church terrace in the nearby hill town of Groznjan then have a drink in the shade of the arches of the Venetian loggia</u>
<u n="665" who="S0689"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will you please stop humming? it's really doing my head in can't</u>
<u n="666" who="S0688">will you stop what?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0689">he keeps humming and he's going <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0690">put some music on then</u>
<u n="669" who="S0687">mum keeps doing her favourite <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0688">I don't</u>
<u n="671" who="S0687"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="672" who="S0688" trans="overlap">when?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0687"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0688">we did it together yesterday for a laugh</u>
<u n="675" who="S0687" trans="overlap">I know me taking you the Michael out of you</u>
<u n="676" who="S0690" trans="overlap">better than your singing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't know anyone who's a worse singer than you</u>
<u n="677" who="S0687">get off</u>
<u n="678" who="S0688">I'm really bad at singing</u>
<u n="679" who="S0690">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0688">she's inherited my voice</u>
<u n="681" who="S0687">speak for yourself</u>
<u n="682" who="S0690">she has no that's not wrong</u>
<u n="683" who="S0687"><unclear/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0688">really no no no no no</u>
<u n="685" who="S0687">just a little bit</u>
<u n="686" who="S0688" trans="overlap">no we're driving <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't wanna be cycling in this would you?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0690">no not really</u>
<u n="688" who="S0687">wouldn't be pleasurable</u>
<u n="689" who="S0689">she had a huge bug on her back anyway</u>
<u n="690" who="S0687">she had a huge bug?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0689">on her back yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0687">that's not nice either</u>
<u n="693" who="S0689"><unclear/> if a</u>
<u n="694" who="S0687" trans="overlap">that's what</u>
<u n="695" who="S0688">if a bug was on me</u>
<u n="696" who="S0687" trans="overlap">that's what I thought about</u>
<u n="697" who="S0688">when I was cycling</u>
<u n="698" who="S0687">that's what I thought about that woman that well woman man lay down in the long grass doing their exercise they'd have had all sorts of creepies crawling all over them</u>
<u n="699" who="S0688" trans="overlap">it would have put you off tickling your skin wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0687">and ticks as well</u>
<u n="702" who="S0688">you're obsessed with ticks you</u>
<u n="703" who="S0687">well it's it's after I saw that cat it's making me itch now</u>
<u n="704" who="S0690" trans="overlap"><unclear/> this roundabout <unclear/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="706" who="S0689">circle round</u>
<u n="707" who="S0687">which circle round? that wasn't a circle round</u>
<u n="708" who="S0689"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says it was so it is</u>
<u n="709" who="S0687">it wasn't just a junction?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0689">I dunno I do like Audis I must say <pause dur="short"/> very very nice <pause dur="short"/> nice Audi R8 I want for my first car</u>
<u n="711" who="S0690">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that ham looked nice I thought she was gonna give me a slice of the ham but the cheese <unclear/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0687" trans="overlap">it looked gross</u>
<u n="713" who="S0689">you didn't want to there were flies on it</u>
<u n="714" who="S0687">it smelt as well</u>
<u n="715" who="S0688">it stunk when you went in there didn't it?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0689">there were flies on it</u>
<u n="717" who="S0687">it smelt like vinegar and just like horrible meat</u>
<u n="718" who="S0690">I wouldn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0688">I didn't <unclear/> it wasn't cold enough was it?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0687">where's Vodnjan mum?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0688">isn't it's Groznjan</u>
<u n="722" who="S0687">no there's another place called Vodnjan</u>
<u n="723" who="S0688">I can't look at that map while we're driving</u>
<u n="724" who="S0687">returning to Fazana where's Fazana?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0688">that's further on I think</u>
<u n="726" who="S0687" trans="overlap">oh Vodnjan's just there</u>
<u n="727" who="S0688">it's further back that way isn't it?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah it's back where we were near Pula it says it is a charming provincial town</u>
<u n="729" who="S0688">do you wanna go and have a look?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0687">no it's like an hour away</u>
<u n="731" who="S0688">is it?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0687">yeah it's look it's down there nearer here</u>
<u n="733" who="S0688" trans="overlap">oh Pula okay</u>
<u n="734" who="S0689">Pula</u>
<u n="735" who="S0687"><vocal desc="gasp"/> bloody hell</u>
<u n="736" who="S0690"><unclear/></u>
<u n="737" who="S0687">swear to god we've been on this road once</u>
<u n="738" who="S0690">well more than once <unclear/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0688" trans="overlap">guys we're exploring chill out</u>
<u n="740" who="S0689">I'm perfectly chilled I'm just stating a fact <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> please stop humming</u>
<u n="741" who="S0688">put some music on</u>
<u n="742" who="S0690" trans="overlap">put some music on then</u>
<u n="743" who="S0689">no</u>
<u n="744" who="S0690" trans="overlap">you're not recording it are you?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0689">yeah we are</u>
<u n="746" who="S0690">oh are we?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0689">yes</u>
<u n="748" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I'm bloody glad we're not</u>
<u n="749" who="S0687" trans="overlap">are we?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0689">we are</u>
<u n="751" who="S0688" trans="overlap">no we're not</u>
<u n="752" who="S0687" trans="overlap">no we're not</u>
<u n="753" who="S0689">we are look</u>
<u n="754" who="S0687">why have you been recording? we've not been speaking?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0689">yeah we have been speaking</u>
<u n="756" who="S0688">been speaking a lot</u>
<u n="757" who="S0690">been speaking a lot don't have to be talking about <unclear/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0688">that olive oil was expensive too did you see how much it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0690">no I</u>
<u n="760" who="S0688" trans="overlap">about a tenner a litre</u>
<u n="761" who="S0690">a tenner a litre? <unclear/> god that's a lot</u>
<u n="762" who="S0688">it is a lot</u>
<u n="763" who="S0690">how how how much is it that bottle we bought at home? cos it was only I think it was only <unclear>twenty-eight</unclear> or something in the shop</u>
<u n="764" who="S0688">yeah it was half a litre</u>
<u n="765" who="S0690">oh it</u>
<u n="766" who="S0687" trans="overlap">it wasn't half a litre it was only a little bottle it was probably about two hundred mil</u>
<u n="767" who="S0688">it was more than that I'm sure</u>
<u n="768" who="S0687">I don't think it was more than that</u>
<u n="769" who="S0688">well it's still er</u>
<u n="770" who="S0690" trans="overlap">I don't really know how you tell the difference between you know</u>
<u n="771" who="S0688">I know</u>
<u n="772" who="S0690" trans="overlap">different qualities to be honest with you</u>
<u n="773" who="S0688">well when you buy an olive oil er the darker it is usually the stronger er it tastes</u>
<u n="774" who="S0690" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="775" who="S0689">olive oil's olive oil to me I mean you know</u>
<u n="776" who="S0690">well people do get a bit anal about it <unclear/></u>
<u n="777" who="S0687">a bit alanal?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0688">a bit a bit anal</u>
<u n="779" who="S0690" trans="overlap">a bit anal about it erm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0687">about olive oil?</u>
<u n="781" who="S0690">yeah can't be much <unclear/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0688">but if you</u>
<u n="784" who="S0687" trans="overlap">it's not like you can taste it when you've made a risotto you can taste it it's not a certain olive oil</u>
<u n="785" who="S0690">well you say that but then this truffle oil you was gonna make presumably gonna be able to taste that difference I'd have thought</u>
<u n="786" who="S0687">I presume</u>
<u n="787" who="S0690">so you just plonk it in do you or do you put shavings of it in or what like?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0687">you don't plonk the entire truffle in</u>
<u n="789" who="S0689">well I think</u>
<u n="790" who="S0687" trans="overlap">I think I think I think you shave it</u>
<u n="791" who="S0688">I think you can</u>
<u n="792" who="S0690">did she then plonk it in an <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0688">no she <trunc>sai</trunc></u>
<u n="794" who="S0690" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="795" who="S0688">oh</u>
<u n="796" who="S0690" trans="overlap">honey honey was it?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0688">that was the honey I think you can put shavings in and then freeze the rest of it she said</u>
<u n="798" who="S0690"><unclear/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0688">eh?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0687" trans="overlap">well she said she <trunc>sai</trunc> she said as soon as it's like a mushroom it only lasts a couple of days <pause dur="short"/> so she said freeze it and then when you need it just take some shavings and then shove it back in the freezer</u>
<u n="802" who="S0689">it's a weird tower that</u>
<u n="803" who="S0690">it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0687">dunno what the point of it is <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="805" who="S0688"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> be nice if we saw a deer wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0689">well as long as it didn't crash through the windscreen yes <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't be so nice if it crashed through the windscreen <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="807" who="S0688">chill grill <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0687">got an itchy toe</u>
<u n="809" who="S0688" trans="overlap">so she said they didn't put any sulphites in it and then she decided</u>
<u n="810" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0687">they put a few sulphates in it</u>
<u n="812" who="S0688" trans="overlap">they do</u>
<u n="813" who="S0687">all natural just with a few sulphates</u>
<u n="814" who="S0688">we'll have to have a look in that erm I suppose you can google if you can buy erm Croatian wine can't you?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0690">you can</u>
<u n="816" who="S0687">I'm sure you can get hold of it</u>
<u n="817" who="S0688">I've never seen it</u>
<u n="818" who="S0687">it's <trunc>probab</trunc> well yeah but you've probably never been looking for it have you when you've been in Tesco's or Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="819" who="S0688">yeah but they just have like Italian French Spanish</u>
<u n="820" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0688">er New Zealand</u>
<u n="822" who="S0687" trans="overlap">they sometimes have like other like other do you know what I mean? another section</u>
<u n="823" who="S0688" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="824" who="S0687">might be in there with like I dunno <unclear/> and places</u>
<u n="825" who="S0688">I sort of thought this would be on a par with Turkish wine and Greek wine</u>
<u n="826" who="S0687">which is horrible</u>
<u n="827" who="S0688">they're not got well we've never tasted anything that's been nice <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="828" who="S0689">wine <unclear/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0687">yeah I can't say</u>
<u n="830" who="S0688" trans="overlap">that red wine was oh</u>
<u n="831" who="S0687">what? that that that you tasted there?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah that was vinegar for sure</u>
<u n="833" who="S0690">erm so what am I going back to this hill toppy place?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0687">erm</u>
<u n="835" who="S0690">or do I go and see what this beach looks like?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0687">it's up to you</u>
<u n="837" who="S0688">yeah go to the beach first</u>
<u n="838" who="S0690" trans="overlap">or we're going to the beach like thing is we're here now aren't we?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0687">is this Novigrad?</u>
<u n="840" who="S0690">it's Novigrad</u>
<u n="841" who="S0688">do you know where it is from here <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0690">I'll find it</u>
<u n="843" who="S0687" trans="overlap">er dad does she showed dad on the map didn't she?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0690">er yeah cos this is the <unclear/> place isn't it? the roundabout</u>
<u n="845" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah so I think we need to go straight</u>
<u n="846" who="S0690" trans="overlap">so probably left</u>
<u n="847" who="S0687">over here</u>
<u n="848" who="S0689">well can we</u>
<u n="849" who="S0687">I think we need to go straight over</u>
<u n="850" who="S0689">can we nip into this <unclear/> to get a drink?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0687">does anyone want some water?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0689">I'll have a <unclear/> of water</u>
<u n="853" who="S0688">I don't think it'll be very cold in there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will it?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0690" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="855" who="S0688">you know the drink?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0689">oh these are the supermarkets we came to</u>
<u n="857" who="S0687">yeah I think it's over here dad</u>
<u n="858" who="S0690">okay</u>
<u n="859" who="S0687">and then you come to a junction up here where you go like slightly left</u>
<u n="860" who="S0690">slightly left yeah you don't want me to go and get a drink from the</u>
<u n="861" who="S0688">you can do yeah pop in</u>
<u n="862" who="S0690" trans="overlap">anybody else?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0689">er</u>
<u n="864" who="S0690">quick</u>
<u n="865" who="S0687">make a decision</u>
<u n="866" who="S0689" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't stress me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="867" who="S0690">don't stress you? well I think I'll <unclear/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0688">that's Mr <unclear>Tesco</unclear> isn't it? the <unclear/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0687"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said they live a couple of streets over there</u>
<u n="870" who="S0688">oh okay</u>
<u n="871" who="S0687">near <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0690">right so you jump out mate and I'll catch up with you and pay the bill</u>
<u n="873" who="S0687">well why don't you just give him some money?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0689">why don't you just give me some money? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0688" trans="overlap">well go in with him <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0687">oh he's alright</u>
<u n="877" who="S0688">I'll come with you love</u>
<u n="878" who="S0689">thanks mum right are you two gonna carry on talking?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0687">mm probably pause it</u>
<u n="880" who="S0689">okay</u>
<u n="881" who="S0687">places like that</u>
<u n="882" who="S0690">although there weren't many nice inland you know like Motovan there was nothing like Motovan was there?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0687">no no they were all coastal</u>
<u n="884" who="S0690" trans="overlap">but the <trunc>bea</trunc> but the beaches the coasts was were nicer</u>
<u n="885" who="S0687">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely mind you did <trunc>y</trunc> we you'll have seen the <trunc>diff</trunc> did you see the difference from when you landed in the south and it being really touristy and</u>
<u n="886" who="S0690">yeah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0687">resorts and then as you got further north it got more</u>
<u n="888" who="S0690" trans="overlap">got nicer</u>
<u n="889" who="S0687">it got nicer?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0690" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0687">that's where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has just gone she's staying in the south I think that's where everyone stays really</u>
<u n="892" who="S0690">right okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="893" who="S0687">yeah I don't know if we're missing something or if people cos people literally rave about it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my friend who went last summer was just like said it was amazing</u>
<u n="894" who="S0690">what? Catalonia?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0687">no here</u>
<u n="896" who="S0690">here?</u>
<u n="897" who="S0687">yeah she stayed at erm one of these Valamar resorts on an island off near Tar and she thought it was amazing</u>
<u n="898" who="S0690">oh right</u>
<u n="899" who="S0687">but I don't know how much stuff she did on the mainland or whether she just stayed in this resort</u>
<u n="900" who="S0690">oh right <pause dur="long"/> everybody wants different I suppose <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0687">be nice if you could pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house up and put it on Catalonia</u>
<u n="902" who="S0690">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0687">that would be like the ideal <pause dur="long"/> although I don't know if I'd go to Catalonia again really cos there's not a great deal to do besides beaches</u>
<u n="904" who="S0690">no</u>
<u n="905" who="S0687">it's kind of once you've done it you've done it <pause dur="long"/> I'm gonna run out of charge soon</u>
<u n="906" who="S0690">yeah we should have bought the car charger shouldn't we? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="907" who="S0687">this guide book's not good either</u>
<u n="908" who="S0690">no it's a bit crap <pause dur="short"/> I might just leave it in the house</u>
<u n="909" who="S0687">yeah I don't think we're gonna be coming back in a rush <pause dur="short"/> not to be unkind <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="910" who="S0690">what about <trunc>mi</trunc> we might go to Dubrovnik or Split I suppose mightn't we?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="long"/> see that list just isn't helpful at all it says where to go out Samobor there are parades with floats on the last weekend of carnival where when people wear masks and fancy dress the climax of the festivities is a Shrove Tuesday fireworks display well that's helpful what's the last weekend of carnival?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0690">well Shrove Tuesday is more Easter isn't it?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0687">yeah I know but it doesn't tell you when the last weekend of carnival is does it?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0690">er <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0687">don't know what I've done with the map again <pause dur="long"/> do you prefer Venice or Rome?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0690">mm I dunno they're very different really</u>
<u n="917" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="short"/> sorted?</u>
<u n="918" who="S0689">can <unclear/> and I can get in easier</u>
<u n="919" who="S0688">got him some of his erm</u>
<u n="920" who="S0687">Fanta</u>
<u n="921" who="S0688" trans="overlap">lemon and lime beer <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="922" who="S0687">if we can get in <unclear/> I'll have a bit of his Fanta Lemon</u>
<u n="923" who="S0688">I need a wee</u>
<u n="924" who="S0687">are there none in there?</u>
<u n="925" who="S0690" trans="overlap">there's a there's a toilet in there</u>
<u n="926" who="S0688" trans="overlap">no there wasn't</u>
<u n="927" who="S0687">oh it was that other one that was a toilet do you want us to take you?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0690">could go there</u>
<u n="929" who="S0689">might be</u>
<u n="930" who="S0687" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> could I have a little drink please?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0689">yeah sure you can</u>
<u n="932" who="S0687">thank you</u>
<u n="933" who="S0689">have you started recording again?</u>
<u n="934" who="S0687">yeah I turned it on cos me and dad were talking</u>
<u n="935" who="S0689">alright fair enough did I I gave you dad's wallet didn't I mum?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0688">you did</u>
<u n="937" who="S0687">I much prefer this lemon one</u>
<u n="938" who="S0689">I think after in hindsight I do too it was nice when I first had it but in hindsight I would</u>
<u n="939" who="S0688" trans="overlap">have you gone off it?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="941" who="S0690" trans="overlap">have you got some of that lemony beer have you?</u>
<u n="942" who="S0688">yeah <pause dur="short"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are sharing I</u>
<u n="943" who="S0690" trans="overlap">well I told you I've got some of that <trunc>oran</trunc> er Pellegrino thing?</u>
<u n="944" who="S0688">you did</u>
<u n="945" who="S0687" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="946" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="947" who="S0689">that's non-alcoholic</u>
<u n="948" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="949" who="S0690" trans="overlap">interesting though isn't it?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0689">yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0688">San Pellegrino? orange?</u>
<u n="952" who="S0687">uhu</u>
<u n="953" who="S0690">different different erm different cans than at home but anyway</u>
<u n="954" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="955" who="S0688">I'm just having a drink</u>
<u n="956" who="S0687" trans="overlap">mum's having a drink</u>
<u n="957" who="S0688">there you go babe</u>
<u n="958" who="S0689">does it have the erm what's it called? what your car has you know when you stop at traffic lights?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0687" trans="overlap">stop-start yeah</u>
<u n="960" who="S0690" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0689">well I wonder how much energy that saves or</u>
<u n="962" who="S0687">it's supposed to save fuel <pause dur="short"/> takes a bit of getting used to though <pause dur="long"/> what's your favourite place so far?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0690">do you think it's down here <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I think it might be down here</u>
<u n="964" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and then</u>
<u n="965" who="S0689">well it looks it</u>
<u n="966" who="S0687">to the right I said what's your favourite place so far? I like Rovinj</u>
<u n="967" who="S0689">I'd say Rovinj</u>
<u n="968" who="S0687">and Motovon Rovinj you was like a nice atmosphere there</u>
<u n="969" who="S0688"><unclear/></u>
<u n="970" who="S0690">must be some money around there's some good old boats to be aren't there?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0688">well there must be cos the cost of it</u>
<u n="972" who="S0687">the cost of what?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0688">sailing here</u>
<u n="974" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="975" who="S0689">well I've seen some very nice cars I suppose no super cars but nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0687">I said to dad I don't know if we're missing something that everyone else seems to</u>
<u n="977" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="978" who="S0687">be aware of do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="979" who="S0688">I I honestly think it's a case of <pause dur="short"/> it's the first time here</u>
<u n="980" who="S0687">do you think so?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0688">I think you you know you grow to</u>
<u n="982" who="S0687">yeah but I I've the people we've spoken to have only been here once and they were like</u>
<u n="983" who="S0688">who have we spoken to?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0687">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came last summer the people at work that you were speaking to</u>
<u n="985" who="S0688">I don't know anyone who's been</u>
<u n="986" who="S0687">can we go a little bit slower over these bumps dad? it's really uncomfortable</u>
<u n="987" who="S0689">well didn't I think everyone had been to like Dubrovnik and Split?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0688">er well I knew someone who was going</u>
<u n="989" who="S0689">where did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> go <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="990" who="S0687">near here <pause dur="short"/> in the north</u>
<u n="991" who="S0689">did they stay at like an apartment or was it a resort?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0687">it was a resort thing</u>
<u n="993" who="S0688" trans="overlap">they had hotel didn't they?</u>
<u n="994" who="S0687">yeah it was a resort <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0688">this looks like is it wheat or barley on the left <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0690">er yeah one of the two I forget how to tell the</u>
<u n="997" who="S0688" trans="overlap">wheat I think</u>
<u n="998" who="S0687" trans="overlap">tell the difference I can't remember</u>
<u n="999" who="S0689">wheat or barley? looks like there's a beach up here</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0690">I think this was the beach she was talking about</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0690">I'd say</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0688">yeah but she said there was no shade</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0687">yeah she said you're parked by</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0688" trans="overlap">and no facilities</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0687" trans="overlap">the side of the road and it's literally just a step down</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0688">so this isn't it</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0687">must be a bit further up I think she said go past like where there's lots of people</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0689">nice Audi nice BM nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="1010" who="S0687">are we sunbathing or are we just having a nosy?</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0690">we're just having a nosy aren't we?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0688">er yeah yeah I I think it's too hot</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0687">gonna say I've not brought any a a book with me or anything <pause dur="short"/> yeah she said go past all the more all the caravans and <trunc>m</trunc> and like erm like these on the left these static things</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0689">static caravans houses really aren't they? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0687">oh this erm inn just at the entrance to Hum it serves typically Istrian dishes such as Fuzi</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0689">what's that?</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0687">with goulash and roast lamb Supa and Istrian speciality of red <trunc>wi</trunc> red wine warmed in a jug and served with sugar pepper olive oil and toast in and its own Biska mistletoe brandy that sounds a bit gross <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1018" who="S0688">these are all like log cabin chalets to and camping carry on campers</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0689">is that meant to be a reference?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0688">er it was a bit of a it was it was a programme called Hi-de-Hi</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0687">looks like this is as far as we can go careful there's a car coming</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0688">blind corners</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0687">she was coming round it just as fast as dad</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0689">no I know I'm just saying there are loads of blind corners</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0688">maybe this is it down here love</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0687">mm she said you literally park and then it's a few steps and you're on the beach didn't she?</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0687">but I'm sure she said past all the static caravanny things</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0688">I'll bet this is a bit like erm what's it called? erm Center Parcs you know</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0687" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0688">like chalets and stuff?</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0687">busy isn't it?</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0688">there's a nice boat out there</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0687">suppose it's a Saturday <pause dur="short"/> I presume this is what she meant here <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1035" who="S0688">I need a wee</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0689">is there even a beach this looks like the sea oh yeah it's over there the beach</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0688">oh it's muddy on the edge it's like black <pause dur="long"/> you can go right round to the end I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1038" who="S0690">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0687">probably quieter won't it?</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0689">doesn't seem to getting <unclear/> I must say but <pause dur="long"/> <unclear>let me know</unclear></u>
<u n="1041" who="S0687">can you see <unclear/> mum?</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0688" trans="overlap">this is quite nice yeah it's rocky</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0687">yeah she said it was</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0689">I don't know things like that were in Croatia</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0687">think so <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1046" who="S0689"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1047" who="S0687">maybe not in the south oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1048" who="S0689">is it a Skoda that?</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0690">behind us?</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0687" trans="overlap">oh it's a Vauxhall</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0689">no the</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0690" trans="overlap"><unclear/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0689">it's like a lightning sign <unclear/></u>
<u n="1054" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah I know it's a Vauxhall <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they call it an Opel</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0689" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0690" trans="overlap">Opel yeah</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0687">abroad but it's a Vauxhall <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0688">looks a bit choppy doesn't it? oh there's someone on a jet ski there</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0689">oh really? <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> what's there?</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0688">nice place to live</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0689">I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> there's an empty plot there look could build a house there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1062" who="S0688">sweet down here isn't it?</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0687">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0689">excuse me</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0688">someone's got a big camper there</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0687"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> move over Ethel</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0689">thank you</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1068" who="S0689">what a moustache woo-hoo</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0687"><vocal desc="laugh"/> look like he'd been electrocuted <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1070" who="S0689">ever told you the moustache joke?</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0688">go on</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0689">I moustache you a question but I'll shave it for later</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0687"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1074" who="S0688">you're a comic and you didn't know it</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0689">I didn't know it a genius</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0688">looks like there's more places to stay up here</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0687">oh it's all getting a bit caravan Joe here</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0688">well there's umbrellas aren't there?</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0689">caravan Joe</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0687">oh no mum that lot'll do us look at that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1081" who="S0689">that's a nice colour <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1082" who="S0688">I think people are camping aren't they?</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0690"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1085" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0687">do you think they are? bloody Nora mum</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0690">get that impression</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0688">no I was I wasn't looking at all those honestly I was only looking by the edge of the water I was thinking</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0687" trans="overlap">oh my days</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0690"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0687">no I was looking at did you not see the like resort thing with a massive swimming pool and about a thousand screaming kids?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0688">hi-de-hi</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0687">I can't imagine anything worse than that</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0689">I could imagine oh nice look</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0687" trans="overlap">that is not a holiday that is torture I'd rather be at home in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> can you imagine no air con <pause dur="short"/> no toilet no shower</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0688">they're still building them there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1097" who="S0687">awful</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0689">I think these static homes are alright</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0687" trans="overlap">I could just about cope with one of these if it had a shower and a toilet one of these static ones</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0690">yeah you've been spoilt you lot</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0689">I wouldn't mind camping</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0687">er you go for it then we'll drop you off pick you up tomorrow see what you say</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0689">I don't think I would for a weekend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1104" who="S0687">oh well you you lot go for it by all means <pause dur="short"/> don't know what you're saying</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0690">well see smart cars and people doing it like</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0688">pardon?</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0690">there's some smart cars people doing it like</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0687">look they've even got golf buggies to get around terrible terrible</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0689">doesn't look that bad</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0688">I wonder what they're like inside</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0687">these static ones look <trunc>r</trunc>reasonably like acceptable so long as they've got showers and bathrooms they're tiny but these look a bit better than the tents</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0689">they'd be cosy</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0687">there can only be one bedroom can't there?</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0689" trans="overlap">might be two</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0688">I don't know how</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0690">plastic stone on the outside</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0688">oh is there?</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0690">well it's not real stone</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0687">it's not real stone <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1122" who="S0689"><unclear/> I snorted erm Fanta lemon up my nose</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0687">nice</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0688" trans="overlap">that's pleasant</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0689">it wasn't very nice</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0688">god this is a huge resort isn't it?</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0687">yeah I don't think we can get to the beach down here</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0690">you're probably right</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0688">is this a dead end?</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0687">and I think that if we did it would be all those screaming children on inflatables</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0690">what do you want me to do? drive back the way we came?</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0688" trans="overlap">I think we'll have to won't we?</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0689" trans="overlap">oh oh dead bird on no it's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1135" who="S0687"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1136" who="S0689">I was sure that was a dead bird</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0687">let's go and park where we were up there <pause dur="short"/> bloody Nora</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0690">take make your bloody mind up mate</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0687">make your mind up <unclear/></u>
<u n="1140" who="S0689">said he's going this way <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1141" who="S0690">and now he's going that way</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0688">I think he was waving you on actually</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0689">no he said I'm going that way</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0688">oh okay he's from Serbia</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0690">oh right that'll be it then</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0687" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that explains it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1147" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1148" who="S0687"><vocal desc="laugh"/> have you snorted lemon Fanta again? let's have a taste <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1149" who="S0689">you'll have to be quick <unclear/></u>
<u n="1150" who="S0687" trans="overlap">see look <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's a Vauxhall Astra on the right it's just an Opel Astra</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0689">what that?</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0687" trans="overlap">this grey one</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0689">oh right</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0687">do you want <trunc>s</trunc>? you can have one if you want <pause dur="short"/> pardon you</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0689" trans="overlap">oh sorry sorry</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0687">filth to be fair these do look alright it's just all a bit in each other's back pockets isn't it?</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0688">hi-de-hi</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0687"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1159" who="S0689">will you shut up doing that</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0687" trans="overlap">you'd make you'd make friends quickly</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0687">you'd at <trunc>lea</trunc> like you sit up out of bed and someone would be there at your window</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0688"><vocal desc="laugh"/> hello</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0687">good morning <unclear/></u>
<u n="1165" who="S0688">I think they position them so you're not like</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0687" trans="overlap">strategically</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0689">oh that's a nice dog</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0688">what is it?</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0690" trans="overlap">yeah you it's something like call it Centre Parcs and charge a grand for a weekend don't they?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0689">do they?</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0687">are Centre Parcs expensive?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0688">oh yeah they are ridiculous</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0687" trans="overlap">why do people do it then?</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0688">I've no idea because I the the place we <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1176" who="S0687" trans="overlap">it's just like this isn't it?</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0690">we've never stayed at Centre Parcs have we?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0688">I went for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fortieth we had an executive place that was</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0690">oh an executive place</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0688">yeah it was six hundred for the weekend</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0687">per person?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0688">no</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0687">for for how many people?</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0688">well er something like eight of us went</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0689">oh that's alright that</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0687" trans="overlap">oh right that's alright then</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0688">that's what I mean it wasn't so bad and it had a sauna and stuff</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0689">oh</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0687">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0690">in your chalet?</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0688">yeah er well just outside</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0687">that's alright</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0688">you would not have stayed in any of the others though</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0687">were they horrible?</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0688">absolutely would not as we drove on cos everyone goes on about Center Parcs don't they? I was like</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0687">grim</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0688">what is this?</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0687">it's it's just like this isn't it?</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0688">but</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0687">and then there's like a swimming pool and like</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0688" trans="overlap">but the things</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0687" trans="overlap">children's play centres and stuff</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0690" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1205" who="S0688" trans="overlap">things looked mouldy</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0687">right</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0688">they there were like there was oh it no it was awful</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0687">well there's like a <trunc>divis</trunc> there's like a dividing line between <vocal desc="laugh"/> like the upper class in the static caravans and the lower class here in the</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0688">these are just tents</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0690" trans="overlap">but these</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0687">tents</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0690" trans="overlap">that's thirty grand's worth of <unclear/> that</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0687">how many holidays could you go on for thirty grand? you could buy one of them houses that you saw on Ebay for thirty grand</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0688">well yeah</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0687" trans="overlap">they've even got a telly satellite</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0688" trans="overlap">yeah but people <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just bought a caravan <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that an old couple have had and never used and they're both in a home now so son's sold it erm</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0689">well that's what you'll be doing <vocal desc="laugh"/> and <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="1218" who="S0690">and they pitch that for five grand for something?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0688">they no <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> er three and a half and have a new bathroom put in it erm <pause dur="short"/> I think it was I think it was on Ebay at something like four two and she went and had a look at it and said I'll give you three and a half</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0690" trans="overlap">I'll give you three and a half</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0688">it needs a new bathroom er and that cost her she spent five hundred pound on it</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0690">well I suppose that's alright it's gonna</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0688">well she said</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0690" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0688">they'll be there every weekend and</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0690">oh they've they've put it on a site somewhere?</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0688">they've <trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>t</trunc>taken it to a <trunc>gar</trunc> they've put it er well leaving it at the <unclear>more take car for</unclear></u>
<u n="1228" who="S0687" trans="overlap">well it's like</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0690" trans="overlap"><unclear>everything like that</unclear></u>
<u n="1230" who="S0689" trans="overlap">well the thing is</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0687">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s parents last summer they bought erm like one of those that you'd put on the back of your car like you've just said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got and they left it <trunc>som</trunc> they left it at erm where is it in Wales? <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1232" who="S0688">yeah</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0687">they left it there pitched it for the summer and then this year they've bought one of these static ones at the same place but if I thought the whole point of it was you could move it around and go</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0687">different places if you buy a static one there's only so much to see in <anon type="place"/> isn't there?</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0688">mm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0689">well I remember</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0690" trans="overlap">then again if you like it</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0688"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got hers at <anon type="place"/> hasn't she?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0687">mm are we gonna stop and have a look along there?</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0689">do you remember when I went down to <anon type="place"/> to watch Bolton and?</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0687" trans="overlap">is she pregnant? sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1243" who="S0690" trans="overlap">no just fat</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0687">no just fat go on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1245" who="S0689">can I speak <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? or</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0687" trans="overlap">yeah continue</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0689">oh erm when I went down to <anon type="place"/> to watch Bolton we went to one of the caravan parks there you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sister's got one?</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0687">oh has she? oh no</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0689" trans="overlap">and and she was saying that like</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0688">is it her sister?</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0689">yeah and they were selling them and they were like fifty grand and it was like five grand a year to moor it there</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0687">you're joking?</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0689">honestly no</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0687">for a caravan? a static</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0689" trans="overlap">honestly</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0687">or a</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0689" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0687">or a wheelie one?</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0689" trans="overlap">no like it yeah</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0690" trans="overlap">some of those static ones are crazy expensive</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0687">oh</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0689" trans="overlap">yeah and like it it was like static but it had like you could put like you could put it on you know tow bar</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0687" trans="overlap">on a on a <trunc>tr</trunc></u>
<u n="1264" who="S0689" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0687">on a yeah you see them</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0690"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1267" who="S0687" trans="overlap">going up the M6 on like the wide loader things that take up like two lanes on the motorway</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0689">but I was I was shocked about how <trunc>expen</trunc>expensive like they are to like just not not even just to buy just to moor I was like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1269" who="S0687" trans="overlap">thank you that's what I mean once you've spent that much you could have just gone on holiday and stayed in a hotel</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0689">mm</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0687">this is quite nice</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0690">it's okay this innit? well not great but it's alright</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0688">stop here like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1274" who="S0687" trans="overlap">be nice if it was a bit more be nice if it were a bit more secluded</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0688">there's a heron on the end now</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0687">a heron? isn't that a cormorant?</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0688">it' might</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0687">I think it's a cormorant cos it's black <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm almost dead</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
