<text id="SX6D">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:57:54</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Work, moodle</topics>
		<activity>Couple discuss teaching computer software.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0144">right okay so <pause dur="short"/> what are we gonna try and change first?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0024">I need to change this thing that it says two thousand and thirteen I want to edit it so that nobody can see it <pause dur="short"/> can I go on yours to see what I can see as a student of yours?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0024">I'll enrol in yours you enrol in mine and then</u>
<u n="5" who="S0144" trans="overlap">see I don't even know how to do that how do I enrol in yours?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0024">I that that actually I think that might be the first thing we need to do isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> not do this editing we need to change the students</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144" trans="overlap">maybe we should go to the er training sessions <vocal desc="laugh"/> what time is it?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0024">it's at two o'clock that you have to register</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144">two o'clock you have to register?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0024">I can't cos I haven't done the milk</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="12" who="S0024">I'm pretending I know what I'm doing which means <pause dur="short"/> teaching myself <vocal desc="laugh"/> if you go to the training session you can come back and teach me</u>
<u n="13" who="S0144">mm but I remember last year the training session was useless <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't come away with anything</u>
<u n="14" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well if you can't do it it's if we can't do it then it's</u>
<u n="15" who="S0144">I just find it really confusing</u>
<u n="16" who="S0024">it's definitely different it looks easier doesn't it?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144">it <trunc>lo</trunc> yeah it</u>
<u n="18" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well maybe</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144" trans="overlap">looks better than it did last year</u>
<u n="20" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144">but I didn't use Moodle last year</u>
<u n="22" who="S0024">I did a little bit</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I just preferred using it using my email just found it a lot easier</u>
<u n="24" who="S0024">I think once it's one of those things once you know how to use it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0024">it's <pause dur="short"/> oh except my internet's just too slow to be able to do anything do <trunc>y</trunc> oh it's do you think it's cos I've got the proxy on?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144">well I've got a proxy on <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="28" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh I haven't got the proxy on</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144">I've got a proxy on</u>
<u n="30" who="S0024">you've got a proxy on and yours is working faster</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so how how do I get a picture on my home page? <pause dur="short"/> or like a welcome screen or something</u>
<u n="32" who="S0024">yeah well that's yeah we've got to write a welcome message I don't think</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but where</u>
<u n="34" who="S0024">oh god <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> maybe we should go to the</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I haven't got a clue <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0024">we need to go to the training <pause dur="long"/> mm or we need to like watch a few er</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144" trans="overlap">there's a help thing here look</u>
<u n="38" who="S0024">a few Moodle help videos</u>
<u n="39" who="S0144">I'd rather to be honest just learn myself cos sitting there and just watching someone do it yeah you can take notes but <pause dur="short"/> the only way to learn it properly is to do it yourself</u>
<u n="40" who="S0024">participants oh look how many participants I've got <pause dur="short"/> oh where have all my students gone?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144">yeah well they were last year's students</u>
<u n="42" who="S0024">yeah but that's what they were saying you have to delete your last year students <pause dur="short"/> mine have already selected themselves from me because I wasn't there <pause dur="short"/> all the <trunc>partic</trunc></u>
<u n="43" who="S0144" trans="overlap">participants no I think <pause dur="short"/> participants <pause dur="short"/> see I've only got one participant and that's me</u>
<u n="44" who="S0024">oh well it must have just deleted everybody because of the new Moodle and</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> couldn't have known about that cos he</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no but it's still got I think what erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> meant was it's still got the part last year's course is enrolled</u>
<u n="48" who="S0024">no no cos she's asked me before how how do I delete my old students?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0024" trans="overlap">over the years she's like built up loads and loads and loads of students and they're still it says still says that they're enrolled in her</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144">oh really?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0144">okay well we've just got to</u>
<u n="54" who="S0024">well okay</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144" trans="overlap">only got one participant</u>
<u n="56" who="S0024">can I sign up to you? then I can see what yours looks like yeah? go in modules?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0144">oh module</u>
<u n="58" who="S0024">I thought I was signed up to you <pause dur="short"/> that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0144" trans="overlap">core modules <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0024">oh dear this is not right this needs some navigating doesn't it?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0024">erm <pause dur="short"/> okay I'm gonna go back to my home <pause dur="long"/> and I thought I could search you from my home <pause dur="short"/> my er no <pause dur="short"/> how about the site home? the site home</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144">erm my media?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0024">search modules are you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's weird because you can see like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s erm <pause dur="short"/> message but you can't see anybody else er er some people have got it switched on that you have to go on <trunc>t</trunc> you have to register for the module</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0024">before you can see what you've written so we need to do that really <pause dur="long"/> send a message to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> last accessed it <pause dur="short"/> wednesday the fourteenth er</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144">there you go look <pause dur="short"/> oh no that's next year <pause dur="short"/> science pathways <pause dur="short"/> yeah this is it reading and writing in academic context look autumn fourteen fifteen</u>
<u n="70" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144">so that's what's gonna become active next week</u>
<u n="72" who="S0024">yeah erm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0144">then we've got freshers' week</u>
<u n="74" who="S0024">freshers' week</u>
<u n="75" who="S0144" trans="overlap">which is the one</u>
<u n="76" who="S0024">that</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144" trans="overlap">we need to show them erm?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well let's have a look</u>
<u n="79" who="S0144">let's go in that that's the one with all the stuff in isn't it all the er this one the treasure hunt and</u>
<u n="80" who="S0024">what do they win for the reading marathon?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0024">cos I know they're gonna ask me what it is last time it was</u>
<u n="83" who="S0144">oh it was a pile of shit wasn't</u>
<u n="84" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Ipad wasn't it?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0144">oh yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0024">no it was good last time</u>
<u n="87" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh yeah well yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0024">do you mean the prize it or the page you're looking at?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0144">just looking at the page <pause dur="short"/> so where do I need no I need to write all this down I don't look a dickhead in class</u>
<u n="90" who="S0024">no <trunc>exact</trunc> that's why we need to spend some time doing it</u>
<u n="91" who="S0144">well we need to download the</u>
<u n="92" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that's what this week is for really isn't it?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0024">I can't believe that do you remember in in erm <pause dur="short"/> er in the listening <pause dur="short"/> briefing</u>
<u n="95" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0024">listening and speaking briefing and that guy I don't know who he is who is he? he said well surely we need to <trunc>ha</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> if er <pause dur="short"/> if we're changing the examination to a one on one we're gonna have to have knowledge of the topics</u>
<u n="97" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0024">it's like how long have you worked here and done the same book?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0024">what? and <vocal desc="laugh"/> what he said well if you're gonna teach it you're gonna know something you don't need to know really the detail</u>
<u n="101" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it's probably it's</u>
<u n="102" who="S0024">and did you see his face? he was</u>
<u n="103" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="104" who="S0024" trans="overlap">sitting right in front I don't know cos you might have been blocked by somebody in front of you</u>
<u n="105" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0024">he was like no <pause dur="short"/> like shaking his head like no why would I know anything about what I so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0144" trans="overlap">come on it's only based on like two reading articles</u>
<u n="108" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0144">you'd find out what exam you're doing and just read the articles</u>
<u n="110" who="S0024">oh my god</u>
<u n="111" who="S0144" trans="overlap">jesus what a loser <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so well if that's your attitude and he must have been here a lot earlier than us I think so he's already taught the course</u>
<u n="113" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah he's been here he's been here years</u>
<u n="114" who="S0024">so he must know that book inside out</u>
<u n="115" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's good that they've upgraded all the wi-fi in the classes so</u>
<u n="116" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0144">students can all bring their laptops now</u>
<u n="118" who="S0024">yeah how are you gonna <pause dur="short"/> how are you gonna do that?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0144">well it depends on the class doesn't it? <pause dur="short"/> but you can tell them</u>
<u n="120" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I need</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144" trans="overlap">to bring them they don't have to have them out every lesson</u>
<u n="122" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144">did I press record on this?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0024">it is hard to do erm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0024">it's hard to suddenly change like to everybody having laptops in front of them doing work</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0024">it's I find that kind of class really hard to prepare for like and how it's gonna go and</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it kind of makes it may be harder for group work kind of creates barriers between people</u>
<u n="130" who="S0024">what physical barriers?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0144">well yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144">and <pause dur="short"/> you kind of focus more on your computer don't you? rather than who's sitting next to you</u>
<u n="134" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0144">Chinese students <vocal desc="laugh"/> kind of do that anyway <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but it would be good for when we're later in the writing course when they're like correcting each other's work <pause dur="short"/> that would be quite good cos they'll be able to edit it actually on the <pause dur="short"/> computer <pause dur="short"/> and they have a record of there rather than</u>
<u n="136" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what do actually all the writing tasks on a computer?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0144">why not? well oh</u>
<u n="138" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well because their exam is handwritten</u>
<u n="139" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="140" who="S0024">the exam is handwritten and half of them need to practice their handwriting cos you can't if you can't read it</u>
<u n="141" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah and their spelling as well if there's spell you know</u>
<u n="142" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0144">auto correct or something</u>
<u n="144" who="S0024">unless they've got unless you can find a programme on the internet you know just like a <pause dur="short"/> not a Photoshop you know where <pause dur="short"/> you can take a photo of your work send it to <trunc>so</trunc> <trunc>t</trunc> send it to your friend next to you on email and you can draw all over it but then</u>
<u n="145" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0024">what's the point?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0024">then you're doing exactly the same as using a pen</u>
<u n="149" who="S0144">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0024">mm anyway where are we? where did you say we'll <trunc>g</trunc> gotta go? freshers' week?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0024">I've got to get my computer fixed too this week I need to go</u>
<u n="153" who="S0144" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0024">well I need to go in and they're <pause dur="short"/> I need to <pause dur="short"/> re back it all up again because there's a few extra things and</u>
<u n="155" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="156" who="S0024">and then get the what a new Windows?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0024">but I like my Windows now <pause dur="short"/> I want to keep my touch screen</u>
<u n="159" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0024">I bought it I love my touch screen</u>
<u n="161" who="S0144">yeah it is good</u>
<u n="162" who="S0024">I bought it for the touch screen be a bit silly if I go revert to an old Windows and then</u>
<u n="163" who="S0144">yeah well if you've got used to Windows 8 and you you wanna and</u>
<u n="164" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well I'm still I've still got to learn a lot about it but I basically use it as a desktop anyway</u>
<u n="165" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0024">I don't er I I hardly ever go into the other one but I know</u>
<u n="167" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0024">but I have organised my little app things</u>
<u n="169" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0024">and I thought maybe I could download some more apps I want to download that Chinese one because it's a bigger screen</u>
<u n="171" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0024">and then I really do need the touch screen</u>
<u n="173" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> we'll go in there and beg them to <pause dur="short"/> do it say look you put it on it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't get a <unclear>cracked</unclear> version</u>
<u n="174" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0144">can't you just give me the code?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0024">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know if they've got it because they're not updating the university to</u>
<u n="177" who="S0144">Windows 8</u>
<u n="178" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0144">it's Windows 8 is</u>
<u n="180" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they haven't</u>
<u n="181" who="S0144">not very user-friendly</u>
<u n="182" who="S0024">well haven't Windows got a new Windows? <pause dur="short"/> isn't there another one?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0024">nine?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0144">don't think so</u>
<u n="186" who="S0024">but how come to see any <trunc>pre</trunc> preliminary year freshers' week <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> freshers' week tutor feedback not available unless you get a particular score in tutor feedback what does that mean?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0024">what does it mean?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0144">I have no idea</u>
<u n="190" who="S0024">oh no</u>
<u n="191" who="S0144">but this is the same look you've got a freshers' week programme</u>
<u n="192" who="S0024">yeah but they're gonna read that and say where's my tutor feedback? well</u>
<u n="193" who="S0144"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0024">and then I wrote some notes from the meeting yesterday on here</u>
<u n="195" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well we need to go and download this freshers' booklet thing don't we?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0024">yeah and print it out I need to print out a copy</u>
<u n="197" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I'll do that tomorrow</u>
<u n="198" who="S0024">yeah yeah that would be good</u>
<u n="199" who="S0144">cos I'll go in and</u>
<u n="200" who="S0024" trans="overlap">let's write let's write down a list of jobs we need <pause dur="short"/> cos yeah I want to have a look I've got the old one <pause dur="short"/> they said there's not that many chances</u>
<u n="201" who="S0144">let's have a look in the self-access centre</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024">mm what's in there?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">this is where we're gonna refer students <pause dur="short"/> for extra <pause dur="short"/> practice</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024" trans="overlap">catch up keep up move ahead <pause dur="long"/> what was I looking for? oh my notes from the meeting right <pause dur="short"/> I took notes on my phone for the first time ever it's good this</u>
<u n="205" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0024">save me having loads of <trunc>piece</trunc> show students SAC resources okay go</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144">okay <pause dur="short"/> so you've got guide to the SAC so we need to just memorise a little blurb of what the SAC does</u>
<u n="208" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144">language and study skills advising</u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144">so basically one to one help <pause dur="long"/> erm and then he said we've got this erm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024">hang on go back to that one <pause dur="short"/> I'm kind of staring at it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0024">but not really taking it in</u>
<u n="215" who="S0144">shall I click on it?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0024">make an an appointment here er languages yeah you said that one</u>
<u n="217" who="S0144" trans="overlap">is is that what he showed us in the meeting where we</u>
<u n="218" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0144" trans="overlap">book our appointment for students?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0024">SAC erm <pause dur="short"/> so they have to book an appointment they can't just turn up anymore? didn't last year they just turn up?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0144">it says make an appointment</u>
<u n="222" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh or drop in</u>
<u n="223" who="S0144" trans="overlap">or drop in</u>
<u n="224" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="225" who="S0144">but when the exams come round</u>
<u n="226" who="S0024">TB three two five</u>
<u n="227" who="S0144" trans="overlap">every everyone wants to go so they need they're gonna need to <pause dur="short"/> do that</u>
<u n="228" who="S0024">I <pause dur="short"/> I want to go there and have a look</u>
<u n="229" who="S0144">at the SAC?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0024">yeah in the library</u>
<u n="231" who="S0144">yeah well</u>
<u n="232" who="S0024" trans="overlap">maybe we</u>
<u n="233" who="S0144" trans="overlap">let's do that tomorrow as well</u>
<u n="234" who="S0024" trans="overlap">could do that tomorrow can we? isn't I don't wanna get distracted by other people saying let's have a coffee</u>
<u n="235" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0024">in the coffee shop but</u>
<u n="237" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no it's</u>
<u n="238" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I wanna go and <trunc>s</trunc> and check out the library and the SAC and go to this meeting we've got tomorrow</u>
<u n="239" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay how do I get this across?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0024">mm it looks a bit <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="241" who="S0144">language skills resources</u>
<u n="242" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0144">wanna have a look at that?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0144">there's loads of stuff here <pause dur="long"/> so writing reading listening speaking vocab self-study exams <pause dur="short"/> shall we just take look at one of them?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0144">the listening one</u>
<u n="248" who="S0024">did you go on this last year?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0144">no this was all different</u>
<u n="250" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0144">I don't think they had it like this <pause dur="short"/> this is much better</u>
<u n="252" who="S0024" trans="overlap">this is brilliant they've done they've done a good job haven't they?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> listening resources okay so you've got all these</u>
<u n="254" who="S0024">wow</u>
<u n="255" who="S0144">that's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> practice</u>
<u n="256" who="S0024">TED <pause dur="short"/> tedded <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0144">TED-Ed</u>
<u n="258" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought it was like new vocabulary you've been tedded</u>
<u n="259" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> eAP talk it okay so let's do those right</u>
<u n="260" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that's the one that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says is amazing</u>
<u n="261" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I always used to send them to that</u>
<u n="262" who="S0024">did you? <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="263" who="S0144">shall we have a look?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah show me</u>
<u n="265" who="S0144">so it's EAP <anon type="place"/> let me just copy</u>
<u n="266" who="S0024" trans="overlap">EAP</u>
<u n="267" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that password <pause dur="short"/> but this is just <trunc>list</trunc> is EAP toolkit just listening?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0024">no I thought it was more</u>
<u n="269" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was everything forbidden great</u>
<u n="270" who="S0024">oh you have to be on campus for that</u>
<u n="271" who="S0144">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> so there's all those things there's so much material for them to do <pause dur="short"/> there's so many tests</u>
<u n="272" who="S0024" trans="overlap">see I I wanna get I need to spend some time</u>
<u n="273" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I mean jesus man when I was at uni</u>
<u n="274" who="S0024">there was nothing</u>
<u n="275" who="S0144">I had nothing yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0144">okay so there's all of that</u>
<u n="278" who="S0024" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="279" who="S0144">there's loads of stuff there</u>
<u n="280" who="S0024" trans="overlap">right my second note show show students SAC resources okay</u>
<u n="281" who="S0144">hang on <trunc>s</trunc> still got another load to look at here</u>
<u n="282" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="283" who="S0144">it's not just those three there's hundreds <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="284" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="285" who="S0144" trans="overlap">SAC workshops</u>
<u n="286" who="S0024">weekly workshops who teaches those?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> key academic and study skills shall we have a look?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0144">I think last year wasn't</u>
<u n="290" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they must</u>
<u n="291" who="S0144">didn't they ask people like if you want to</u>
<u n="292" who="S0024" trans="overlap">to do much</u>
<u n="293" who="S0144" trans="overlap">do one?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0144">so I might do one this year</u>
<u n="296" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0144">just just to erm put it on my PDPR</u>
<u n="298" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0144">cos I'm struggling of things to think of I</u>
<u n="300" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah why not? we need to do <trunc>som</trunc> something</u>
<u n="301" who="S0144" trans="overlap">effective study strategies</u>
<u n="302" who="S0024">what would you do yours on?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0144">improving your reading <pause dur="short"/> sentence taking notes <pause dur="short"/> improving your listening <pause dur="short"/> reading close up effective study strategies vocabulary speaking fluency proofreading <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> well that's good isn't it?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0024">so they've got all the</u>
<u n="305" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so I</u>
<u n="306" who="S0024">workshops for this term have they?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0144">well all the material is there I don't know if they've got someone to teach it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0024">wow <pause dur="short"/> they must have worked some people</u>
<u n="309" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="310" who="S0024" trans="overlap">have worked really hard over summer have they?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0144">well I think this new Moodle just makes it a bit clearer doesn't it?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0144">and they've tied it together a bit more <pause dur="short"/> more listening and reading resources so what's the difference between that before? <pause dur="short"/> and would be</u>
<u n="314" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what was the other one called?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0144">it was EAP toolkit</u>
<u n="316" who="S0024">oh okay well let's</u>
<u n="317" who="S0144">come on events there's the EAP toolkit</u>
<u n="318" who="S0024">just general</u>
<u n="319" who="S0144">ET yeah shall I have a look how that's different to the</u>
<u n="320" who="S0024">I don't think you can access it without the</u>
<u n="321" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no but does it split into more than just listening? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0024">thirty to forty minutes <pause dur="short"/> of learning activity around a particular learning point <pause dur="short"/> doesn't say does it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0144">so</u>
<u n="324" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you have to go right the way in</u>
<u n="325" who="S0144">we'll have to have a look</u>
<u n="326" who="S0024" trans="overlap">to find out</u>
<u n="327" who="S0144" trans="overlap">at those <pause dur="short"/> cos you could spend a whole lesson just talking about this</u>
<u n="328" who="S0024" trans="overlap">principal or principle</u>
<u n="329" who="S0144">couldn't you?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0144">before you'd get familiar with it</u>
<u n="332" who="S0024">well if they've all got wi-fi in their computers they can all sit there and really have a look at it</u>
<u n="333" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0024">they need time don't they?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0144">yeah er I'd give them like half an hour just <pause dur="short"/> half an hour just have a look through some of these and get familiar with them</u>
<u n="336" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't need a quiz or anything do they?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="338" who="S0024">no they're adults</u>
<u n="339" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I mean they well they don't have to do it in class but it will make them do it wouldn't it and they won't <pause dur="short"/> half of them wouldn't do it if you just say do it in your own time</u>
<u n="340" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0144">cos I remember last year</u>
<u n="342" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="343" who="S0144">the first week <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of a lot of the time was wasted</u>
<u n="344" who="S0024">getting <pause dur="short"/> them to log in and stuff</u>
<u n="345" who="S0144">just</u>
<u n="346" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah well and then when I got to whoever did the freshers' week of my students last year they didn't get them to sign up to <pause dur="short"/> to the to the <unclear>arwac</unclear> to the <unclear>alsac</unclear> I <trunc>th</trunc> <trunc>go</trunc> you've got</u>
<u n="347" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I mean that that was</u>
<u n="348" who="S0024" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0144">thrust down our throats to do that</u>
<u n="350" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0144">look at all this stuff</u>
<u n="352" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I'm sure I still had students that weren't signed to <unclear>ning</unclear> no no no not to <unclear>arwac</unclear> and <unclear>owac</unclear> <unclear>alsac</unclear> to to <trunc>m</trunc> to <unclear>min</unclear> to <unclear>mun</unclear> oh no</u>
<u n="353" who="S0144">no professional</u>
<u n="354" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I'm thinking of a different university</u>
<u n="355" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="356" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I think I'm thinking of a different university</u>
<u n="357" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've got National Geographic</u>
<u n="358" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">got signed up to</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024">what's this you're on?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0144" trans="overlap">all these were it's the same thing they're all just different magazines</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024">wow</u>
<u n="363" who="S0144">pulse on the planet</u>
<u n="364" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I bet</u>
<u n="365" who="S0144">two minute sound portraits of planet earth nature and science <pause dur="short"/> so before we were just saying yeah go and <trunc>t</trunc> talk to practitioners <vocal desc="laugh"/> speaking er</u>
<u n="366" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0144" trans="overlap">listening sorry <pause dur="short"/> they've got oh that's good they've put a lot more on here <pause dur="short"/> or <pause dur="short"/> brilliant that's great</u>
<u n="368" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0144">okay I mean that will take ages in class to get through all that <pause dur="short"/> that's long well or we gonna have to get through this</u>
<u n="370" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what you're just gonna have to show them and let them explore it aren't you?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well well we need to look at the actual <trunc>sch</trunc> the timetable don't we?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0024">okay shall we have a look at freshers' week?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0144">erm hang on</u>
<u n="374" who="S0024">oh oh you <trunc>were</trunc></u>
<u n="375" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I don't wanna jump around</u>
<u n="376" who="S0024">no I thought you'd finished sorry</u>
<u n="377" who="S0144">was that <pause dur="short"/> right so that's the SAC part of that of the freshers' week thing yeah?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="379" who="S0144">we've also got to tell them about the freshers' week programme which is here</u>
<u n="380" who="S0024">but <pause dur="short"/> oh the programme <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0144">session one getting to know you <pause dur="long"/> basically we'll just introduce <trunc>every</trunc> them all to that stuff in there</u>
<u n="382" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0024">library <trunc>tre</trunc></u>
<u n="385" who="S0144" trans="overlap">introduction to Moodle toolkits</u>
<u n="386" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0144">section two <pause dur="short"/> writing writing emails dictionaries reading</u>
<u n="388" who="S0024">oh yeah I remember they none of them could write an email</u>
<u n="389" who="S0144">well none of them could by the end of the year either <vocal desc="laugh"/> they were useless</u>
<u n="390" who="S0024">well they're just not polite enough and like and no nothing in the subject heading and stuff like that wasn't it <pause dur="long"/> session six getting to know your LSAT tutor now this really confused me they didn't they changed something and they didn't seem to know what I thought they said that</u>
<u n="391" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0024">there was only one teacher</u>
<u n="393" who="S0144">there's one teacher <pause dur="short"/> cos last semester we had to split it didn't we or last year we had to split it</u>
<u n="394" who="S0024">yeah what happened? I can't <trunc>remem</trunc></u>
<u n="395" who="S0144" trans="overlap">because there was two introduction things one for the <unclear>arwac</unclear> teacher and one for the <unclear>alsac</unclear> teacher <pause dur="short"/> erm but one but the two activities weren't assigned to a particular class so there was a danger that you would both do the same introduction in class so you have to liaise with the other teacher just to find out what one they were doing</u>
<u n="396" who="S0024">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="397" who="S0144">but he said we're not doing that this year <pause dur="short"/> we're just teaching one class</u>
<u n="398" who="S0024">then why did it say session six getting to know your LSAT teacher?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="400" who="S0024">mm?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> treasure hand graded reader okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0024">eight sessions</u>
<u n="403" who="S0144">mm?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0024">eight sessions in all</u>
<u n="405" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah we're teaching what sixteen hours</u>
<u n="406" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0144">next week</u>
<u n="408" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0144">which is just normal isn't it?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0024">yeah normally eighteen hours</u>
<u n="411" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="412" who="S0024">isn't it eighteen hours eighteen students?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0144">sixteen hours <pause dur="short"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0024">no it's eighteen hours</u>
<u n="415" who="S0144">eighteen really?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0024">yeah do you remember last term I <trunc>ev</trunc> I was on a fifteen hour one?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="418" who="S0024" trans="overlap">cos I was three hours down</u>
<u n="419" who="S0144">eighteen hours okay</u>
<u n="420" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0144">we need to meet our personal tutor groups as well don't know when that's gonna happen</u>
<u n="422" who="S0024">that's not next week is it?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="long"/> I remember it as in the first week last year</u>
<u n="424" who="S0024">table of contents instructions for freshers' week session two introduction to Moodle <pause dur="short"/> so if I go here will it give me the</u>
<u n="425" who="S0144">go where?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0024"><trunc>i</trunc> if I go to a session one is this the actual <unclear/> we're using?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0144">where's session one?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0024">it was just on the left hand box</u>
<u n="429" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0024"><unclear/> oh oh I was still in the freshers' week programme <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0144">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0024">next week you will be begin your semester reading and writing in academic contexts and listening and speaking in academic contexts <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0144">yeah so it doesn't say oh here you go win Amazon book tokens worth tally a total of a thousand RMB</u>
<u n="434" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="435" who="S0144">that's for the reading marathon yeah?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0144">so what's that a hundred pounds? <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="438" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm hang on <pause dur="short"/> ah no that's what's that? the three people who submit the greatest number of worksheets will win tokens worth twenty pounds</u>
<u n="440" who="S0024">oh I see</u>
<u n="441" who="S0144">and the four runners up will get ten pounds each</u>
<u n="442" who="S0024">oh that's why I thought that total that word total is</u>
<u n="443" who="S0144">that's a bit <pause dur="short"/> you can't even buy a book for twenty <pause dur="short"/> pounds</u>
<u n="444" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0144">or you can download them now I suppose <pause dur="short"/> bit cheaper</u>
<u n="446" who="S0024">evening lectures</u>
<u n="447" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> the academic support unit now I get confused with the academic support unit is that for first year students or is that the one for?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no you see I don't know why they even tell</u>
<u n="449" who="S0144" trans="overlap">cos that got so confusing last year</u>
<u n="450" who="S0024" trans="overlap">the students about it I'm sure when we had our personal tutor presentation on the Powerpoint it said you can go to the academic support unit and then all of the students went there and we all got do you remember?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0024">we got that email saying why on earth did <trunc>ev</trunc> all of you <pause dur="short"/> send them here? it was because</u>
<u n="453" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0024">I'm sure it was on the we have to check the tutor erm Powerpoint won't we?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0024">yeah why are they even told about it</u>
<u n="457" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no I don't know</u>
<u n="458" who="S0024" trans="overlap">if they're not to go there?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0144">I dunno</u>
<u n="460" who="S0024">I think they're allowed to go there for their final <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I what is what do we tell them?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah this so this is what the students get isn't it in the class like so this is what he said by bringing in their computers like this isn't gonna be printed so this is what the students are gonna be seeing in class <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0024">oh right so they can bring in their computers and you can just</u>
<u n="463" who="S0144" trans="overlap">they can go yeah you just</u>
<u n="464" who="S0024">take them up as</u>
<u n="465" who="S0144" trans="overlap">go through here</u>
<u n="466" who="S0024">unless there's a few activities you want to print out</u>
<u n="467" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="468" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are you hungry? are you hungry? hello</u>
<u n="469" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0024">hello mm mm I'll do it here</u>
<u n="471" who="S0144">yeah? okay</u>
<u n="472" who="S0024">yeah you can keep showing me</u>
<u n="473" who="S0144">I might turn that off now</u>
<u n="474" who="S0024">no you just keep showing me what erm what we're doing</u>
<u n="475" who="S0144">are you hungry? mm?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0024"><shift new="singing"/> are you hungry <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0144">dinner time</u>
<u n="478" who="S0024"><shift new="singing"/> little girl <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0144">right erm so evening lectures is the fourth part <pause dur="short"/> introduction to information services is the fifth part</u>
<u n="480" who="S0024" trans="overlap">are you sure this is the same as the Powerpoints yeah?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0144">erm pretty sure I'm sure that's what he said</u>
<u n="482" who="S0024">right okay</u>
<u n="483" who="S0144">ten runs so that's the same and then we had those classroom rules which is just patronising</u>
<u n="484" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what's this? we'll call you <trunc>st</trunc> your tutor will call you stupid what's that? what do you think complete the questionnaire on following rules</u>
<u n="485" who="S0144">yeah yeah it's class rules</u>
<u n="486" who="S0024">oh <trunc>th</trunc> yeah but it's done from problems people have had oh it's okay oh it's okay</u>
<u n="487" who="S0144">right so that's session one and he said we don't have to do these in the same order</u>
<u n="488" who="S0024">are you listening?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0144">you can do them in any order</u>
<u n="490" who="S0024">yeah that was good everything became a bit more flexible didn't it?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0024">and yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0144" trans="overlap">introduction to Moodle and toolkit so this is where we get them to self enrol <pause dur="short"/> into our Moodle <pause dur="short"/> areas and we look at the EAP toolkit</u>
<u n="494" who="S0024">okay yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0144">don't know how that's gonna take two hours <pause dur="short"/> login's</u>
<u n="496" who="S0024">we've got get to know you <shift new="singing"/> getting to know you <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0144">yeah but that would be done in the first one wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0024">yeah but well er it's probably a two hour session that's what they said</u>
<u n="499" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0024">like you might not have one hour you might do but you</u>
<u n="501" who="S0144">I suppose with the first week I mean if they've done everything just let them go early <pause dur="short"/> mm? <pause dur="short"/> there's no point</u>
<u n="502" who="S0024">oh <event desc="sound of baby"/> yeah but you've got to remember that the first week is due for discipline and <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of baby"/> oh what's the matter? alright?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0144">oi are you too interested in our conversation? it's not very interesting</u>
<u n="504" who="S0024">no it's not <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0144">eh?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0024">we're talking about professors and things</u>
<u n="507" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="508" who="S0024">oh okay you settle down now</u>
<u n="509" who="S0144">EAP toolkit okay self-study task</u>
<u n="510" who="S0024">are you just? <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of baby"/> why are you being so funny?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0144">so there's a self-study task here for thirty minutes I don't know if that's to be done in class</u>
<u n="512" who="S0024">what what is it? what do they say?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0144">just says log on to EAP toolkit choose one of the skills areas you'd like to improve spend at least thirty minutes doing some of the <unclear>exercises</unclear></u>
<u n="514" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh no self-study's at home</u>
<u n="515" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0144">it's not self-study in class? <event desc="sound of baby"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of baby"/> got no milk?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0024">yeah it's just she's got to persevere a little bit at the beginning <unclear>could do</unclear></u>
<u n="519" who="S0144">go on get stuck in <pause dur="short"/> number three <pause dur="long"/> academic skills writing by the end of this fifty minute session?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0024">yeah two lots of fifty minute sessions</u>
<u n="521" who="S0144">oh so we do both of those? oh okay I was gonna say</u>
<u n="522" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well yeah a double</u>
<u n="523" who="S0144">so it's four classes?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0024">yeah basically</u>
<u n="525" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but then we've gotta double that with another class yeah?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0144">okay so this one's differences between academic and non academic writing</u>
<u n="528" who="S0024">fine okay</u>
<u n="529" who="S0144">some online resources <pause dur="short"/> academic synonyms oh I remember doing this it's the same as last year isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> write a paragraph <vocal desc="laugh"/> what? er <pause dur="short"/> and then some homework okay that's fifty minutes</u>
<u n="530" who="S0024">you have to look at those paragraphs</u>
<u n="531" who="S0144">no bugger that</u>
<u n="532" who="S0024">well no they need they need feedback though if they're gonna do any writing</u>
<u n="533" who="S0144">yeah peer er correction</u>
<u n="534" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I need a <trunc>pr</trunc> you know what I need? I need a proper peer er peer correction table</u>
<u n="535" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0024">you know er a proper structure like <vocal desc="misc"/> I'm always this week you have a look at <vocal desc="misc"/> erm sentence structure</u>
<u n="537" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0024">and then the next time I'm like right have a look at this like different focuses</u>
<u n="539" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0024">have a look at their academic vocabulary and tell me what you think but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know they always seem to <pause dur="short"/> they never seem to do it properly</u>
<u n="541" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="542" who="S0024">then I say write you've gotta write at least one comment</u>
<u n="543" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0024">and they just put very good or something</u>
<u n="545" who="S0144">so then session four's about writing emails at university</u>
<u n="546" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0144">er salutations sign offs all that kind of stuff <pause dur="short"/> blah blah blah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0024">blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0144">so the content of emails</u>
<u n="550" who="S0024">do you want to do some blah blah blahs?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0144">looking at</u>
<u n="552" who="S0024" trans="overlap">blah blah blah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0144" trans="overlap">silly mistakes <pause dur="long"/> basically write us an email okay easy <pause dur="short"/> don't know how that's gonna take</u>
<u n="554" who="S0024">come on</u>
<u n="555" who="S0144">fifty minutes either <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="556" who="S0024">so this week and next we er we've got to do as much stuff to just to just to get ready for the year basically haven't we?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0144">yeah and session five dictionaries? by the end of this ten minute session?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0024">ten minute session? <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0144">oh okay it's split so dictionary work <pause dur="short"/> ten minutes</u>
<u n="560" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="561" who="S0144">and then by the end of this forty minute session <pause dur="short"/> sAC and that reading <trunc>spee</trunc> er speed reading test</u>
<u n="562" who="S0024">oh speed reading <vocal desc="misc"/> speed reading</u>
<u n="563" who="S0144">and then some reading comprehension <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0024"><event desc="sound of baby"/> <pause dur="short"/> alright you alright?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0144">just some more information about reading basically</u>
<u n="566" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="567" who="S0144">session six <pause dur="short"/> think it's fairly easy <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="568" who="S0024">but it is there's not much many changes from last year</u>
<u n="569" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> session six thirty minutes <pause dur="short"/> just telling them about the RSAC <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0024">you alright?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0144">and the exam and everything</u>
<u n="572" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she wants to listen to you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0144">is that why she's not?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0024" trans="overlap">she just keeps turning around and looking at you</u>
<u n="575" who="S0144">is that why she's not eating?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0024">she is eating but she just every so often wants to look at you</u>
<u n="577" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0024">check you're still there is he still there?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0024">yes yes he's still there look</u>
<u n="581" who="S0144">hello <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="582" who="S0024">he's still there</u>
<u n="583" who="S0144">are you alright? is that nice today? mm? <pause dur="short"/> yeah? go on then finish <pause dur="short"/> finish your dinner are you having a little break? mm? <pause dur="short"/> go on it's gonna get cold</u>
<u n="584" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s nipple that is not your dinner <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0024">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I'm getting cold don't leave me out</u>
<u n="587" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> tongue twisters <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0024">oh they were quite fun weren't they?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0024">but I I'm useless</u>
<u n="591" who="S0144" trans="overlap">they only take ten minutes though</u>
<u n="592" who="S0024" trans="overlap">at those kind of things like I'd rush through them I don't know why but they actually really enjoy them</u>
<u n="593" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0024">but I well I don't know why I rush through things like that and like oh here's some tongue twisters let's practice them de de de de de de and er they they enjoy them</u>
<u n="595" who="S0144">and time management thirty minutes <pause dur="short"/> some questions <pause dur="short"/> discussion <pause dur="short"/> er giving these things priority</u>
<u n="596" who="S0024">oh cos they had a struggle getting just becoming adapted to university life basically</u>
<u n="597" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0024">that's why <pause dur="short"/> they have to think about their health because er otherwise they study too hard</u>
<u n="599" who="S0144">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0024">make sure you do some sports they have to do sport don't they?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh no and then they have to make that stupid plan in your in their diary</u>
<u n="602" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="603" who="S0144">remember that?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0024">I think that's one of the obligatory activities isn't it?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0144">is it?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0024">I think so I'll have to check</u>
<u n="607" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that's so patronising write a diary for tomorrow to <pause dur="short"/> showing you're what you're gonna do well I mean what?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0024">yeah but didn't you say they were playing what in the university grounds the other day? what did you say they were playing? that</u>
<u n="609" who="S0144">stuck in the mud</u>
<u n="610" who="S0024">stuck in the mud well</u>
<u n="611" who="S0144">yeah but they're eighteen</u>
<u n="612" who="S0024">yeah I know well if they're playing stuck in the mud as a warm up game</u>
<u n="613" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0024">at university to get to know you then er</u>
<u n="615" who="S0144">yeah but there's gonna be a lot of foreign students in here as well aren't there? <pause dur="short"/> they're just gonna look at that and go what the hell is that? <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0024" trans="overlap">thing is hang on go back to that timetable</u>
<u n="617" who="S0144">study groups yeah?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0024">like what does it say? plan your day tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> okay well <trunc>l</trunc> that's not too bad if they have a look what <pause dur="short"/> what's there</u>
<u n="619" who="S0144">it's I dunno</u>
<u n="620" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I dunno</u>
<u n="621" who="S0144">I just think that's quite insulting <pause dur="short"/> be embarrassed teaching that <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> autonomy study groups blah blah blah some questions discussions <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty much the same I think from what I remember <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0024">I remember most of them didn't do that timetable did they?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> and last one fifty minutes using the book <pause dur="short"/> looking at some online materials</u>
<u n="624" who="S0024">we're introducing the book before term starts?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0144">so they need to get their books which they need to pick up don't they? from the office <pause dur="short"/> discussion</u>
<u n="628" who="S0024">I think I need to go in a bit of a quiet room for her cos erm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0144">is she gonna go to sleep?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0024">no she's just <pause dur="short"/> she just wants to look at you</u>
<u n="631" who="S0144">ah you love daddy er? you just wanna look at me oh that</u>
<u n="632" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0144">cradle cap's looking a bit disgusting isn't it?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0024">well it's coming off it's coming off in patches that's why</u>
<u n="635" who="S0144">oh <pause dur="short"/> you don't care though do you?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0024">it's gonna look lovely when it's off isn't it? it's gonna her head will look</u>
<u n="637" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0024">completely different mm?</u>
<u n="639" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="640" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="641" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="642" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0024"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="644" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="645" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0024"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="647" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0024"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="649" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did she eat two?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0024">bye a little bit</u>
<u n="653" who="S0144">yeah bye</u>
<u n="654" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">do you want some more? some more?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0024" whoConfidence="low">do you want some more?</u>
<u n="656" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">bye bye</u>
<u n="657" who="S0024">bye bye</u>
<u n="658" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0024">oh she'll come back <pause dur="short"/> right right what else do we have to do by the end of the day? let's get cracking so that's basically all of the freshers' week you've just gone through with me yeah?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0144">yeah just this last one some listening yeah that's basically</u>
<u n="661" who="S0024" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="662" who="S0144">okay shall we</u>
<u n="663" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah so we've got to make our Moodle pages</u>
<u n="664" who="S0144">well how do we do that? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0024">I dunno one of us has to figure it out and then do the other because the meeting's</u>
<u n="666" who="S0144" trans="overlap">navigation my home <pause dur="short"/> I guess that's a good place to start</u>
<u n="667" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah that's coming up on my home customise this page</u>
<u n="668" who="S0144">oh where's it say that?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0024">right there <pause dur="short"/> welcome to new Moodle customise are you in China or Malaysia?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0144">where does it say that?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0024" trans="overlap">more improvements to follow soon to make Moodle even faster</u>
<u n="672" who="S0144">oh here</u>
<u n="673" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0144">oh er?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh yeah customise page</u>
<u n="676" who="S0144">customise this page okay</u>
<u n="677" who="S0024">no <unclear/> modules to display show them all <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> is that that's all it says</u>
<u n="678" who="S0144">what is that it?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0024" trans="overlap">my perfect <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> upcoming events <pause dur="short"/> moodle contents <pause dur="short"/> reset my home page <pause dur="short"/> I don't want it to go on default I want to do home page <pause dur="short"/> actions can <trunc>s</trunc> no <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="680" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0024">I don't know</u>
<u n="682" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think you'd need to go into that wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0024">okay <pause dur="long"/> and then we need to</u>
<u n="684" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and that's</u>
<u n="685" who="S0024">edit it</u>
<u n="686" who="S0144">that's gonna be the page that the students go to</u>
<u n="687" who="S0024">right</u>
<u n="688" who="S0144">and then</u>
<u n="689" who="S0024">see you don't want that <unclear>arwac</unclear> on there I said I was going</u>
<u n="690" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no I can edit it here look <pause dur="short"/> delete</u>
<u n="691" who="S0024">no you don't want to delete it because you'll need it later you'll need the same activity what you need to delete is erm the answers that they gave</u>
<u n="692" who="S0144">what answers?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0024">well they all typed in their their websites that they researched didn't they? I'm getting bitten to smithereens in here <pause dur="short"/> look I'm just scratching there's some</u>
<u n="694" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah there's</u>
<u n="695" who="S0024" trans="overlap">there must be some mosquitos under your desk</u>
<u n="696" who="S0144">yeah there is</u>
<u n="697" who="S0024"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh why do you invite me in here?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0024">I just know I've got loads of bites</u>
<u n="700" who="S0144">cos I knew they'd go for you instead of me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="701" who="S0024">oi <pause dur="short"/> oi where are they?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0144">that's alright they're all full up now <pause dur="short"/> so where does this one <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't it be easier just to delete it and then er add an activity?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> module</u>
<u n="704" who="S0144">so that's what we need the forum is that the thing that we need to set up?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0144">is that what this was?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0024">oh hang on I've got hang on where's my notes? <pause dur="short"/> enrolment methods self enrol to remove old students</u>
<u n="708" who="S0144">well they're all removed</u>
<u n="709" who="S0024">mm oh I went to <pause dur="short"/> participants I didn't go to <pause dur="short"/> enrolment</u>
<u n="710" who="S0144">where's that?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0024">hang on give individual <trunc>pron</trunc> pronunciation feedback by week five essays see Moodle page if students need a referral weak students go to Moodle to refer for any problems on Moodle need a forum for activity next week <pause dur="short"/> make Moodle nice student no Moodle <pause dur="short"/> centre e-learning support</u>
<u n="712" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="713" who="S0024">that's it that's that's that's basically it for the <pause dur="short"/> for the meetings <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="714" who="S0144">edit profile maybe up here in the top right hand corner <pause dur="short"/> where it's got your name and a drop down</u>
<u n="715" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="716" who="S0144">box</u>
<u n="717" who="S0024">oh yeah oh did turn a <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>tur</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you've got your name up there my name doesn't come up</u>
<u n="718" who="S0144">yeah it's got my name <pause dur="short"/> do bi di do bi do do</u>
<u n="719" who="S0024">where's that?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0144">description is that where I put the</u>
<u n="721" who="S0024">view profile did you edit <trunc>prof</trunc> edit profile?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="723" who="S0024">what did you do?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0144">oh yeah edit profile</u>
<u n="725" who="S0024"><trunc>mo</trunc> <trunc>par</trunc> ow ow shh that's a massive bite from the little <pause dur="short"/> oh I hate those</u>
<u n="726" who="S0144">ah use a picture here look</u>
<u n="727" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="728" who="S0144">interests optional</u>
<u n="729" who="S0024">are you putting a picture on?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0144">so this description is that what like the welcome screen or something?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah I er can must be hello yeah I don't know I don't want it to sound too kiddy like I read <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s it was just hello welcome to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> my name is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I'm your <unclear/> <trunc>tea</trunc> you know tutor don't know what put what are you gonna hey that's why I wanted to look at some other people's but like</u>
<u n="732" who="S0144">erm well I need a picture <pause dur="short"/> what about this one with me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0024">oh yeah you could do yeah put <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on it <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> ah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0144">oops</u>
<u n="735" who="S0024"><anon type="place"/> I'm sure my dad gave me loads of <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> pictures didn't he? <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure I just bunged them in <pause dur="short"/> here with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one of these which one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0144">dunno can I use that one?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh see you're all</u>
<u n="738" who="S0144">er?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0024">I was yeah that's nice</u>
<u n="740" who="S0144">it's not great quality but it doesn't matter does it?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0024">it doesn't matter it will only be small</u>
<u n="742" who="S0144">yeah that will do we can use that <pause dur="short"/> so ah no I crashed</u>
<u n="743" who="S0024">which one do you think is best of me? shall I use one of those?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0144">yeah you look lovely</u>
<u n="745" who="S0024">which one?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="747" who="S0024">that one?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0144">you look good in all of them <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0024">I look friendlier in that one don't I?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0144">okay is that a good thing? <pause dur="long"/> use a picture right okay</u>
<u n="751" who="S0024">yeah I think it is good to look friendly isn't it?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0144">you can drag your files in here</u>
<u n="753" who="S0024">well which would you <trunc>th</trunc> say? my cheekbones look quite high in that one <pause dur="long"/> I've got a picture of you here do you want it?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0144">mm? <pause dur="short"/> no I don't like that one</u>
<u n="755" who="S0024">you choose one for me</u>
<u n="756" who="S0144">erm <pause dur="short"/> that one's quite dark</u>
<u n="757" who="S0024">well I can lighten it up can't I?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0144">you don't wanna spend too long working on it</u>
<u n="759" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="760" who="S0144">yeah that that one they're all I like all of those</u>
<u n="761" who="S0024">anyway it doesn't matter if it's dark does it? <pause dur="long"/> copy that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0144">picture description</u>
<u n="763" who="S0024">me</u>
<u n="764" who="S0144">me and my baby <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="765" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="766" who="S0144">can I put that?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0024">you don't need a picture description do you? <pause dur="short"/> here's a picture</u>
<u n="768" who="S0144">me and my baby <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0024" trans="overlap">how do you new picture? <pause dur="short"/> you can drag and drop file</u>
<u n="770" who="S0144" trans="overlap">or with me and my</u>
<u n="771" who="S0024">well you can just drag and drop a file</u>
<u n="772" who="S0144">daughter</u>
<u n="773" who="S0024">oh you can just drag and drop a file</u>
<u n="774" who="S0144">yeah it's much better <pause dur="short"/> me and my daughter <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sound better doesn't it? <pause dur="short"/> current picture none <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="775" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0144">additional names interests blah blah blah so this description is that <pause dur="short"/> is that basically what they're gonna see?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0024">I guess</u>
<u n="778" who="S0144" trans="overlap">they're gonna see a <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="779" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I well I think we've got to do it and then go in as a student and have a look</u>
<u n="780" who="S0144">so they'll see a picture of me and whatever I write here?</u>
<u n="781" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0144">so I change the font and everything yeah? make it big and</u>
<u n="783" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0144">colourful if I can you change the colours? <pause dur="short"/> welcome <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0024">where's the font change?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0144">just at the top <pause dur="short"/> oh it's not really a font change it's</u>
<u n="787" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="long"/> can I put hello?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0144">yes you can</u>
<u n="789" who="S0024">hello welcome</u>
<u n="790" who="S0144">or you <trunc>s</trunc> insert an image look <pause dur="short"/> so I might just insert an image that says welcome</u>
<u n="791" who="S0024">no I can't be bothered doing that welcome to my Moodle page what do you put?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0144">welcome <pause dur="short"/> to my Moodle page</u>
<u n="793" who="S0024">oi get off that's what I'm putting</u>
<u n="794" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I wrote it first <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="795" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0144">well how about?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0024" trans="overlap">so inventive we are</u>
<u n="798" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well why is that not as a big as it was? welcome to my Moodle page <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0024">oi <pause dur="short"/> I knew I shouldn't have worked with you</u>
<u n="800" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0024">you just copy everything I do <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0144">come on what's next?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0024" trans="overlap">next <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> don't we need to write something like <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> I'll be your CELE I'll be your CELE teacher this year?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0144">no I think</u>
<u n="805" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="806" who="S0144">erm something like</u>
<u n="807" who="S0024">I work in CELE?</u>
<u n="808" who="S0144">I will be your</u>
<u n="809" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0144">CELE teacher this year</u>
<u n="811" who="S0024" trans="overlap">tutor <pause dur="short"/> oh you can put teacher</u>
<u n="812" who="S0144">tutor</u>
<u n="813" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="814" who="S0144">I'll be your CELE tutor this year I look <pause dur="long"/> damn but that means I'm gonna have to keep changing it aren't I? cos I can't leave that message up there all year</u>
<u n="815" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="816" who="S0144">I am <pause dur="long"/> lucky you I'm your teacher <pause dur="short"/> I'm your CELE tutor <pause dur="long"/> do I need to put that? no <pause dur="long"/> what are you typing away?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0024">well</u>
<u n="818" who="S0144" trans="overlap">you've</u>
<u n="819" who="S0024" trans="overlap">nothing exciting <pause dur="short"/> yeah well I've stopped telling you</u>
<u n="820" who="S0144" trans="overlap">you've thrown you've thrown me a dummy sentence didn't you?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> my name is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I work in CELE in <trunc>C</trunc> in CELE tutoring reading writing listening and speaking in an academic context erm I'm here <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="long"/> I doing it do I need a comma there? I work in CELE <pause dur="long"/> do I need a comma</u>
<u n="822" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0024">do I need one of those <pause dur="short"/> well I'm not very good <pause dur="short"/> at semicolons <pause dur="short"/> I work in CELE tutoring reading writing listening speaking <pause dur="short"/> in a <pause dur="short"/> yeah? that'll do right <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0144">I've no idea what I</u>
<u n="825" who="S0024" trans="overlap">my</u>
<u n="826" who="S0144">what to write on this</u>
<u n="827" who="S0024">specialities</u>
<u n="828" who="S0144">specialities?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0024">no my speciality is</u>
<u n="830" who="S0144">is what?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0024">genre analysis? no I don't wanna put like</u>
<u n="832" who="S0144" trans="overlap">is that gonna help them? <pause dur="short"/> that's the</u>
<u n="833" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no because they'll</u>
<u n="834" who="S0144" trans="overlap">kind of thing you put on your <pause dur="short"/> uni page not your student page <pause dur="short"/> they're not gonna know what genre analysis is</u>
<u n="835" who="S0024">okay that'll do I'll just put that</u>
<u n="836" who="S0144">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0024">I've got a picture er</u>
<u n="838" who="S0144">on your</u>
<u n="839" who="S0024">additional names interests optional no don't need that do we? he did say make it look pretty</u>
<u n="840" who="S0144">I look forward</u>
<u n="841" who="S0024">erm</u>
<u n="842" who="S0144">to teaching <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="843" who="S0024">no I I don't like mine I don't like mine <pause dur="short"/> no I'm changing mine need something nice and friendly don't you? I'm gonna change it change it <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0144">I will always be available</u>
<u n="845" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="846" who="S0144">no that's a silly thing to say</u>
<u n="847" who="S0024">who shall we go and speak to about our problems? oh Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> he'll be a good one</u>
<u n="848" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I look forward to teaching you all this year <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="849" who="S0024">it says my name on it why do I have to put <pause dur="short"/> okay CELE I'm happy erm <pause dur="long"/> to</u>
<u n="850" who="S0144">welcome to my Moodle page I</u>
<u n="851" who="S0024">we</u>
<u n="852" who="S0144">do we need like a history of what you've done or</u>
<u n="853" who="S0024"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0144">or what?</u>
<u n="855" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="856" who="S0144">mm they don't care for that do they? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0024">they can look at you your university page for that whether you've got an MA or an like you said for the other thing <pause dur="long"/> working with you <pause dur="long"/> we <pause dur="long"/> oh <trunc>go</trunc> you're <trunc>j</trunc> making it just like mine</u>
<u n="858" who="S0144">really? I'm not looking at yours</u>
<u n="859" who="S0024">well I've put I work in CELE you've put I work as a CELE tutor <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I suppose that's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="860" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah phrasing</u>
<u n="861" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0144">as a CELE tutor for <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="863" who="S0024">I'm just gonna put my <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="864" who="S0144">is it a foundation year? is that what's called?</u>
<u n="865" who="S0024">preliminary year <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0144">glee reminanan preliminarary</u>
<u n="867" who="S0024">liminary</u>
<u n="868" who="S0144">prelimin er limin ah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="870" who="S0144">pre lim in ary <pause dur="short"/> what's wrong with that? oh <pause dur="short"/> how do you spell preliminary? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0024">P R E</u>
<u n="872" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="873" who="S0024">LIM</u>
<u n="874" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0024">I N A R <unclear>I</unclear></u>
<u n="876" who="S0144">I <pause dur="long"/> okay erm I work as a CELE tutor for reading writing and listening and speaking aspects of the UNNC preliminary year is that okay? <pause dur="short"/> I look forward <pause dur="long"/> I am very much <pause dur="short"/> look forward to teaching you all this year <pause dur="short"/> yeah? that'll do anyhow <pause dur="short"/> don't wanna write a load of crap <pause dur="short"/> interests? <event desc="sound of baby"/></u>
<u n="877" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="878" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="und"/></u>
<u n="879" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="880" who="S0144">yeah she's still hungry</u>
<u n="881" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come here yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">ah I don't <unclear/> put her down mm</u>
<u n="883" who="S0024"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="884" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">we'll put her there</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
