<text id="SXAQ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:26:23</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0251 S0252</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Dining room in Malton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Scottish Independence and referendum</topics>
		<activity>Upcoming Scottish referendum</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0251">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>North Ferriby, East Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>GCSE Maths Examiner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0252">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>York</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0252">what are your views on the upcoming Scottish referendum?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0251">well I'm surprised at the momentum that the whole argument has generated at the moment we're about a week or so away from the actual vote and the people that want to stay in the union are only winning by a short head polls vary but it's pretty evenly matched really there's maybe only a couple of percentage points in it I don't think it is a good idea for Scotland to become a separate country and I think it's better for England if they stay with us as well so I think it's better for both places that we stay together because I think it would undermine both the countries both in Europe and in the world if they were separate because they're too small</u>
<u n="3" who="S0252">it's interesting I read in the Telegraph that apparently on average each Scottish person receives one thousand eight hundred pounds more in erm sort of state funding compared to an English person via free prescriptions and free tuition fees and that sort of thing so they do certainly have a privileged status within the United Kingdom</u>
<u n="4" who="S0251">I think so I think we're on to a pretty good thing on those two scores the debate seems to have deteriorated if you want to use that word into Scotland versus Westminster rather than Scotland against England they seem to be just focusing on this political aspect erm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0252">and they'll think you could almost go further to say that it's more or less SNP versus Conservative to some extent</u>
<u n="6" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="7" who="S0252">I think the Scots dislike or generally the conservatives it hasn't helped</u>
<u n="8" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes they haven't got any conservative MPs in Scotland it's just one now is it? they're hardly represented at all</u>
<u n="9" who="S0252" trans="overlap">just one</u>
<u n="10" who="S0251">but that's democracy I mean sometimes when you have the general election in this country one party doesn't have a very big majority so it still means that nearly half the people have got a government that they haven't actually elected so that is how democracy works so you have to lump it until the next time you have a vote and then see if it changes</u>
<u n="11" who="S0252" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yes but I think really that's just whether different people's views are represented to some extent</u>
<u n="12" who="S0251">yes I think at the beginning it seemed that the cry for independence was just confined to a small fanatical and nationalistic minority yes</u>
<u n="13" who="S0252" trans="overlap">group mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0251">as time's gone on it seems to have gathered momentum so I think it's always more difficult to defend something than it is to attack it</u>
<u n="15" who="S0252">it is</u>
<u n="16" who="S0251">so</u>
<u n="17" who="S0252">erm not sure that it has been thoroughly thought through because there was a comparison of statistics between Office of National Statistics and what the researchers the SNP <unclear/> and on every score it seemed to be different to quite an extreme</u>
<u n="18" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0252">for example the SNP reckon that there's a lot more royal in Scotland than what the Office of National Statistics estimate</u>
<u n="20" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0252">and the cost of independence is Office of National Statistics have estimated it would cost ten times as much as what the erm SNP have erm calculated so there does seem to be some discrepancy between statistics</u>
<u n="22" who="S0251">see it's difficult to know what to believe really isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0252">it is one thing it certainly does is I I do think Scotland is in a relatively strong position currently it's got a good welfare system it's more economically developed country erm they've got the backing of erm about sixty million people within the Scotland Wales and England and Northern Ireland</u>
<u n="24" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="25" who="S0252">but I think the idea of independence it it just shuts off all that security</u>
<u n="26" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="27" who="S0252">you know <unclear>we're</unclear> even talking about currency and borders and it it just gets very complicated in a way that's not really necessary it's not going to make any difference to the everyday lives</u>
<u n="28" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="29" who="S0252">well people still have to go to work they still have to pay tax</u>
<u n="30" who="S0251">yes they will</u>
<u n="31" who="S0252">it doesn't change really</u>
<u n="32" who="S0251">no that's right one other thing is that if it does turn out that the vote for leaving the union has a majority that they want to have a separate vote because they think they will have a majority of people wanting to stay and they've got the oil fields nearest to them</u>
<u n="33" who="S0252" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="34" who="S0251">so that's an interesting development</u>
<u n="35" who="S0252">but in some ways it would almost create like a new Gibraltar but north of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yeah it's painful isn't it? on the one hand you've got people from other countries in Europe travelling into France and trying to get into England because we've got from their point of view this fantastic system going with all the welfare care and all the National Health et cetera risking their lives on the underside of a lorry to try to get in and on the other hand we've got the Scottish folk or half of the Scottish folk wanting to eh call it a day</u>
<u n="37" who="S0252">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0251" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yes I think once the vote has been counted I don't think things are ever going to be quite the same again</u>
<u n="39" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="40" who="S0251">even if they do stay I think a lot of people feel a bit different I don't really think it's added to the stability of the situation in either Scotland or in England</u>
<u n="41" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="42" who="S0251">especially seeing as the vote looks like it's going to be pretty close I think I'm going to feel a little bit different about it now</u>
<u n="43" who="S0252"><unclear>course</unclear> in a more negative way perhaps</u>
<u n="44" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yes because I've really liked going to Scotland in the past when we've been on holiday and buring all the tartan shops and seeing the bagpipers and when we went to Edinburgh Edinburgh Tattoo I really enjoyed that but now it seems that there's so much antipathy towards the English it's not going to be the same</u>
<u n="45" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="46" who="S0251">I don't think there's going to be quite the same welcoming in the hillside</u>
<u n="47" who="S0252">erm must admit when I've been in Scotland I've not felt a particular nationalistic stance</u>
<u n="48" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no I haven't actually</u>
<u n="49" who="S0252">I've just been sort of treated as more or less erm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="51" who="S0252">well not a local but someone within the same country</u>
<u n="52" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no yes yes no we really enjoyed it haven't we? <unclear/> think Edinburgh is a very vibrant place to be it seems</u>
<u n="53" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes it does</u>
<u n="54" who="S0251">bustling and you know lots of tourists and we really enjoyed seeing the castle hadn't we?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0252">yes I think the erm Royal Collection Trust will be put in a a bit of a difficult position with <unclear/> I don't quite know how that would quite work out if they were separate</u>
<u n="56" who="S0251">no I don't know <unclear/> a lot of it it seems to be up in the air doesn't it?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0252">it does</u>
<u n="58" who="S0251">then from the point of view of the position of the queen the position of the currency side of things and erm whether they're going to be in Europe or not some commentators think that people such as the Spanish will say that they don't want them in because they think that it might aggravate the situation in Spain with the Catalonians wanting independence that it might yeah trigger them and give them more ideas</u>
<u n="59" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> trigger but I think there are similar situations in other parts of Europe in particular though <unclear/> and the Flemish in Belgium and erm ah Catalonians have been mentioned even somewhere in Austria and erm parts of Italy just seem to be a sort of nationalistic <unclear>tone</unclear></u>
<u n="60" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0252">I don't really know why it's suddenly surged or whether it's because of erm the latest economic crisis that's created a bit of unstability or erm why that is because I don't really think that it's a particularly fruitful task</u>
<u n="62" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yeah no I don't I think it's going to lead to greater vulnerability</u>
<u n="63" who="S0252">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0251">there's already lots of military cuts in <unclear/> so I don't know how that will pan out when countries get even smaller</u>
<u n="65" who="S0252">mm but when Scotland's if they do separate they're planning to have a a small military unit of themselves or <unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="67" who="S0252">but from the English point of view it means that we're going to have to move our nuclear erm submarines and stockpiling units and it'll be very expensive</u>
<u n="68" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm I think it's just too complicated I don't really think there's such a big problem that we need to do something so drastic</u>
<u n="69" who="S0252">I know and which how would Scottish soldiers work out because the erm British taxpayer has paid for their training and their salaries and obviously the patriotic the sworn oath and that sort of thing how is that going to work if that becomes independent they can't swear an oath to the <unclear/> or</u>
<u n="70" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> no you can't I don't know how it's going to work out I don't think anybody knows how it would all work out there's a lot of uncertainties about it really</u>
<u n="71" who="S0252">yeah well I just think they've got it wrong really I just don't think it'll stand to improve or progress anything</u>
<u n="72" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="73" who="S0252">I think they've got a certain amount of control at Holyrood anyway and er to be honest they might've just been better off saying that they would like some more powers rather than kicking off a</u>
<u n="74" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah well I think they have been promised them haven't they?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0251">it does turn out to be no in the end that they're going to get more powers anyway so I think they would be in a very strong position from that point of view</u>
<u n="77" who="S0252">mm it's not going to be far off</u>
<u n="78" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0252">from <unclear>independent though</unclear> just without all the</u>
<u n="80" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0252">the <unclear>tricky</unclear> aspects</u>
<u n="82" who="S0251">mm I think so</u>
<u n="83" who="S0252">mm I thought the er Tattoo is erm a nice part of the Scottish heritage</u>
<u n="84" who="S0251">it is there's lots of things that are very appealing about it all the tartan and I think when you go in the tartan shops everybody's wanting to find their tartan and their name and claim some kind of link to it it's that popular</u>
<u n="85" who="S0252">it is in some ways erm I would like to erm visit er the Macbeth's castle er is it <unclear/> castle or something like that?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0251" trans="overlap">don't know</u>
<u n="87" who="S0252">and erm I would like to visit Balmoral as well</u>
<u n="88" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0252">yes er</u>
<u n="90" who="S0251">I think that's quite far north though isn't it?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0252">it is it is but obviously that's not really er well that does shouldn't really stop you going if you would like to go</u>
<u n="92" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="93" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="94" who="S0251">we found it much easier on the train didn't we the second time?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="96" who="S0251">rather than the coach</u>
<u n="97" who="S0252">indeed</u>
<u n="98" who="S0251">that was far too long wasn't it?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0252">it was</u>
<u n="100" who="S0251">quite gruelling really</u>
<u n="101" who="S0252">I think train is really a very good form of travel I I don't think it gets much better <unclear/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0251">mm no <unclear>cos</unclear> you can go a lot quicker can't you?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0252">it does yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0252">it er it's not sort of er super high-speed line but it is you know you should be doing at least a hundred miles per hour for most of the way</u>
<u n="106" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm should be plenty</u>
<u n="107" who="S0252">yes <pause dur="short"/> but that would be another complication <unclear/> you have to er er apply Eurostar procedures to travel up to Scotland <unclear/> separate?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0251"><unclear/> they say not but I don't know and what about the railway companies?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0252">I know <unclear>don't <trunc>kn</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="110" who="S0251">would they have to have a separate one?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0252">don't know just <unclear/> add more complication doesn't it?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0252">er obviously the currency they have will be a bit complicated and also the assets Edinburgh technically parts of the network are run by the UK so</u>
<u n="114" who="S0251">mm mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0252">don't know how that would work out</u>
<u n="116" who="S0251">because they already have a separate schooling system don't they? with the Scottish highers instead of the A levels</u>
<u n="117" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="118" who="S0251">and they actually get their exam results two weeks</u>
<u n="119" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="120" who="S0251">before the A levels come out so</u>
<u n="121" who="S0252">they do</u>
<u n="122" who="S0251">they have a bit of time to think about their options before the English A level results are published</u>
<u n="123" who="S0252">yes but another aspect of they're not in the EU and we are in the EU that does mean you will have to have some non-EU check</u>
<u n="124" who="S0251">don't know we might not be staying in yet I don't know</u>
<u n="125" who="S0252">I know that's</u>
<u n="126" who="S0251">David Cameron is making a lot of promises isn't he?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0252">he is hope he can remember them all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0251">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0252">I think erm that <trunc>the</trunc>the like the the sort of the castle and erm sort of sort of rather imposing buildings and stuff I don't think there are a lot of imposing buildings in Scotland I think there are a lot</u>
<u n="130" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="131" who="S0252">of sort of groups of sort of like erm erm almost like medieval feel to <unclear/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0251">yes it does have that kind of original kind of original Macbeth feel to it</u>
<u n="133" who="S0252">oh</u>
<u n="134" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0252">when the Romans came of course they put Hadrian's Wall up there didn't they and decided to call it a day and not to bother with Scotland because they thought it was a bit too much trouble and probably getting a bit too cold up there for them as well</u>
<u n="136" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes <unclear/> I think it would be erm really funny from Salmond's point of view if erm Scotland voted yes and then the <unclear/> came back to the UK</u>
<u n="137" who="S0252">mm strange</u>
<u n="138" who="S0251">have you seen that there's been some mock-ups of what the flag would look like if erm we are separate and that and blue would be removed and it would be a black background with yellow next to the erm the white stripes</u>
<u n="139" who="S0252" trans="overlap">oh really <pause dur="short"/> why black and yellow?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0251">because that's one of the Welsh flags is black and yellow</u>
<u n="141" who="S0252">oh right</u>
<u n="142" who="S0251"><unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0252" trans="overlap">sound a lot different lot different</u>
<u n="144" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0252">I don't think that will catch on there's some people saying that if they do decide to go separate that we wouldn't need to bother with changing the clocks</u>
<u n="146" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0252">back and then change them again in the spring because that's done for the benefit of Scotland so that they get better daylight hours but if they weren't with us any more we probably wouldn't have to bother about it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="149" who="S0252">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> they may not want to stick to Greenwich Mean Time I don't know</u>
<u n="150" who="S0251">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0252">oh yes</u>
<u n="152" who="S0251"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0252">I think that's one thing that England has given to the world is the time isn't it?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="155" who="S0252">everything seems to be calculated from that Greenwich Mean Time doesn't it?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0251">yes do you like the Falkirk Wheel in Scotland? are you surprised at how that works sort of lift</u>
<u n="157" who="S0252">it was it was an amazing structure wasn't it? how they thought that one out</u>
<u n="158" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah did you enjoy <unclear/> or were you a little bit sort of scared?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0252">yeah it was a bit of an experience wasn't it?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah it was a bit like a Ferris wheel in some respects</u>
<u n="161" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes it was wasn't it?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="163" who="S0252">yes I'm glad we did it though</u>
<u n="164" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="165" who="S0252">bit strange in some ways</u>
<u n="166" who="S0251">then <unclear/> sort of ah a river can sort of have like two tiers or on different levels</u>
<u n="167" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0252">how did the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0251">I don't know with difficulty probably</u>
<u n="171" who="S0252">obviously it was just have a big splash if you just <vocal desc="laugh"/> didn't eh come down the wheel itself</u>
<u n="172" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0252">apparently Stirling is meant to be quite a nice ahm place</u>
<u n="174" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0252">are you aware of <unclear/> Stirling?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0251">no I haven't been there</u>
<u n="177" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="178" who="S0251">I don't know what it's like there's a castle isn't there</u>
<u n="179" who="S0252">yes I think it's meant to be very medieval very sort of unchanged</u>
<u n="180" who="S0251" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0252">eh</u>
<u n="182" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0252">mm and so it's a university town as well</u>
<u n="184" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="185" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="186" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="187" who="S0252">I don't know whether it would be like York or</u>
<u n="188" who="S0251">I don't know</u>
<u n="189" who="S0252"><unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0251">anything about it?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0252">in some ways I suppose we only really explored the erm lower part of Scotland Lothian and the er Borders</u>
<u n="192" who="S0251">yes Edinburgh <unclear/> yes yes</u>
<u n="193" who="S0252">yes I think there is possibly quite a large part north of that that is isn't really too much to see it's just</u>
<u n="194" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0252">like more or less nothing there really just countryside</u>
<u n="196" who="S0251" trans="overlap">just countryside yes</u>
<u n="197" who="S0252">which is very nice</u>
<u n="198" who="S0251" trans="overlap">that's a good thing isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0252">some very sparse</u>
<u n="200" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0252">do you think the erm retailers threatening a an increase in prices will will worry some sort of John Lewis and Asda saying that they have to increase prices due to additional costs associated with</u>
<u n="202" who="S0251">yes I don't think that would help and also some companies saying that they would want to relocate I think Royal Bank of Scotland said that they would want to relocate wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="204" who="S0251">but then in some ways it wouldn't be the Royal Bank of Scotland if it was in England would it?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0252" trans="overlap">no would be a bit strange and also seems to be a bit of a question of the Clydesdale Bank which is apparently the national bank of Australia is wanting to erm sell that part of its portfolio</u>
<u n="206" who="S0251">really?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0252">really</u>
<u n="208" who="S0251">in any event or just if they separate</u>
<u n="209" who="S0252">well it's just looking at in any event</u>
<u n="210" who="S0251">oh right why?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0252">but it was saying that it it might speed up the sale if there's independence</u>
<u n="212" who="S0251">oh right is it not as profitable</u>
<u n="213" who="S0252">I don't know I haven't I haven't seen any analysis on the effect or</u>
<u n="214" who="S0251">oh right I'm surprised mm but why would John Lewis have more costs than then do now?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0252" trans="overlap">well they're saying that ahm the Scottish John Lewises are currently partially subsidised by the English John Lewises</u>
<u n="216" who="S0251">they don't have as much business as</u>
<u n="217" who="S0252">from so don't have as much business and eh the increase in logistic cost</u>
<u n="218" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="219" who="S0252">because apparently parts of the royal <unclear/> above Edinburgh is on a single carriageway</u>
<u n="220" who="S0251">right</u>
<u n="221" who="S0252">so that means lorries are only restricted to fifty miles per hour</u>
<u n="222" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="223" who="S0252">but also I imagine it's a long way from eh depots I imagine their depots will be in the Midlands and south of England so obviously it's a long way to drive up</u>
<u n="224" who="S0251">mm in some ways though I'm surprised they've got one because York has only got one this year hasn't it?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="226" who="S0251">so they've gone further north before York</u>
<u n="227" who="S0252">yes yes they've I think they've they have six stores in Scotland</u>
<u n="228" who="S0251">oh right</u>
<u n="229" who="S0252">yes there's at least one in Edinburgh</u>
<u n="230" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="231" who="S0252">there's one in Glasgow and there's a few further north</u>
<u n="232" who="S0251"><unclear/> because it's the John Lewis partnership is only just started making a presence in the north Yorkshire area hasn't it?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm particularly the Waitrose side of things</u>
<u n="234" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="235" who="S0252">and the John Lewis as well bit of a down</u>
<u n="236" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes it was</u>
<u n="237" who="S0252">ah surprising in some ways if you're taken sort of them eighty odd years to get up here</u>
<u n="238" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="239" who="S0252">yes I wouldn't say that we're now really north</u>
<u n="240" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="241" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="242" who="S0251">doesn't seem to have been a priority does it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0252">no ah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0251">got there in the end though</u>
<u n="245" who="S0252">I think <trunc>s</trunc>some parts of the north have been <unclear/> perhaps erm not as affluent as part of the south of England</u>
<u n="246" who="S0251">mm well there's pockets aren't there?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0252">yes they're just pockets I think in the south of England it might be a little bit more than pockets in some areas</u>
<u n="248" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> you've probably heard about the erm pockets in Yorkshire the</u>
<u n="249" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="250" who="S0251">having deep pockets and short arms</u>
<u n="251" who="S0252">indeed</u>
<u n="252" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0252">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="254" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0252">but Asda as well they're saying that it will increase costs as well which obviously would affect quite a number of people</u>
<u n="256" who="S0251">for the same reasons</u>
<u n="257" who="S0252" trans="overlap">in Scotland? <unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0252">and eh people would not like that because obviously erm that would mean increased costs for not really too much</u>
<u n="260" who="S0251">no I think it's strange though that for instance Morrisons the prices are not the same and Sainsbury's would be <unclear/> prices are not the same in all the shops throughout the country and that sometimes we see prices advertised on the internet but when you go to your local store it's actually more than that isn't it?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="262" who="S0251">so we're actually paying the premium for living in the area that we do</u>
<u n="263" who="S0252">yes but furthermore a certain express delivery companies will not deliver to this <unclear/> at this postcode</u>
<u n="264" who="S0251">no yes and that could affect the Royal Mail as well</u>
<u n="265" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="266" who="S0251">because the the erm price for delivery and to the Orkneys and far flung corners is just the same as the <unclear>flat</unclear> rate isn't it?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0252">it is</u>
<u n="268" who="S0251">so that must be subsidised as well so that might have to be sorted out separately</u>
<u n="269" who="S0252">there's no pun intended <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0251">thought you'd missed that one</u>
<u n="271" who="S0252"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but ah it does certainly seem to erm potentially affect the men who sort of retail side of things a bit <unclear>and in not such a good way</unclear></u>
<u n="272" who="S0251">mm yes and I wonder if some people who are saying that they're going to vote yes when it actually comes to it I think they might decide not to do it because I think it is going to adversely affect them and I think they might have gotten a little bit too erm embroiled in it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0252" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="274" who="S0251">because they are well known for being quite canny aren't they?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0252">they are</u>
<u n="276" who="S0251">and they won't want it to adversely affect their personal finances will they?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0252">definitely not <pause dur="short"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
