<text id="SXBE">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:22:57</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-07</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0022 S0023</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers’ home, Hungerford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Future plans, writing, politics, tattoos, the domestic sphere, describing a perfect day</topics>
		<activity>Husband and Wife taking about their future holiday plans then discussing various hypothetical situations</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0022">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kettering, Northamptonshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hungerford, Berkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>PA to director</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- Advanced; Spanish -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0023">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Taplow, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hungerford, Berkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>IT consultant</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0023">yeah let's carry on now</u>
<u n="2" who="S0022">okay <pause dur="short"/> erm so it's still recording? Sorry</u>
<u n="3" who="S0023">yeah it's recording now</u>
<u n="4" who="S0022">yeah it is okay <pause dur="short"/> so tell me what you're most looking forward to about erm going away next week</u>
<u n="5" who="S0023">ah well <trunc>ama</trunc> it's come round amazingly quickly but it's my birthday and so I'm looking forward to being you know treated like a king really er even more than normal <pause dur="short"/> so erm we're going to the cos of the erm <anon type="place"/> in the main place we're going to I'm looking forward to all the industrial heritage and seeing that museum</u>
<u n="6" who="S0022">that sounds amazing doesn't it</u>
<u n="7" who="S0023">where they all dress up <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0023">yeah it should be <pause dur="short"/> it should be <pause dur="short"/> I want to use old money and actually be able to pay for something with it cos I was born in nineteen-seventy which was the year they stopped using it <pause dur="short"/> but there's I've always had some hanging about the house</u>
<u n="10" who="S0022">but I think used Victorian coins</u>
<u n="11" who="S0023">no they <trunc>did</trunc> well one or two carried over <pause dur="short"/> the florin carried over <pause dur="short"/> the ten P <pause dur="short"/> the big fat old go on</u>
<u n="12" who="S0022" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I think  I think  at the museum they use Victorian coins</u>
<u n="13" who="S0023">oh <pause dur="short"/> well that's alright <pause dur="short"/> what I mean is it's real money <pause dur="short"/> it's brass it's not just plated copper it's worth something <pause dur="short"/> or plated nickel or whatever it is <pause dur="short"/> so erm that will be fun <pause dur="short"/> and you'll be able to buy penny chews for a penny <pause dur="short"/> well maybe more than one <pause dur="short"/> that will be nice</u>
<u n="14" who="S0022">that will be good <pause dur="short"/> I think erm you know that writing assignment the one about writing about a place?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0023">yes yes</u>
<u n="16" who="S0022">I think I'm going to use that and write about it</u>
<u n="17" who="S0023" trans="overlap">that's a good idea <pause dur="short"/> maybe we'll both be inspired</u>
<u n="18" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0023">but it's it's famous for being you know in the heartland of industrial revolution and er it all is grassy and sort of pleasant that it looks now <pause dur="short"/> it was a furnace of creativity at the time and it's what made the country what it is so I'm really interested to see</u>
<u n="20" who="S0022" trans="overlap">really? Yeah I think it will be very interesting</u>
<u n="21" who="S0023">oh that reminds me don't let me forget that next this year is the anniversary of that steam engine down the road <pause dur="short"/> two-hundred years</u>
<u n="22" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="23" who="S0023">it's a good reason to try and submit an article</u>
<u n="24" who="S0022" trans="overlap">you should yeah <pause dur="short"/> you should definitely <pause dur="short"/> you should get a Wiltshire magazine</u>
<u n="25" who="S0023">yeah that would go well in there <pause dur="short"/> you're right</u>
<u n="26" who="S0022">it is in  wasn't it?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0023">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0022">oh right okay here's a question for you <pause dur="short"/> erm what amendments these these cards must have been made in America <pause dur="short"/> so the question is what amendments should be made to the US Constitution?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0023" trans="overlap">hmm <pause dur="short"/> well nice er <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> the main one that I know of and thought about is the need to explicitly mention the right to property <pause dur="short"/> so they've got if you remember the the what's in the Declaration of Independence</u>
<u n="30" who="S0022" trans="overlap">I know very very little about it I'm ashamed to say</u>
<u n="31" who="S0023">something about inalienable rights to er life liberty and the pursuit of happiness</u>
<u n="32" who="S0022">mm mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0023">along those lines anyway <pause dur="short"/> so right to life <pause dur="short"/> no-one really argues about that <pause dur="short"/> liberty means can't lock you up unless there's good reason to <pause dur="short"/> er pursuit of happiness <pause dur="short"/> I think it should even if it doesn't say it say the pursuit of your own happiness as opposed to making everyone else happy</u>
<u n="34" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0023">which otherwise you'd just be back into slavery <pause dur="short"/> but yeah the bit they're missing there is property because erm America despite being a very individualist capitalist country over the years er and particularly right now with Obamacare has decided it's going to not let you be free <pause dur="short"/> they're going to tell you what to do and take your property away <pause dur="short"/> well all the time though in America unlike this country whenever anything comes up they often refer to the Constitution and say that's unconstitutional <pause dur="short"/> and and you know an individual can bring a court case that will go all the way to the Supreme Court if they can make a case for the fact that it is to do with the Constitution <pause dur="short"/> so if you put in a line there about erm property <pause dur="short"/> probably something else about interstate commerce as well <pause dur="short"/> people justify the regulations they have now <pause dur="short"/> loads of them <pause dur="short"/> they have these federal regulations like er what you can and can't do with guns and stuff based on</u>
<u n="36" who="S0022" trans="overlap">so is federal the whole country?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0023">yeah federal is the whole country</u>
<u n="38" who="S0022">right</u>
<u n="39" who="S0023">so there's  there's a  there's a thing in the original Constitution that allows erm it says and there are mustn't be any laws between the states that restrict trade</u>
<u n="40" who="S0022">mm mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0023">but they've taken them that to mean the negative which means the federal system can make laws because it's not a state</u>
<u n="42" who="S0022" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="43" who="S0023">so they've twisted the Constitution in order to fit it in with Socialist type ideas with which I obviously don't agree</u>
<u n="44" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="45" who="S0023">so to be true to what the original people of the Constitution said I think we should put in a thing about property and make trade erm free <pause dur="short"/> that's my basic answer <pause dur="short"/> what's yours?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0022" trans="overlap">hmm <pause dur="short"/> ah well see I know so little about it <pause dur="short"/> erm I mean I think it's really good they do have a Constitution <trunc>obvious</trunc> something that we're lacking</u>
<u n="47" who="S0023" trans="overlap">why? What's the what's important about having one do you think? Why do you miss it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0022" trans="overlap">well from what I understand from you is what you've just said that you know there is  there is  that  that a  that a citizen can can kind of <pause dur="short"/> that you can't just make up any old law you fancy  there is  there is a <trunc>s</trunc> there is a document on you know the founding of the country which is based on the fact that it was a document that that that people can't do X Y Z but governments can't do X Y Z either</u>
<u n="49" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0022">and I was thinking this morning for some reason I'm not quite sure why <pause dur="short"/> but erm  you know you know the  erm you know the smoking ban in this country</u>
<u n="51" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0022">and I've heard this too many times for it not for me not to believe it's correct that that you can smoke in the bar of the House of Commons</u>
<u n="53" who="S0023" trans="overlap">I know it's outrageous isn't it <pause dur="short"/> typical <unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> and I heard it the first time and I thought it can't be true it just can't be true</u>
<u n="55" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0022">but then I heard it again and how could you and that is just so much like you know one rule for us and one rule for you <pause dur="short"/> I E one rule for the government and one rule for you <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that makes perfect sense <pause dur="short"/> look at it this way <pause dur="short"/> they're the politicians are the ones who make the rules up because we're not fit to run our own lives <pause dur="short"/> so if their and the the implication and the definite position is we're not intelligent enough or wise enough or right enough to do the right thing <pause dur="short"/> they are <pause dur="short"/> so whatever they do is okay by definition because they're the ones with the  with the  all the cleverness and all the  all the  rights and they have to tell us what to do <pause dur="short"/> what they the idea that we should be equal ooh no that's that's all out the window in the first instance <pause dur="short"/> so yeah they wouldn't even look at that as a contradiction</u>
<u n="58" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0023">they'll happily put up with it <pause dur="short"/> contradiction has nothing to do with it <pause dur="short"/> we have to be controlled</u>
<u n="60" who="S0022">okay here's another one <pause dur="short"/> can I ask you this <trunc>ques</trunc>? Oh it's kind of your turn but I really like this question</u>
<u n="61" who="S0023">oh go on then as long  as long  as we both as long as I get to hear your answer as well</u>
<u n="62" who="S0022">well I just think well I know you're not going to approve of this but I think this is quite funny</u>
<u n="63" who="S0023">uh-oh <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0022">right <pause dur="short"/> if you got a tattoo where would you? What would you get? And where would you put it? So</u>
<u n="65" who="S0023">well obviously I'd have a  have a  a heart with an arrow through it and it would say A for R or R for A or something like that</u>
<u n="66" who="S0022" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="67" who="S0023">and I'd have it somewhere so that you could see it but it wasn't too painful wasn't too large and erm I'm not quite sure</u>
<u n="68" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0023">traditionally men have it on their arms</u>
<u n="70" who="S0022">could you get a dot? And that would be your tattoo</u>
<u n="71" who="S0023" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0022">A dot you could pretend it was erm a beauty spot</u>
<u n="73" who="S0023">yeah I would want to get something that you know if I was going to <unclear/> or like go through all that is something that hopefully was aesthetically pleasing and traditionally men have things about their ladies but that's not always true <pause dur="short"/> there's this bloke at work now and erm because he wears suits normally I didn't notice but he's been he's wore a T-shirt the other Friday and he's got these elaborate tattoos all up his arms with god knows what they're meant to be <pause dur="short"/> snakes or something like that <pause dur="short"/> but it's he must have spent hours in the tattoo parlour</u>
<u n="74" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0023">and I can't think what it's for I mean why? It just looks odd</u>
<u n="76" who="S0022">I think if you're  if you're  well I was going to say if you were young but if you have well-muscled arms then they sort of I suppose they sort of showcase them</u>
<u n="77" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0022">but you'd have to keep your arms well-muscled</u>
<u n="79" who="S0023">oh is it like if you have pictures of snake and then you sort of <trunc>m</trunc> stretch your biceps then it makes the snakes move <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit</u>
<u n="80" who="S0022" trans="overlap">well I think there are you can get tattoos that are very very clever and I think they like I've heard of someone having a panther on their leg and when they  when they  run it looks like the panther's running</u>
<u n="81" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="82" who="S0022">which is it's kind of clever but the trouble is that if you're very honed and toned you've got to stay like that otherwise it's going to look horrible isn't it</u>
<u n="83" who="S0023" trans="overlap">Cos it the panther would get a bit fat won't it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0022">but I was thinking if I had to have one erm I would you could  you could  either go for the well okay I've got to get one so I'll have to <trunc>m</trunc> that says it as <trunc>un</trunc> erm <trunc>un</trunc> er what's the word?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0023">Obtrusive</u>
<u n="86" who="S0022">yeah unobtrusive as possible <pause dur="short"/> but then I thought well in a way you could have a like a sort of erm a maxim for life</u>
<u n="87" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh there you go like a motto <pause dur="short"/> oh that's good</u>
<u n="88" who="S0022">like yeah like something carpa diem but a bit more than that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="90" who="S0022">and and then I thought well you'd have to have it then so you could see it all the time <pause dur="short"/> so I suppose you'd have it <pause dur="short"/> you could have it somewhere like your wrist for example so you could see it but then you could cover with a bracelet or a watch or something</u>
<u n="91" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm not in favour of the idea in general I think it's er it's a bit of a strange thing to do</u>
<u n="92" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah I'm not</u>
<u n="93" who="S0023">it's a marriage of slavery actually <pause dur="short"/> branding of course is a a marking of the skin for you know bad reasons</u>
<u n="94" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> but then you have erm but then you have them tribal markings don't you like you like I think they erm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well again I wouldn't agree with the reasons for that <pause dur="short"/> I mean what's the reasons for that? To make you part of the collective</u>
<u n="96" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0023">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> you may change your mind and join another tribe <pause dur="short"/> then what are you going to do? You're a bit stuck aren't you</u>
<u n="98" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0023">mm <pause dur="short"/> my turn now or is it you?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> go on <pause dur="short"/> no no you ask me one</u>
<u n="101" who="S0023">let's see what's on this list <pause dur="short"/> so oh this will be fun <pause dur="short"/> what's the most significant problem facing the world? And you have to answer in less than twenty-four hours</u>
<u n="102" who="S0022">hmm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> mm okay I was going to say well I was going to say bad philosophy</u>
<u n="103" who="S0023">oh</u>
<u n="104" who="S0022">because you can up with something like hunger</u>
<u n="105" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0022">but if you take a country like Africa with the person who's listening to this <pause dur="short"/> I hope they're not a raving Socialist <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0023" trans="overlap">they'd stopped listening a long time ago</u>
<u n="108" who="S0022">I know <pause dur="short"/> but erm if you take a sort of country like Africa then they Africa should be the richest country in the world with all its resources <pause dur="short"/> and I can't help and maybe it's me being very simplistic but  there are  there are countries that erm have <trunc>obvious</trunc> are obviously what I <pause dur="short"/> start again <pause dur="short"/> there are  there are  unsuccessful countries and I think why aren't they looking at the successful ones and kind of thinking well why don't we do it the way they do it?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0023" trans="overlap">hmm mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0022">like for example erm and I know it sounds very arrogant and it's not meant to but erm I think it was two-thousand eight when there was erm oh there was some well anniversary's totally the wrong word but there was <pause dur="short"/> oh Live Aid Live Aid that was it</u>
<u n="111" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0022">and there was another big sort of charity erm drive to get money to Africa</u>
<u n="113" who="S0023">oh I remember it yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0022">and there was a program about AIDS in Africa and it was sort of saying how much of a problem it was and as I was watching it I it was saying you know how many people died of AIDS blah blah blah and I temporarily forgot that the Western world doesn't have a cure for AIDS either <pause dur="short"/> but we have the Western world has dealt with AIDS through behaviour <pause dur="short"/> largely</u>
<u n="115" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I guess yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0022">but Africa hasn't managed to do that and I think it's down to beliefs <pause dur="short"/> I think it's down to the Church but</u>
<u n="117" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0022">so yeah I would say and that's just one example <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0023">well what I take that from that <pause dur="short"/> excuse me for interrupting</u>
<u n="120" who="S0022">no that's fine</u>
<u n="121" who="S0023">but is it would lead on to what I would say which is basically it's erm the biggest problem facing the world is a lack of rationality <pause dur="short"/> people believing things that there's no rational basis for <pause dur="short"/> for example that er you know God will punish you if you wear a condom</u>
<u n="122" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0023">or you know you could say the fiscal crisis that we're in is erm down to lack of rationality as well <pause dur="short"/> people have pretended that they've got money that they haven't and you could point the finger at lots of different people who are making the same mistake <pause dur="short"/> but er again it's erm not thinking properly</u>
<u n="124" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0023">pretending things are the case when they you know they're not</u>
<u n="126" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0023">we're evading the need to try and figure out whether they are true or not <pause dur="short"/> so yeah a lack of rationality is the biggest problem</u>
<u n="128" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and and another another classic erm answer for that would be people say oh poverty but again there are <pause dur="short"/> I think the trouble is like</u>
<u n="129" who="S0023" trans="overlap">that's a symptom though</u>
<u n="130" who="S0022">yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> and I think chucking money <pause dur="short"/> I mean that I'm going to bring up Africa again but how much money has been chucked at Africa?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0023">oh yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0022">and it's about I think if you really want to help someone you've got to help them <pause dur="short"/> the biggest thing is helping someone help themselves <pause dur="short"/> you can't just <pause dur="short"/> it's like if someone's crap with money <pause dur="short"/> I mean in an individual <pause dur="short"/> if an individual's crap with money  you don't just  you don't just throw a hundred pounds at them because if they can't manage money they're not going to be able to manage a hundred pounds <pause dur="short"/> the if you really want to help someone I would say you've got to teach them how to deal teach them themselves how to solve the problem</u>
<u n="133" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0022">it's like you know the maxim erm give the man a fish and you feed him for a day <pause dur="short"/> teach him how to fish and feed him for life</u>
<u n="135" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0022">I think that's true <pause dur="short"/> I think it sounds harsh but</u>
<u n="137" who="S0023" trans="overlap">so if there was a way to <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know what you mean though if there was a sort of way to impart er to educate people who can't help themselves then that would be a better long-term solution <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think you are right <pause dur="short"/> I'd agree <pause dur="short"/> alright</u>
<u n="138" who="S0022" trans="overlap"><unclear/> world peace</u>
<u n="139" who="S0023">yeah but that's how you've would achieve it <pause dur="short"/> people wouldn't fight each other if they didn't think they could steal things from each other <pause dur="short"/> or they had to do it that way</u>
<u n="140" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> oh here's an interesting question <pause dur="short"/> ah okay <pause dur="short"/> do you want a philosophical question? Or do you want a sort of easier question?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0023" trans="overlap">let's have the  let's have the  other one for a change because we've been very deep already</u>
<u n="142" who="S0022">the easy one <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="143" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> give us the easy one for now</u>
<u n="144" who="S0022">what makes a house a home?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0023">oh that's a good one <pause dur="short"/> as I  as I  sit here in in our beautiful home which has been largely made by your good self er <pause dur="short"/> well you could look at the I wouldn't say superficial but not in the sense of unimportant but you could say decoration and tidiness so that you can <pause dur="short"/> it's not just a big mess it's actually our home which is a lovely place to come to every evening and to wake up in because it's beautifully arranged and aesthetically pleasing and has colour schemes and objects of value around the place erm <pause dur="short"/> so many things that make it very erm personal and pleasant place to be <pause dur="short"/> er so that would be you know the sort of physical things but then you could look on the more spiritual level and you could say well <pause dur="short"/> is a house a home is where I suppose it's where things like the artefacts come in</u>
<u n="146" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0023">you know the things that you put in place aren't just there for utilitarian purposes if you were say sharing a flat or you were in a barracks you know there's your suit there's your knife and fork there's your blanket <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0022">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0023">no we've chosen things because they're what we value <pause dur="short"/> and all the things kind of</u>
<u n="150" who="S0022">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's kind of putting your own stamp on it <pause dur="short"/> it's a cliché but I think that's true isn't it <pause dur="short"/> it's it's erm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0023" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a part of us because of all the choices we've made to make it the way it is and all the mementos there are that remind of things that we've done together in our life together and so on</u>
<u n="152" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so what what you've been this room for example <trunc>e</trunc> everything everything in here is is pretty much I mean apart from the sort of hard furnishings if that's a word</u>
<u n="153" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0022">it's been chosen by us and and erm yeah so there's obviously photos which are very personal but then there's pictures that we've chosen cos erm flowers that we've chosen</u>
<u n="155" who="S0023">furniture</u>
<u n="156" who="S0022">yeah there's furniture that we've chosen and and it's they all reflect to a greater or lesser extent our taste and our what we like</u>
<u n="157" who="S0023">it's like an extension of yourself in a way isn't it? The house</u>
<u n="158" who="S0022">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0023">I suppose that's what it is <pause dur="short"/> when you walk in to someone's home for the first time you know you get a very strong impression based on what you see as to what kind of person they are <pause dur="short"/> you get huge amount of clues don't you when you see</u>
<u n="160" who="S0022">I find it really really odd when I walk into people's houses and there's no</u>
<u n="161" who="S0023">oh stark places right yeah I know</u>
<u n="162" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah but there's like no it's no reflection of them it's just it it seems to be</u>
<u n="163" who="S0023">like a show home you mean</u>
<u n="164" who="S0022">I'm not sure I mean I think sometimes you can get a sort of you can get that show home effect but but more I would say erm don't need to determine is the right word but there's no sort of any any <trunc>i</trunc> any sense of making things decorative or in some way other than totally <trunc>utilitar</trunc></u>
<u n="165" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0022">I find it odd going to people's house when there's absolutely no attempt to sort of style or or colour or but then that's quite important to me so</u>
<u n="167" who="S0023">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know cos I don't have the knowledge or the time or or the interest to do it but yeah maybe they</u>
<u n="168" who="S0022" trans="overlap">but you like it though don't you?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0023">oh I love it and I wouldn't say that I was totally ignorant  of the  of the need for it but certainly didn't have the skills and arrangement ideas of how to arrange colours and so on like you have <pause dur="short"/> that's very clever <pause dur="short"/> on the other hand I can do DIY which helps doesn't it? So</u>
<u n="170" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes it does</u>
<u n="171" who="S0023">we put the two together and you've got the best er best of both worlds hopefully <pause dur="short"/> handy Andy you know</u>
<u n="172" who="S0022"><unclear/> programme</u>
<u n="173" who="S0023">no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0022">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0023">okay that's all I was going to say on that one</u>
<u n="176" who="S0022">okay <pause dur="short"/> who is? Is it me next or you?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0023">oh I'll pick one <pause dur="short"/> let's have a look</u>
<u n="178" who="S0022">you you pick one</u>
<u n="179" who="S0023">erm oh we've done that one <pause dur="short"/> what does your perfect day look like?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Erm perfect day is oh it certainly not a day I have to get up really early <pause dur="short"/> or it I tell you what it might be oh yes it could be erm in a hotel waking up in a gorgeous hotel and there's a lovely day outside lovely maybe it's sort of spring so it's like sunny but it's not hot hot</u>
<u n="181" who="S0023">mm</u>
<u n="182" who="S0022">and then you get a lovely breakfast brought to your room and so you put on a nice fluffy robe and you go and have your breakfast and you sit there</u>
<u n="183" who="S0023" trans="overlap">would it  would it  have a balcony maybe that you could sit on outside in the sun in private?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0022" trans="overlap">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> sit on <pause dur="short"/> yes and <pause dur="short"/> ah overlooking the sea like Saint <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0023">oh yes <unclear/> that's lovely</u>
<u n="186" who="S0022">oh yes and you might get because it might be a special occasion you might get a little glass of fizz with your breakfast</u>
<u n="187" who="S0023" trans="overlap">oh okay it's never to early to start with that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0022">and then you know sometimes it's a tricky one sometimes it's nice to have things planned but then sometimes I can really enjoy just not having any specific agenda and just sort of erm <trunc>ma</trunc> maybe mooching around the shops or going have a look at something and then having a nice lunch and or maybe lazing by the pool or something like that</u>
<u n="189" who="S0023" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0022">so it wouldn't be  it wouldn't be  totally devoid of doing stuff <pause dur="short"/> but I think there's something lovely about not having a fixed agenda and kind of  kind of  doing what you feel like at the time</u>
<u n="191" who="S0023">yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="192" who="S0022">what do you think? What's your perfect day?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0023">it's a good question <pause dur="short"/> some ways you want to say well the perfect day would be the day when you feel the happiest because you know something has happened so obviously our wedding day would be my perfect day</u>
<u n="194" who="S0022">thank you my love</u>
<u n="195" who="S0023">but we can't repeat that I don't think that's what the question's exactly about except we might renew our vows but that's you know that's another occasion</u>
<u n="196" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0023">er yes it's sort of a day you could  you could  have you know by design as opposed to say things that happen very rarely <pause dur="short"/> er yeah I think it's <trunc>be</trunc> because of you know working so hard and being out of the house all the time there is something very charming about relaxing and I although I'm a man I'm prepared to admit that I like spas</u>
<u n="198" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah you know what we're I was thinking we're it's ages since I've we've been to a spa <pause dur="short"/> we should go</u>
<u n="199" who="S0023" trans="overlap">it is rather <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well we've got <anon type="place"/> relatively on our doorstop <pause dur="short"/> we just need to get a few quid together and go there <pause dur="short"/> that's lovely <pause dur="short"/> that's my favourite place <pause dur="short"/> wokingham's okay but it's not as private</u>
<u n="200" who="S0022">no it's not <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> quite expensive though</u>
<u n="201" who="S0023">yeah but that's the reason why it's exclusive you see</u>
<u n="202" who="S0022" trans="overlap"><unclear/> That's true</u>
<u n="203" who="S0023">but it's got wonderful facilities there <pause dur="short"/> I really like it there</u>
<u n="204" who="S0022">it does</u>
<u n="205" who="S0023"><unclear/> some of my favourite times have been going to spa you know obviously having done loads of work to justify it and earn the money and then going to a spa and then with a big fat Harry Potter book of course there won't be any new ones of those and then just drowning myself</u>
<u n="206" who="S0022" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> she's writing a new novel though for adults</u>
<u n="207" who="S0023">oh good</u>
<u n="208" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0023">you know and then just drowning yourself in the book in a sense</u>
<u n="210" who="S0022">okay</u>
<u n="211" who="S0023">you know no I mean figuratively</u>
<u n="212" who="S0022">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="213" who="S0023">so you just immerse yourself is the word sorry not drown <pause dur="short"/> immerse yourself in the  in a  in a really book and then have nothing much else to do <pause dur="short"/> that would be nice</u>
<u n="214" who="S0022" trans="overlap">the trouble is with <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I really love the spa but I just I don't really like the food at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0023" trans="overlap">you don't like the food do you <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> you can always take a sandwich <pause dur="short"/> take a packed lunch</u>
<u n="216" who="S0022" trans="overlap">so we should erm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind the food in the erm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0023">or the popcorn in the cinema</u>
<u n="218" who="S0022">yeah I don't mind the food in the er spa place though</u>
<u n="219" who="S0023">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0022">but we should there's a new place near <trunc>Hamp</trunc> in erm in Hampshire er er called <anon type="place"/> erm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0023">oh towards the erm The New Forest or in The New Forest</u>
<u n="222" who="S0022">it's at <anon type="place"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's always in the <trunc>p</trunc> it's always in the papers <pause dur="short"/> I think it's quite expensive <pause dur="short"/> although Mr and Mrs Smith as in the website Mr and Mrs Smith they had <unclear/> Glen erm two nights for the price of one</u>
<u n="223" who="S0023">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's amazing value <pause dur="short"/> it's quite an expensive place <pause dur="short"/> is it? I bet it's a limited offer <pause dur="short"/> certain season etcetera</u>
<u n="224" who="S0022" trans="overlap">probably yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0023">but that might be a good opportunity to go there because it's so expensive otherwise</u>
<u n="226" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh I could really fancy just lazing about <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="227" who="S0023" trans="overlap">is there a spa there? At <unclear/> Glen</u>
<u n="228" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay well look we're going to have some free time soon probably so er that might be a good thing</u>
<u n="230" who="S0022"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I could fancy be it would be lovely to go somewhere and oh if we can get two nights that would be brilliant because you could in effect have three days by the spa <pause dur="short"/> ah how lovely would that be?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0023">I do also enjoy days when you have planned loads and you get loads achieved and you come home and think did we really manage to do all that?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0022">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0023">but as the mood takes you at the moment yeah I would go for the more relaxing one but</u>
<u n="234" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0023">yeah there is something good about change is as good as a rest <pause dur="short"/> that is true as well <pause dur="short"/> so I could  I could  do that <pause dur="short"/> so you're going somewhere for the first time <pause dur="short"/> that's amazing like say Rome or Venice <pause dur="short"/> that's just mind-blowing <pause dur="short"/> that's that's an amazing thing to do</u>
<u n="236" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0023">but there are only so many cities like that that you actually go to so I'd find us more of those probably <pause dur="short"/> that would be another goal</u>
<u n="238" who="S0022" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0023">it's just that they're really impressive <pause dur="short"/> I would really like to go to Istanbul sometime <pause dur="short"/> is it still called that? Is it still called that or something else?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0022" trans="overlap">would you? Yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0023">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well just briefly but you know you can dig dig into the history of it <pause dur="short"/> it's got lots of Roman architecture and Greek architecture and all sorts of things still going there <pause dur="short"/> it would be interesting</u>
<u n="242" who="S0022">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0023">anyway that's our twenty-two minutes that will do for now I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0022" trans="overlap">is it?</u>
</body>
</text>
