<text id="SXC6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:37:28</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-05-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0653 S0654 S0655</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s room, Comberton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>ANON’s cartoon, hashtags, @, Facebook, Twitter, trending topics, social media, drawing using computers, films, anthropomorphic characters, colours, books, being naked, the Great Birds of Paradise</topics>
		<activity>Family talking about cartoons and social media</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0653">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dartford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0654">
				<exactage>7</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0655">
				<exactage>9</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury St Edmunds</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0653">okay so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can you tell us about can you stop doing Lego and about your cartoon?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0655">oh yeah well my cartoon is called The Adventures of Bob and</u>
<u n="3" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="4" who="S0654">the characters are Mummy Guy Mummy Guy's mummy which is possibly the daddy although it's a mummy</u>
<u n="5" who="S0653">oh I see the okay</u>
<u n="6" who="S0655">and then there's a microphone not a character cos it's down there Snail Random Explorer Angel in Training James Pond who is also known as double 0 seven point five one six and there's Stick Man from another comic Angry Bighead and Angry Bighead's clone and Bob</u>
<u n="7" who="S0653">okay so Stick Man is from another one</u>
<u n="8" who="S0655" trans="overlap">another comic</u>
<u n="9" who="S0653">of the comics that you have written?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0655">no it's <trunc>f</trunc>from a random other comic</u>
<u n="11" who="S0653"><trunc>j</trunc> well what comic?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0655">I have no idea it's just a Stick Man comic</u>
<u n="13" who="S0653">oh I see but he's made up? okay</u>
<u n="14" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0653">yes tell me take me through the story?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0655">okay shall I read it out?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0653">well yeah go on</u>
<u n="18" who="S0655">okay have you heard about Bob and Angel in Training? yeah I heard they're awesome if that's true then why are we on a plane? er on the ground yeah blast yahoo ooph where am I? I'm Lucy Agent in Training ah? and where are we? in here cheese</u>
<u n="19" who="S0653">why are they thinking about cheese?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0655">no he thinks he's in a giant piece of cheese</u>
<u n="21" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0655">for some reason</u>
<u n="23" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="24" who="S0655">you've been chosen to go find a mummy what? gross gross in Egypt stay quiet</u>
<u n="25" who="S0653">don't whisper cos we can't here</u>
<u n="26" who="S0655">stay quiet stay quiet er hello somebody? agh wow I'm hungry no have dinner with me run that's a dance safe huh ring ring my phone at Angel in Training did you find the mummy? at mummy why did you run away from me? hashtag mummy coffin at coffin er at James Pond I'm double 0 I'm double 0 seven point five one six contacts reply like <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0653">this is a crazy comic</u>
<u n="28" who="S0655">the end yey</u>
<u n="29" who="S0654"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can you actually read it again?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0653">that's alright we'll have a bit why why are there ats and hashtags in it and stuff?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0655">that's <trunc>h</trunc> that's Facebook</u>
<u n="32" who="S0653">oh he's got a Facebook page?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0655">yeah he's my phone <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0653">did you know that it used to just be Twitter that had all the ats and hashtags and stuff? but it has it has reached Facebook and people are using hashtags and ats and stuff like that so then you get topics that are called trending topics so people put hashtag for lots of things and it's a public post and and it so say a very famous person dies everyone would put a hashtag about that and then it means that it is trending and that you can see the trends that people are talking about <pause dur="short"/> gosh so you're putting social media into your comic?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0654">can you read it again I didn't</u>
<u n="37" who="S0655" trans="overlap">it's very short and very random</u>
<u n="38" who="S0654" trans="overlap">because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I couldn't I couldn't keep up with what you're saying</u>
<u n="39" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and there's if you were wondering I did have every single character in I had James Pond on Facebook</u>
<u n="40" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="41" who="S0655">I had coffin on Facebook and if you noticed there's Random Explorer</u>
<u n="42" who="S0654">what about microphone?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0655">microphone not a character</u>
<u n="44" who="S0653">why do you have the microphone on your list of characters then?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0655" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="46" who="S0653">just to be a bit weird?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0655">erm that Mummy Guy's mummy is singing <shift new="singing"/> I'm alive <shift new="normal"/> when she's dead</u>
<u n="48" who="S0653" trans="overlap">okay that's nice</u>
<u n="49" who="S0655">but and a dead person</u>
<u n="50" who="S0653">so this is a mummified person?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0655">a mummified person</u>
<u n="52" who="S0653">so is this what's all inside your head then?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0655">erm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0653">I don't know if I want to know</u>
<u n="55" who="S0654" trans="overlap">it's not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0653">it's scary isn't it?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0655">it's not what's in my head</u>
<u n="58" who="S0653">Lucy the Angel in Training</u>
<u n="59" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0653">looks a little bit scary though don't you think?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0654">why is she scary?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0653">I don't know she looks a bit skeleton-like in her face she looks cute on the main character list why are they thinking of cheese when someone said it's heaven? do they like cheese?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0655" trans="overlap">no they never said it's heaven she said I'm Lucy Angel in Training</u>
<u n="64" who="S0653">why are they thinking about cheese?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0655">because Bob's an idiot</u>
<u n="66" who="S0653">oh this is erm this is a very postmodern avant-garde type thing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'd definitely say it's post</u>
<u n="67" who="S0654" trans="overlap">can you read it again cos I <unclear>like it</unclear></u>
<u n="68" who="S0653" trans="overlap">no he can read it again later</u>
<u n="69" who="S0654">also I couldn't keep up so <unclear/> where are you?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0655">it is a very bad story though</u>
<u n="71" who="S0653">yes I don't think you're meant to be able to keep up with it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos it</u>
<u n="72" who="S0654" trans="overlap">are you?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0653">it doesn't really make any a lot of sense does it?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no I couldn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><unclear/> a more random one I like it</u>
<u n="76" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I was I was listening but I didn't know where I was looking at the pictures as well but at some point I got stuck on the pictures there</u>
<u n="77" who="S0653">don't take any more Lego out leave them in there and you just need to select the Lego one bit at a time</u>
<u n="78" who="S0655">I didn't really have I could only fit it on that page because</u>
<u n="79" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I love it</u>
<u n="80" who="S0655">so I couldn't really do much of a story</u>
<u n="81" who="S0654">I want <unclear/> can you <unclear/> comic</u>
<u n="82" who="S0653" trans="overlap">but there is a story there</u>
<u n="83" who="S0654">because I like it?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0653">you like it?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0653">there is a story story there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's lovely and it's got</u>
<u n="87" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I was</u>
<u n="88" who="S0653">a beginning a middle and an end</u>
<u n="89" who="S0655">I was planning to do a different story but then I found out how much how little I had left so I</u>
<u n="90" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0655">couldn't properly do Mummy Guy</u>
<u n="92" who="S0653">well you could always have done two pages <pause dur="short"/> no no but on a new piece of paper</u>
<u n="93" who="S0655">true</u>
<u n="94" who="S0653">but that's partly why writers plan isn't it so they can <trunc>wo</trunc>work out do you know it's called storyboarding?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0655">storyboarding</u>
<u n="96" who="S0654">what's storyboarding?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0653">when you literally do write sort of you are drawing squares and in those squares you work out what's gonna happen in terms of the action so if you're doing a cartoon you know that you've got you need twelve squares for the action but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this is terrific cos you did this all on your own</u>
<u n="98" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0653">it's lovely</u>
<u n="100" who="S0655">and I did do it out of my mind as well</u>
<u n="101" who="S0653">that's my concern to be honest</u>
<u n="102" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I love you</u>
<u n="103" who="S0655" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0653" trans="overlap">cos it's crazy no I love it I love it</u>
<u n="105" who="S0654">and I also love <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0653">and do you know what? when you are like twenty-nine and you look back and you think wow I did this when I was just nine</u>
<u n="107" who="S0655" trans="overlap">well if</u>
<u n="108" who="S0653">you'll be very impressed</u>
<u n="109" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> probably</u>
<u n="110" who="S0654">yeah maybe when you <unclear/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0655" trans="overlap">although twenty-nine I wonder how erm far I'll be in the drawing world or the <trunc>egle</trunc> electronics world?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0653">yeah well and I was gonna say that's the easier thing about doing cartoons when you can do it using computers because then <trunc>i</trunc>if you run out of space it doesn't matter you can sort of sort it all out it's like when people used typewriters and I think I've shown you and they made a mistake and it's like er man and that's when they invented Tippex to that white liquid fluid to go over mistakes because if you'd written a whole letter out typed a whole letter out and you made one mistake you didn't want to rewrite the entire document whereas as a <trunc>com</trunc> on a computer if you make a mistake you just go back and change it</u>
<u n="113" who="S0655">yeah that's why people can go really fast on the computer</u>
<u n="114" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0655">but when they're typing they make loads of mistakes and they go over them</u>
<u n="116" who="S0653">yeah I mean if you get if you do a lot of typing you do get used to it and you don't make too many mistakes I'm pretty good at not making too many mistakes but I I do make a few but yes as you say it's the getting it down on the on that page that you can do without worrying about spelling and things so much</u>
<u n="117" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0653">I love it but you have you got yes so did you look at the <trunc>c</trunc> book that I gave you for Christmas about how to draw cartoons and stuff?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="120" who="S0653">did you do that?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0655">I did</u>
<u n="122" who="S0653">ah is there a space in there to draw cartoons too?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0655">erm let's have a little check <pause dur="short"/> I think there probably was</u>
<u n="124" who="S0654">no remember when you did that pirate book that pirate story?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0653">which?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0654">he did a pirate story</u>
<u n="127" who="S0653" trans="overlap">you did a pirate story? did you?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0655">I think so I might have done it in here</u>
<u n="129" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="130" who="S0655">while <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing Lego I couldn't in fact write in here <pause dur="short"/> oh those er are cartoon characters and you can see them there's even Danger Mouse</u>
<u n="131" who="S0653">ah but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yours is amazing I really like it</u>
<u n="132" who="S0654">and Mickey Mouse</u>
<u n="133" who="S0653">you're and Mickey Mouse yes</u>
<u n="134" who="S0655">yeah expressions a basic face</u>
<u n="135" who="S0653">oh yes</u>
<u n="136" who="S0653">that you can do for</u>
<u n="137" who="S0653" trans="overlap">because you're very good at making characters up aren't you and the story?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0654" trans="overlap">he's also very handsome</u>
<u n="139" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yes I'm amazing at characters</u>
<u n="140" who="S0653">so that's not an issue is it? but this is a good all-round guide to how to</u>
<u n="141" who="S0654" trans="overlap">he's also handsome</u>
<u n="142" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="145" who="S0653">that well how was that useful in terms of his cartoon career <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0654">he's got a nice face and it'll sell books</u>
<u n="147" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0653">well that is actually true a pretty face does help to sell books did you know that my friend <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was originally a cartoonist <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="150" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0654">oh by the way mum I want to make up how to make a style er a Millennium Falcon bed and then do it</u>
<u n="152" who="S0653">a Millennium Falcon bed?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0654">yes</u>
<u n="154" who="S0653">like an actual real bed?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0654">yes</u>
<u n="156" who="S0653">oh why do you want that is that for when? Asterix and Obelix you've never read them but they were my that was all I read when I was your age <pause dur="short"/> I should totally get one ooh now what I was gonna say to you was we were going to go into the bookshop weren't we this weekend and</u>
<u n="157" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0653">with all our saved pennies and buy some books however we are now going to go to Linton Book festival so Heffers will be selling books there so we could go there couldn't we</u>
<u n="159" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0653">and get some books?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0654">mm this is very comfy</u>
<u n="162" who="S0653">I'm very comfy but you know <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0653">who writes Goth Girl?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0653">so he also was a cartoonist</u>
<u n="167" who="S0654" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="168" who="S0653">and he and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> used to work together on newspapers doing cartoons</u>
<u n="169" who="S0654">cool</u>
<u n="170" who="S0653">and he was the one that said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know what you should write a story for children</u>
<u n="171" who="S0654" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="172" who="S0653">so that's why <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ended up doing that</u>
<u n="173" who="S0654">yay</u>
<u n="174" who="S0653">but but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would be very impressed with your cartoons <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0654">oh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0655">what even at <trunc>h</trunc> would he compare that to his age <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0653" trans="overlap">ooh I don't know when he started actually shall I take a photograph of some of them and like one particular character</u>
<u n="178" who="S0655" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0654">or a little bit and then I can put it on Facebook and I'll ask him</u>
<u n="180" who="S0654" trans="overlap">hey that looks like Gazelle</u>
<u n="181" who="S0653">gazelle?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0653" trans="overlap">well it's actually a giraffe isn't it?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0654">I like giraffes</u>
<u n="185" who="S0653" trans="overlap">but who's is it is Gazelle a character?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0653" trans="overlap">erm Gazelle is a <trunc>per</trunc> is a</u>
<u n="188" who="S0653" trans="overlap">a character?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0655">real person in Zoetropolis</u>
<u n="190" who="S0654">she actually is she actually</u>
<u n="191" who="S0653" trans="overlap">is she a girl or an animal?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0654">she's an animal and she's and she's</u>
<u n="193" who="S0655" trans="overlap">an animal</u>
<u n="194" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right she's not a person then is she?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0654">actually and also</u>
<u n="196" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and she is a singer</u>
<u n="197" who="S0654">I wonder if they actually chose a famous popstar?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0653">ooh <trunc>wha</trunc>what to to do the voice?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0654" trans="overlap">cos cost she actually sings</u>
<u n="200" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah Gazelle is a famous popstar</u>
<u n="201" who="S0654" trans="overlap">try every erm and there's an actual song called Try Everything</u>
<u n="202" who="S0653">well</u>
<u n="203" who="S0654" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> try everything oh oh oh oh oh <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0653">what I can reveal to you is sometimes in films they sometimes have one person doing the voice and then another person doing the singing part but they could well have got a singer to do both the the singing and the speaking part</u>
<u n="205" who="S0654">I definitely knew it was the same person because</u>
<u n="206" who="S0653" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="207" who="S0654"><unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0653">well well I think it would be interesting</u>
<u n="209" who="S0654" trans="overlap">these pages are hard to turn</u>
<u n="210" who="S0653">yeah don't do that cos that's too noisy but Gazelle is a nice name actually isn't it?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0654">yeah Gazelle isn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0653">ah and she's an anthropomorphic character</u>
<u n="213" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0653">do you know what that means? can you remember?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0655" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="216" who="S0654">made up?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0653">no it's when they make an animal or something like that to be human-like be person-like</u>
<u n="218" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0654">also they do</u>
<u n="220" who="S0653" trans="overlap">they give it human characteristics</u>
<u n="221" who="S0654" trans="overlap">also in New York</u>
<u n="222" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0654"><trunc>Zootrop</trunc> a lot of Zoetropolis is based on New York because of the rabbit has the most tiniest car you can get those in <trunc>Zootr</trunc> and you can get those in New York</u>
<u n="224" who="S0653">like a taxi? or just a car?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0654">just a <trunc>poli</trunc></u>
<u n="226" who="S0655" trans="overlap">a really really small car</u>
<u n="227" who="S0654">er a really small police car</u>
<u n="228" who="S0653">is this the story of the sloth?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="230" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="231" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0655">what? do you mean?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0653">what's the Zoetropolis one?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0654">the Zoetropolis one you know that's</u>
<u n="235" who="S0655">it does have Flash who's a sloth</u>
<u n="236" who="S0653">right so when I said is it the one with the sloth and you said no</u>
<u n="237" who="S0655">I thought you said is it the one with the sloth who jumps off the cliff</u>
<u n="238" who="S0653">you didn't think I said that cos I blatantly didn't say anything like that at all</u>
<u n="239" who="S0655"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0653">but it's the one the sort of police one and he works at a bank the sloth?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0654">yes</u>
<u n="242" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0654">and do you know what? at the end</u>
<u n="244" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I really want to see that</u>
<u n="245" who="S0654">do you know why he's called Flash?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0653">cos he's quite slow?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0654">he's a race car driver</u>
<u n="249" who="S0655">yeah he's a really really fast car driver</u>
<u n="250" who="S0653" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0653">oh is he? oh yes I remember you telling me this about about him very strange</u>
<u n="253" who="S0655"><unclear/> yeah it's just a funny joke at the end</u>
<u n="254" who="S0654" trans="overlap">also at the end</u>
<u n="255" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="256" who="S0654">she has a really really big car</u>
<u n="257" who="S0653">ah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0654">it's really big</u>
<u n="259" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0653">mind out so</u>
<u n="261" who="S0654">I've finished my model</u>
<u n="262" who="S0653">oh it's lovely so describe it to me?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0654">well <unclear/> you see these bits here?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0654">they can shoot out water</u>
<u n="266" who="S0653">right</u>
<u n="267" who="S0654">the grey bits</u>
<u n="268" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0654">they can shoot out rock</u>
<u n="270" who="S0653" trans="overlap">rock</u>
<u n="271" who="S0654">the brown bits</u>
<u n="272" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0654">they can shoot out like vines and stuff</u>
<u n="274" who="S0653">vines oh like creepers?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0654">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0653" trans="overlap">nice things or nasty things?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0654">erm nice and nasty</u>
<u n="278" who="S0653">you might want a little supportive <trunc>p</trunc></u>
<u n="279" who="S0654" trans="overlap">this can shoot out fire</u>
<u n="280" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="281" who="S0654">and these can shoot out poisonous no these can shoot out erm yeah poison</u>
<u n="282" who="S0653">poison dart <trunc>f</trunc> look this is coming apart you need to fix it underneath</u>
<u n="283" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0654">it is supposed to come apart because you can levitate</u>
<u n="285" who="S0653">oh cos you can levitate? oh cool now</u>
<u n="286" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I just <unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0653">I was doing colours with my students last week can you think of a different way to describe the some of the colours there?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0654">scarlet red</u>
<u n="289" who="S0653">er lovely</u>
<u n="290" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0654">earth brown</u>
<u n="292" who="S0653">lovely description</u>
<u n="293" who="S0655">sky blue</u>
<u n="294" who="S0653">sky blue yes very much so</u>
<u n="295" who="S0654">waterfall blue</u>
<u n="296" who="S0653">ah that's lovely</u>
<u n="297" who="S0655">peacock blue</u>
<u n="298" who="S0653">peacock blue yes that's the colour for me</u>
<u n="299" who="S0654">midnight black</u>
<u n="300" who="S0653"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <pause dur="short"/> what about yellow? I always think of mustard for that one</u>
<u n="301" who="S0655">golden yellow</u>
<u n="302" who="S0654" trans="overlap">vivid</u>
<u n="303" who="S0653">vivid yes</u>
<u n="304" who="S0655" trans="overlap">golden yellow</u>
<u n="305" who="S0653">golden yellow</u>
<u n="306" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0653">but vivid is a <trunc>des</trunc> sort of er <trunc>a</trunc>about a colour but can you think of a yellow colour that you could use in er instead of it?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0655">gold</u>
<u n="309" who="S0653">yes you've got gold which is a good one what do you think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? what does it remind you of?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0655"><unclear>trying to make a car with square wheels</unclear></u>
<u n="311" who="S0654" trans="overlap">flower yellow</u>
<u n="312" who="S0653">yeah maybe like a buttercup</u>
<u n="313" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0653">or a daffodil</u>
<u n="315" who="S0654" trans="overlap">buttercup yellow</u>
<u n="316" who="S0653">do you remember who was it that used to say daffolilliums for daffodils was it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0654">daffolilliums me</u>
<u n="318" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I think that was possibly me</u>
<u n="319" who="S0654">no also it erm then rock grey</u>
<u n="320" who="S0653">you could say granite grey for that</u>
<u n="321" who="S0654" trans="overlap">granite grey</u>
<u n="322" who="S0653">cos that's a type of rock and you don't have to say red you could just say scarlet you don't need to say scarlet red</u>
<u n="323" who="S0655">I just thought of a really good one</u>
<u n="324" who="S0654" trans="overlap">okay erm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0653" trans="overlap">you've thought of a good one?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0654">this is white</u>
<u n="327" who="S0653">hang on</u>
<u n="328" who="S0655">marble black</u>
<u n="329" who="S0653">yes you could definitely have that</u>
<u n="330" who="S0654">marble white</u>
<u n="331" who="S0653">yes marble can be both but you could have both you could just say as white as marble</u>
<u n="332" who="S0654" trans="overlap">but okay then you should teach your words erm so erm how about turquoise?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0653">that's a lovely word yes vermillion we like don't we?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0654">vermillion?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0653">vermillion that's one of</u>
<u n="336" who="S0655" trans="overlap">what is it?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0653">that's a type of red I thought that was one that was in your Minecraft? oh no it's obsidian is the random word that you know but vermillion is a very rich red</u>
<u n="338" who="S0654">also</u>
<u n="339" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0654">there's erm maroon</u>
<u n="341" who="S0653">maroon yes which is a type of purple</u>
<u n="342" who="S0654">also brown</u>
<u n="343" who="S0653">mm mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0654">no there's some brown pens at school which are called maroon</u>
<u n="345" who="S0653">no well that's wrong cos maroon is a very dark purple</u>
<u n="346" who="S0655">yeah I know</u>
<u n="347" who="S0654" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="348" who="S0655">it's not proper brown</u>
<u n="349" who="S0653">cos remember I've said my joke there was a ship carrying red paint and a ship carrying blue paint they crashed into each other and all the sailors were marooned do you get it?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0654">they turn purple yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0654">yeah like they'll go oh ooh I'm sexy</u>
<u n="353" who="S0653">why do you keep saying things are sexy?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0653">you're only seven</u>
<u n="356" who="S0654">I know you taught</u>
<u n="357" who="S0653" trans="overlap">is it your favourite <trunc>wor</trunc>? I didn't teach you</u>
<u n="358" who="S0654" trans="overlap">it's my favourite word</u>
<u n="359" who="S0653">I didn't <trunc>s</trunc> I didn't say hey <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you wanna learn a really useful word in your life?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0654">you <vocal desc="laugh"/> you taught us widdle</u>
<u n="361" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah you were the one who</u>
<u n="362" who="S0654">and stool</u>
<u n="363" who="S0655">if it wasn't if it wasn't for you we wouldn't know the word existed</u>
<u n="364" who="S0653">sit up but what what's the context what was I talking about at the time?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0654"><unclear/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0655" trans="overlap">you were talking about you when you when you mentioned sexy</u>
<u n="367" who="S0654" trans="overlap">about how there was erm a film about a little programme about how you about how</u>
<u n="368" who="S0655" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0654">about people having sex</u>
<u n="370" who="S0653">what?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0655">yeah it's true</u>
<u n="372" who="S0653">did I?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0655" trans="overlap">remember when you were telling us that it doesn't erm tell you how to have sex properly</u>
<u n="375" who="S0653">huh no I don't remember this conversation at all</u>
<u n="376" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0653">was I very tired?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="379" who="S0653">what was the <trunc>f</trunc> programme about?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0655">it was about we were talking about babies and then you said that on Youtube you can look at how to have sex but it doesn't show it properly</u>
<u n="381" who="S0654">and people just started wanting to have things like they like when they're trying to do it exactly like that</u>
<u n="382" who="S0653">I was yes I was talking about how children <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s age are watching something called pornography</u>
<u n="383" who="S0654">what's pornography?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0653">which is what I've so yes which is people having</u>
<u n="385" who="S0654" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="386" who="S0653">er they get paid to have sex and it yes</u>
<u n="387" who="S0655">ah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0653">and yeah often the women are very badly treated and it hurts and it's not very nice erm and</u>
<u n="389" who="S0654">ah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0653">and <trunc>ye</trunc>yes you're absolutely right all the boys that watch it then think that that is how you're supposed to have sex all the time and the girls watch it and think that they must behave like the the women in the films which is not very nice usually so that's the correct context</u>
<u n="391" who="S0654"><unclear>they hurt them</unclear></u>
<u n="392" who="S0653">and that's called parenting whereas the way you were saying it sounded like I was just saying yeah there's this programme that shows you how to have sex but it doesn't show you how to have sex properly</u>
<u n="393" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0653">and that means it's like alarm bells are going off and I'm thinking what on earth were we talking about and when did that conversation occur? and so I understand and I was just drawing your attention to it because</u>
<u n="395" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0653">shh I want you to know about this so if you do encounter this at some point with your friends then you will be aware of it and hopefully</u>
<u n="397" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0653">stop it <trunc>hope</trunc> don't do that so noisy and if you do if somebody shows you that I hope that you will say I don't want to see it</u>
<u n="399" who="S0655">yeah it's gross</u>
<u n="400" who="S0653">it's gross but also the people involved are often in a lot of pain it's not nice</u>
<u n="401" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0653" trans="overlap">sorry?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0653">I beg your pardon? sorry?</u>
<u n="405" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0655">I said</u>
<u n="407" who="S0653">sorry? what did you say? no I do I genuinely didn't hear</u>
<u n="408" who="S0655">I randomly sang a song</u>
<u n="409" who="S0653">you randomly sang a song? was it a silly song?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0653">do we need to hear it?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="413" who="S0653">no</u>
<u n="414" who="S0655">my tummy's vibrating</u>
<u n="415" who="S0653">your tummy's so what kind of things are you gonna say to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0655">what?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0653">have you got lots of questions?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0655">yes</u>
<u n="419" who="S0653">are they about the books that we haven't read yet cos she may not be able to tell you?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="421" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="422" who="S0653">oh okay what are your questions then?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0655">what happened to the pigster?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0653">to?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0655">the pigster</u>
<u n="426" who="S0653">who's the pigster?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0655">Mr Piggott</u>
<u n="428" who="S0653">oh is he not still working at the museum or was he arrested?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0653">huh that's a very good question we could ask her</u>
<u n="431" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="432" who="S0654" trans="overlap">also</u>
<u n="433" who="S0655">but where which prison was he sent to what happened to him?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0655">is he planning a comeback?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0654">is red is red fox <unclear/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0655">oh yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0653">who's red fox?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0655">you <trunc>rea</trunc> are you listening to these books?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0653">yeah but we've read like five now</u>
<u n="442" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0654" trans="overlap">red fox the one who shot er the one who shot</u>
<u n="444" who="S0655"><trunc>al</trunc>almost shot Jack</u>
<u n="445" who="S0653">the Australian?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0653">he oh Simon Fox?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0653">not red fox</u>
<u n="450" who="S0654">I call him red fox <unclear/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0653">you don't call him red fox</u>
<u n="452" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I call him red fox cos he just gets scabs on his head all the time</u>
<u n="453" who="S0653">because he what?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0654">he just gets like he's got a little</u>
<u n="455" who="S0653">he's got a scar on his face yes but I didn't if you had said Simon Fox I would have known who he was</u>
<u n="456" who="S0654" trans="overlap">he doesn't actually have a scar</u>
<u n="457" who="S0653">he does he does have a mark on his face doesn't he?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="459" who="S0653">oh alright well thanks for your brilliant description then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's great erm what other questions will you ask her?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0655">what's happened to Mrs Roberts?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0654" trans="overlap">erm what's happened to</u>
<u n="462" who="S0653" trans="overlap">wait well I think we're gonna find out what happened to Mrs Roberts in this book</u>
<u n="463" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah and what's happened to Bella <pause dur="short"/> erm Bianca?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and what happened to the other guy?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0653">the two erm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0655" trans="overlap">idiots</u>
<u n="468" who="S0653">Brazilian art thieves</u>
<u n="469" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0653">I think it would be good to get a list of all these questions</u>
<u n="471" who="S0655">Brazilian bra thieves</u>
<u n="472" who="S0653">now sorry?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I said Brazilian bra thieves</u>
<u n="474" who="S0653">now she is doing at Linton a talk for children but that we can't make that because of your exam but then she's also</u>
<u n="475" who="S0655" trans="overlap">exam</u>
<u n="476" who="S0653">doing erm a discussion about how to be a writer so she's in charge of that and I'm sure we'll have time to speak to her later</u>
<u n="477" who="S0654">but we're not <unclear/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> so when I be thirty years old travel the world <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0653" trans="overlap">stop it and we'll still we'll see and we're gonna see my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who is lovely but you haven't read any of her books yet</u>
<u n="480" who="S0654" trans="overlap">ooh she sounds sweet</u>
<u n="481" who="S0653">and she yes she does sound sweet good good pun there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm perhaps you could get some candies for her she's lovely she's really nice and there's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0654">yeah can we get some candies for her?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I really hope she's not lactose intolerant or her name would be ironic</u>
<u n="484" who="S0653">well it wouldn't because there isn't any lactose in candy is there?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0655">no in chocolate</u>
<u n="486" who="S0653">yes but there isn't necessarily in candy we could make her some sweets that say candy and I was gonna say to you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my friend <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> has is there's a book being published in the summer called Mumnesia and you are going to love it</u>
<u n="487" who="S0654" trans="overlap">what is it about?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0653">it is about</u>
<u n="489" who="S0655" trans="overlap">a mum</u>
<u n="490" who="S0653">a girl and a mum and they lose their memories and then they get switched around or something so they end up having to so imagine if you were in my body and I was in your body and I had to go to school and pretend to be you and you had to go to work and pretend to be me</u>
<u n="491" who="S0655">that wouldn't be hard</u>
<u n="492" who="S0654">you're silly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0654">you're silly</u>
<u n="495" who="S0653">I'm silly? would you like it though?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="497" who="S0653">do you like going to work?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="499" who="S0653">you wouldn't?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="501" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I would I'd love it</u>
<u n="502" who="S0653">freedom you could go to the gym</u>
<u n="503" who="S0654">I wouldn't do that</u>
<u n="504" who="S0653">no?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="506" who="S0653">you could dye your hair like me</u>
<u n="507" who="S0654">don't want to do that</u>
<u n="508" who="S0653">you could stay up late</u>
<u n="509" who="S0654">I don't wanna do that</u>
<u n="510" who="S0653">you don't wanna do that are you quite happy being you?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0654">yeah cos I stay up late all night even though you don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0653">I do know because I check on you quite often <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would you like to swap places with me for a day?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0655">yes</u>
<u n="514" who="S0653">what would you get up to?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0655">I'd probably</u>
<u n="516" who="S0653" trans="overlap">ow <unclear/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0655">I would probably go out and spend loads of money on sweets</u>
<u n="518" who="S0653">oh good grief</u>
<u n="519" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0655">I'd go to <anon type="place"/> and buy the erm <anon type="place"/> and buy the shop</u>
<u n="521" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0655">and then I'd have all the sweet shippings in</u>
<u n="523" who="S0653">and would you just eat them all yourself without telling anybody or would you share them with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0655">well I'm the mum</u>
<u n="525" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0655">I'd be the mum it would be my special sweets and I'd be able to have special chocolate or I could erm er</u>
<u n="527" who="S0654" trans="overlap">mummy you could take</u>
<u n="528" who="S0653" trans="overlap">wait</u>
<u n="529" who="S0655">erm sell all your I could sell all your clothes and then when you switched back into my body you'd be like ah where have my clothes gone I can't go to work? going I can't go to commando this soon</u>
<u n="530" who="S0653">why would you be selling my clothes?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0655">cos I cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0653" trans="overlap">for more sweets?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0655">no I want I've always wanted to see you go commando</u>
<u n="534" who="S0653">I go commando at home quite a lot <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't wear</u>
<u n="535" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I saw you go naked once</u>
<u n="536" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0654">when you were in the shower I see <vocal desc="laugh"/> I saw you running around the house</u>
<u n="538" who="S0653">what naked? I'm often naked</u>
<u n="539" who="S0655">yes in the bath</u>
<u n="540" who="S0654">you do not need to share that with the world</u>
<u n="541" who="S0653">but I wasn't I was naked this morning when I came into your bedroom to show you my abs</u>
<u n="542" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0653">wasn't I?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0653">because I'm very proud of them</u>
<u n="546" who="S0654">but you do not</u>
<u n="547" who="S0655">but you do not need to share that with the world of cheese</u>
<u n="548" who="S0653">well I'm not planning on</u>
<u n="549" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I can't actually <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0653">do you know what it's called when you run around naked outside?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0655">it's going commando</u>
<u n="552" who="S0653">it's called streaking some people do that sometimes at football matches or cricket matches</u>
<u n="553" who="S0654">they go naked?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0655" trans="overlap">why? that's so stupid</u>
<u n="555" who="S0653">they take their clothes off and then run across the pitch and then people catch them and usually policemen and they wrestle them to the ground</u>
<u n="556" who="S0654">why?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0653">I don't know why anybody would go <trunc>s</trunc> doing you know streaking</u>
<u n="558" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I don't know why anyone would wrestle them down</u>
<u n="559" who="S0653" trans="overlap">no cos</u>
<u n="560" who="S0655">it would be different if it was a girl person going</u>
<u n="561" who="S0653" trans="overlap">to stop them causing a nuisance</u>
<u n="562" who="S0654">why are <unclear/> start doing it</u>
<u n="563" who="S0655" trans="overlap">why doesn't why doesn't the football player just shoot the football at their bum?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0653">oh would it be like Nuddy Ned <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we'd all just start doing?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0654">yeah let's do that as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0655" trans="overlap">can you imagine if it was contagious?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0653">what if everybody stripped off?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0653">shush with your blooming Lego yes right so long as it wasn't like in the snow</u>
<u n="570" who="S0654">ooh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah that <unclear/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0655">they'd wear see-through warm clothes so they could still see you their</u>
<u n="574" who="S0653" trans="overlap">stop it</u>
<u n="575" who="S0655">body parts so you'd know if you wanted to have sex with them</u>
<u n="576" who="S0653">er my god you've got sex on the brain at the age of nine</u>
<u n="577" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0653">well there there is</u>
<u n="579" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0653">there is a there is a very famous photographer who does take pictures of like hundreds and hundreds of people naked and then he was doing one er in Leicester this year</u>
<u n="581" who="S0655" trans="overlap">of you?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0653">and what he no and then he asked volunteers so everybody turned up to have their photo taken and then they had to take their clothes off the last minute and all kind of stand in like a regimented order</u>
<u n="583" who="S0655">what's regimented order?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0653">in like like soldiers all nice and neat so I think that would be really good fun to do actually</u>
<u n="585" who="S0655" trans="overlap">all nice and naked</u>
<u n="586" who="S0654">I'm not going to do that</u>
<u n="587" who="S0653">well I'm not asking you to do it so that's</u>
<u n="588" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I know cos people will see my vagina</u>
<u n="589" who="S0655" trans="overlap">all nice and neat all nice and naked</u>
<u n="590" who="S0653" trans="overlap">people first of all I don't think people are going to see your vagina <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0654" trans="overlap">well that's cos I wear knickers</u>
<u n="592" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and second of all</u>
<u n="593" who="S0653" trans="overlap">no because you're tiny and no one is going to be looking at that they might just be a photograph from the back</u>
<u n="594" who="S0654">what about my backside?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0653">what about your backside? well yes they might see that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos you would be naked</u>
<u n="596" who="S0654">yey <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="597" who="S0653">see I don't think you're that mind that</u>
<u n="598" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no you said blooming <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0653">I said what?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0654">blooming</u>
<u n="601" who="S0653">blooming?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0654">bloom bloom</u>
<u n="603" who="S0653">blooming Lego yes</u>
<u n="604" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0654" trans="overlap">blooming</u>
<u n="606" who="S0653">that's me not swearing</u>
<u n="607" who="S0654">what about bloom bloomers?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0655">Mr Bloom's <unclear/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0654" trans="overlap">blooming bloomers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0653">blooming bloomers or Mr Bloom from Mr Bloom's Nursery courtesy of Cbeebies</u>
<u n="611" who="S0654" trans="overlap">you said blooming</u>
<u n="612" who="S0655">or Mr Blooming Person</u>
<u n="613" who="S0653">you don't really watch Cbeebies any more do you?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0655">yes cos it's for babies</u>
<u n="615" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no I watch</u>
<u n="616" who="S0653">well it is for it is for sort of six and under really but</u>
<u n="617" who="S0655">for babies</u>
<u n="618" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I watch Pop which is for babies <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0653">mm good grief do you know what you're doing for Brownies tomorrow are you going for that walk soon or is that in June?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="621" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0654">I don't know</u>
<u n="623" who="S0653">are you looking forward to doing the walk?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="625" who="S0653">no I can't think so erm right are you going to remain sensible for a for the little bit please?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0655">or are you gonna go commando?</u>
<u n="627" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0653">good grief</u>
<u n="629" who="S0654">maybe</u>
<u n="630" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's like you've taken a funny drug</u>
<u n="631" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0653">a little pill that makes you giggle</u>
<u n="633" who="S0654">it's a <unclear/> what I like it depends what I want okay?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0655">what a funny drug?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0653">what do you want?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0654"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it depends what I feel like</u>
<u n="637" who="S0653">do you know they they used to and I don't know if they give it any more but in hospitals people used to give erm patients things</u>
<u n="638" who="S0655" trans="overlap">manners</u>
<u n="639" who="S0653">to relax them and there was a special gas and it was called laughing gas cos it would make people giggle</u>
<u n="640" who="S0654">ah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0653">it's like you have had some of that</u>
<u n="642" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0653">that's how it seems to me</u>
<u n="644" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't stop laughing</u>
<u n="645" who="S0653">you can't stop laughing well I'm glad you found your cardigan anyway when we sorted it all out who gave you that in the end by the way?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0655">Bob</u>
<u n="647" who="S0654">erm a girl who <unclear/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0653">but did when did she appear?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0654">well she was in the office and she</u>
<u n="650" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh did you go to the office then?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0655">she pulled it out of out of thin air</u>
<u n="652" who="S0654" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0653">I didn't know you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had gone to the actual office</u>
<u n="654" who="S0655">she's a magic monster</u>
<u n="655" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0653">did you go through the school to the office then? oh and what did she say? did she have a look and then realise?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0655" trans="overlap">she said that she was <unclear/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0653" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm not talking to you</u>
<u n="659" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no she she just gave it to me cos it said my name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0653">ah now can I ask you <pause dur="short"/> stop it now please</u>
<u n="661" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I've had a funny drug</u>
<u n="662" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or I won't allow you to do this any more</u>
<u n="663" who="S0655">I've had the laughing gas</u>
<u n="664" who="S0653">so you know I'm gonna have to dress up as a bird for this</u>
<u n="665" who="S0654" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0653">aerial hoop thing what are your costumes going to be? are you going to be ladybirds or unicorns or?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0655">a great bird of paradise</u>
<u n="668" who="S0653">or a caterpillar or a great bird of paradise</u>
<u n="669" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0653">you're gonna have to get your costume</u>
<u n="671" who="S0654" trans="overlap">a great bird of paradise</u>
<u n="672" who="S0655"><shift new="singing"/> a great bird of paradise <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0653" trans="overlap">together quite soon</u>
<u n="674" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah so we need to</u>
<u n="675" who="S0653">shh</u>
<u n="676" who="S0654">we need to dress up in black</u>
<u n="677" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="678" who="S0654">and we need to like get some puffy we need to like</u>
<u n="679" who="S0653" trans="overlap">we need to be able to look like a bird yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0654">get something over here like there</u>
<u n="681" who="S0653">no one is going to know who you are though</u>
<u n="682" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I'm thinking also I'm going to <unclear/> a chain which says I'm a great bird of paradise</u>
<u n="683" who="S0653" trans="overlap">hang on a minute I can't hear anything you've just said</u>
<u n="684" who="S0654" trans="overlap">we've got to get a chain which says</u>
<u n="685" who="S0653">a what?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0654">we might get a chain get a chain</u>
<u n="687" who="S0653" trans="overlap">a chain?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0655" trans="overlap">a chain</u>
<u n="689" who="S0654">that says I'm a great bird of great bird of paradise</u>
<u n="690" who="S0653">well nobody's gonna see that</u>
<u n="691" who="S0654" trans="overlap"><unclear/> get blue dots on here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and the blue and a big blob of <unclear>yorgenspere</unclear></u>
<u n="693" who="S0654" trans="overlap">you can have a blue and they can</u>
<u n="694" who="S0653" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0655">have a big blob of <unclear>yorgenspere</unclear></u>
<u n="696" who="S0654">and then we can have a blue carrot</u>
<u n="697" who="S0653">shush stop talking together at the same time what did you say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0655">I'm the big blob of <unclear>yorgenspere</unclear></u>
<u n="699" who="S0653">of what?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0655"><unclear>yorgenspere</unclear></u>
<u n="701" who="S0653">what is <unclear>yorgenspere</unclear>?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0655">a really weird place that I've just made up</u>
<u n="703" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right you need to be able to look like a bird if you're going as a bird so you need to have</u>
<u n="704" who="S0654">but we need to be a great bird of paradise</u>
<u n="705" who="S0655">awkward</u>
<u n="706" who="S0653">yeah but then but when they're not sticking their arms out wings out and looking weird?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I wanna do that</u>
<u n="708" who="S0653">you want to do that? but then no one would know what you are</u>
<u n="709" who="S0654">yeah I can just say I'm a bird</u>
<u n="710" who="S0653">but nobody's gonna ask you cos they'll be so weirded out by the weird</u>
<u n="711" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="712" who="S0653">jumpy blobs that you both are</u>
<u n="713" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/> or we can say I'm a bird</u>
<u n="714" who="S0653">you can say you're a bird</u>
<u n="715" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I'm a bird I'm a bird a big fat bird</u>
<u n="716" who="S0653" trans="overlap">shh I think if you just dress up in colourful clothes and find some feathers and get a beak-shaped we'll make a sort of beak-shaped hat type thing and some wings</u>
<u n="717" who="S0654">I wanna dress up like that</u>
<u n="718" who="S0655">I want to go commando</u>
<u n="719" who="S0653">well you don't really <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I would have to keep you at home if you did that</u>
<u n="720" who="S0655">okay I'll stay at home then</u>
<u n="721" who="S0653">right</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
