<text id="SXCB">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:53:29</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-03-08</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0326 S0328 S0383</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>On train</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>emails, plane journeys, travel, work, driving, complaining, being drunk</topics>
		<activity>3 friends chat to pass the time on a train from London to Margate</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0326">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0328">
				<exactage>29</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England, USA, Australia</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Baker</occupation>
				<socgrade>C2</socgrade>
				<nssec>5</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0383">
				<exactage>30</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Devon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Devon/London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Producer - film and photography</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0326">so what shall we do go swimming?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0383">definitely can't go swimming</u>
<u n="3" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0383">it's got one of those crazy beaches though that's like shallow for fucking ages</u>
<u n="5" who="S0326">oh yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0383">so you can just like walk out for like half an hour</u>
<u n="7" who="S0328">like wade</u>
<u n="8" who="S0383">and just like that's</u>
<u n="9" who="S0328">what do you do wade?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0326">what's that?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0328">I don't know sounds like</u>
<u n="13" who="S0383">wade them</u>
<u n="14" who="S0328"><unclear/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0326">did you just drink that?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0383">I accidently on New Year drunk a half pint there was like this buffet and I had like a pint glass and I was so drunk that my friend just kept putting the buffet in it and I never realised</u>
<u n="19" who="S0326">what was the buffet?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0383">like sausage rolls and like</u>
<u n="21" who="S0328" trans="overlap">like food and stuff</u>
<u n="22" who="S0383">little</u>
<u n="23" who="S0326">put booze in it</u>
<u n="24" who="S0383">yeah true</u>
<u n="25" who="S0328">it doesn't even have a straw that's lame</u>
<u n="26" who="S0383">I know it's like definitely was like sausage rolls hitting me in the face while I was drinking</u>
<u n="27" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0383">so that was gross and then I lost a wrestling match to a girl</u>
<u n="29" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0383">then I fell in <unclear/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0326">you fell in a what?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0383">I tried I made a date with a sixty-year-old woman to go skinny dipping on New Year's Day</u>
<u n="33" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0326">it's a great line</u>
<u n="35" who="S0328"><unclear/> on New Year's funny</u>
<u n="36" who="S0383">and exposed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad's infidelities to the village</u>
<u n="37" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0326">to the village</u>
<u n="39" who="S0383">yeah we were at like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dads</u>
<u n="40" who="S0328">for New Year?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0328">where?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0383">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0328">what where?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0383">she's got this this house that's insane so it's like you know the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0328">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0383">it's just like basically you go down this like National Trust path that's like five minutes' walk from the cliffs it's in like National Trust land it's next to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house there where it's got like his old like kiln and it's like the most amazing house in the world</u>
<u n="48" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0383">but her dad is like this <trunc>ar</trunc> he used to be in like the <trunc>mi</trunc> he like went to <anon type="place"/> and then he was like really high up in the military and now he's like a really bad businessman that no one likes</u>
<u n="50" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0326">and like a not like a good one</u>
<u n="52" who="S0383">yeah he's no he's like he's a terrible businessman but still makes like millions of pounds</u>
<u n="53" who="S0326">what like morally bad but <trunc>en</trunc> <unclear/> good</u>
<u n="54" who="S0383">no he's just bad a he's just bad a business and no one likes him</u>
<u n="55" who="S0328">oh shit</u>
<u n="56" who="S0383">so he basically anyway but he was having like this affair with like a couple of women in the village</u>
<u n="57" who="S0328">ah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0383">yeah and then my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was staying at this woman's house and we went over to the house and had a</u>
<u n="59" who="S0328">does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> know about it</u>
<u n="60" who="S0383">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knows about it</u>
<u n="61" who="S0328">and she doesn't care</u>
<u n="62" who="S0326">as do you</u>
<u n="63" who="S0383">no she doesn't care like well he's not married to her mum but erm but my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was staying in the woman who he was having an affair with's house and it's in the middle of a field and then I like outed it to the whole village cos they're like where are you staying? I'm like oh at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house <unclear/> called and then everyone obviously hates him cos he's some like <anon type="place"/> banker that's moved to the village and then they started gossiping and I like was said yeah cos he's having an affair with that like the woman that's and they're just like fucking mortified basically I still haven't told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0328">mm you'll still haven't told her you've ruined her dad's life</u>
<u n="65" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0328">have to get round to it next</u>
<u n="68" who="S0383">I mean it can't be that ruined like there's been</u>
<u n="69" who="S0328">it can't be that ruined if it was already bad</u>
<u n="70" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0328">can't ruin something that's already <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0326">so what kind of like <unclear/> is it like old fashioned?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0328">I've never been there</u>
<u n="74" who="S0383">didn't go inside</u>
<u n="75" who="S0328"><unclear/> what you like is old fashioned</u>
<u n="76" who="S0326">no I don't mind</u>
<u n="77" who="S0383">there's this <unclear/> at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0326">got a pool table in it?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0383">dunno there's this arcade <anon type="place"/> and the machines are so old fashioned the motorbike one is just a motorbike on rollers you just sit on it and it's just like rollers that like make the wheels go round</u>
<u n="80" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0326">what you just sit there?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0383">you just sit there there's not even a screen even you just sort of like sit on the motorbike and don't go anywhere it's like a motorbike on treadmill basically it's pretty shit I went to <anon type="place"/> on Friday</u>
<u n="83" who="S0328"><unclear/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0383">and none of the machines work in the arcades but they don't put out of order things on them and I was like I</u>
<u n="85" who="S0328">it's well out of order</u>
<u n="86" who="S0383">it's well out of order and I complained cos I'm like in to complaining these days <unclear/> I've like turned and basically I bought an ice cream the other day and it was really nice</u>
<u n="87" who="S0328">and didn't want it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0383">yeah no I didn't and my friend got the same ice cream and got loads of pistachios on it and I moaned and they overheard me moaning and they're like do you have a problem? I I like really I was like that's really unfair you got loads more pistachios and then the guy was like do you want more pistachios I'm like yeah and he bought me another ice cream with loads more pistachios on it and then I got the bill and he charged me for two ice creams this is such a boring story</u>
<u n="89" who="S0328">he charged you for two ice creams?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0383">yeah and they were like seven pound each so I like complained and then he gave me another free ice cream and I was like <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="91" who="S0326">so you got you got two you paid for two and you got three</u>
<u n="92" who="S0383">I paid for one and I got three</u>
<u n="93" who="S0326">oh</u>
<u n="94" who="S0383">and loads of pistachios so then I was complaining totally works so I complained about the arcades</u>
<u n="95" who="S0328">where where were you?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0383">at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0328"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0383"><anon type="place"/> their ice creams are really good cardamom and saffron flavour solid</u>
<u n="99" who="S0328">erm yeah also if you get if you if you like <unclear/> and get fired then you get loads of money <unclear/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0383">really?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0328">well like cos obviously his staff were like totally took it it was quite funny actually like I'll make it a short story but she she he had this member of staff working who was always always always stitching him up like come in late not show up and like sort of lie about it to get out of shifts and stuff and then the <unclear/> she's she's <unclear/> and stuff anyway so she wanted to get out of the shift and she was like no you know like <unclear/> I emailed you about it and he's like okay I haven't got it but if you forward me the email then  like fair enough so like a day later she forwards him this email it's like obviously been doctored and really badly like she forwarded to herself and then edited it and then forwarded it and then was like yeah see here I wrote this but like she'd done it in a way that totally left this like clear evidence of what she'd done you know</u>
<u n="102" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0328">she didn't change it in any way but the main thing that she did wrong just cos it was like supposed to have been in January like twenty <trunc>s</trunc> twenty-ninth or she forwarded the email to herself to change it on twenty-sixth of February so she changed it to twenty-ninth but left it as February and so it was like twenty-ninth of February which actually doesn't exist</u>
<u n="104" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0328">he was like</u>
<u n="106" who="S0383">hasn't happened yet</u>
<u n="107" who="S0328">no cos it's like a leap year it's like the one so it actually doesn't exist</u>
<u n="108" who="S0383">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh it actually doesn't exist</u>
<u n="109" who="S0328">it's like so I got this email that you sent either three years in the past or when you're in the future but either way like it didn't come through yeah anyway so he was like look we were like you can't have the shift off and like you've obviously sent me this like really awful lie like she didn't say anything she didn't go to work to the shift and then <trunc>sh</trunc> and then he messaged her like cos of that you're fired she was like you know long time coming wasn't it? anyway so she's got a lawyer and was like unfair dismissal and now he has to pay her like severance and like it's in the eyes of the law like she's in the right no matter what cos you have to do a written <trunc>aw</trunc> verbal warning written warning <unclear/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0326">physical warning</u>
<u n="111" who="S0328">not matter what physical warning <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm so anyway</u>
<u n="112" who="S0326">you have to do a warning can you do like a written warning and then like just ten minutes later fire them?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0328">I don't think so I think I don't know actually I don't know bit there's a definite like clear thing that you have to do and he didn't do it so</u>
<u n="114" who="S0383">what so then he?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0328">so then she wins man he has to pay her stiff</u>
<u n="116" who="S0383">how much?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0328">well it's like they're closing the restaurant in three weeks anyway so it's like the rest of the shift that she would have done</u>
<u n="118" who="S0383">oh is it at thingy?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0328">Railroad yeah so that's three weeks' worth of work erm and then I think you have to do like severance pay so he reckons about six hundred quid could be worse but like also sucks just to have to give it to her she's like <unclear/> but anyway</u>
<u n="120" who="S0383">what a dick for actually pursuing it as well</u>
<u n="121" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like so you just have to get a job and then you get fired and then you'll get severance</u>
<u n="122" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> plan sorted</u>
<u n="123" who="S0383">I'm sure like you know when like mad like people in really urban corporations get like fired cos they're like fucking prostitutes and then they get like two million pounds severance I'm sure people just do that on purpose</u>
<u n="124" who="S0328">hard to get another job then though</u>
<u n="125" who="S0383">don't need it when you get get like</u>
<u n="126" who="S0328" trans="overlap">you have to open a street food van or something maybe a hotdog van selling hotdogs I once heard the best erm like announcer on the train it was like the lady was like maybe she was erm but she she she was like talking about what they had in their erm the in the snack cart and she was like and today we have special get one sandwich get one Kit Kat free lucky</u>
<u n="127" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0326">lucky</u>
<u n="129" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0328">everyone's a winner on this train</u>
<u n="131" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0383">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0328">we went we had dinner at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yesterday</u>
<u n="134" who="S0383"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at Railroad</u>
<u n="136" who="S0383">haven't they moved to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0328">no he hasn't he's still based in here but he's always <unclear/> like working in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0383">what was he saying?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0328">just saying</u>
<u n="140" who="S0326">he said that he's a green man now</u>
<u n="141" who="S0328">he's a green man now so what? don't you have that turn of phrase here?</u>
<u n="142" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0328">unless you mean alien no erm but basically he's had this like thing ever since I've known him but I think even longer like he got really really stitched by his agency with like you know how they send your book out and whatever you wrap up like a debt to them</u>
<u n="144" who="S0383">oh yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0328">he was earning a shit ton of money and then he was like you know can I have some money back? and they were like no you owe us like a hundred and fifty thousand pounds he's like what? I've been like doing like really well for ages for years</u>
<u n="146" who="S0326"><unclear/> money</u>
<u n="147" who="S0328">and they're like no no no you owe us loads of money so he was working really hard doing loads of like campaigns and shit to the trade farers and then like when I got back from <anon type="place"/> which <trunc>li</trunc> this was like a year ago he was like went to me he was like okay he was like finally cleared the hundred and fifty grand loan he was he went to them and was like really expecting they'd be like okay cool like champagne like you know and that and they're like no no no like in the mean in that time you <trunc>vo</trunc> you've owe us another like seventeen thousand pounds they spent money on his behalf you know?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0328">so anyway they've got him right by the ball by the shackle and arms you know and</u>
<u n="150" who="S0383">by the shackle and arms?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0328">by the shackle and arms yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0326">by the ball single ball</u>
<u n="153" who="S0328">yeah ball</u>
<u n="154" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0328">and then he's finally cleared it now so apparently in <anon type="place"/> like they do a green man who isn't green or whatever it's like no we don't have that</u>
<u n="156" who="S0383">yeah to invest there the ones like agents are so fucking retarded I deal with them every day and like they lose their like clients so <trunc>man</trunc> much work just</u>
<u n="157" who="S0328">really?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0383">yeah like one the other day we were like <trunc>o</trunc>offering them like I can't remember what it was oh yeah it was like Topshop campaign so they pay like fifteen thousand quid like no sorry he's gone blah blah and then phones up the day before and was like sorry I fucked up erm <unclear/> obviously he'd actually <unclear/> obviously didn't put someone else there it's like you've just lost that person fifty grand and they always like they spend so much money like we do it as well we spend so much money on like shit the amount of shit that I buy on other people's jobs</u>
<u n="159" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0383">but it's also like you kind of balance it out though it's kind of fair like the way we do it cos like we put like loads of money on like corporate jobs so then like when we work with photographer so say if if we worked with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0326">it's sunnier now</u>
<u n="162" who="S0383">like we do all this editorial stuff for him but like pay for it and like so he doesn't have to pay anything to use that portfolio</u>
<u n="163" who="S0328">that's what that's what they were saying like I think that's what the</u>
<u n="164" who="S0383">yeah but agents don't do that production companies do that</u>
<u n="165" who="S0328">I think that they they were covering for like editorial but they were charging him for it cos they were like oh when you wanted that thing like and we sorted it out for you this is how much it cost but they never told him that you know they were spending this money on his behalf erm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0383">it is amazing the amount of money the amount of shit we buy and just charge random people but I kind of like</u>
<u n="168" who="S0328">like <unclear/> like the cold presser?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0383">yeah like the cold press but we lay we <vocal desc="laugh"/> we laid</u>
<u n="170" who="S0328"><unclear/> press</u>
<u n="171" who="S0383">a pink carpet across the entire office which cost two thousand pound to get fitted and then buying the carpet on another job cos we had to get carpet for this other job it was AWS some like fashion chain</u>
<u n="172" who="S0328">when you said you were getting a pink carpet I meant I thought you mean like  a red carpet like for her birthday just laying down a pink carpet</u>
<u n="173" who="S0383">oh no no we've got like a pink carpet actually</u>
<u n="174" who="S0328">yeah you need a pink cake? get a pink <unclear/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0383">yeah got a pink Lamborghini pink limo erm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0328">that's so naughty how do you pretend that's part of the job? the carpet</u>
<u n="177" who="S0383">because there's like loads of people like some people ask you for backups some of them will ask for backup but it's like Robin Hood like you stick like</u>
<u n="178" who="S0328">oh I see</u>
<u n="179" who="S0383">you steal from your stuff from those people</u>
<u n="180" who="S0326">that's right you</u>
<u n="181" who="S0383">you steal from those people and then like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0328">bring out the pink carpet</u>
<u n="183" who="S0383">then you're like other ones you like give them free shit you like help them out it's like you do a job for Zara and charge them like five hundred grand and then you give and then you do a shoot</u>
<u n="184" who="S0328">roll out the pink carpet</u>
<u n="185" who="S0326">bit of castle</u>
<u n="186" who="S0383">we're not <unclear/> the other day</u>
<u n="187" who="S0328">oh yeah how was that?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0383">and she's gonna basically her parents are gonna inherit a castle <anon type="place"/> castle</u>
<u n="189" who="S0328"><anon type="place"/> castle</u>
<u n="190" who="S0383"><anon type="place"/>'s got a castle</u>
<u n="191" who="S0328">yeah I've heard of that</u>
<u n="192" who="S0383">and I was like so she's basically gonna be a princess if you get a castle</u>
<u n="193" who="S0328">are you are you pissed off that you broke up with her now?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0383">yeah like honestly I was like fuck let me know about the castle and maybe</u>
<u n="195" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0383">that's my biggest incentive of people other people is like what I get out of it a castle land</u>
<u n="197" who="S0328">what are you going to <unclear/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at the <unclear/> now</u>
<u n="198" who="S0383">no but erm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0328">erm let me know how it goes with the castle maybe we can get back together</u>
<u n="200" who="S0326">I want to get a castle as well actually how fucking cool</u>
<u n="201" who="S0383">but she was saying when she was like</u>
<u n="202" who="S0326">but you become a princess how do you do that?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0328">marry a prince</u>
<u n="204" who="S0326">I was <trunc>gu</trunc> I was gutted that the the royal baby was a boy cos otherwise I would become marry it and become king</u>
<u n="205" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0328">George you could hook up with George</u>
<u n="207" who="S0326">first gay king yeah gay king</u>
<u n="208" who="S0383">don't think it'd be the first</u>
<u n="209" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0326">look how sunny it got well good</u>
<u n="211" who="S0383">oh look at that cool light? there's a Tesco in <unclear/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0326">must be their depot</u>
<u n="213" who="S0383">that's so cool</u>
<u n="214" who="S0326">what is this place?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0328">I don't know man</u>
<u n="216" who="S0383">do you know how many mines there are in Spain?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0326">a lot</u>
<u n="218" who="S0383">there's not that many mines in England I don't think like <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0326">had <trunc>an</trunc> did any mines get turned into museums I'd like to go down one <pause dur="short"/> in Cornwall or something</u>
<u n="220" who="S0383">I dunno there's a witchcraft museum that's in a mine</u>
<u n="221" who="S0328">where's that?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0383">Cornwall the witchcraft museum</u>
<u n="223" who="S0328">is it any good?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0383">never been I've been to the <anon type="place"/> it's pretty good pretty magical</u>
<u n="225" who="S0328">pretty magical</u>
<u n="226" who="S0383">pretty pretty magical</u>
<u n="227" who="S0326">how long do you think it takes to learn to drive?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0383">ages</u>
<u n="229" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like think he seems like <unclear/> he thinks he can go everything half time like there was like a course like horse riding course</u>
<u n="230" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I didn't think that</u>
<u n="231" who="S0328">it's like it's like a week it's like a week in like <anon type="place"/> or wherever to learn how to do horse riding it's like two hundred and ninety-five quid or whatever he's like what about for smart people? have you go a one hour one for smart people what if you're smart?</u>
<u n="232" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0328">so I'll take that one fifty quid</u>
<u n="234" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0383">d'you know what though horse <trunc>ri</trunc> I learnt I can horse ride cos when I was in <anon type="place"/> I just got a <unclear/> horse after twenty minutes you've got to learn to do it else you're fucked he just like put me on a horse and went go and I was like and I just figured it out</u>
<u n="236" who="S0326">yeah see I think that's what it'll be I thought in car might be a bit like that</u>
<u n="237" who="S0383">I mean you can learn to drive like it's easy to drive but like you have to learn so much shit</u>
<u n="238" who="S0326">the theory test?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0383">no the theory is easy that's just like common sense</u>
<u n="240" who="S0326">and it's like when to look in your mirror and like due to have to develop those sort of habits</u>
<u n="241" who="S0383">yeah it's like no one <trunc>dri</trunc> if I did my driving test now I'd a hundred percent fail there's absolutely no  chance in hell</u>
<u n="242" who="S0326">cos I did a</u>
<u n="243" who="S0383">cos it's really</u>
<u n="244" who="S0326">motorbike one and passed that and you've got to do stuff like look in the blind spot every five seconds</u>
<u n="245" who="S0383">yeah it's just basically all the stuff you have to do is really like counterintuitive</u>
<u n="246" who="S0328" trans="overlap">you could probably do it do it now when you've got when you're young you can learn things in ten minutes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0383">yeah but I reckon it would take about six months</u>
<u n="248" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0383">well you do like one lesson a week</u>
<u n="250" who="S0326">I'd rather do like three a week and do it in like a month</u>
<u n="251" who="S0328">I want to go to boot camp</u>
<u n="252" who="S0326">it's a grand though you can definitely do it for cheaper than that</u>
<u n="253" who="S0383">having a car is the best thing in the world</u>
<u n="254" who="S0326">exactly that's what I was thinking</u>
<u n="255" who="S0383">you can literally</u>
<u n="256" who="S0328">you you learn to drive I'll get a car</u>
<u n="257" who="S0326">and then also I can get a bike and have people on the back</u>
<u n="258" who="S0328">I ain't getting on the back of that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0326">you liked it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0328">what are you talking about you nearly killed me on a push bike in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0326">yeah that's cos I was drunk I wouldn't drive a motorbike wasted</u>
<u n="262" who="S0328">people were like what the fuck people were literally like</u>
<u n="263" who="S0383">dude <unclear/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0328"><unclear/> get off that bike</u>
<u n="265" who="S0383">when I was in <anon type="place"/> I hired this scooter I had like so I was just like got it in the thing and before I even got on it I revved the engine and the scooter shot out across the street and smashed the like petrol tank spilt all over the thing</u>
<u n="266" who="S0328">oh my god</u>
<u n="267" who="S0383">and they still hired it to me</u>
<u n="268" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0383">fucking idiots</u>
<u n="270" who="S0326">you still hired the same one can I have another one please?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0383">no yeah I got a different</u>
<u n="272" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0326">that's like remember the one we got in <anon type="place"/>? the headlight didn't work</u>
<u n="274" who="S0383">I'm getting a car next time we go</u>
<u n="275" who="S0328">which we don't we didn't find out until it was nightfall and we were like</u>
<u n="276" who="S0326">on a cliff</u>
<u n="277" who="S0328">on like his precipice of like curvy and lost like definitely definitely miles even from the next turning like didn't know where we were no signal no headlights <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like night blind basically like</u>
<u n="278" who="S0326">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't know left or right either</u>
<u n="279" who="S0328">I don't know left or right so I was being the eyes</u>
<u n="280" who="S0326">she's like right I'm like that's the cliff on the right</u>
<u n="281" who="S0328">I can see the bend and so I was like telling him which way to go but I fucking like fifty fifty on left and right really like when I get I'm like he's like are you sure? we could so easily have died but then we finally saw some lights in the distance we were like let's just go to that</u>
<u n="282" who="S0326">we'd been doing it for like an hour or like two hours</u>
<u n="283" who="S0328">it was cold we were just in bikini like it was cold and it was just so stupid</u>
<u n="284" who="S0383">both in bikinis</u>
<u n="285" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in his bikini and we were like we saw some lights and we were like go to it went to the lights and it's literally this restaurant called Oasis and it was like this cosy</u>
<u n="287" who="S0383">got roll</u>
<u n="288" who="S0328">we were like yes we'll just hang out here get the bike in the morning drink some wine eat some squid so and then we were like</u>
<u n="289" who="S0383">yey squid</u>
<u n="290" who="S0328">can they had started packing up the restaurant and we were like okay do you know if we can can you book us a cab to go home the guy's like what? no what are you talking about  a cab? oh man we have to drive these fucking tourists home</u>
<u n="291" who="S0326">he drove us home</u>
<u n="292" who="S0328">he drove us all the way via his wife and like his daughter and his new baby and he had to be like sorry I'm not coming for hours cos these bloody idiot</u>
<u n="293" who="S0326">it was like a hour drive as well</u>
<u n="294" who="S0328">took us home but then I gave him a bunch of money in the end and I think he was like mm not expecting that cos like it was <trunc>f</trunc> it was a long long journey with him being really pissed off but I knew he was going to give him money at the end but he didn't know that you know</u>
<u n="295" who="S0326">yeah he was pissed off and like just like not like wasn't mean</u>
<u n="296" who="S0328">wasn't mean it was nice erm and then we went bank the next day to get the bike and he was he was happy to see us</u>
<u n="297" who="S0326">I like the little bike</u>
<u n="298" who="S0383">they're so fun</u>
<u n="299" who="S0326">they're so fun</u>
<u n="300" who="S0383">they're seriously so fun</u>
<u n="301" who="S0328">we should go <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying when we go to erm <anon type="place"/> and like that place like we should just get some like <unclear/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0326">are you talking about our <unclear/> thing</u>
<u n="303" who="S0328">what?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0326">talking really quiet</u>
<u n="305" who="S0328">oh</u>
<u n="306" who="S0326">you're talking <unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0328">erm yeah we should do that you know for a bit</u>
<u n="308" who="S0383">get those like cool like euro scooters that you like pedal to start</u>
<u n="309" who="S0326">nah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0383">they're really cool the one's that like all the rude boys have in France</u>
<u n="311" who="S0326">they're not that fast though</u>
<u n="312" who="S0383">that's good</u>
<u n="313" who="S0326">you can go like sixty though</u>
<u n="314" who="S0383">you can go quite fast on those scooters</u>
<u n="315" who="S0326">yeah you can only get like forty and actually if you're trying to get somewhere it's kind of annoying to go that slowly it takes ages</u>
<u n="316" who="S0328">what are you doing next week? you should come to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0383">work</u>
<u n="318" who="S0328">oh yeah ha ha</u>
<u n="319" who="S0383">got a job <pause dur="short"/> working with this really amazing ballerina actually</u>
<u n="320" who="S0328">really who?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0383"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's this like Russian ballerina no not ballerina well she is a ballerina but she was like the Russian erm <pause dur="short"/> rhythmic gymnast champion in like the nineties and stuff but she's really amazing</u>
<u n="322" who="S0328">and what are you going to do with her?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0383">she's just doing this photo shoot <pause dur="short"/> we're doing like gymnastics shit <pause dur="short"/> I got really drunk on Friday night and watched loads of gymnastics dude it's fucking insane I watched the Chinese State Circus do a production of Swan Lake there's this woman and she stands on this guy's head and does a pirouette like on like on her like toes like point pirouettes on the guy's head and he's just stood there and then she does all this like bendy shit</u>
<u n="324" who="S0328">do you reckon you'd get a headache off that?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0383">no he wore the special hat</u>
<u n="326" who="S0328">Neurofen Plus for that pirouette on your</u>
<u n="327" who="S0326">it's in this part of England the sunniest part?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0328">which part?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0326">the part near <anon type="place"/> is that where we're going?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0328">oh yeah he said the weather was always nice in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0328">where are we going? I mean where do you we go via where else do you we stop?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0383"><unclear/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/> garden of England <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> strawberry and er I was like oh you know at <unclear/> we've been like getting married next month and he was like really? really? oh my god</u>
<u n="336" who="S0326">tell that story to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0328">oh yeah cos he knows them it's really funny erm but the only person who was smart was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I was like yeah yeah we're getting married next month she goes where's the ring then? if you are getting married where's the ring? I was like yeah you've got me actually point no one else thought of that</u>
<u n="338" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0328">erm I had dinner with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0326">is that what do you call her?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0328">her name is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0326">I thought you said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wet the bed</u>
<u n="343" who="S0328">that's what we call her messing around <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm the the the craziest thing is that we've known each other since were like nineteen and I only just thought of that</u>
<u n="344" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0328">just so immature but erm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I had dinner with them and you know they're like well well into like I dunno <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got like kids in <anon type="place"/> now met a guy but he has kids and she's married to him</u>
<u n="346" who="S0383">he's got a kid?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0328">he's got two</u>
<u n="348" who="S0383">how old is he?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0328">they're like fourteen and he's like forty</u>
<u n="350" who="S0383">and he's like really in to hats</u>
<u n="351" who="S0326">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0328">yeah hats and trainers that's his thing</u>
<u n="353" who="S0383">oh that's so bad especially if you're fourteen</u>
<u n="354" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0328">yeah erm so anyway she's married happily married to him in <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="357" who="S0383">do the kids live with her?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> finally no only in the weekends or something or sometimes erm so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has finally like shackled <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know he's like getting married this year poor <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0383">dude</u>
<u n="360" who="S0328">and they were talking about <unclear/> but they're like <unclear/> so we're like</u>
<u n="361" who="S0383">they're very into their lives</u>
<u n="362" who="S0328">so we're like</u>
<u n="363" who="S0326">they're into being adults</u>
<u n="364" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0383">but they are really into their lives</u>
<u n="366" who="S0328">yeah they want all the stuff they're getting all the stuff anyway so we're like sitting down to dinner and the waitress is coming over and we're about to order I was like anyway me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are getting married in <anon type="place"/> next month and  they're like oh my god what? oh my god <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how did he propose? oh my god and they're they're like they're like <unclear/> so the waitress was like what? and they're like oh my god did he propose? no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like took me five years to snag <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0326">oh you were a saying you could like you could see in her eyes like</u>
<u n="368" who="S0328">ensnare</u>
<u n="369" who="S0326">how did it take me six years five years to snuff the life out of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> enough to marry him</u>
<u n="370" who="S0328">it took me five years to ensnare her</u>
<u n="371" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0326">you know when I met her she kept talking about this person called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and like she like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum was staying there or something and I kept thinking that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a child and she lived with her flatmate who had a kid called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="373" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0326">the way she was talking about him about him about him</u>
<u n="375" who="S0328">it's true though the way she sees it is like what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinks he likes but then there's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> likes cos I know no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you just think you like that change I was going to wear blue today <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> take that off and put pink on</u>
<u n="376" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0328">funny</u>
<u n="378" who="S0383">it's quite an easy way to live your life though</u>
<u n="379" who="S0328">what? marry and</u>
<u n="380" who="S0383">yeah no be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s husband you don't have to think about anything it's just like</u>
<u n="381" who="S0328">yeah he doesn't have to think about anything she knows exactly what he likes and what he wants and what he's going to do she can just tell him and like boss him it's not it's not it's not very nicely done through either it is like aggressive she puts him down quite badly</u>
<u n="382" who="S0326">I don't understand why that's attractive for a woman you know</u>
<u n="383" who="S0328">what?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0326">just like step all over them like trample over them like</u>
<u n="385" who="S0328">no what attractive to him?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0326">well or to her to have like a wet blanket type thing?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0328">yeah I guess they've found a way that works I don't know know <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0326">I like this train journey it's got like a ride</u>
<u n="389" who="S0328">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0383">kind of like a ride</u>
<u n="391" who="S0326">it's got lots to look at compared to like the <anon type="place"/> one</u>
<u n="392" who="S0383">what's between <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0326">swamp <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0326">there's one really cool there's a quite liked it when I was getting there in the morning and it was early and the sun was coming up and it was like <trunc>fro</trunc><trunc>fro</trunc>frosty yeah it's just kind of a bit shitty and like a puddle</u>
<u n="396" who="S0383">a big puddle</u>
<u n="397" who="S0326">it's like a puddle from there to here</u>
<u n="398" who="S0383">between <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> a puddle</u>
<u n="399" who="S0328">puddle</u>
<u n="400" who="S0326">there's one really nice house</u>
<u n="401" who="S0383">are you going to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wedding?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0328">yeah I'm the slave bitch making the cake aren't I? she wants me to do the food and all it's like in erm <anon type="place"/> in October and it's going to be cold and I'm not allowed to bring <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stich</u>
<u n="403" who="S0383">what?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0328">I know</u>
<u n="405" who="S0326"><unclear/> assistant</u>
<u n="406" who="S0328">I don't even want to go if I can't take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0326">I don't really want to go either</u>
<u n="408" who="S0328">I know obviously</u>
<u n="409" who="S0383">are they paying for the wedding or do you have to pay for yourself to go?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0328">you have to pay to go</u>
<u n="411" who="S0326">even though you're making the cake?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0328">yeah even though I'm making the cake I think I should be allowed to bring you at least it's like</u>
<u n="413" who="S0383">just put him in the cake surprise</u>
<u n="414" who="S0328">but like but then it's like if someone</u>
<u n="415" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0328">it's like then you're just going there to like be part of his like performance you know people should be allowed to bring their partners I don't I don't know her friends like</u>
<u n="417" who="S0326">I'm not your partner man</u>
<u n="418" who="S0383">I I when I went to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wedding I I didn't even want to I had to take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> fucking annoying</u>
<u n="419" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0328">well she's got a castle now innit? he's off</u>
<u n="421" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0383">but I can't believe did you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> before he like got with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0328">no they met at <anon type="place"/> when I lived when I lived in that house with her where you used to live</u>
<u n="424" who="S0383">but has their relationship always been that? that she just tramples all over him did she just pick him at <trunc>Vi</trunc> <anon type="place"/> and go that one</u>
<u n="425" who="S0328">erm I don't think it took that long <vocal desc="laugh"/> to erm get get get a grip on him but she likes him she <trunc>re</trunc> she doesn't dislike him it's not like that</u>
<u n="426" who="S0383">yeah I know</u>
<u n="427" who="S0328">it's you know some people like they just it's like they know they don't even like each other she does and she does respect him like <trunc>e</trunc>even though like <trunc>sh</trunc> you know like he used to do all like <unclear/> those thing about him that she would want to change he's like no no and I know that she respects him for that still it's just erm it's funny with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like I can never tell if she's joking or not cos she used to so like it's like she's become the caricature of herself which happens often where it's like erm she used to kind of say those kinds of things as like an impression of like that kind of girl who's like just like a manipulative bitch like shallow and like bossy</u>
<u n="428" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0328">but now I'm just like woah woah woah woah woah are you still joking? cos it seems really real now it's funny you know erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is making her wedding dress you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0328">and erm she makes these like amazing dresses like really really detailed and she was talking about it she's like yeah about me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we're looking erm <unclear/> I dunno <unclear/> seamstresses are if if they're all that good so I was looking at it it's like I don't want it to look handmade you know I want it to look and I was like machine made? she's like yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0383">yeah but I thought</u>
<u n="434" who="S0328">and she wasn't joking</u>
<u n="435" who="S0326">I don't want it to look machine made</u>
<u n="436" who="S0328">like not handmade what's the word? I was like machine made? she's like yeah it's actually</u>
<u n="437" who="S0383">but I feel like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like that as well though cos he like hits he like decided he wants to be that kind of person and he's really not that kind of person and it's like</u>
<u n="438" who="S0326">what kind of person?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0328">what a bitch?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0383">I mean cos he's not really that completely a gay guy but he's like the worst greedy like bitchy gay guy in the world</u>
<u n="441" who="S0328">yeah he's got a</u>
<u n="442" who="S0383">but actually he's a really nice guy</u>
<u n="443" who="S0328">he's got he's got a sweet side but he is actually a bitch</u>
<u n="444" who="S0383">not but he's like</u>
<u n="445" who="S0328">he's would he would do dodgy shit if he could get away with it</u>
<u n="446" who="S0383">but I feel like he's very conscious of it like it's totally constructed</u>
<u n="447" who="S0328">he has moments of remorse but he he'll fucking throw you under a bus though don't don't don't mistake that I've seen him do the sneakiest shit to his friends but like you know he'll still consider them friends and really love them but like he's definitely a bitch I don't know man he smokes too much weed or something</u>
<u n="448" who="S0326"><unclear/> greedy gay guy who smokes a lot of weed</u>
<u n="449" who="S0328">like it's not very glamorous is it?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's good though like she's still funny</u>
<u n="452" who="S0326">that's <pause dur="long"/> I know what that went into</u>
<u n="453" who="S0328">that was so funny I when you were when you were gone on the water run erm I bought this like weird thing from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like my neighbour in the <anon type="place"/> and she was like and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like she's one of those flying girls</u>
<u n="454" who="S0326">flying girls?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0328">yeah who when they like <unclear/> they're always like <pause dur="short"/> flying</u>
<u n="456" who="S0383">it just hurts that they're like trying to take off the <unclear/> of the situation</u>
<u n="457" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0326">I'm considering the wedding like</u>
<u n="459" who="S0328">and it's going to be cold its like not</u>
<u n="460" who="S0326">it won't get that it won't be cold</u>
<u n="461" who="S0328">in October</u>
<u n="462" who="S0326">it's hot in like my mum was there like in February and it was warm it'll be hot it'll be warm in October probably cos it's way in the south</u>
<u n="463" who="S0328">she said it was going to be cold but erm it's that your ticket where's mine?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0326">I gave it to you oh no that's yours there you go</u>
<u n="465" who="S0328">sorry <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0326">railcard is really good <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0383">I might buy one on Ebay</u>
<u n="468" who="S0328">can you get one onEbay?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0383">yeah like a fake ones</u>
<u n="470" who="S0326">it's they're yeah they're letting the erm the</u>
<u n="471" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">tickets please thanks very much yeah lovely cheers thank you that's great cheers thanks a lot</u>
<u n="472" who="S0326">they've erm they're been outsold by the voice of the <unclear/> Tesco points vouchers for Tesco</u>
<u n="473" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0326">you get like five hundred pound Tesco voucher for like <unclear/> three hundred and fifty pounds</u>
<u n="475" who="S0383">so lame there's <trunc>loa</trunc> there's a whole there's so much of that shit on Ebay as well like get like buy one get one free tickets to Alton Towers and shit like that</u>
<u n="476" who="S0328">Tesco points</u>
<u n="477" who="S0383">I bought I used to when I first went to uni I bought loads of Subway stamps I bought like whole rows of them</u>
<u n="478" who="S0326">off the internet?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0383">yeah and then they stopped doing Subway stamps but like cos you used to get a like stickers rubber stamps and I used to buy like filled cards and basically ate just ate Subway for about a year and I was vegetarian so there was only one Subway option veg patty</u>
<u n="480" who="S0328">what cheese?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0326">probably wasn't vegetarian either</u>
<u n="482" who="S0383" trans="overlap">veg patty</u>
<u n="483" who="S0328">er veg patty</u>
<u n="484" who="S0326">so the other the other day I I had some Mcdonald's vouchers on the train and I went and got a Mcdonald's with them but</u>
<u n="485" who="S0383">I really want to get a Mcgrill</u>
<u n="486" who="S0326">a Mcgrill?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0383">it's got like about a billion spices in it that's illegal</u>
<u n="488" who="S0326">it's not illegal</u>
<u n="489" who="S0383">I thought it was illegal too just <unclear/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0326">I'm not defacing it I'm just folding it up did you see that thing about people in Canada  like drawing that Star Wars guy they've done it on so many nuts that's it's kind of a problem now</u>
<u n="491" who="S0383">really</u>
<u n="492" who="S0326">what's he called Spock they drew Spock on the president everyone's being doing I for years er since he died or something they're on overdrive</u>
<u n="493" who="S0328">Spock apparently died</u>
<u n="494" who="S0326">yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="495" who="S0383">oh yeah he died the other day didn't he?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0326">yeah Leeroy <unclear/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0383">yeah he died</u>
<u n="498" who="S0328"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0383"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to <anon type="place"/> for one day what an what an idiot</u>
<u n="501" who="S0383">what did she go for?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0328">she got wasted and booked the flight</u>
<u n="503" who="S0326">hangout with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0328">is that a real name?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0326">I don't know man <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been in the army</u>
<u n="506" who="S0328">has he?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0326">yeah he has to he's Israeli</u>
<u n="508" who="S0383">yeah it's like my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's Israeli she was in the army for like a year she was like secret like intelligence service</u>
<u n="509" who="S0328">oh</u>
<u n="510" who="S0326">you can't like it's all like you can't not do it</u>
<u n="511" who="S0383">she got home like she pleaded like compassion or something but she still had to be in for a year</u>
<u n="512" who="S0326">yeah you can do stuff like he would they must have used like a radio operator or something</u>
<u n="513" who="S0328">did the radio?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0326">like it kind of makes you complicit in such like terrible things do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0328">what does he actually do now?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0326">erm he's like</u>
<u n="517" who="S0383">erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0328">huh?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0383">doesn't he like doesn't he work for <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0326">he's just like a <unclear/> journalist <pause dur="long"/> are we going to change at the <unclear/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0328">but we don't</u>
<u n="522" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0328">we don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0326">no like on the back they wanted to put tickets on it</u>
<u n="525" who="S0328">what?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0326">some feminists were trying to get the <unclear/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0328">on Charles Dickens?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0383">plonk and <unclear/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0328">shut up</u>
<u n="531" who="S0326">plonk it</u>
<u n="532" who="S0383"><unclear/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0326">who's on the twenty pound note I don't even know or the fiver</u>
<u n="534" who="S0328">the queen</u>
<u n="535" who="S0326">yeah on the other side though innit? let's have a look you got one?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0328">no I only got that one bought a juice didn't I? twenty quid</u>
<u n="537" who="S0326">it's a tenner</u>
<u n="538" who="S0328"><vocal desc="yawn"/> when I got loads of money robbed at my house now that house we lived in actually were you then when we got robbed?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0383">yeah yeah my laptop got robbed</u>
<u n="540" who="S0328">and the police was like this is all pointless and like they <trunc>do</trunc> they'd basically just taken a bag with massive one with loads of money that I had fair enough and the guys were like yeah we had to answer all these stupid questions he was like did they have any distinguishing marks? I was like yeah they mine had pictures of the queen on them</u>
<u n="541" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0328">go go look for those</u>
<u n="543" who="S0326">what is marked bills anyway?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0328">when it's like got an invisible like you know one of those <unclear/> something like</u>
<u n="545" who="S0326">I thought it was in the numbers of the</u>
<u n="546" who="S0328">oh in the serial number</u>
<u n="547" who="S0326">you get like a bunch of bills and numbers and like a number like between <trunc>ze</trunc> de de de de de de de de de de</u>
<u n="548" who="S0383">are you reading a book <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0326">what book?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0383">blah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0328">blah blah blah blah finished</u>
<u n="552" who="S0383" trans="overlap">blah blah blah I remember I got really busted actually in my primary school cos you know there's like workbooks so like I had these really good orange pens so I just coloured all the pages in orange finished finished finished and then they used to hire hire? I used to hide cos like you know you used to get like pen pots with like the foods on we had like the tables and each able had like a name for then you'd have to do a name so we would be like instead of <unclear/> cos all the girls would be like <unclear/> so we took the piss and we were like six doing like delicate swans anyway that was our table name</u>
<u n="553" who="S0326">why? babies</u>
<u n="554" who="S0383">I got really really passive aggressive with a baby the other day</u>
<u n="555" who="S0328">like what did you do?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0383">no not with the baby with the parents I was at the <anon type="place"/> castle yesterday</u>
<u n="557" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0326">why of all the carriages?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0328">oh my god</u>
<u n="560" who="S0383">they should make</u>
<u n="561" who="S0326">baby carriages</u>
<u n="562" who="S0383">I think it's the same on planes as well</u>
<u n="563" who="S0326">it's just like this isn't it?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0383">fuck first class make a crche class</u>
<u n="565" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0383">or babies are only allowed on planes at a certain one flight a day</u>
<u n="567" who="S0328">no it's like this isn't it? have a crche class</u>
<u n="568" who="S0326">all those people the people with babies sit at the back or something</u>
<u n="569" who="S0383">no it pisses me I <trunc>li</trunc> I played like fucking two grand for a flight and I've got to listen to a baby the worst ever I sat I went to <anon type="place"/> and I sat you know when you sit like where you get extra leg room I paid like fifty quid more to get extra leg room and I was sat there and you know like the fold down things with a baby on the woman was sat there and the husband there and the fold down thing was in front of me</u>
<u n="570" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0383">so they put the baby in front of me</u>
<u n="572" who="S0328">so you had</u>
<u n="573" who="S0383">and I like honestly I had a twenty-two hour journey with this baby just</u>
<u n="574" who="S0328">what's your worst flight experience?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0383">this got worse basically actually you know what this I had quite a few bad ones this was bad like basically the baby threw everything at me I'd wake up just covered in like whatever it had</u>
<u n="576" who="S0328">oh my god</u>
<u n="577" who="S0326">like why didn't they swap why didn't they swap with you?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0383">and then the parents I have no idea and they'd like look at me and like you got to be like you can't turn around and be like your baby is fucking horrible it's not cute anyway and then so we had to change in <anon type="place"/> no cos we were going to <anon type="place"/> so I had to fly to <anon type="place"/> and then get a plane to <anon type="place"/> then that leg I sat next to this girl that puked up the entire journey</u>
<u n="579" who="S0328">oh man that's bad</u>
<u n="580" who="S0383">once this is actually the worse I still have now comprehension how this happened I was getting a plane to <anon type="place"/> I don't know how the plane took off but there was too many people on the plane and there wasn't enough seats and I was sat next to this woman honestly there was this guy that was stood up for the whole journey and we had to like he like I don't have no idea how it happened but anyway I was sat next to this woman and she had a baby and she was breast feeding and she asked me to move cos she was <trunc>un</trunc> she was uncomfortable with me like trying to <trunc>s</trunc> like I'm not trying to stare at your like baby sucking on your tit love</u>
<u n="581" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0383">so then I had to oh that was a really bad plane experience but the worst one of all time is I was going to <anon type="place"/> and there was just this old woman sat behind me that couldn't work the TV and just was like</u>
<u n="583" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0328">yeah that's</u>
<u n="585" who="S0383">jamming it</u>
<u n="586" who="S0328">people do that with the touch screen it's like it's like you do not need to touch it that hard</u>
<u n="587" who="S0383">yeah it's like it's called a touch screen like you don't touch yourself that hard do you</u>
<u n="588" who="S0328">not poke poke</u>
<u n="589" who="S0383">not the <unclear/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0326">did you why did you say anything to her?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0383">no I just kept looking at her</u>
<u n="592" who="S0326">you got to say something on planes</u>
<u n="593" who="S0383">oh plane journeys are always terrible I hate I hate it</u>
<u n="594" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0326">I think they're funny man</u>
<u n="596" who="S0328">I used to love them but now</u>
<u n="597" who="S0326">that's the best bit man</u>
<u n="598" who="S0383">I used to love it cos it's just like it's the best bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0328">the best bit of life</u>
<u n="600" who="S0326">the one our one to <anon type="place"/> last time was fine I think</u>
<u n="601" who="S0328">yeah it was fine</u>
<u n="602" who="S0326">especially when they were</u>
<u n="603" who="S0383">I never had I never had like do you know actually the worst ever the worst ever I'd been to <anon type="place"/> I was on this plane I don't there was like quite a like well to do couple that I was like sat next to and she was kind of like a like buxom home counties like lady and I feel asleep and nuzzled into her boobs and I I dribbled on her</u>
<u n="604" who="S0328">oh my god</u>
<u n="605" who="S0383">and I woke up and her husband was like looking at me and I I freaked out I was like I'm so sorry I really apologise I'm like so sorry but she was like and I just feel straight back asleep and woke up again in the same</u>
<u n="606" who="S0326">I did that on the way to <anon type="place"/> I don't know about dribbling but when I was with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just like of passed out a bit on the plane and like some businesswoman I'd been up all night and really like high some stranger taking me to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0383">the <trunc>wo</trunc> the worst is just get yeah I always wake myself up by snoring on planes as well like <vocal desc="misc"/> I always do it in cinemas do it in the cinema when did you see that film Rust the Bone?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0328">yeah no no I haven't seen it</u>
<u n="610" who="S0383">it's the one where like the girl gets her like legs eaten off my a killer whale</u>
<u n="611" who="S0328">I watched it on a bit of that one plane actually</u>
<u n="612" who="S0383">oh my god it is like Marion Coutillard or whatever she's called and I woke myself up by doing I was really drunk it was in <anon type="place"/> and I woke myself up as she was getting the scene where she was getting her leg and I burst out laughing in the cinema and <trunc>ev</trunc> like people were looking like pissed just looking at me with disgust laughing at his woman's legs getting eaten but erm I've never had a really bad plane experience you know that thing when you get like achy legs</u>
<u n="613" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0383">what's it called?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0328">DVT well that's the official</u>
<u n="616" who="S0326" trans="overlap">actually I have had a bad one</u>
<u n="617" who="S0328">what?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0326">when I went to from Heathrow to <trunc>Te</trunc> somewhere in <anon type="place"/> but I went from <anon type="place"/> and my <anon type="place"/> flight was at got into <anon type="place"/> at like midnight and my flight from Heathrow was at like seven or six AM so I had to spend all night getting like trekking from Luton to Heathrow and I'd come from <anon type="place"/> and I'd already been up for like a while at like parties and stuff and then I got on the plane to <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> and I passed out straightaway and I was in the middle of the middle surrounded by a family of obese people</u>
<u n="619" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0326">and like I was woke up and I didn't have any hand luggage or anything and I couldn't they were so fat I could literally not like couldn't get the attention of anybody</u>
<u n="621" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you were blocked in</u>
<u n="622" who="S0326">and I didn't there was no TV on the plane there all the magazines were in Spanish I didn't have a phone I didn't know what time it was but I didn't know how long I'd been on the flight or anything I couldn't work out I was like had nothing to do I didn't know how long it was going to go on for and I was just stuck there between all these fat people like staring at the back of a plane seat like doesn't that sound bad to you?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0328">yeah that sounds awful</u>
<u n="624" who="S0383" trans="overlap">yeah that sounds pretty bad</u>
<u n="625" who="S0328">I had one that was really bad but it was kind of lolzy after a while I had a kind of if you can't beat them join them attitude I was like oh well better to enjoy it where like there was like a couple and they were quite chubs and erm they pulled down this like when they get on the flight they like immediately got out this massive like M and S like bag stuffed with food and I was like oh sweet they bought food for their whole trip it was like no man they ate it all on the plane <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was they were snacking like heaps heaps heaps it was so gross they kept offering me it was like no no no thank you cheesy dizzles for me</u>
<u n="626" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0383">cheesy dizzles</u>
<u n="628" who="S0328">all these like weird snacks you know and erm anyway the guy had a er Ipad and he was playing Fruit Ninja and he he was just sat there doing this like the whole trip right and I was like <vocal desc="nonsense"/> at first he was oh excuse me but they he just didn't get it but he kept getting quite high scores so he was like ah</u>
<u n="629" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0326">out</u>
<u n="631" who="S0328">and after a while he was just like I know right? after a while I was just like yeah man good <trunc>sc</trunc> good go <vocal desc="laugh"/> score yeah you got really good points</u>
<u n="632" who="S0326">I went I went on a quite bad one to <anon type="place"/> actually because the plane got delayed by about four hours when it everyone was already in the gate when it happened the plane got hit by lightning so obviously everybody started tucking into their duty free booze by the <trunc>ti</trunc> like within like an hour people were like smoking in the gate they had to send like armed police to like supervise</u>
<u n="633" who="S0383">no way</u>
<u n="634" who="S0326">and like by the time we got on the plane people could barely walk like half the people on the flight were like wasted <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then they're like just typical like that like when air hostess is doing their like <trunc>secu</trunc> the like how to put on a life jacket stuff all the lads were like heckling her</u>
<u n="635" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0328">oh my god I had a really funny picture there</u>
<u n="637" who="S0383">being an air hostess must be the worst job in the world</u>
<u n="638" who="S0328">I think some people really like it but yeah I agree</u>
<u n="639" who="S0326">I think it I think it was it's got he's like <unclear/> it's probably got worse</u>
<u n="640" who="S0383">yeah it used to be like quite glamorous in the seventies</u>
<u n="641" who="S0326">do you know that guy that</u>
<u n="642" who="S0328">Ryanair people it's just like you work in shop</u>
<u n="643" who="S0326">my mum's you <unclear/> you that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> guy</u>
<u n="644" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0326">he was talking when he was over once his dad was an air pilot in like the seventies and they used to go to <unclear/> just be like sort of drugs sex cos they all got really bored on these like long flights</u>
<u n="646" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0326">and he like was based on New Zealand or whatever so every flight was long and <trunc>ha</trunc> they used to do stuff just do like loads</u>
<u n="648" who="S0383">that where most <trunc>pilo</trunc>pilots train isn't it in Australia</u>
<u n="649" who="S0326">he was in New Zealand yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0383">cos there's like loads of land to fly over</u>
<u n="651" who="S0326">they used to do like shit loads of smuggling</u>
<u n="652" who="S0383">really?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0326">like cos they had a had a memory of his mum like sewing in the pockets to like stash gold in into the dad's flying jacket and when he put it on he could barely walk cos it was so heavy with gold</u>
<u n="654" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0328">it's like gold lining I was on a flight once in erm something happened to this lady like she got sick or whatever but I couldn't quite see but it was like in front of me and em that thing happens which always happens in cartoons where the like air hostess goes on the voice on the voice over and she's like is there a doctor on the plane? is there a doctor on the plane?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0383">I've been on a plane where that happened</u>
<u n="657" who="S0326">I have <unclear/> plane as well</u>
<u n="658" who="S0328">yeah so then this guy is like er I'm a doctor and like she's like are you? and is like goes over like I couldn't see exactly what was happening but like he like leans over he's like there for a while and then he goes back to his seat and then she goes to is there another doctor on the plane?</u>
<u n="659" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0328">and some guy is like yeah I'm a doctor it was funny he was able to help</u>
<u n="661" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0326">yeah I might next time someone asks that like me</u>
<u n="663" who="S0328">are there any more doctors on the plane?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0326">doctor of philosophy</u>
<u n="665" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0383">did you did you see that Derren Brown when he like there was this guy that was terrified of flying and he like it was over a really long period of time and then he like hypnotised him and then he got on the plane and they faked like an emergency on the plane and they hypnotised him not to knocked him out and put him in a flight simulator and he had to like land the plane it was really amazing like so they like hypnotised him and then like they're like we need someone to like <trunc>la</trunc> to land the plane the pilot has died or whatever and no one on the plane volunteered so it got to the point at which he was like I'm gonna have to do it cos everyone on the plane was actors but it was like a real flight and then they hypnotised him knocked him out put him in a flight simulator so he genuinely thought he was in a a cockpit and like landed the plane it was really funny but erm</u>
<u n="667" who="S0328">and then he wasn't scared of flying any more?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0383" trans="overlap">but apparently like he didn't it wasn't to do with like to overcome his fear of flying</u>
<u n="669" who="S0326">probably just make it worse</u>
<u n="670" who="S0383">it was just like a TV show</u>
<u n="671" who="S0328">that's crazy</u>
<u n="672" who="S0383">have you ever thought you were going to die on a plane?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0328">no er a couple of times I've been like er you can you know when it gets like <trunc>real</trunc> and you can erm imagine</u>
<u n="674" who="S0383" trans="overlap">I've been yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0328">I've never like really thought it though</u>
<u n="676" who="S0383">I've got like shit scared where it's just like dropped and like turbulence I've just been like fuck</u>
<u n="677" who="S0326">my brother's too scared to go on planes</u>
<u n="678" who="S0328">ah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s told me he was really scared we were talking one time <unclear/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0326">there's another story about erm when Justin Bieber took his private jet to the Super Bowl his pilots had to get their oxygen masks to come down cos of the when they were flying so they could weed smoke on the plane</u>
<u n="680" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0383">JB JB</u>
<u n="682" who="S0326">now now he can drink legally it's gonna be crazy</u>
<u n="683" who="S0328">when can you drink legally in</u>
<u n="684" who="S0326">like I can drink in <anon type="place"/> in the next couple of months</u>
<u n="685" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh man it was so funny when we was we were hanging out with my friend in erm <anon type="place"/> and he's like we'd hung out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a couple of times in <anon type="place"/> and erm and anyway he's like my age or a bit older or whatever and erm and we were we'd been like up for like two days or some shit and like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it was like ten AM in the morning and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to get some beer he's like oh I better take my fake ID and like looked about the house</u>
<u n="686" who="S0326">I'd forgotten it</u>
<u n="687" who="S0328">my friend just looked at me like what? are you fucking kidding me? how old is he?</u>
<u n="688" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0326">but the funny thing about that is actually forgot it after all that and when I went downstairs to the <trunc>ge</trunc> deli to get beer they were I obviously they ID'd me and I had to like <trunc>ma</trunc> I made up that it was a tradition in <anon type="place"/> that on Boxing Day you have to drink beer at ten forty AM I'm like my ID's just upstairs but I've got to get the beer up there now</u>
<u n="690" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0326">like I'll be back later to get more and I'll bring my ID but I've just got to go now and the guys like okay er fine</u>
<u n="692" who="S0328">oh he said okay yeah fine <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="693" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0383">that one's ours</u>
<u n="695" who="S0326">that one ours</u>
<u n="696" who="S0328">that one's ours</u>
<u n="697" who="S0326">we drank a hundred Becks a hundred bottles of Becks</u>
<u n="698" who="S0328">we drank so much Becks man Becks on the beach</u>
<u n="699" who="S0326">the whole <unclear/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0328">Posh and Becks</u>
<u n="701" who="S0383">are we near the beach now? look at those colours</u>
<u n="702" who="S0328">looks pretty beachy</u>
<u n="703" who="S0383">beachy</u>
<u n="704" who="S0326">it looks nice down there</u>
<u n="705" who="S0328">look at the graves graves graves end innit</u>
<u n="706" who="S0326">they're all bent over though</u>
<u n="707" who="S0328">cos they're old</u>
<u n="708" who="S0383">quite a sparse grave yard innit?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0326">it's pretty remote</u>
<u n="710" who="S0328">it looks like giants</u>
<u n="711" who="S0383">it's where they put all the yeah tall people <pause dur="long"/> do you reckon you have to pay more for like having</u>
<u n="712" who="S0328">extra leg room</u>
<u n="713" who="S0326">there's a really funny Curb Your Enthusiasm when they have an arguments about that who's going to be next to who in their plot</u>
<u n="714" who="S0328">yeah I don't want to be next to you for eternity</u>
<u n="715" who="S0326">oh yeah and he doesn't <unclear/> sell his plot to some like terrible person just to annoy them so they're going to be buried</u>
<u n="716" who="S0328">yeah that random chick whose like the alcoholic erm alcoholic chauffeur's dad who died or whatever</u>
<u n="717" who="S0326">oh yeah that's so funny when he becomes a limo driver <pause dur="long"/> you tired?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0328">I know cos I can read it on the thing</u>
<u n="719" who="S0326">not everyone can read though</u>
<u n="720" who="S0328">erm what</u>
<u n="721" who="S0326">not everyone can read</u>
<u n="722" who="S0328">especially not those kids you had to teach erm do you reckon there's a coffee bit on this train?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0383">yeah but I think we're nearly there</u>
<u n="724" who="S0326">that's the that's the end no we came through there didn't we?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0383">oh no that was the toilet</u>
<u n="726" who="S0326">yeah we walked all the way through no we've got an hour left</u>
<u n="727" who="S0383">we've got an hour left?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0328">what?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0383">nah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0326">it's a two hour train innit?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0383">no</u>
<u n="733" who="S0326">yeah we only stopped at three places like two pages of stations</u>
<u n="734" who="S0328">what?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0326">see what time it is</u>
<u n="736" who="S0328">I want a snack there is coffee there</u>
<u n="737" who="S0383">I want a coffee</u>
<u n="738" who="S0328">where's the coffee man?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0326">I want coffee go and explore a bit</u>
<u n="740" who="S0328">you can't have a train this big and no coffee</u>
<u n="741" who="S0383">oh yeah it is an hour left if you find coffee can you get me a coffee?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0328">yeah I'll get you one</u>
<u n="743" who="S0326">get the window seat</u>
<u n="744" who="S0383">got a window seat I thought <anon type="place"/> was like right near the beach?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0326">I think we are I think we're just going to like dawdle our way the rest of the way</u>
<u n="746" who="S0383">yeah like go along the coast</u>
<u n="747" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0383">from everybody off school bus <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0326">Kent is next to Devon right?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0383">I don't totally not totally not</u>
<u n="751" who="S0326">is it next to it?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0383">London</u>
<u n="753" who="S0326">and then what what about on there?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0383">I don't know let's have a look oh let's have a look</u>
<u n="755" who="S0326">we're going to <anon type="place"/> LOL Earl of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="756" who="S0383">see we are right by the beach</u>
<u n="757" who="S0326">yeah that's the ocean over there</u>
<u n="758" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0383">shit</u>
<u n="760" who="S0326">let's sit over there man</u>
<u n="761" who="S0383">get a sea view <unclear/> sea</u>
<u n="762" who="S0326">what can I do with this? <unclear/> in the end it's only a it's out there you know?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0383">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah like we've basically got to go all the way round yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0326">well we it'll be nice to look out the window though</u>
<u n="765" who="S0383">you know what though you can get the train from <anon type="place"/> usually to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="766" who="S0326">yeah we stopped at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0383">did we?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0326">yeah it's a slow one I think that's <pause dur="short"/> did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> tell you when we went to <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> we nicked all the champagne and got pissed drunk?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0383">up at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0326">but it's so unlike her though</u>
<u n="771" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's totally like her</u>
<u n="772" who="S0326">yeah I guess more like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though <pause dur="long"/> whatever</u>
<u n="773" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0326">it looks well good <pause dur="short"/> isn't this?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0383">the sea is pretty cool</u>
<u n="776" who="S0326">look at the cliffs</u>
<u n="777" who="S0383">yeah cos we're gonna it's all like the white cliffs innit like Dover and all that</u>
<u n="778" who="S0326">that's why people call it <unclear/> Albian and that cos it's <trunc>La</trunc> Latin for white is Albus</u>
<u n="779" who="S0383">oh really?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0326">yeah it's the white cliffs so like when the Romans come they decided to call it Alpa</u>
<u n="781" who="S0383">interesting</u>
<u n="782" who="S0326">is this the train line that got totally fucked in the storms last?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0383">no that was in Devon it's like <anon type="place"/> it's like along the like Jurassic coast the Jurassic coast</u>
<u n="784" who="S0326">we should go there as well that's what's good about having a car you just go anywhere like England's a small country</u>
<u n="785" who="S0383">yeah and then you just like sleep in the car</u>
<u n="786" who="S0326">yeah you know I'm convinced that people you know those <trunc>Zi</trunc> erm Zipvans that you hire per hour?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0326">I I think whenever it <trunc>sm</trunc>smelt of weed I think it was going as like smoke weed</u>
<u n="789" who="S0383">I like loads of times I got Zipcars it just stunk of weed or people just like dealing weed you know cos it's like you're not going to get the number</u>
<u n="790" who="S0326">yeah take prostitutes in there and stuff</u>
<u n="791" who="S0383">doing like massive drug deals yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0383">totally like moving shit around like if you get caught you can just leg it and like not last summer but the summer before I went to so many places and just like stayed in my car</u>
<u n="794" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0383">drove all the way to the the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0326">you can sleep outside as well if it's hot</u>
<u n="797" who="S0383">yeah we stayed there's this really amazing beach called <anon type="place"/> some like</u>
<u n="798" who="S0326">and you go through the drive up drive in to like Europe and you can go anywhere</u>
<u n="799" who="S0383">yeah I've never really I've driven I like driven in Europe but I haven't driven like across Europe</u>
<u n="800" who="S0326">yeah that's like when I was younger my my dad went to a holiday where we just like drive to <anon type="place"/> and drive back</u>
<u n="801" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0326">bit boring</u>
<u n="803" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no but I always like I used to go to <anon type="place"/> like quite a lot and just like get a car and just drive <anon type="place"/> is amazing for doing that cos you drive all the way through the <anon type="place"/> and then you drive into the desert</u>
<u n="804" who="S0326">yeah it sounds good</u>
<u n="805" who="S0383">no?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0328">no nothing on this train</u>
<u n="807" who="S0383">you see you see</u>
<u n="808" who="S0328">are we on the right train?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0383">it just like goes around the coast basically</u>
<u n="812" who="S0328">it doesn't say <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0326">I'm sure it is</u>
<u n="814" who="S0383">devotion</u>
<u n="815" who="S0328">they didn't say <anon type="place"/> on the announcer</u>
<u n="816" who="S0326">it is to <anon type="place"/> though</u>
<u n="817" who="S0328">they didn't say <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0326">it did it did earlier</u>
<u n="819" who="S0328">they said <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> but there's no sandwich cart</u>
<u n="820" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0328">I checked</u>
<u n="822" who="S0383">checked it</u>
<u n="823" who="S0328">er</u>
<u n="824" who="S0383"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0328">are you sure it says <anon type="place"/> it said <anon type="place"/> are you sure it said <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0326">yes I'm sure</u>
<u n="827" who="S0328">I don't mind we can go somewhere else as well</u>
<u n="828" who="S0383">apparently <anon type="place"/> is actually really nice</u>
<u n="829" who="S0328">let's go there</u>
<u n="830" who="S0383">it's not going to it's not going <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it doesn't say <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0328">yeah obviously</u>
<u n="833" who="S0326">it is it is</u>
<u n="834" who="S0383">we got them but he checked our ticket</u>
<u n="835" who="S0326">we didn't we didn't we didn't get on the wrong train because its twelve thirty-seven and it said to <anon type="place"/> on the announcement at the start when he spoke it</u>
<u n="836" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0326">when he just <unclear/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0383">yeah it definitely says this is the South East service to <anon type="place"/> now we'll be calling at <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0326">let me see that map</u>
<u n="840" who="S0383">and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0328">yeah where's the sandwiches? that's what I want to know</u>
<u n="842" who="S0326">I reckon it I reckon it still goes to</u>
<u n="843" who="S0383">yeah I reckon that's</u>
<u n="844" who="S0328">no way man</u>
<u n="845" who="S0326">alright I bet you a fiver babe</u>
<u n="846" who="S0328">well when's <anon type="place"/> then? what does it say on there?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0326">well <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> is basically the same thing and obviously</u>
<u n="848" who="S0328">yeah but if it was stopping at <anon type="place"/> it would say so right?</u>
<u n="849" who="S0326">not necessarily that could be wrong</u>
<u n="850" who="S0328">what does this say?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0326">cos that's the map <pause dur="long"/> shit I've got no battery did you bring a charger?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0328">no did you?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="855" who="S0328">that's that then</u>
<u n="856" who="S0326">have they got an Apple Store in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0383">probably they've got a Primark <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0328">shall we just go somewhere else?</u>
<u n="859" who="S0326">what do you mean you want us to go and get off?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0328">no I mean if it doesn't go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0326">it goes to <anon type="place"/> is there any information guys anywhere?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0328">what? no</u>
<u n="863" who="S0326">we're on the train that goes to <anon type="place"/> and it's and we're doing a bet as well</u>
<u n="864" who="S0328">well maybe let's check it</u>
<u n="865" who="S0326">fiver</u>
<u n="866" who="S0328">but I don't want to go to all the stops to find out why don't we just check</u>
<u n="867" who="S0326">cos I know for a fact</u>
<u n="868" who="S0383">next stop we'll get off and see what it says not like off just go to the door</u>
<u n="869" who="S0326">I can see that going wrong</u>
<u n="870" who="S0383">I'll just poke my head out the door oh sick look at that tunnel we just came through right through there</u>
<u n="871" who="S0326">we definitely <trunc>we</trunc> like massively went downhill then cos we were on top of that cliff just now</u>
<u n="872" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="873" who="S0326">anyway so are we doing a bet?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0328">uhu I didn't know train tracks could go down</u>
<u n="875" who="S0326">do you want to do a bet? makes it fun</u>
<u n="876" who="S0328">mm</u>
<u n="877" who="S0326">why not?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0328">what are you basing it on?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0326">I base it on my sense of certainty</u>
<u n="880" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0328">yeah but I just want to find out you know</u>
<u n="882" who="S0326">I'll find out if you do the bet</u>
<u n="883" who="S0328">no</u>
<u n="884" who="S0326">we got on a train at twelve thirty-seven to <anon type="place"/> takes two hours</u>
<u n="885" who="S0328">I've got no reason to think that there's like to strongly believe that we're not going to <anon type="place"/> except for that it doesn't say it on the train I just want to find out if we are or not</u>
<u n="886" who="S0326">there should be an app for what train am I on?</u>
<u n="887" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0326">he definitely said it out loud</u>
<u n="890" who="S0328">he might have said <anon type="place"/> innit?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0326">no cos I was listening</u>
<u n="892" who="S0328">when at the beginning?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0328">did we miss it?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0326">and even if we go up <anon type="place"/> it'll just be like it's like two minutes away from <anon type="place"/> on another train <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0383">we're going through another tunnel <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0326">we'll go on a boat get seasick</u>
<u n="898" who="S0328">mm mm</u>
<u n="899" who="S0326">it's what is this?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0328">mm?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0326">what is this? <pause dur="short"/> I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I couldn't get into Weatherspoons last night</u>
<u n="902" who="S0328">they wouldn't let <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> into Weatherspoons</u>
<u n="903" who="S0383">why not?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0328">too drunk</u>
<u n="905" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they said I was ID'd</u>
<u n="906" who="S0328">I always get ID'd at that Weatherspoons</u>
<u n="907" who="S0326">not old enough</u>
<u n="908" who="S0328">it's like I run a business <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going to come and help me</u>
<u n="909" who="S0326">I know</u>
<u n="910" who="S0328">I know these guys</u>
<u n="911" who="S0326">I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> go help her help her get into Weatherspoons</u>
<u n="912" who="S0328">it's hard to get into Weatherspoons</u>
<u n="913" who="S0326">when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is drunk he can't not can't look not drunk <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="914" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0326">it's like in his eyes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0328">erm actually on that very same Weatherspoons when I was leaving to go to <anon type="place"/> I was like with my friend and she got ID'd and the guy was like she was like I'm twenty-five or something like that and then the bouncer goes do you expect me to believe that? and she goes I don't expect anything from you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0383"><unclear/></u>
<u n="918" who="S0326">did she get in?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0328">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="920" who="S0326">oh man is it going to be this slow all the rest of the way?</u>
<u n="921" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="922" who="S0328">so how are you going to find out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="923" who="S0326">wait till we get there er I'll go on the app</u>
<u n="924" who="S0328">I think any of these towns will be these little places will be lovely</u>
<u n="925" who="S0326">I don't want to go to I want to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="926" who="S0328">check if it's going there then <pause dur="short"/> that says <anon type="place"/> and it's going that way we missed the stop no that's the this side</u>
<u n="927" who="S0326">what are you on about?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0328">oh never mind oh well</u>
<u n="929" who="S0326">we missed the stop</u>
<u n="930" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> or not</u>
<u n="931" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">it is definitely going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0326">yeah thanks</u>
<u n="934" who="S0328">thank you</u>
<u n="935" who="S0326">can I have a fiver now?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0328">no I didn't bet you on it I just wanted to know for sure</u>
<u n="937" who="S0383">now we know</u>
<u n="938" who="S0328">I know better than <unclear/> thank you</u>
<u n="939" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">alright</u>
<u n="940" who="S0326">can I have a fiver?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0328">you wish man no way</u>
<u n="942" who="S0326">the fact that I was going to do a bet on it should have been enough</u>
<u n="943" who="S0328">it was</u>
<u n="944" who="S0383">people are really into fashion</u>
<u n="945" who="S0328">you're well you're wilfully surrounding yourself by them</u>
<u n="946" who="S0383">by them? oh</u>
<u n="947" who="S0328">by them</u>
<u n="948" who="S0383">not wilfully I just need to have a job oh god it's so it's like the most boring shit in the world</u>
<u n="949" who="S0328">obviously and it's retarded</u>
<u n="950" who="S0383">everyone's really thick</u>
<u n="951" who="S0328">and they really really care about nothing</u>
<u n="952" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="953" who="S0328">I mean they do</u>
<u n="954" who="S0383">I think it's just cos it's it's really easy</u>
<u n="955" who="S0328">some of the most like highly strung intense and angry people I've ever met it's like you're talking about nothing</u>
<u n="956" who="S0383">that's the thing it's really easy to talk about oh my god did you see that and it's like yeah it's amazing it's so cute and you're just like and they get to like speak any like all you can talk about is like an understanding of why they did something you're like that's like that because of that but there's no like there's nothing deeper than that obviously there's like massive like cultural social shit addressed but they never obviously engage with that</u>
<u n="957" who="S0328">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="958" who="S0383">like did you see that Celine thing yeah it's like that Alexander Mcqueen thing last yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0328">yeah but did you see Madonna fall over?</u>
<u n="960" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="961" who="S0383">I met the girls that pulled her cape off</u>
<u n="962" who="S0328">no way? what happened to them?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0383">apparently she was just totally chill about it she was like oh don't worry</u>
<u n="964" who="S0328">no way</u>
<u n="965" who="S0383">yeah cos we were doing this film with these like</u>
<u n="966" who="S0328" trans="overlap">that's not what I read</u>
<u n="967" who="S0326">what happened to them?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0383">no we're doing this film with like these like Japanese lesbian couple that are like they like they're like voguers and they Madonna recruited them and cos they were over here they were over here doing that and then we like</u>
<u n="969" who="S0328">that's who pulled the cape?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0383">well they were part of the crew of dancers and literally they just</u>
<u n="971" who="S0328">she didn't care</u>
<u n="972" who="S0383">apparently she was just like it happens</u>
<u n="973" who="S0328">wow Madonna zen it's all like Kabbalah innit? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0383">yeah it was really funny I was hanging out the other day they came to like say hello at the office</u>
<u n="975" who="S0328">mm</u>
<u n="976" who="S0383">and there's like one that's like the dominant one and then this other one because they're like Japanese everything is like so over the top so the dominant one like literally looks like a like erm what's it called? like a</u>
<u n="977" who="S0328">S and M</u>
<u n="978" who="S0383">like an S and M like mistress or like a maid or whatever like a dominatrix</u>
<u n="979" who="S0328">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="980" who="S0383">and the undominant one like had a teddy bear</u>
<u n="981" who="S0328">wow</u>
<u n="982" who="S0383">and she like pulled her round and then they like you know like have you been to Japan?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="984" who="S0328">no</u>
<u n="985" who="S0383">there's like quite a thing like there's a lot of like older <trunc>Jap</trunc> like they're kind of like middle age but like really into like the whole like not like hariuki shit but like just really like cutesy shit so they and they're all like the like they're nerdy mum's basically and they have this woman and we're like what is her role? and they're like she's out godmother so she's just like their mum so she's not their assistant they have like an assistant they have a manager she's just like kind of takes care of them</u>
<u n="986" who="S0328">makes them tea?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0383">no she just like looks after them it's like having a family member that travels with you or whatever she's so cute and she was like obviously like in like her mid forties and she and you know Japanese people love whisky and every she made us take so many photos and she'd be like whisky</u>
<u n="988" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="989" who="S0383">and but you know and she wears like she had three baseball caps on <vocal desc="laugh"/> one pointing forwards one pointing backwards and one pointing to the side</u>
<u n="990" who="S0328">what?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0383">yeah and like a massive backpack and like a huge like oversized like Mickey Mouse jumper and like huge trainers that were like snow boots</u>
<u n="992" who="S0328" trans="overlap">seriously?</u>
<u n="993" who="S0383">it was so funny and she's like I am godmother</u>
<u n="994" who="S0328">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0383">it was so odd</u>
<u n="996" who="S0328">what were you doing with them?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0383" trans="overlap">and then <pause dur="short"/> we're doing this film next week <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> they asked me so like cos we're just like hey just come over and meet us cos their manager was going home before the film and then he like took me aside and he's like I can't remember what he said but he was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> san erm</u>
<u n="998" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> san?</u>
<u n="999" who="S0383"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> san cos like san is like sir or whatever in Japanese but they say it at the end and like but then the if they're they they call me Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on emails they call me like Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="1000" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1001" who="S0383">anyway</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I wanna start calling you Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1003" who="S0383">and he's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> san make sure we have Coca-Cola Zero and I was like any other requests he's like nope like nothing about paying them or anything it's just like make sure we have Coca-Cola Zero like okay</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0328">yeah take care of that</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0383">got it got loads of Coca-Cola Zero</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0326">castle there's a castle <pause dur="short"/> is that the one that your friend's getting?</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0383">no friend's one's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1008" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1009" who="S0328">where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0326">I've been there</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0383">dunno</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0328">where is it? in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0326" trans="overlap">that's where that's where the house at</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0383" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0326">when I was a kid I used to go to a house there</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0383">yeah that's what's it called again <anon type="place"/>'s?</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0326">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> well the people from <anon type="place"/> know each other</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0383">yeah my brother's like best friends with her <pause dur="short"/> my brother</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0328">how weird</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0383">she's got like stuffed monkeys in her house and stuff</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0326">yeah it's weird it's weird I quite like it's like</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0383">whose house is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> peed in it</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0383"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> peed in the house?</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0326">no don't tell him that cos he'll tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1027" who="S0383">I don't even know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1028" who="S0328">what did you pee in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0326">I don't know</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0328">a corner</u>
<u n="1031" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1032" who="S0326">I got lost</u>
<u n="1033" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0326">a moody cat there was a cat as well</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0328">frightened</u>
<event desc="sound of train announcement"/>
<u n="1036" who="S0328">actually there was some confusion being caused <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's confusing when you keep saying sandwich and I checked the whole train for it</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0383"><anon type="place"/> is actually really nice like <anon type="place"/> has got this really I think like Charles Dickens like resided for a bit in <anon type="place"/> it has a really good restaurant with this incredible it's a called like <anon type="place"/> or something it's like this like gelato like ice cream  parlour that's all pink and it's like really seventies it's quite cool</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0328">let's go there but I bet it's closed on Sunday</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0383">I've been there on Sunday</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0328">yeah I mean I don't I don't mind going wherever</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0326">I want I want I want to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to go to <anon type="place"/> let's go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0383">let's got to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1044" who="S0326">I haven't been there</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0328">he's never been he's never been</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0326">I've never been to the other place either but</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0328">I've never been to any of them</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0383">I've been to them all</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0328">done them all</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0383">see this is what you can do when you got a car man went to all of them I went to <anon type="place"/> three times in one day</u>
<u n="1051" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1052" who="S0383">honestly I went and then went to find somewhere better but can't find anywhere better went back got to be somewhere better wasn't</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0326">it's like when I <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you like <anon type="place"/> she's like yeah man I went four times in one year</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0328">it's true</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0383">is <anon type="place"/> nice?</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0328">I really liked it I really liked <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1057" who="S0383">I was thinking of going</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0328">but I oh it will have changed a lot recently you know I don't know what it'll be like now I <trunc>h</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to go back we went together and we had a really good time but like</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0383">the thing is Thai people are really savage</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0328">no Thai people are really really friendly Chinese people can be like tougher Thai people are very calm and like there is like Buddhist culture and it yeah</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0383">but that whole like <pause dur="short"/> cambodians they get</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0328">they've got a very mild manner it's really striking in <anon type="place"/> cos it's a huge huge city like over populated and we were like everybody is like always like really really tidy like really really polite and l like you see people who are just like older people sort of just sitting by the side of the street and eating lunch of like a crate or something and it's like excellent table manners you know like <trunc>s</trunc> like generous</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0326">did I tell you that I think I did tell you erm my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his uncle who went moved to <anon type="place"/> got a wife</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0328">yeah this is funny</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0326">and he brought his wife back to <anon type="place"/> like introduced her to her family like she knew some English and stuff and then he went back to <anon type="place"/> and like two years later he had to come back for like a funeral or something and he came back and his wife he said that it was a different woman and he just pretended that it was the same woman and this one didn't speak and English and looked different</u>
<u n="1066" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1067" who="S0328">the other one did speak English</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0326">and he just thought no one would <trunc>no</trunc>notice</u>
<u n="1069" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1070" who="S0326">so he probably was like obviously never really his wife at all just like his</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0383">my housemates dad just moved to <anon type="place"/> and got a wife he used to be a mercenary <pause dur="long"/> I didn't really understand like the full extent</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0328">is this that girl <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0383">no this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1074" who="S0328">you've lived with so many people</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0383">I did not understand the extent to which like British and the US military use like mercenary forces</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0383">and they've basically like <trunc>e</trunc> pretty much every other country in the world has signed like all these conventions about like using mercenary forces apart from the UK and the US</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0326">yes I like my mum has a friend who used to be a ABC correspondent for Middle East and had all these connections and was friends with people like Imran Khan and we like go to lunch at his house there's always like mercenaries and stuff this one has got a private army like twenty thousand people who are like they're getting paid so much money</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0383">I think it's like certain people enjoy killing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1081" who="S0383">no we won't be</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0326">can you get good fish?</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0328">I don't know I've never been there</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0383"><anon type="place"/> is nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="1085" who="S0326">that's good I mean like fish and chips or</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0383">I well wanna get fish and chips</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0328">there must be so many</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0326">I want to have a snooze on the beach</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0383">yeah but it's cold and stuff</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0328">it's cold and stuff last time we went to <anon type="place"/> we got so wasted we had to stay the night in</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0383">it was so funny</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0328">I go one the train and like just fell over straightaway</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0326">it was pouring with rain</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0328">it was so rainy we still had so much fun though</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0326">while it's called</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0383">we just went to a pub then that's like</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0328">we went to a bunch of pubs walked around in the rain heaps ate some dinner and then we got to stay at this place and then the rain stopped and we went down to the beach</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0326">we nicked the we nicked the balls I already told him like I was like it's so unlike <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he's like whatever it's exactly like her</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0328">no it's not it's not like me it's really not erm I did do it though</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0326">while while she's booking you a cab</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0328">I did do that however it's not it's not it's not the kind of thing I normally do anyway so then we went back stayed at this like cheap hotel the night</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0326">stayed at Premier Inn</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0328">stayed at Premier Inn and erm and then the rain stopped and we went down to the beach and we saw shooting stars and went in the water and it was really nice</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0383">did you go out cos you know at <anon type="place"/> you can go out</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0328" trans="overlap">it was like torrential</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0383">to like where they've got the like like big poles in the water and there's like a platform so they're like really far out but I think you can stand up on them in the middle of the ocean</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0383">we <trunc>di</trunc> we we just sort of like went in and got out quickly</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0326">you didn't go in?</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0328">I did</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0326">oh yeah you did</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0383">night swimming is really I love night swimming</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0328">yeah me too</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0383">have you seen that crazy like erm kelp that they've just discovered?</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0328">no</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0383">that like basically it's like erm florescent so like if a fish like swims passed it all like illuminates it's really amazing</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0328">like by phosphorus</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0326">we went night swimming right like in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1118" who="S0328">oh yeah ha ha we went night swimming in <anon type="place"/> or we were going to we were like there was like moonlight it was sort of warm like left this restaurant like a little bit drunk</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0326">you were fucking wasted</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0328">wasted and erm went in and then like I don't know what it was like man or war or some shit but like some crazy like jellyfish like stung me</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0383">oh shit</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0328">it was like I felt like my legs were being cut off and we just like walked a bit</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0383">did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have to pee all over you?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0328">and then we like ran out like screaming I had these like welts went to the pharmacy and like to see if they could help me and he looked at my legs he went hey Madonna</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0326">I think it was actually lucky you were so off your face I think if you were sober it would have been like a lot worse</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0328">why? more painful?</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0326">cos you remember how drunk you were? until we made friends with the people who owned the restaurant and they just <trunc>co</trunc> just kept giving us Ouzo</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0328">I remember that</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0383">I hate Ouzo</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0328">I remember having the hiccups</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0383">I've never been to Greece</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0326">it's good</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0383">I was meant to go to <anon type="place"/> last year but I didn't <pause dur="short"/> it's like the party island like party</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0328">I really liked it</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0383">I hear it's really good to go like yachting in like <anon type="place"/> I really would like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1136" who="S0326">yeah my friends they did that in <anon type="place"/> but they don't really know how to sail but my friend she erm forged a boat license on Photoshop and they rented out like a cos they're like quite good at computers then and then rented out a erm like two million euro yacht and kind of knew how to sail but not really they didn't know any of the rules about how to park it and stuff so every time they wanted to get stuff they'd have to like they just left it in the ocean and like rowed cos they <unclear/> they didn't want to get caught</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0383">yeah just swim in</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0326">and they <trunc>sa</trunc> and they didn't have enough they didn't like have enough like water or like they'd never been like yachting before they had a there's like reservoirs in <anon type="place"/> that they used to do it but they'd forgotten to get like fresh water and stuff and</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0383">yeah the problem is all I want to do is go on holiday and just <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1140" who="S0328">we're all gonna run out of battery do you know that?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0326">do I know that?</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0328">did you know that?</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0326">yeah I'm used to it man</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0328">you're like what is battery?</u>
<u n="1145" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1146" who="S0326">can't wait to try and fix this</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0383">what? you can't wait to fix it?</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0326">try and fix it yeah I'm trying to fix the screen myself maybe as well <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1149" who="S0383">it's well easy to do it actually like</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0326">apparently they <trunc>fi</trunc>they're <trunc>fi</trunc> they five five S is more difficult</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0383">oh really? I had to fix my whole laptop just like Youtube guides</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0326">yeah did we send you that? did we talked about the one we saw for fixing the bent one</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0383">you sent me something but I haven't watched it</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0326">they're just like stoned and they're doing a tutorial video</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0328">they're really funny</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0326">they are funny they are funny <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1157" who="S0383"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1158" who="S0328">ow</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0326">ow</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0328">yes it's hardly at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1161" who="S0383"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0326">still like forty minutes</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0328">it's <unclear/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1164" who="S0326">it's still a long time to go</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0328">what?</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0383">we've got half an hour still</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0326">if we took the other train</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0328">but the other train was stopping at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1169" who="S0383">we'd have had to wait for an hour but we'd be there now</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0326">really?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0328">no</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0383">yeah oh no we'd be there</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0328">we'd get there the same time</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0383">yeah we'd get there at the same time it's just less time on the train <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1175" who="S0326">you're not going to run out of battery cos you have like seventy why does it go down so fast?</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0383">yeah its looks like <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0328">it's funny it is</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0383">why?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0328"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1180" who="S0383">I didn't know it was International Women's Day today</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0328">huh? what?</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0383">any words for International Women's Day?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0328">any words?</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0326">let's have a speech</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0328">as an international woman</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0326">I want to start</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0328">I want to thank a few people <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'd like to thank <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1188" who="S0326">is there an international man's day?</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0328">every day</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0326">yeah every day that's right</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0383">yeah we got three hundred and sixty-three days</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0328">three hundred and sixty-three</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0383">forget that one how many days in a year?</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0328">seventy-two I think</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0326">three hundred and sixty-five three hundred and sixty-five?</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0383">I vote there's so much shit like that that I don't know</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> my my brother doesn't know doesn't even know all the months in the year</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0328">oh</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0383">I didn't know my alphabet until I was about fifteen and I still can't I have to if someone's like what's after I was going to say Z but obviously there's nothing after it</u>
<u n="1200" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1201" who="S0328">I still don't know what's after Z I only got only ever got up to that</u>
<u n="1202" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1203" who="S0383">I have to go all the way through the alphabet</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0326">I can yeah I can't</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0383">actually no I can do J K L M N O P I can't start at like</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0326">what's after V?</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0383">W</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0328">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1209" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1210" who="S0383">what?</u>
<u n="1211" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1212" who="S0328"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1213" who="S0326">you know how I persuaded <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0383">no</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0326">but he he hasn't really been to the countryside erm I think he had a video of reindeer at Christmas market and I told him that there was actually those were horses with things stuck on he was like no?</u>
<u n="1216" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1217" who="S0328">and they all take the piss</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0326">he believed it what's that a donkey?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0328">donkey</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0326">it looks kind of like a hyena</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0383">it's a bit dark innit? it looks like a hyena?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0328">what do they have donkeys for? for kids to</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0326">you can ride donkeys can't you on the beach? I think that's banned these days</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0328">what what do they use donkeys for seriously?</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0326">to carry stuff</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0383">do you know what I've got an encyclopaedia of horses that all the different horse breeds</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0326">sounds good</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0328">when we were in when we were on holiday erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> pointed at something in the street in <anon type="place"/> he's like what kind of animal is that? and I was like that's a human</u>
<u n="1230" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1231" who="S0326">it was lying on the ground doing something to the drain</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0328">and then he did it another time he said what kind of animal is that? It's like duh</u>
<u n="1233" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1234" who="S0326">well it looked like a raccoon or something that's all</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's human</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0326">I saw a raccoon once</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0383">I saw a possum I tried to shoot it</u>
<u n="1238" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1239" who="S0326">what's the most exciting animal that you've see not in a zoo?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0383">I saw an elephant in the wild</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0328">kangaroo</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0326">I've never seen a kangaroo</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0383">I've never seen a kangaroo in the wild</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0328">I think he was a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1245" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I've seen a kangaroo on Youtube boxing at Woody Allen though</u>
<u n="1246" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1247" who="S0328">me too</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0383">I must have seen a lizard or something</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0326">yeah I've seen a lizard</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0383">snake?</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0326">seen a snake</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0328">yeah if it's not in a zoo</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0326">where have I been I've been to like</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0383">have you seen those miniature parrots that are like this big?</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0328">no but I want to</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0383">they're really cute</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0326">I saw a parrot in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1259" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0326">took a picture</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0328">took a picture</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0383">seen like wild monkeys</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0328">I've seen wild monkeys riding on the backs of tortoises for real like big big tortoises in Barbados</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0383" trans="overlap">did you see that did you see that like squirrel on the internet or whatever that rides on the back of the bird</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0326">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0383">quite strange</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0328">ooh on a bird</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0326">it's like a <unclear/> right? it was it was a hummingbird or something</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0383">it went viral</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0326">a woodpecker it was a woodpecker and a baby raccoon like I don't know</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0328">did it die?</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0326">yeah it was trying to eat it</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0383">it looks really</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0328">it was trying to easy the bird?</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0328">the bird flew away?</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0326">I think so yeah but it's like it hopped on to it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1278" who="S0328">well I saw these monkeys literally just like sitting on the tortoise and fucking on him all day long and that was the life or the tortoise <unclear/></u>
<u n="1279" who="S0326">did you I've seen a on a you on Youtube I've seen a monkey riding a pig</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0383">I've seen that</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0328">yeah you showed me that</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0383">that's don't they do that like</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0326">hunt them or something</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0328">they train them</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0383">no but they like race them?</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0328">yeah man they're crazy</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0383">have you seen those like robots <trunc>ra</trunc> camel race jockeys that they have in like Dubai and shit? they've got these like little robots that ride camels like</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0328"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1289" who="S0383">yeah and then they drive a long side it in their cars and they've got a remote control that like controls the whip</u>
<u n="1290" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1291" who="S0328"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1292" who="S0326">it's alright it'll be worth it when we get there</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0328">I dunno why am I so tired</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0326">we're in <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0383">I'm massively tired I stayed up until like four in the morning watching Has Beens</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0328">I couldn't sleep either oh yeah what's happening with that website now anyway? where are we up to?</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0383">the website? well we have to decide what to do with the</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0328">that page</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0383">that page cos I it's just gonna look retarded if you've got a page that shows like there's like not one single good photo of Camp Bestival</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0328">it can just be text that one though</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0383">I just don't know I mean it won't be a lot to do</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0328">just do it just do whatever even if it looks shit it's just like it's driving me nuts now</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0383">it's just opened a whole can of like demanding worms</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0328">I wish I haven't like let him give feedback in the first place cos now it's like it's his project and I'm like he's telling me whether it's right or not it's like if you wanted to do it you should have just done it from the start it's just like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1305" who="S0383">erm but I I'm going to get up early tomorrow and like do like three page designs for that page cos it doesn't to make it's not going to take anything more just to be like click to this click to this but erm that's why I was just like maybe we just keep it as it is so it can get built but</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0328">I told him that too but he's being</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0326">get things done</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0328">mm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0383">erm but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been emailing you right? about like actually like the build</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0328">erm I was just asking about that thing about the</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0383">about the form?</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0328">form which seems fine it's just going to go the Gmail and then a spreadsheet or something</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0383">cos all of that shit's built anyway but they're not having to rebuild that it's all it's all</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0328">yeah it's fine</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0383">but yeah I'll send you some options for that in the morning and if they</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0328">can't they get going with what you've got while you do that page?</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0383">erm</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0328">cos if it's going to be three days we'll just give them everything that's been signed off</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0383">yeah cos what did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> say? said it's going to be three days but</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0328">it's going to be three four days' work and like if it's just the working with us page or whatever can't we just like while we're going it</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0383">yeah I I'll speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the morning and just see if they could like what the time</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0328">get on with that other shit</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0328">cos it I I'm scared that it won't be three days it'll be like three weeks</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0328">well</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0383">but yeah I'll speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the morning and get him to do it</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0328">I don't know what to do about my site should I still get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do it or not?</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0383">well it's <trunc>ba</trunc></u>
<u n="1330" who="S0328">cos you've done the design but like nothing else has been done on that so like</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0383">well the guy <vocal desc="cough"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> started it I dunno I I'll update I just</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0328">cos I could just get someone else to do but but I don't know what to do</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0383">let me see where it's at? because I think it's like half built it's just like it's just got to be like touched up you know? it's just like it's built but it's just like</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0328">really? I thought nothing had been done on it</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0383">no it's like built to you know it's like you build the framework and then it's just like going back through the code cos you like the way you do it is like you build it and write all the code or whatever and then you'd be like oh that bit doesn't swirl properly you've got to like you know it's like a process of like fixing as opposed to like</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0383">so I think like that's done and it's just about like working out the bits so it's like yeah it's probably at a stage where you can just get someone else to look at that or but I feel like if we get someone else to work it out it'll just take longer</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0383">you know and it they'll be like well that's gonna cost <vocal desc="nonsense"/> whereas with us it's like I'm just like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you have to finish this</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1341" who="S0383">did and like I can't wait to be able to lose my shit on him he's <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1342" who="S0328">where did you meet him?</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0383">you know my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? there's like his</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0326">how do you how do you find them?</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0383">no but it's like I've known him for years <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I was never really like friends with him it's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wife <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he's like her old school friend and he was always one of those like cos he used to work at <anon type="place"/> he had like really good jobs</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0328">he always struck me as a pothead</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0383">yeah he's like he totally is and he's like I told you he like made loads of money buying shit for <unclear/> and stuff like that he's like a bit of a blagger but then he had like a really good job at <anon type="place"/> and a really good job at like some other like 3D motion company but</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0328">what happened to those?</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0383">well it's since transpired that actually his friend this guy's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is basically like just like a whizz kid at code and he just got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the jobs and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just like the guy that knows a abut about everything but doesn't really do it so he like clung on to me to be like oh yeah you can do the design and clung on to this other guy to be like and it's just like <unclear>like I said</unclear> so he doesn't really do anything he's just but he's not even good at that</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0383">you know it's like if you're that like you become a project manager and you're like really good at overseeing stuff and getting like this is the timeline this is <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="1352" who="S0328">cos what he really did or what really happened to the whole thing is that it was really badly project managed</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0328">I mean that's like what went wrong basically like he just wasn't upfront about things</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0383">yeah yeah because <trunc>basi</trunc> but also basically it's like what really</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0328">didn't really run with it</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0383">yeah and it's just like even stuff it's like I'm like yo have you sent that email? he's like oh didn't forgot to press reply or and it's just like are you fucking retarded? like</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0328">yeah too stoned</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0383">but but also there's just too <trunc>ma</trunc> it's like it would have just been easier if we but also like that's the whole thing it's like it's not like confident putting him in a room with like  <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and that you know it's like?</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0328">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0383">but actually that would have been well easier if at the beginning we were just like okay guys what do you want? <vocal desc="nonsense"/> and then it's like we'd be at the stage that we've got to now which actually could have got done it two weeks</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0328">yeah but I didn't know he was going to suddenly like have a really really really strong idea about exactly what it is and to be honest I haven't even been looking at what he's been saying I've just been going yeah yeah fine make you happy but it's <trunc>pos</trunc> it's likely that I wouldn't even agree with him you know that I would have done it differently like I don't know when it became his thing he's not even one of it's just like he's <trunc>constan</trunc> I dunno it's super annoying man I don't know how we've got into this situation where</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0383">I don't know</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like I'm going to <trunc>ch</trunc> and putting at retarded like the one bit I did read was like when he changed the home page text it was like I'm not saying that that's so lame</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0383">no but half the shit as well the thing that's really annoying is like when people propose stuff like maybe this will be a good idea and just be like I want this I want his and that kind of shit you can't be like oh maybe I want this and it's like actually no I want this and</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0328" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah I know well I <trunc>di</trunc> I did speak to him</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0383">but again that's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s but that's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s shit cos like <trunc>ac</trunc> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> kept you know when's like well we don't have all the stuff so I haven't done it I'm like if you need all the shit tell them that this is what you need</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0328">I told I was constantly saying do you have all the content you need from us? and he'd be like oh I need this one thing and that's it and I'd get him the thing and then he'd be like you know but like I was asking that all the time</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0383">that's what I mean like that's why I was trying to be like look like if you</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0328" trans="overlap">and now I'm like where is it? he hasn't even saved all the stuff I sent him I have to get it again</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0383">yeah but that's what I'm saying it's like but also it's like if that is the case you just be like look this is a stage we don't move on to that stage until this stage is complete rather than be like hey we have a bit coming in and cos then you're always like it's basically just not committing to something and just being like yeah we'll we'll like make it through like like we've always got an excuse you know it's always like a bit like yeah well we didn't do this because he didn't do that</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0328">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0383">and like de de it's like it doesn't matter if you need that to do that</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0328">should have got it</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0383">get it</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0328">oh man</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0383">it's just fucking tedious process</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0328">anyway what are we going to do to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to get him?</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0383">well one the thing is I don't want to say anything to him until the site's done until we figure out what's happening with yours</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0383">and then like <trunc>lu</trunc> we haven't paid him the second half of this one yet anyway so we're definitely not paying him that</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0328">you should get it</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0383">erm but I just I just don't I want to keep him sweet until we get what we need out of him before we torture him</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0328">break his legs take away his weed take away his like Netflix subscription and like delete all the pizza delivery numbers from his phone</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0383">ruin him</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0328"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and what</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0326">what's the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0383">he he's just</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0328">some reason and I don't know why whenever I do stuff for YBFs it goes wrong I'm not I'm good at stuff like you know if I say I'm going to do something I do it like and I do it well like on my own stuff it's like fine I think it's happened before like I did a photo shoot and I got a friend and like somebody who was like I really thought was going to be great and he just did like an awful job</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0383">really?</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0328">we can never use the photos so for some reason I just things go wrong when I do it for anyone else apart from me almost like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1392" who="S0326">maybe cos you get your friends to do it</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0328">no like no more than I do in normal thing and like this guy was like it's like somebody <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always works with and like was really highly recommended and like should have been great he just got it wrong he just fucked it up wasted loads of people's time waste of money</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0328">but also to an extent maybe that's like not being used to working with other people who have opinions any more cos like if it's my thing I just do it I know if it's right if I'm trying to please somebody else and like guess what they want then it's like</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0383">that's the thing is that you're constantly second guessing</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0383">but it's the <trunc>shi</trunc> it's the same shit as like when I was working for that guy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in <anon type="place"/> it's like he was the one who had the relations with the client but I was like <trunc>li</trunc> I was like delivering to him to then <trunc>deli</trunc> I was trying to</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0383">understand what he wanted to be the what he wanted me to deliver to him to deliver to the client rather than him just being like you guy you can speak to the client and then I know what they delivered so it's like I was second guessing what he wants or am I doing something that the client wants</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0328">yeah</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0383">cos I know what he's asked for they're not going to want to so it's like</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0328" trans="overlap">right yeah that's it er but now I feel like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like I feel like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s my client you know what I mean it's like what? it's my thing</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0383">but that's the thing it's like as soon as you give people like the ability to exercise</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0328">yeah yeah and I only did that</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0383" trans="overlap">that they like they take</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0328">because I like felt guilty cos we missed the deadline and I and I had vouched for it and like it's fine leave it with me <pause dur="short"/> I really <unclear/></u>
<u n="1408" who="S0383" trans="overlap">because actually it's the easiest thing to be able to go through something and be like no that needs to be like this and this needs to be like that like</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0328" trans="overlap">crossing the things out and then I actually looked at what he'd written and I wrote to him I was like <pause dur="short"/> we're not writing that on my home page it's fucking retarded</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0326">what was it?</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0328">ah I don't want to say it out loud man it's just like this like awful like matey language like trying to be your mate yeah</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0383" trans="overlap">trying to be your friend</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0328">trying to be your friend</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0326">back of an Innocent smoothie</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0328">yeah like Innocent smoothie</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0383" trans="overlap">I still think that like no age hashtag no age limit is the funniest shit in the world <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1417" who="S0328">that's not on there though</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it is</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0328">where?</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0383">I don't know</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1422" who="S0383">it's like hashtag no age limits but also to make that like your Twitter handle it's like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1423" who="S0328">it's not a Twitter handle</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0383" trans="overlap">it's not a Twitter handle but it's a Twitter hashtag that would for a while it was on the end of everything hashtag no age limit</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0328">that's probably me writing that to be honest</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know but just like if people like search hashtags for no age limit like the weirdest shit is going to come up it's not going to like <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="1427" who="S0328" trans="overlap">well if you search YMF you get you're my fabulous that's what that means <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1428" who="S0326">we're allowed to <unclear/> whoever texted you joins saying are you coming to the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1429" who="S0328">I mean <trunc>tr</trunc> I was trying to get an email address but it's like YBF everything is taken it's just like yeah YBF one hundred? it's like ah</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0383">the darker shit MIA if you search MIA it's like something erm anorexic</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0328" trans="overlap">M I A?</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0383">yeah like it's some like anorexia thing so dark like you look it up and there's like a picture of MIA and some fucking neon on and then just like girls like self harming and like</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0328">does MIA mean something?</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0383" trans="overlap">don't know like you know there's like that whole like pro ana stuff as well? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="sound of train announcement"/>
<u n="1435" who="S0328">well that was a <unclear>good joke</unclear> whoever did that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1436" who="S0326">is that what you you're just getting used to doing it <pause dur="short"/> says <unclear/></u>
<u n="1437" who="S0383" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0326">like when you're a teenager you can go to a park</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0383">go to a park yeah</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0328">go to a park</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0383" trans="overlap">drink some cider</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0383">on the slide</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes to me what's mother and son day?</u>
<u n="1445" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1446" who="S0328"><unclear/> mothering mothering here's</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0326" trans="overlap">oh Mothering Sunday? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1448" who="S0328" trans="overlap">it's mothering  son day why what about daughters?</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0383"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what about them? they get to be mum's at some point</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0326">what about them? they get to be mothers at some point</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0328">yeah I was like yeah it's your day when you procreate</u>
<u n="1452" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1453" who="S0328">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1455" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yes oh yes erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the kid in the <unclear/> because he was like went through a phase when he was always working in the bakery and like I don't know why she started doing it she calls him Mr I went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1456" who="S0383"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1457" who="S0328">no school</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0383">school</u>
<u n="1459" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1460" who="S0328">she says oh</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0383">intuitive</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0328">I went to <anon type="place"/> she didn't even get to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1463" who="S0326">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0383">what's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doing these days?</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0328">he's doing this project for like some company which is like developing er future plans for the Olympic space cos like they have to use that space like going forward some art projects architecture and something something culture</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0383">and playing World of Warcraft</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0328">it's like research it's like a research position mostly I don't know he he took it begrudgingly as part time it's just for money I think really like parts of it are fairly interesting and I think he has lot of like freedom and control you know and like no one like telling him what to do and like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1468" who="S0383" trans="overlap">turn the whole thing into a big ball park</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0328">yeah ball pit</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0383">ball pit</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0326">man I saw this <trunc>sta</trunc><trunc>sta</trunc>statistic about all the sort of if you add together all the hours that have been spent playing World of Warcraft</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0383">oh my god</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0326">it's like I can't remember how much it is but it's like something like sixty thousand years or something</u>
<u n="1474" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1475" who="S0328"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1476" who="S0383" trans="overlap">my friend went to like well not my friend my brother's friend went to <anon type="place"/> like to just before Christmas like go somewhere on like a gap trip gap year trip to <anon type="place"/> for like two months</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0328">gap trip</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0383">and he said they came back and they all got really obsessed with erm Age of Empires so they obviously went over like that colonial shit was well good and they're all like really into playing Age of Empires and then spent all Christmas just playing it</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0328">I once went to like my friend who was like well it wasn't my friend he was the guy who fixed my Mac but I was quite fascinated by him for a while cos he was like such a dude he was really into Warcraft and erm he had like two tickets to like go to the thing where they like launched the new like upgrades or whatever you know when they like release like a new level or like whatever it's just like this fucking insane dweeb fest you know</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0383">dweeb fest</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0328">nanas and like</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0326">no it it's six million years</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0383">oh my god that's disgusting</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0328">way more than sixty thousand</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0326">fifty billion hours of game time</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0383">there's only eight billion people of the world</u>
<u n="1487" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1488" who="S0326">eight billion that means like it's enough to say everybody in the whole world has played for like five hours</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0383">thirty-two yeah fucking hell</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0326">but er</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0383">how many users are there?</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0328">twelve</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0383">twelve</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0328">twelve users</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0383">I've done three billion hours he's done about six erm so what happened at the dweeb fest?</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0328">ah bless them that's really that's the end of the story it was just weird</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0383">it just went</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0328">yeah it just went and then I and then I all went like pretty quickly and then I had a wristband we went really early to get the wristband and when we got it we just left and I like kicked a door cos there was just like people queuing up for ages to get this ticket and I just picked one kid and gave him my thingy he looked like he wanted to marry me</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0326">probably the first time he's talked to a girl</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0328">yeah and I gave him my wristband for Warcraft like picked him out of a crowd of dweebs</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0326">reminds me about <anon type="place"/> do you notice how like <unclear/> just buying toys</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0328">yeah we stumbled across it it was quite cool actually but it was like a erm like a trade like a vintage toy market or something but like right in the middle of <anon type="place"/> and everything <trunc>col</trunc> like a collectors' fair everyone just had loads of shit out of the floor cos it was like this there were loads and loads of like goths and like you know like Mexican goths</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0383">Mexi goth did you guys <unclear/> like did you go to a pet market?</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0383">where they just have loads of pets</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0328">oh well in <anon type="place"/> they have pets but at the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1507" who="S0383">are they actually</u>
<u n="1508" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">there's yours</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0328">ah thank you yes</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0383">yeah</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0328">is that where you went? <anon type="place"/>? did they have witchy stuff too?</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0383">yeah it was like a witchcraft fair</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0328">and then they have toys so weird it's like witchcraft witchcraft spell spells spells piatas</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0383">animals to sacrifice</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0326">the funny piatas is like the one that was like a stripper</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0328">yeah the strippers one has fake dollars in it</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0326">and be and it's like by a stripper</u>
<u n="1518" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1519" who="S0383">don't do that</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0326">this is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1521" who="S0383">more than one stairs</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0328"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1523" who="S0383">I don't really like <anon type="place"/> to be honest</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0328">I really liked it I'd like to go ages and stay there stay there for ages</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0383">I didn't really like it</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0328"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did you ever meet a girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? she's friends with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's a an artist anyway she's Mexican or maybe she's Spanish but erm she was with this guy for ten years and they decided to like pack up her house here everything they sold and move to Mexico together they got married got mazzed she went to Mexico ahead of him like literally like the next week after they got married just like he was just like going to <unclear/> and like going to meet her in a week she got there and she was like actually do you know what I want a divorce I'm just going to move here by myself</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0383">oh my god that's for real?</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0328">she goes yeah she's just ditching him he's moved in with his parents</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0383">that is really harsh</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0328">yeah that's fucked</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0326">what happened?</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0328">huh?</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0326">she moved they moved to Mexico</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0328">they were together for ten years they got married decided to pack up their life sell the house move to Mexico he was like yeah I'll catch you up you know finish things up like meet you in  week and erm</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0383">ah man</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0328">and went there she was like I've had some second thoughts over here and like she's had a lover <unclear/> she had like four lovers or something like just like on <unclear/></u>
<u n="1537" who="S0383">Mexicans love having lovers like</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0328">yeah she got like a harem</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0383">like I know this girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1540" who="S0328">she's like actually I want to divorce they could get well no they opt they're trying to get a quicky divorce by saying it was never meant to be</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0326">ten years</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0383">oh really?</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0328">I think that they did I think never did technically</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0326">they never did it for ten years?</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0328">no not after they actually got married</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0326">they only got married at the very end</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0328">they got married at the end yeah like they were married for like four weeks or something</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0326">that would be that would be they obviously <unclear/> and then</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0328">how are you going to tell?</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0326">how are you going to tell cos <trunc>wha</trunc> we on the wedding night it'll be fun</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0328">it'll be fun well I I can't remember you'll have to ask <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about that it was something like that cos then then you don't have to it's like cheaper or something like that</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0326">yeah that's like what they used to do in the fifteenth century</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0328">no way I'd consummate anything in the fifteenth century <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1554" who="S0326">that would be well wicked</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0383">it's like last time we came well not last time we came on a road trip here with the <unclear/> money it was really fun my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we just drove down snoozed at we didn't even get out of the car just snoozed in the car and drove back</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0328">that's like when we went on that fishing trip it was like really expensive it was like four hundred dollars or something like US in <anon type="place"/> got up in the morning was like super hungover got seasick for the first time in my life like vomming</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0383">yeah vomming</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0328">just slept for seven hours came back</u>
<u n="1559" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1560" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1561" who="S0328">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0383">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0328">ah at least we haven't got to pay again</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0326"><unclear/> all that houses</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0328">what the hell is that?</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0383">ah</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0328">ha ha look at that one <unclear/></u>
<u n="1568" who="S0326">so I'm thinking a roller coaster</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0328">no way yes they are</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0326">well they actually are</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0328">that's the bones of a roller coaster either that or a dinosaur <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1572" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1573" who="S0328">what's the <unclear/> plan? Premier Inn?</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0383"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1575" who="S0328">where are we staying tonight</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0383">Premers Innus</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0328">Premers</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0383">which is better Premier Inn or Holiday Inn?</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0326">Premier Inn man</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0328"><unclear/> Holiday</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0326">Holiday is fancy</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0383">is it?</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0326">it's like its Premier Inn and Travelodge is</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0328">when me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are <unclear/> around we choose the Premier Inn</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0326">the bar wasn't open till five PM</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0383">charge my phone and</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
