<text id="SXCU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:10:03</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0167 S0378</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A pub in London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Work, friends, buying food</topics>
		<activity>Cups of tea in London</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0167">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ashford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East/Kent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Romney Marsh, Kent</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Copywriter</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0378">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Oxford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Streathan, London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Student/ part time survey programmer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0167">thank you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0378">that's okay</u>
<u n="3" who="S0167">you don't <trunc>ha</trunc> you don't have to feel uncomfortable</u>
<u n="4" who="S0378">no I don't it's just your phone</u>
<u n="5" who="S0167" trans="overlap">your the phone is there</u>
<u n="6" who="S0378">it's just a phone</u>
<u n="7" who="S0167">you've also got to do a consent form</u>
<u n="8" who="S0378">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> this is so hilarious</u>
<u n="9" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I was hoping you'd say yes</u>
<u n="10" who="S0378">oh good god <vocal desc="laugh"/> after a year please fill out the form in order to talk to me</u>
<u n="11" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you can only talk to me if you fill out that form</u>
<u n="12" who="S0378">today's date is the twenty-sixth isn't it?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0167">yes</u>
<u n="14" who="S0378">twenty-sixth of the second</u>
<u n="15" who="S0167">yeah so I'm in London a lot this week</u>
<u n="16" who="S0378" trans="overlap">mm are you?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0167">I erm I'm on on Monday and Tuesday as well</u>
<u n="18" who="S0378">are you?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0167">yeah I've got two interviews</u>
<u n="20" who="S0378">ha we'll have to catch up for a cup of tea again then</u>
<u n="21" who="S0167">yeah well I'm in both mornings I've got cos what happened was okay so at the beginning of January I got this email well I I emailed this publishing company and they said come in for an interview we're looking for an intern paid intern</u>
<u n="22" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0167">I went for the interview and they offered me an internship</u>
<u n="24" who="S0378">wait where's this?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0167" trans="overlap">for six weeks this is at <anon type="place"/> like literary agency</u>
<u n="26" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0167">okay so which was really good except they wanted me to start</u>
<u n="28" who="S0378">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0167">it was four days before they told me with four days notice they wanted me to start the day I was going to Germany</u>
<u n="30" who="S0378">oh god</u>
<u n="31" who="S0167">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had already paid for everything and I like obviously had to go I couldn't like turn it down</u>
<u n="32" who="S0378" trans="overlap">yeah was it a gift? the trip?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0167" trans="overlap">well it was <trunc>kin</trunc> well it was kind of just cos I couldn't afford anything so</u>
<u n="34" who="S0378">oh bless him</u>
<u n="35" who="S0167" trans="overlap">he kind of was just like paying for everything</u>
<u n="36" who="S0378">that's nice nice guy</u>
<u n="37" who="S0167" trans="overlap">erm I did pay for a few bits but yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0378" trans="overlap">you've got a nice guy there</u>
<u n="39" who="S0167">I mean he paid for my flights over and most of the hotels we stayed in and</u>
<u n="40" who="S0378">aw bless him</u>
<u n="41" who="S0167" trans="overlap">every now and again I'd give him a few a few euros but</u>
<u n="42" who="S0378">that's sweet he's in my good books</u>
<u n="43" who="S0167">yeah he's a good guy so yeah I phoned up and said can I start two weeks later? erm cos it was a six week internship and I said I can do the last fours week you know obviously won't expect payment in the first two weeks I can even take work with me to Germany to do</u>
<u n="44" who="S0378">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0167">if you need me to do reading or anything and they were like oh we'll have to get back to you and three days later they got back to me and they were like I'm really sorry we erm really kind of need someone</u>
<u n="46" who="S0378">oh no</u>
<u n="47" who="S0167">as soon as and so I had to turn that one down</u>
<u n="48" who="S0378">ah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0167">which was annoying cos that I'd be finishing that tomorrow that would be my last day tomorrow so that would have been really great it was like two hundred and fifty pounds a week</u>
<u n="50" who="S0378">oh that's really nice</u>
<u n="51" who="S0167">I know</u>
<u n="52" who="S0378">was it full time then?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0167">it was only six yeah it was full time for the six weeks I mean it wasn't that great but for an internship it's better than nothing</u>
<u n="54" who="S0378">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="55" who="S0167">anyway so that was turned down I've been looking for jobs and erm I got this email the other day from this woman that said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at <anon type="place"/> this company has just emailed me recommending you and I wondered if you wanted to take up this opportunity that we've got going I'm not still not sure if it's paid or not</u>
<u n="56" who="S0378">someone actually just recommended you and you got a call about it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0167">I got an email</u>
<u n="58" who="S0378" trans="overlap">like that is so awesome</u>
<u n="59" who="S0167">I know I was like I didn't even apply for it this email I was like oh thank you so much for sending my email on and yeah cos she was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought you might like this opportunity thought you might be interested and said you you know he liked your interview and stuff so it's this weird company it's this book publishing company that they do these erm breakfast meetings with authors and stuff that they film and do Q and As and stuff</u>
<u n="60" who="S0378" trans="overlap">oh oh cool</u>
<u n="61" who="S0167">erm and she said do you want to come in on Thursday and meet us and help out with our breakfast meeting erm with Alistair Campbell? and erm I was like sure but then she rang me yesterday and was like actually could you come in on Monday cos we've got Walter Isaacson he's the author of the Steve Jobs biography erm I've never heard of him <unclear>until now</unclear></u>
<u n="62" who="S0378" trans="overlap">oh Steve Jobs as in Apple?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0378">ah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0167">he wrote the biography for him anyway so she was like come and erm you're going to be involved with like the filming of the Q and A and stuff and meeting people at the door and everything</u>
<u n="66" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0167">and erm just see see if you like us and everything and see if you kind of want to carry on helping us so I guess I'll find out on Monday like all the info like what it's about and whether I want to take it or not</u>
<u n="68" who="S0378">it's really that's really quite cool like it might be interesting</u>
<u n="69" who="S0167">yeah could be I just really hope it's paid</u>
<u n="70" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0167">she hasn't mentioned money yet and I didn't want to mention money so <trunc>clo</trunc> so soon</u>
<u n="72" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0167">erm yeah on on Tuesday also I've got an interview like for an internship but it's unpaid but it's expenses paid so it's like I won't be out of pocket but I'm not going to actually gain any money but at least I won't be losing money</u>
<u n="74" who="S0378">you're going to be living at home?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I'll have to live at home yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0167">erm but that's for a digital marketing company</u>
<u n="78" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0167">in in central London and they said it's kind of they really want to employ someone so she said essentially you know it will be kind of like an extended job interview so if I get that that might be good I know I'll do a few weeks of free work but hopefully if it goes well that could end up being something</u>
<u n="80" who="S0378" trans="overlap">oh yeah interesting no you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are actually going for the same kind of jobs now</u>
<u n="81" who="S0167">what's yeah what's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up to?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0378">he well we're not together anymore</u>
<u n="83" who="S0167">I heard about that yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0378" trans="overlap">you know that yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0167">from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0378">we're not together anymore but it's been about four months now</u>
<u n="87" who="S0167">okay</u>
<u n="88" who="S0378">and it's still really really hard</u>
<u n="89" who="S0167">oh no</u>
<u n="90" who="S0378">cos we tried and we tried and we tried</u>
<u n="91" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0378">and then yesterday was like the <trunc>la</trunc> the kind of like this really isn't working so but <trunc>any</trunc> that's another story we'll go in to</u>
<u n="93" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0378">but anyway yeah he he's looking at erm copywriting and marketing</u>
<u n="95" who="S0167">that yeah that's what I did in Peru I was a copywriter</u>
<u n="96" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0378">so he's looking at that he really wants to get into that and he said erm he's going for a job at the moment that's erm <pause dur="short"/> that's to do with advertising Adidas and someone else some other Smirnoff I think it is</u>
<u n="99" who="S0167" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="100" who="S0378">Adidas and Smirnoff for university students</u>
<u n="101" who="S0167">oh okay</u>
<u n="102" who="S0378">so it's particularly for for unis</u>
<u n="103" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0378">which is quite cool</u>
<u n="105" who="S0167">so I guess he's got the experience of being a student <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0378">exactly yeah and he's got a job now as well</u>
<u n="107" who="S0167">what's he doing now?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0378">a full time waiter at a pub but like a gastro pub</u>
<u n="109" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh cool so yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0378" trans="overlap">in <anon type="place"/> do you know where <anon type="place"/> is? it's like the tiniest village outside of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0167">yeah I remember stopping at that sometimes when I was going home</u>
<u n="112" who="S0378" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it's really small who'd have thought he'd end up there?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh my god in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0378">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0167">how did he end up there?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0378">you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friends from home</u>
<u n="117" who="S0167">oh yeah he's living with them?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0378">he's living with them</u>
<u n="119" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0378">so weird so weird</u>
<u n="121" who="S0167">that's hilarious</u>
<u n="122" who="S0378">erm but yeah it sounds like a really cool er</u>
<u n="123" who="S0167">yeah that does sound cool actually</u>
<u n="124" who="S0378">sounds like a really cool kind of area to go into cos it can be really creative can't it?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0167">mm yeah and there's lots of like it's really interesting as well it's not just like you know sitting on a a desk and doing the same old thing every day</u>
<u n="126" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0167">I erm applied for this travel copywriter job like a couple of weeks ago and it sounded so cool it was like erm it's a <trunc>lu</trunc> it was a luxury travel website based in London and they deal with like four and five star hotels and stuff and they you know it's like they wanted a travel copywriter as an intern but possibly to stay on</u>
<u n="128" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0167">and it's a paid internship it's only fourteen K but it's better than nothing</u>
<u n="130" who="S0378">well that's better than nothing like that's quite that's quite good actually I mean for an</u>
<u n="131" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah for an internship apparently that's good</u>
<u n="132" who="S0378">it's a thousand er</u>
<u n="133" who="S0167">it's over a thousand a month</u>
<u n="134" who="S0378">that's actually like a pretty good job well not good</u>
<u n="135" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah and hopefully if it if it leads on to something</u>
<u n="136" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0167">and erm so I was thinking oh yeah I've got loads of travel writing experience and erm copywriting experience so I'll ham that up I was like I've got these blogs and I was in Peru and I was copywriting in Peru and blah blah blah and erm she emailed back and was like erm could you <trunc>li</trunc> I like your CV could you send in erm two hundred and fifty words about this she sent me this hotel erm research this hotel send me two hundred and fifty words about this hotel so we can test your style of writing</u>
<u n="138" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0167">so I sent that in but I I don't know yet that was only sent like two days ago so I really hope I get an interview for that one cos that would be so cool</u>
<u n="140" who="S0378" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0167">if they send me off to like five stars hotels at</u>
<u n="142" who="S0378" trans="overlap">that oh my god do you know what my mum</u>
<u n="143" who="S0167" trans="overlap">in the world across the world</u>
<u n="144" who="S0378">has a friend that does that and she's done it for a long time</u>
<u n="145" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0378">and erm yeah and she goes everywhere like five stars hotels</u>
<u n="147" who="S0167">I'd love that yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0378">like actually really good money too like they live in a beautiful house in London with yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0167">yeah nice</u>
<u n="150" who="S0378">crazy how many years months have you lived there? I've lived there for two years now</u>
<u n="151" who="S0167">so how are your house mates going?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0378">two years</u>
<u n="153" who="S0167">do you live on your own or do you still live with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0378">erm no I live with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0167">yeah I thought you lived with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and how is that going?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0378">good it's really nice really nice you have to see our flat at some point</u>
<u n="157" who="S0167">yeah I'd love to</u>
<u n="158" who="S0378">and come and stay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0167">I'd love to</u>
<u n="160" who="S0378">erm it is</u>
<u n="161" who="S0167">shall we go and order?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0378">yeah let's do that</u>
<u n="163" who="S0167">I'm starving</u>
<u n="164" who="S0378">yeah erm <unclear/> languages other than</u>
<u n="165" who="S0167">are you having any food?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0378">erm yes</u>
<u n="167" who="S0167">well do you want me to order it and I'll instead of taking all our stuff?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0378">erm I have to use my card though cos I don't have cash I'll just I'll erm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0167">what are you ordering?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0378">post graduate er job role position</u>
<u n="171" who="S0167">job role position?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0378">oh oh I don't really have a job at the moment</u>
<u n="173" who="S0167">just say student</u>
<u n="174" who="S0378">student well I guess I do a bit</u>
<u n="175" who="S0167">I keep going to write student on stuff and then I'm like oh I'm not actually a student anymore</u>
<u n="176" who="S0378">oh yeah survey programmer <pause dur="short"/> topic of recording</u>
<u n="177" who="S0167">catch up life</u>
<u n="178" who="S0378">life yeah just life</u>
<u n="179" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> life in general</u>
<u n="180" who="S0378">oh oh my god is there more?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0167">sorry you just have to put your signature on it</u>
<u n="182" who="S0378">okay</u>
<u n="183" who="S0167">you can read it if you want you might be signing your life away</u>
<u n="184" who="S0378"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I trust you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0167">thanks</u>
<u n="186" who="S0378">I can't multitask I'm terrible at <trunc>mu</trunc> trying to talk and also write at the same time</u>
<u n="187" who="S0167">I know I remember that</u>
<u n="188" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0378">is it the twenty-fifth? no it's the twenty-sixth</u>
<u n="190" who="S0167">twenty-sixth</u>
<u n="191" who="S0378">twenty-sixth of the second fifteen contact details <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's not a dot <anon type="email"/> there you go</u>
<u n="192" who="S0167">perfect you're the best this is my part time job this is what I do I talk to people</u>
<u n="193" who="S0378" trans="overlap">this is your part time job I'm going to cover your phone are you going to take it with you?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0167">erm yeah I might do just incase someone has seen the</u>
<u n="195" who="S0378">right</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
