<text id="SXCW">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:51:37</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics></topics>
		<activity>Friends getting ready to go out, chatting</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the key to the cupboard has been returned</u>
<u n="2" who="S0084">oh good <pause dur="short"/> so does that mean that you can um put your boxes away?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> thank fuck</u>
<u n="4" who="S0084">that's very good <pause dur="short"/> and in fact actually cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s coming over maybe we can get him to lift said boxes up the stairs</u>
<u n="5" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0041">fricking awesome</u>
<u n="8" who="S0084">yep <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> he's coming over at some point <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously last time he said he'd come over at seven and he turned up at like half eight <pause dur="short"/> because</u>
<u n="9" who="S0041">that's normal</u>
<u n="10" who="S0084">he decided that was the time to A eat dinner um</u>
<u n="11" who="S0041">huh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0084">when I was cooking dinner</u>
<u n="13" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="14" who="S0084">and B have a really long lengthy conversation with the PPI people <pause dur="short"/> tut <pause dur="short"/> and that's what he was doing <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0041">are you  are you  being serious?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0084">huh?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0041">are you being serious?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0084">that's what he was doing <pause dur="short"/> he was on the phone for forty-five minutes with the PPI people <pause dur="short"/> because they call you don't they <pause dur="short"/> and they say have you been</u>
<u n="19" who="S0041">oh my God</u>
<u n="20" who="S0084">mis-sold PPI?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0041">that's what he was doing?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0084">that's what he was doing</u>
<u n="25" who="S0041">holy fuck</u>
<u n="26" who="S0084">because he's such a retard <pause dur="short"/> he obviously just got like completely forgot he he answered the phone and he was like yeah I have had loans <pause dur="short"/> and then sat back down and was like yeah I've had loads of loans <pause dur="short"/> well actually let me start from the beginning <pause dur="short"/> I've had this loan and this loan  and this loan and this loan  And er he said he just couldn't get rid of them <pause dur="short"/> and I said well obviously because you</u>
<u n="27" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0084">you've let them start <pause dur="short"/> once they start</u>
<u n="29" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0084">well anyway that's what he was doing <pause dur="short"/> so um yeah <unclear/> just a bunch of retards <pause dur="short"/> so this <trunc>w</trunc> this there's this really long lengthy e-mail I've had about one of the projects and then something else started on one of the other projects that isn't even mine and I'm just covering for someone on holiday <pause dur="short"/> um and it's just er like a massive</u>
<u n="31" who="S0041">fuck off</u>
<u n="32" who="S0084">nightmare <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> she's just a retard <pause dur="short"/> she's just everything is really hard in her life <pause dur="short"/> and I can't hold her hand <pause dur="short"/> like we have catch up meetings in production um in my team with the editors every two weeks <pause dur="short"/> to just talk about whatever's going on <pause dur="short"/> budget <pause dur="short"/> schedules <pause dur="short"/> issues with the proofs <pause dur="short"/> whatever <pause dur="short"/> marketing don't come <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> you know it's not really relevant <pause dur="short"/> that's why they have no idea about the schedule <pause dur="short"/> so they have no idea <pause dur="short"/> they have no concept of the priority of your deadlines <pause dur="short"/> they've got they don't care <pause dur="short"/> so you e-mail them and say okay well this is absolutely what I need from you <pause dur="short"/> and I really need it by this date <pause dur="short"/> oh right <pause dur="short"/> and that just goes off</u>
<u n="33" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0084">somewhere <pause dur="short"/> they're just not interested <pause dur="short"/> and they're not made to come to this meeting</u>
<u n="35" who="S0041">who's</u>
<u n="36" who="S0084">whereas if they were</u>
<u n="37" who="S0041">who's supposed to make them?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0084">well interestingly er interestingly enough the head of marketing left in November <pause dur="short"/> what month are we in now? March <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah March <pause dur="short"/> yeah they have no head <pause dur="short"/> um so it's just I mean it was a shambles before <pause dur="short"/> and it's er carrying on being a shambles <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>s</trunc> the director of corporate affairs is supposed to be heading up the section <pause dur="short"/> but he that means he's in charge of like I dunno a hundred people <pause dur="short"/> and he he's off doing his own job <pause dur="short"/> so in theory they report to him <pause dur="short"/> but they don't <pause dur="short"/> and he if even if he tried</u>
<u n="39" who="S0041">and really need</u>
<u n="40" who="S0084">to call a meeting about it they'd be like he's like well we'll just wait for the new person <pause dur="short"/> but there's no sort of er date by which er the new person's gonna be in place</u>
<u n="41" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0084">huh <pause dur="short"/> it's just a fucking joke <pause dur="short"/> absolutely it just makes you so angry <pause dur="short"/> and like the thing is the the <trunc>peop</trunc> er the people that you rile at understand and know</u>
<u n="43" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0084">and they know that it's bad <pause dur="short"/> I think someone's got to take responsibility</u>
<u n="45" who="S0041">they could just employ me <pause dur="short"/> interim period <pause dur="short"/> three months</u>
<u n="46" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0041">bosh bosh <pause dur="short"/> off you go</u>
<u n="48" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="49" who="S0041">that'd be great</u>
<u n="50" who="S0084">well they're supposed to be going through this</u>
<u n="51" who="S0041">they could just pay me for a little while and then</u>
<u n="52" who="S0084">you could be like a consultant <pause dur="short"/> consultancy fee</u>
<u n="53" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna do that actually <trunc>actu</trunc></u>
<u n="54" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0041"><unclear/> finish the last place</u>
<u n="56" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="57" who="S0041"><unclear/> consultancy <pause dur="short"/> but I <trunc>d</trunc> the the clients that I knew that would pay for me automatically</u>
<u n="58" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0041">would basically make me the same wages I could do sat there <pause dur="short"/> so I just thought well</u>
<u n="60" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't wanna do it if they're gonna pay you a hundred pounds a day</u>
<u n="61" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="62" who="S0084">well that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> they've been paying someone a consultancy fee for the last year</u>
<u n="63" who="S0041">huh</u>
<u n="64" who="S0084">in order to introduce new um process review <pause dur="short"/> like a process review and then get everybody doing work in the same way <pause dur="short"/> why they weren't in the first place fine whatever</u>
<u n="65" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0084">they weren't <pause dur="short"/> so it's taken them the best part of two years to do this <pause dur="short"/> ever since I've been there they've been doing it <pause dur="short"/> and er finally finally the role out is next month <pause dur="short"/> but you just think with no head of marketing <pause dur="short"/> with no one to drive it</u>
<u n="67" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0084">they're not gonna do it</u>
<u n="69" who="S0041">doesn't matter</u>
<u n="70" who="S0084">you're still gonna have to hold their hand <pause dur="short"/> you're still gonna have to tell them what you need and when</u>
<u n="71" who="S0041">which</u>
<u n="72" who="S0084">rather than being proactive</u>
<u n="73" who="S0041">is extra work for you</u>
<u n="74" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's <unclear/> completely ridiculous</u>
<u n="75" who="S0041">that's you doing your own job and then making sure somebody else does theirs <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="76" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0041">if they don't do their own job they're fired <pause dur="short"/> end of story</u>
<u n="78" who="S0084">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what er it got escalated to my operations boss <pause dur="short"/> who's sort of my boss while <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s away <pause dur="short"/> um cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said this is fucking ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said you know it's only because we work our arses off to make sure that that covers are actually there in time for the books to be printed <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> it's only by the grace of God the books actually end up with a  with a  cover is <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="79" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0084">certainly not through marketing <pause dur="short"/> and she said actually you kind of want a massive cock-up for them to take er</u>
<u n="81" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0084">responsibility <pause dur="short"/> um er I mean even at Christmas we had a um an instance where all the books were printed you know two thousand copies had been printed with no covers <pause dur="short"/> which meant that they manually then had to <vocal desc="laugh"/> add the covers after <pause dur="short"/> because the covers weren't signed off <pause dur="short"/> it's a fucking nightmare</u>
<u n="83" who="S0041">two thousand books?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0084">two thousand books <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they had to manually do it <pause dur="short"/> which is completely ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> cos er what you should do is then just feed it straight through <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> and that was the marketing team <pause dur="short"/> because they decided to have a massive rebrand of the exams covers last summer</u>
<u n="85" who="S0041">gosh</u>
<u n="86" who="S0084">oh don't get me started <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I'm quite looking forward to a beer <pause dur="short"/> but I thought I'd better have a shower first in case you know drown <pause dur="short"/> oh well also these fucking recordings that I've been doing <pause dur="short"/> I submitted all my invoices and I er would've the eighteen pounds an hour that I get I'd calculated that for the number of hours I'd recorded I would've got paid three hundred and fifty-five pounds</u>
<u n="87" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="88" who="S0084">but in my head I forgot that they would tax me on that <pause dur="short"/> but I thought I would get paid at the end of the month <pause dur="short"/> because that's when invoices get paid <pause dur="short"/> like our back salary comes out on the eighteenth <pause dur="short"/> so today there was an extra hundred and fifty pounds in my bank in my salary <pause dur="short"/> cos I get paid today <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh is that must  that must  be the recordings but it's two hundred quid shy</u>
<u n="89" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0084">and then I thought well er well they'll have taxed me</u>
<u n="91" who="S0041">not two hundred quid though</u>
<u n="92" who="S0084">but shit yeah <pause dur="short"/> so but the but one of the invoices was missing <pause dur="short"/> so in the end it was actually two hundred and fifty pounds but <trunc>bec</trunc> but with tax it was only a hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="93" who="S0041">benefits</u>
<u n="94" who="S0084">huh fuck me</u>
<u n="95" who="S0041">it's <trunc>ab</trunc> that is just disgusting isn't it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0084">A hundred pounds  hundred pounds</u>
<u n="97" who="S0041">that can't be right</u>
<u n="98" who="S0084">well er</u>
<u n="99" who="S0041">that can't be right</u>
<u n="100" who="S0084">I've chased it up with our payroll and I've said have you charged me at forty percent rather than twenty percent? Um and they said yeah we've charged you at twenty percent <pause dur="short"/> and it'll be your national insurance which is twelve percent and your student loan which is nine percent</u>
<u n="101" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="102" who="S0084">so it comes out at forty percent <pause dur="short"/> so it's a fucking joke <pause dur="short"/> forty percent? Er you <trunc>ju</trunc> you might as well just die</u>
<u n="103" who="S0041">oh my God</u>
<u n="104" who="S0084">I mean what the hell? So that really fucked me off</u>
<u n="105" who="S0041">that's horrendous</u>
<u n="106" who="S0084">Cos er I mean I you know I'm not really relying on it but it would've been really good</u>
<u n="107" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0084">Cos I need to get out of my overdraft this year <pause dur="short"/> that was the plan <pause dur="short"/> tut fine <pause dur="short"/> it just pisses me off</u>
<u n="109" who="S0041">that is such a pisser <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go to work tomorrow and ring the tax office about my tax code</u>
<u n="110" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0041">huh <pause dur="short"/> I'm just grateful that it's now the end of the tax year so I can rebate this past year <pause dur="short"/> cos they owe me at least three hundred</u>
<u n="112" who="S0084">do they?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0041">from this year alone <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> er yeah you've gotta keep an eye on them because er <trunc>w</trunc> last year when I got a tax rebate from when I worked I think it was from when I worked at Waterstones they massively taxed me and um cos I worked at Waterstones at the same time as I went back for Christmas so it was like a second job</u>
<u n="115" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0084">um and I got a rebate <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't get my rebate until November <pause dur="short"/> it took them from May to November <pause dur="short"/> so what is that? Five months <pause dur="short"/> six months</u>
<u n="117" who="S0041">God</u>
<u n="118" who="S0084">to pull their finger out</u>
<u n="119" who="S0041">it's such a piss-take</u>
<u n="120" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="121" who="S0041">actual piss-take</u>
<u n="122" who="S0084">you know <pause dur="short"/> unless you actually write the letters and chase them which is what I did when I was at uni cos you need the money more when you're at uni you know <pause dur="short"/> at least when I was earning I had money coming in <pause dur="short"/> but you rely on them that's the thing</u>
<u n="123" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="124" who="S0084">they're the tax office</u>
<u n="125" who="S0041">so I've got them to contact <pause dur="short"/> I've got my bank to contact <pause dur="short"/> cos they've charged me a hundred and fifty quid for something</u>
<u n="126" who="S0084">huh</u>
<u n="127" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0041">something's happened <pause dur="short"/> right basically I've got two accounts</u>
<u n="130" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0041">which are both at their overdraft limit <pause dur="short"/> as usual</u>
<u n="132" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0041">since I've taken this job <pause dur="short"/> one of them tax free student sixteen hundred quid bosh</u>
<u n="134" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0041">it's two hundred I paid two hundred and fifty off it so they don't really give a crap until this next September or something</u>
<u n="136" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0041">fine <pause dur="short"/> good for me <pause dur="short"/> the other one is five hundred interest overdraft <pause dur="short"/> so I pay about depending on how much I'm in the overdraft by which is usually the whole fricking lot I pay about a tenner a month</u>
<u n="138" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0041">interest on it <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> and when the <trunc>s</trunc> that stupid Swinton thing was coming out of my</u>
<u n="140" who="S0084">tut</u>
<u n="141" who="S0041">account</u>
<u n="142" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0041">and we didn't know what it was <pause dur="short"/> I'd gone over my overdraft limit and they charged me blahdy blah blah <pause dur="short"/> anyway these charges have just racked up <pause dur="short"/> and I went in and they said oh well for every day you're over your overdraft limit we charge you twelve pounds or something</u>
<u n="144" who="S0084">per day?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0041">per day right <pause dur="short"/> and at the time I was in such a fluster I didn't listen <pause dur="short"/> and I just said what? No way <pause dur="short"/> and then I thought about it <pause dur="short"/> I thought that's a lie <pause dur="short"/> I've had that overdraft at that overdraft limit since I was eighteen years old <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> it has been there for a hell of a long time</u>
<u n="146" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0041">and never once have I been charged per day like that <pause dur="short"/> never <pause dur="short"/> I've had</u>
<u n="148" who="S0084">they can change the terms though <pause dur="short"/> have you had any letters?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="150" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="151" who="S0041">I haven't had anything <pause dur="short"/> so I think they've changed the terms of my overdraft</u>
<u n="152" who="S0084">and not told you</u>
<u n="153" who="S0041">and not told me</u>
<u n="154" who="S0084">Cos they just basically write to me and tell me they'd <trunc>s</trunc> they'd changed the terms <pause dur="short"/> but there's fuck all you can do about it because you need your overdraft <pause dur="short"/> so if er cos if if you're fifteen hundred pounds into your overdraft which thankfully I'm not anymore and then they say right well actually the interest free bit's over now <pause dur="short"/> bye bye <pause dur="short"/> we're gonna start charging you at nineteen percent <pause dur="short"/> you're fucked <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing you can do</u>
<u n="155" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what happened to me <pause dur="short"/> and then you've gotta get out as soon as as er humanly possible you've gotta clear your overdraft <pause dur="short"/> because that's what they do <pause dur="short"/> they lower your er graduate account or your student account the interest free amount</u>
<u n="157" who="S0041">and then flip it</u>
<u n="158" who="S0084">and then flip it</u>
<u n="159" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0084">over to interest <pause dur="short"/> er which is what I was expecting to be doing them to do at five hundred pound intervals</u>
<u n="161" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0084">and then one day they just wrote to me and said right you've got</u>
<u n="163" who="S0041">and said no</u>
<u n="164" who="S0084">no you've gotta pay</u>
<u n="165" who="S0041">oh shit <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> if they do that I'm fucked</u>
<u n="166" who="S0084">and they charge you twenty-five pounds arrangement fee</u>
<u n="167" who="S0041">for doing it?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> for doing nothing <pause dur="short"/> press er pushing in a button on the computer</u>
<u n="169" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> absolute bullshit <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna write them a letter <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna say to them cos the thing is as well it's really irresponsible lending if that's what they're</u>
<u n="170" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0041">saying they're gonna do <pause dur="short"/> they can see my salary</u>
<u n="172" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0041">they can see my outgoings <pause dur="short"/> everything I have goes through their bank only</u>
<u n="174" who="S0084">they've got no morals mate</u>
<u n="175" who="S0041">they know</u>
<u n="176" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0041">that there is no way on God's earth that I can afford to pay out a hundred and fifty quid</u>
<u n="178" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0041">plus the whatever er whatever they're gonna whack on this month</u>
<u n="180" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0041">another a hundred and fifty quid</u>
<u n="182" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> who do you bank with?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0041">Natwest</u>
<u n="184" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they don't give a shit</u>
<u n="185" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="186" who="S0084">my mum left HSBC for that exact same reason <pause dur="short"/> because obviously she's you know she doesn't have much money <pause dur="short"/> because they kept charging her <pause dur="short"/> she would go over her overdraft because</u>
<u n="187" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0084">she didn't have any money coming in and er they were just like oh yeah well that's the terms of the agreement <pause dur="short"/> sorry love <pause dur="short"/> on your bike <pause dur="short"/> so she's now with the Co-op <pause dur="short"/> who don't charge</u>
<u n="189" who="S0041">it's just bullshit</u>
<u n="190" who="S0084">well er it used to be that you could claim back your bank charges because they were illegal <pause dur="short"/> they weren't</u>
<u n="191" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0084">in your contract <pause dur="short"/> and then they passed a judgement</u>
<u n="193" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="194" who="S0084">that says you can't</u>
<u n="195" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="196" who="S0084">but</u>
<u n="197" who="S0041">Cos they owed me about three grand and I never got it back</u>
<u n="198" who="S0084">I know <pause dur="short"/> my ex-boyfriend managed to get in there just at the last minute <pause dur="short"/> but I was looking at this on the Money Saving Expert <pause dur="short"/> because I you know I've <trunc>g</trunc> everyone's got bank charges <pause dur="short"/> I've got bank charges that I'd like to claim <pause dur="short"/> and it said on occasion you can send your claim to the ombudsman <pause dur="short"/> and they look at it all <pause dur="short"/> so if you <trunc>s</trunc> were to say you know I've <trunc>d</trunc> I'm in a very fragile delicate position <pause dur="short"/> because they're more likely to look at the ones for people who can't afford to pay these charges <pause dur="short"/> which you can't <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="199" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no way</u>
<u n="200" who="S0084">you're on a very basic salary <pause dur="short"/> they would be more inclined to look at you because you know you're living hand to mouth <pause dur="short"/> you're living at the</u>
<u n="201" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0084">end of your overdraft <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="203" who="S0041">I'm just gonna write her a letter</u>
<u n="204" who="S0084"><unclear/> compared to your salary</u>
<u n="205" who="S0041">and just see see what response I get back <pause dur="short"/> cos at least if I put it in writing</u>
<u n="206" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0041">if it ever comes back on me I can say look I I tried to do the responsible thing and sort this out</u>
<u n="208" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0041">Cos I don't know what the hell you did but you knowing</u>
<u n="210" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0041">it's so frustrating</u>
<u n="212" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0041">that they they've done it knowing there's no chance of me paying it back</u>
<u n="214" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="215" who="S0041">what the fuck? You can't drop someone in the shit like that</u>
<u n="216" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0041">after</u>
<u n="218" who="S0084">well they will just take the money</u>
<u n="219" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0084">that's the thing</u>
<u n="221" who="S0041">they just take it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0084">they'll just keep taking it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0041">and the worst part is I think</u>
<u n="224" who="S0084">you'll get more and more in debt</u>
<u n="225" who="S0041">how it actually happened in the first place was that they tried to cash a cheque right</u>
<u n="226" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0041">which bounced</u>
<u n="228" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0041">legally they're not allowed to reclaim for that cheque because they are aware then <pause dur="short"/> they have the knowledge that you don't have the funds</u>
<u n="230" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="231" who="S0041">and they did it twice again</u>
<u n="232" who="S0084">did they?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0041">I think that's where</u>
<u n="234" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="235" who="S0041">all this started spiralling from <pause dur="short"/> so I I to be honest I don't really understand it <pause dur="short"/> so I'm just gonna write and say look I don't understand how this has happened <pause dur="short"/> I have come in and spoke to you about this before <pause dur="short"/> you can see I paid in a cheque of two hundred pounds two months ago to hopefully clear this <pause dur="short"/> and it hasn't <pause dur="short"/> it's just been eaten by more charges and I'm in the same position again <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand it <pause dur="short"/> can I have a meeting with you please and go through this account cos it's just gonna get out of control</u>
<u n="236" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think that's all you can do really <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> I mean I would look at the Money Saving Expert website because they A they give you the templates for the letters to write to the banks but and they also give you the wording</u>
<u n="237" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0084">so they say you know maybe maybe you would want to write a an initial letter and then write them again and say well actually it's good isn't it <pause dur="short"/> it's my mum and she'll only complain because of my phone <pause dur="short"/> so you can see that my phone is still here <pause dur="short"/> it's not with Vodafone</u>
<u n="239" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Why is that?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0084">it's not been  it's not been  picked up</u>
<u n="241" who="S0041">oh good</u>
<u n="242" who="S0084">so today was <trunc>b</trunc> was about the fifth time that I've spoken to Vodafone <pause dur="short"/> um and er a really nice guy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> um <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't very helpful</u>
<u n="243" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a bit dim?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0041">I've had one of them today</u>
<u n="246" who="S0084">bit spec <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but has assured me that there will be someone to collect my phone even though they've assured me about five times</u>
<u n="247" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="248" who="S0084">and it turns out <vocal desc="laugh"/> it turns out that er the day that they were supposed to collect the phone this week Wednesday that didn't happen <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> on no Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> tuesday was the day <pause dur="short"/> I called them Monday <pause dur="short"/> tuesday they were supposed to collect the phone <pause dur="short"/> tuesday they didnt collect the phone <pause dur="short"/> wednesday I went in <pause dur="short"/> took my phone back from the post room took it up to my desk <pause dur="short"/> called Vodafone and said you haven't come to collect it <pause dur="short"/> oh okay sorry <pause dur="short"/> we'll er send it to us <pause dur="short"/> I said I don't wanna do that <pause dur="short"/> okay well we'll send you a pouch for you to send it back <pause dur="short"/> said pouch has never arrived <pause dur="short"/> the next day the courier arrives to pick up my phone two days later <pause dur="short"/> my phone's not there because I don't <trunc>im</trunc> imagine that it's supposed to be coming because it didn't come on the day it was supposed to come <pause dur="short"/> it comes at five o'clock when I've left <pause dur="short"/> man I was so</u>
<u n="249" who="S0041">oh fuck</u>
<u n="250" who="S0084">so fucked off</u>
<u n="251" who="S0041">uh</u>
<u n="252" who="S0084">so now</u>
<u n="253" who="S0041">these people need smashing in the face</u>
<u n="254" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they don't  they don't  care</u>
<u n="255" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="256" who="S0084">they really don't care <pause dur="short"/> so when I come called on the Wednesday and they said put it in the pouch I said can I speak to a manager? I'm really sorry there's no one here to speak to <pause dur="short"/> funny that</u>
<u n="257" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0084">yeah right <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>w</trunc> but we'll escalate your call and someone will call you back <pause dur="short"/> obviously no one's called</u>
<u n="259" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0084">so young <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who I spoke to today he said oh no there's never anyone here to speak to <pause dur="short"/> so whatever that guy told me the other day was absolute bollocks <pause dur="short"/> you have to go on the website and fill it in in an e-mail <pause dur="short"/> and I said is this one of the ones that goes into the ether and no one ever replies? Because you can fuck off <pause dur="short"/> I'm not filling that in <pause dur="short"/> and he said no you know I've I've filled it in <pause dur="short"/> and said what? You work for Vodafone</u>
<u n="261" who="S0041">huh</u>
<u n="262" who="S0084">Don't give me that shit</u>
<u n="263" who="S0041">oh they anger me</u>
<u n="264" who="S0084">you just  you just you just  know they're lying to you</u>
<u n="265" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="266" who="S0084">constantly <pause dur="short"/> and I think I've been with you for seven years <pause dur="short"/> and this is  this is  the best kind of service you can offer me is it?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0084">so and of course they don't collect on the weekends cos that'd be you know</u>
<u n="269" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="270" who="S0084">helpful customer service</u>
<u n="271" who="S0041">Cos everybody else is off work <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so the day that I would be at home</u>
<u n="273" who="S0041">and the majority of the population</u>
<u n="274" who="S0084">to give you my phone <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0041">Will be off home ready to give phones when</u>
<u n="276" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0041">when required <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="278" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0084">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> um so the well who knows if they're coming on Monday <pause dur="short"/> who can say? They're supposed to be coming on Monday to collect my phone <pause dur="short"/> and then I dunno  I dunno  what's gonna happen <pause dur="short"/> obviously when I went into the shop and said there's a massive echo and he said oh that's standard</u>
<u n="281" who="S0041">no it's not</u>
<u n="282" who="S0084">it's probably not standard if you can't hear me <pause dur="short"/> and all you can hear is your own voice</u>
<u n="283" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> that's not standard</u>
<u n="284" who="S0084">that's probably not standard is it you fucking retard</u>
<u n="285" who="S0041">twat</u>
<u n="286" who="S0084">oh huh</u>
<u n="287" who="S0041">I spoke to my <trunc>sc</trunc> high school today</u>
<u n="288" who="S0084">your high school? About getting your certificates?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>r</trunc> bearing in mind I have called them <trunc>twi</trunc> on two different occasions before and they've told me they don't have access to mine cos they were too long ago <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="290" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="291" who="S0041">I then called actually with the intention to ask them <trunc>w</trunc> who which board I would then contact <pause dur="short"/> because they must report my results to someone</u>
<u n="292" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0041">at the authorities for when they <trunc>r</trunc> release the league tables every year</u>
<u n="294" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0041">er to oh we do have your A-level results <pause dur="short"/> are you fucking joking me mate?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0041">no way</u>
<u n="298" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="300" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh</u>
<u n="301" who="S0041">yes we do have them <pause dur="short"/> so then I said right fucking fantastic <pause dur="short"/> do you wanna get those over to me? They need to be with a letter <pause dur="short"/> headed paper <pause dur="short"/> signed by <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> get it in the post</u>
<u n="302" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> this girl was so painfully stupid</u>
<u n="304" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0041">painfully dim</u>
<u n="306" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0041">it was awful <pause dur="short"/> she sounded like the gaunt one</u>
<u n="308" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="309" who="S0041">huh</u>
<u n="310" who="S0084">really slow</u>
<u n="311" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my <trunc>Go</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she kept slurp slurp</u>
<u n="312" who="S0084">huh</u>
<u n="313" who="S0041">er I think she was wearing a brace or what <pause dur="short"/> and she kept saying things like er she kept repeating I'm sure you can appreciate that a million times <pause dur="short"/> she obviously had no intellect whatsoever <pause dur="short"/> and it wasn't even as if she was the receptionist</u>
<u n="314" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> she was the examinations officer</u>
<u n="316" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So she's supposed to have you know like qualifications <pause dur="short"/> a brain</u>
<u n="317" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0084">et cetera</u>
<u n="319" who="S0041">so she first she told me that that would be they've got other priorities basically than to write me a letter</u>
<u n="320" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0041">Cos of their own students now that are doing stuff <pause dur="short"/> and I was like look I will write you a letter if you want</u>
<u n="322" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0041">I will write the letter for you</u>
<u n="324" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0041">just print it on headed paper <pause dur="short"/> get it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> get her to sign it <pause dur="short"/> send it off</u>
<u n="326" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0041">I'll just check with a colleague <pause dur="short"/> everything I said to her <pause dur="short"/> every sentence <pause dur="short"/> I'll just check with a colleague <pause dur="short"/> putting me on hold <pause dur="short"/> I was on the phone to her for forty-five minutes</u>
<u n="328" who="S0084">huh <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="329" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> and then she suggested at this point</u>
<u n="330" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0041">that I should er the only way I could get <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> to sign it head teacher er because obviously she's so busy saving the world that er I could</u>
<u n="332" who="S0084">oh this isn't your mum? This is</u>
<u n="333" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="334" who="S0084">another <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? Oh right</u>
<u n="335" who="S0041">this is another <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> head teacher <pause dur="short"/> she's a douche as well</u>
<u n="336" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0041">I remember her <pause dur="short"/> she was um there the year before I left <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> that I have to go and make an appointment with the head teacher and go in and see her with the letter and get her to sign it</u>
<u n="338" who="S0084">but you live here</u>
<u n="339" who="S0041">but I live here</u>
<u n="340" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0041">but that's okay</u>
<u n="342" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0041">what? I said do you want me to drive four hours across the country</u>
<u n="344" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0041">so because you can't walk down the corridor?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0084">that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="347" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I said no way <pause dur="short"/> I said if you wanna go down this route put me through to her now</u>
<u n="348" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0041">and let let her explain to me why that's the case</u>
<u n="350" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0041">Cos that's absolute bullshit</u>
<u n="352" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0041">I said look can we have this conversation by e-mail? Because then at least I've got it in paper what you've said <pause dur="short"/> I can prove that I've requested it</u>
<u n="354" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0041">and then if all else fails at life at your end</u>
<u n="356" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0041">then <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can prove to the navy that this is what I've done</u>
<u n="358" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0041">she said yeah that's fine <pause dur="short"/> I said so what about my GCSEs then? She said um tut well we do have them <pause dur="short"/> what are you saying?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0041">we do have them?</u>
<u n="362" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0041">you've told me you don't have them</u>
<u n="364" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0041">then she said</u>
<u n="366" who="S0084">do you think she's the same person you've been talking to? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0041">I know it is  I know it is</u>
<u n="368" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0041">that's the worst part <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0084">was it someone else? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0041">I recognize the voice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0084">it's always her?</u>
<u n="373" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0041">and she said but they're in an archive <pause dur="short"/> and I have said to her before shouldn't you have them paper copies</u>
<u n="375" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0041">in an archive <pause dur="short"/> oh no</u>
<u n="377" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0041">paper archive <pause dur="short"/> but you can I'm <vocal desc="laugh"/> sure you can appreciate</u>
<u n="379" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0041">I'm sure you can imagine</u>
<u n="381" who="S0084">of course</u>
<u n="382" who="S0041">um that there are <vocal desc="laugh"/> really a lot of them</u>
<u n="383" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="385" who="S0084">but surely it's in some sort of order?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0084">I mean they're not just <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0041">I don't think so</u>
<u n="389" who="S0084">scattered around <pause dur="short"/> they're not just in some sort of fort</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And then I said</u>
<u n="391" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">okay so don't worry <pause dur="short"/> I tell you what <pause dur="short"/> we'll get the A-level ones on their way</u>
<u n="393" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0041">in the letter write thank you for requesting your GCSE results <pause dur="short"/> due to the <trunc>f</trunc> archiving</u>
<u n="395" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="396" who="S0041">bluh bluh bluh</u>
<u n="397" who="S0084">being shit <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0041">we'll give you</u>
<u n="399" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0041">due to us not actually having an archive <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And piling all the shit in one room and slamming the door</u>
<u n="401" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0084">it's in a shed</u>
<u n="403" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0041">in an old coal-mine in Yorkshire</u>
<u n="405" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0041">then</u>
<u n="407" who="S0084">oh man <pause dur="short"/> I mean don't joke</u>
<u n="408" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0041">give me a <trunc>ti</trunc> we can estimate a timescale of two to six weeks slash four to six weeks for this information <pause dur="short"/> she said oh let me just see <vocal desc="laugh"/> if I can do that</u>
<u n="410" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0041">I though oh my God <pause dur="short"/> if she gets me on</u>
<u n="412" who="S0084">your life is</u>
<u n="413" who="S0041">hold she's <vocal desc="laugh"/> gonna disappear</u>
<u n="414" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0041">forever <pause dur="short"/> um she well</u>
<u n="416" who="S0084">and by the time the next you speak to her she'll</u>
<u n="417" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0084">be like no we haven't got your results</u>
<u n="419" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0041">and so I made her <vocal desc="laugh"/> put it all in writing</u>
<u n="421" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="422" who="S0041">and then she told me huh <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then she told me I said how long will it take you to get them out of the archive? Well probably a couple of months <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0084">where is the archives?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was like what? You have an on-site archive <pause dur="short"/> and it will take you two months to send me a fax? And she said yeah yeah I mean it's  it's rather it's  rather big <pause dur="short"/> not extensive <pause dur="short"/> big <pause dur="short"/> it's rather big</u>
<u n="425" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0041">I said oh</u>
<u n="427" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0041">I said it must be pretty massive</u>
<u n="429" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0084">it's gonna take you two months to trek through it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and she said you know I'm sure you can appreciate again this is not our top priority <pause dur="short"/> we've got students here at the moment that we're trying to get through their exams <pause dur="short"/> and I said I'm sure that's great <pause dur="short"/> I said but whatever comes happens hell or high water all your students will sit their exams <pause dur="short"/> if you don't actually walk down to the archive and get me that piece</u>
<u n="433" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0041">of paper I will be in this position chasing things in January <pause dur="short"/> I have an official application going through and I'm requesting information <pause dur="short"/> it's not a choice</u>
<u n="435" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0041">you don't have a choice whether or not to provide me with that</u>
<u n="437" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0041">if you don't give it to me as I request it the Royal Navy will request it from you officially</u>
<u n="439" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0041">and then you'll be obliged to do it <pause dur="short"/> so I'm basically giving you a head's up</u>
<u n="441" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="442" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> well I'll see what we can do <pause dur="short"/> she just wasn't getting it <pause dur="short"/> it's as if she it wasn't her job to do it <pause dur="short"/> as if she wasn't the person</u>
<u n="443" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0041">got it in writing now <pause dur="short"/> I don't hold out much hope</u>
<u n="445" who="S0084">well at least you've got it in writing <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="446" who="S0041">I actually debated driving up there</u>
<u n="447" who="S0084">tut</u>
<u n="448" who="S0041">er that's how much easier</u>
<u n="449" who="S0084">well</u>
<u n="450" who="S0041">it would be</u>
<u n="451" who="S0084">it would be easier <pause dur="short"/> but I mean you might get there and them go oh well you can't have access to the archive <pause dur="short"/> oh and then that would be worse because you'd probably punch her in the face</u>
<u n="452" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought also about</u>
<u n="453" who="S0084">how frustrating</u>
<u n="454" who="S0041">writing <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> a letter saying</u>
<u n="455" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0041">I thought I'll keep the  I'll print the  and just say look I don't know what type of staff you're employing but there's <trunc>cl</trunc> clearly a bit of a communication problem here</u>
<u n="457" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0041">if I have to drive to Sheffield</u>
<u n="459" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0041">to collect it I will be claiming back my mileage</u>
<u n="461" who="S0084">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> I mean ultimately they have a <trunc>resp</trunc> um a duty of care</u>
<u n="462" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0084">you were a student once</u>
<u n="464" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0084">do you know what I mean? It's not like you you you exit out the door</u>
<u n="466" who="S0041">it's not a big school Liz</u>
<u n="467" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0041">it's not a big school <pause dur="short"/> it's not like a city school with thousands of students</u>
<u n="469" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0041">in the entire school there's two thousand students <pause dur="short"/> four hundred of those are sixth formers</u>
<u n="471" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="472" who="S0041">so it's not</u>
<u n="473" who="S0084">no it's tiny</u>
<u n="474" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0084">I can't believe they need your certificates from school when you've got a degree</u>
<u n="476" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="477" who="S0084">that's mental</u>
<u n="478" who="S0041">but they've said you know if we don't have the certificates this is the next best thing <pause dur="short"/> a letter from your school <pause dur="short"/> you'd think thanks for that bit of leeway</u>
<u n="479" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0041">come on school <pause dur="short"/> buck it up</u>
<u n="481" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="483" who="S0084">I mean I'm really ridiculous with things like that <pause dur="short"/> so I've kept all mine <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="484" who="S0041">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might have them</u>
<u n="485" who="S0084">but no we don't wanna go down that road</u>
<u n="486" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="487" who="S0084">I mean you're better off you know you'd prefer to be on the phone to some retard than having to actually you know strike up communication with your mum</u>
<u n="488" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that was</u>
<u n="489" who="S0084">well worst case scenario then that's a trip to er the North</u>
<u n="490" who="S0041">so worst case scenario gonna go</u>
<u n="491" who="S0084">where's your school? Wrexham?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0041"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0084"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> near Sheffield <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="495" who="S0084">uh</u>
<u n="496" who="S0041">also in <trunc>ad</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> in addition I rung the navy people</u>
<u n="497" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="498" who="S0041">and said look I don't know I'm I'm stuck now <pause dur="short"/> and I need to choose which job I wanna do</u>
<u n="499" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="500" who="S0041">I can't decide now</u>
<u n="501" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0041">it's problematic <pause dur="short"/> and he was like right okay <pause dur="short"/> I said so I'm gonna come in and see you <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing on Friday? Cos I've got the day off <pause dur="short"/> and he said right let me just get your paperwork <pause dur="short"/> did you pass your recruit test? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> what did you get? And I thought I can't tell you cos I'm not supposed to know <pause dur="short"/> I know I passed it</u>
<u n="503" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="504" who="S0041">okay <pause dur="short"/> so he checks that I'm can do both jobs <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> lovely <pause dur="short"/> gotta go in and see him on Friday</u>
<u n="505" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="506" who="S0041">and he was like I said I'm gonna need quite a bit of time <pause dur="short"/> I have a lot of questions <pause dur="short"/> all the questions</u>
<u n="507" who="S0084">all of those questions</u>
<u n="508" who="S0041">um and he said okay <pause dur="short"/> well don't worry <pause dur="short"/> um have you had a look on the website? Done it <pause dur="short"/> and every other website in the world <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> and he was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> right er</u>
<u n="509" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0041">I said um I'll bring biscuits <pause dur="short"/> he was like okay <pause dur="short"/> can I have Hobnobs? And I said yes that's fine <pause dur="short"/> he said right it's a date I'll see you at one on Friday</u>
<u n="511" who="S0084">oh nice</u>
<u n="512" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0084">oh that sounds good</u>
<u n="514" who="S0041">so</u>
<u n="515" who="S0084">that'll just you know give you the opportunity to just ask every question you've ever heard of <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="516" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="517" who="S0084">and get it clear in your mind</u>
<u n="518" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0084">that's interesting though that you've had a bit of a one eighty <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't  I don't  know <pause dur="short"/> I I huh</u>
<u n="521" who="S0084">is it purely financial then? Or do you just think you'll have more fun? Or?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0041">I I think I would have more fun</u>
<u n="523" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0041">which is what I'd I'm thinking this is gonna be my whole life</u>
<u n="525" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and and it's short term as well <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="526" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0084">so it's only <trunc>gon</trunc> if you are only gonna sign up for four years</u>
<u n="528" who="S0041">you want to make the most of that</u>
<u n="529" who="S0084"><trunc>w</trunc> you wanna have the best time</u>
<u n="530" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0084">you know it's not er you don't  you don't  I suppose you don't know but you don't know whether it's gonna be fifteen years <pause dur="short"/> you know if it's fifteen years you might wanna go in as an officer and really you know work your arse off and</u>
<u n="532" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0084">make it your career <pause dur="short"/> but if you're only gonna do it for four years</u>
<u n="534" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or even</u>
<u n="535" who="S0084">might as well</u>
<u n="536" who="S0041">six years</u>
<u n="537" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0041">but I thought you know you don't go to work do your job and come home</u>
<u n="539" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0041">you don't</u>
<u n="541" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="542" who="S0041">your home life is with the people that you work with all the time</u>
<u n="543" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0041">and if you don't like the people you work with cos er per vessel per ship there's only eighteen officers out of the two hundred people on that ship</u>
<u n="545" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="548" who="S0041">there's a real big difference <pause dur="short"/> and so I thought I know it sounds awful but I thought huh if they're all kiss arses</u>
<u n="549" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0041">and not fun at all and I'm stuck with two people that I would actually be friends with</u>
<u n="551" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0041">that's really not gonna be a nice lifestyle for months and months  and months  at a time</u>
<u n="553" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0041">so that's that's my only thing <pause dur="short"/> my think my thought process <pause dur="short"/> because really graduate-wise the majority of them are boring fuckers</u>
<u n="555" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0041">like people that are gonna go in there <trunc>en</trunc> doing engineering</u>
<u n="557" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0041">and <trunc>s</trunc> satellite navigation stuff</u>
<u n="559" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">at officer level are gonna be pretty clued up</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0041">I can't imagine there being a lot of fun</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041">I can't  I can't  see it <pause dur="short"/> so I just I <trunc>c</trunc> I think intellectually I'd be much happier doing the officer job</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041">but I'd be willing to sacrifice that if I would enjoy my time there</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084"><vocal desc="cough"/> Well absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's what life's about isn't it <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta really enjoy it</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084">ultimately <pause dur="short"/> but um what was I gonna say? Like what would your responsibilities be if you were just ratings? Like what would you be doing? What would your job be?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0041">that's what I wanna know</u>
<u n="571" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="572" who="S0041">Cos I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> er because Michael can't I had him on the phone last night for two and a half hours</u>
<u n="573" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="574" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> two and a half hours <pause dur="short"/> I mean a lot of it was not navy-related</u>
<u n="575" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="576" who="S0041">but he's like I can't really describe it to you cos you do so many different things all the time</u>
<u n="577" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="578" who="S0041">if you were as a rating</u>
<u n="579" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0041">then it's really changed <pause dur="short"/> so you'd be he said I don't <trunc>kn</trunc> I can't tell you <pause dur="short"/> er he was like</u>
<u n="581" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0041">if I was gonna choose that's what I'd do</u>
<u n="583" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0041">Cos he's a communications specialist <pause dur="short"/> which is like one below</u>
<u n="585" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="586" who="S0041">so the progression path for both is different</u>
<u n="587" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="588" who="S0041">I don't think I don't know if er he obviously can't cross over <pause dur="short"/> or if he can he can't do it or something <pause dur="short"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="589" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="590" who="S0041">but an officer he said basically he spends quite a lot of time pretty standard <pause dur="short"/> I said what do you mean? He said you well like you know in front of a computer <pause dur="short"/> making decisions <pause dur="short"/> going to meetings <pause dur="short"/> doing the paperwork <pause dur="short"/> writing reports for the ratings <pause dur="short"/> so it sounds very much like a manager job anywhere</u>
<u n="591" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="592" who="S0041">with more fun thrown in <pause dur="short"/> he said the only thing I can see you getting fucked off with is that because you're at the same level for so long a lot of your time will be training for you as well</u>
<u n="593" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">and they just <trunc>p</trunc> they spend a lot  a lot  of time planning <pause dur="short"/> and I am a planner <pause dur="short"/> I do it now <pause dur="short"/> it fucks me off though  fucks me off</u>
<u n="595" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">and they er they plan for stuff and it's not even real stuff <pause dur="short"/> it's test stuff</u>
<u n="597" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">so you might spend he said you might spend three or four weeks planning</u>
<u n="599" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="600" who="S0041">for a fake attack that never</u>
<u n="601" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0041">is never gonna actually happen</u>
<u n="603" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> seems a bit redundant doesn't it</u>
<u n="604" who="S0041">yeah it does</u>
<u n="605" who="S0084">but then I suppose that's that's the nature of the beast isn't it <pause dur="short"/> they rely on people like you <pause dur="short"/> like you could spin it on its head <pause dur="short"/> yeah the your test doesn't come up but it means that you're prepared because it could and in fact in real life it could <pause dur="short"/> so it's better</u>
<u n="606" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0084">to be prepared <pause dur="short"/> and at least you know <pause dur="short"/> cos you er ultimately you don't wanna be in a position where you sort of let your guard down <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? Like you're really responsible</u>
<u n="608" who="S0041">that's it</u>
<u n="609" who="S0084">you're responsible for people's safety <pause dur="short"/> for their lives</u>
<u n="610" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0084">and and if that means that you know you're preparing for something that never actually happens in reality it could happen</u>
<u n="612" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0084">and you wanna make sure that you're prepared for it</u>
<u n="614" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0084">so it's what it's how you get satisfaction from your job I suppose</u>
<u n="616" who="S0041">that's what I'm thinking <pause dur="short"/> and am I really gonna get satisfaction out of doing that?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0041">I don't know</u>
<u n="619" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0041">until I actually know what they do from day to day <pause dur="short"/> I want somebody to say if I was to plan you an average week in this job this is what you can expect to do</u>
<u n="621" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="622" who="S0041">if someone I don't think it's too much to expect</u>
<u n="623" who="S0084">oh no</u>
<u n="624" who="S0041">if somebody <trunc>c</trunc> asked me to my job I'd be able to tell them</u>
<u n="625" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0041">it's varied</u>
<u n="627" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0041">but I know it's gonna be contracts <pause dur="short"/> answering e-mails <pause dur="short"/> quoting stuff <pause dur="short"/> chasing people <pause dur="short"/> showing people round the hotel</u>
<u n="629" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0041">planning weddings <pause dur="short"/> ordering stuff from suppliers <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="631" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0041">it's varied but you <trunc>c</trunc>  you <trunc>c</trunc>  it stops somewhere</u>
<u n="633" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0041">but every time I've asked it seems like they can't  they can't  give me the the box version</u>
<u n="635" who="S0084">boundaries</u>
<u n="636" who="S0041">they're just saying it's just it's so different <pause dur="short"/> it's so varied and</u>
<u n="637" who="S0084">well maybe the reality of it</u>
<u n="638" who="S0041">from what I can gather</u>
<u n="639" who="S0084">is is that the <trunc>re</trunc> the <trunc>offi</trunc> er just like in any er in any job you're probably doing a lot of the same stuff but there as an officer you're looking at it from a top level and you're responsible for people <pause dur="short"/> so you're responsible for their</u>
<u n="640" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0084">training</u>
<u n="642" who="S0041">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <pause dur="short"/> he said you'll find that the ratings that do CT are technically much more accurate and capable than the</u>
<u n="643" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0041">officer</u>
<u n="645" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0041">but the officer oversees more people doing</u>
<u n="647" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0041">it</u>
<u n="649" who="S0084">well you're cos you're not  you're not  actually doing the job necessarily yourself are you</u>
<u n="650" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="651" who="S0084">you're just <trunc>u</trunc> you have an understanding of it <pause dur="short"/> but because you you're doing so much other stuff you only see it from a top level</u>
<u n="652" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0084">not at a micro level <pause dur="short"/> because it's like be you'd be</u>
<u n="654" who="S0041">it's not necessary is it</u>
<u n="655" who="S0084">micromanaging otherwise</u>
<u n="656" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0084">wouldn't you</u>
<u n="658" who="S0041">so um</u>
<u n="659" who="S0084">sounds like a good idea <pause dur="short"/> sounds like a good time to go and speak to him <pause dur="short"/> you know while you're a bit</u>
<u n="660" who="S0041">and while I'm there I'm gonna fill out all the paperwork in the world they ever need and just give it to them there</u>
<u n="661" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="662" who="S0041">instead of posting it</u>
<u n="663" who="S0084">well er hopefully you'll at least have your letter from the school by then</u>
<u n="664" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="665" who="S0084">fingers crossed</u>
<u n="666" who="S0041">fucking bastards <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="667" who="S0084">I mean it seems unlikely <pause dur="short"/> I don't <trunc>s</trunc> they're probably  they're probably  passed on <pause dur="short"/> that probably was quite a challenging conversation for her</u>
<u n="668" who="S0041">I think that was the end of her life <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and do you know what her name is?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0084">er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0084">oh no</u>
<u n="672" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I thought you are exactly why I'm a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and not a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> you</u>
<u n="673" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0041">and really just before I spoke to her <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I have this thing in the office that you have an idea of what people of a certain name are like <pause dur="short"/> and you came up today and er</u>
<u n="675" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0041">we don't know a <trunc>b</trunc> a <trunc>n</trunc> a nasty <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0041">all the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> between us that we both know none of them are nasty</u>
<u n="679" who="S0084">ah okay</u>
<u n="680" who="S0041">so you came out as a nice always a nice well-rounded person <pause dur="short"/> like balanced persons are <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> so you were in that category</u>
<u n="681" who="S0084">excellent</u>
<u n="682" who="S0041">and I said what do you what would you think of when you see a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="684" who="S0041">Cos I mentioned that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't realize <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was my real name <pause dur="short"/> and he's known me all my life</u>
<u n="685" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="686" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> and he said to be honest quite meek and mild <pause dur="short"/> usually mousy hair or blonde</u>
<u n="687" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="688" who="S0041">not really much of a muchness</u>
<u n="689" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="690" who="S0041">not very capable <pause dur="short"/> and I was like yeah I see that <pause dur="short"/> and all the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've ever known</u>
<u n="691" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0041">have been quite like that or quite swotty <pause dur="short"/> studiers</u>
<u n="693" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have I known? I see cliquey bitchy girls actually <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0041">oh do you?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0084">sort of but that could be where er I've come from <pause dur="short"/> like my background's quite middle upper class</u>
<u n="696" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="697" who="S0084">so I think the girls that I went to school with are a bit like that <pause dur="short"/> they're a bit sort of girls who play hockey <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="698" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="699" who="S0084">netball girls <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> although the girl that you know I worked with a couple of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>s at Waterstones and they were one was very arty but a bit simple</u>
<u n="700" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0084">big eyes <pause dur="short"/> like Kermit eyes <pause dur="short"/> like white all the way around <pause dur="short"/> freakish</u>
<u n="702" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="703" who="S0084">and the other one is a teacher <pause dur="short"/> loves kids</u>
<u n="704" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="705" who="S0084">A bit scary</u>
<u n="706" who="S0041">I see this</u>
<u n="707" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so we decided that that's why I'm a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and not a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then I e-mailed her and I was like this is her I've got one <pause dur="short"/> this is her <pause dur="short"/> this is it</u>
<u n="709" who="S0084">this is why</u>
<u n="710" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this is one of them</u>
<u n="711" who="S0084">so do your parents call you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0084">do they?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0041">chose <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> before they chose <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0084"></u>
<u n="716" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then they went to write <vocal desc="laugh"/> apparently they went to write the birth certificate and she was like should be call her something proper in case she becomes something professional?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="718" who="S0041">okay <pause dur="short"/> we'll call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0084">so that's quite nice <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose that happens more and more doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> you know kids are named and baptized the <trunc>deri</trunc> the derivatives as opposed to the the formal names</u>
<u n="720" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0084">and you get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>s and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>s and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>s or you know</u>
<u n="722" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0084">whatever</u>
<u n="724" who="S0041">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made me laugh today cos I always call her <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> all the time</u>
<u n="725" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Right</u>
<u n="726" who="S0041">huh <pause dur="short"/> and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> called her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I said why did you call her that? He said I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I said I like to call her <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> not that it's her name or whatever <trunc>n</trunc> no idea who this person is but</u>
<u n="727" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So she googled it and it's this artist and she started reading all about her <pause dur="short"/> and then she said oh dear <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I said what?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="730" who="S0041">online obituary of <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> died in <vocal desc="laugh"/> Massachusetts yesterday</u>
<u n="731" who="S0084">huh</u>
<u n="732" who="S0041">I was like huh but because of the <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> we were both like huh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> She opened it up and was reading <vocal desc="laugh"/> reading out this woman's obituary</u>
<u n="733" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="734" who="S0041">and I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you realize <vocal desc="laugh"/> how crazy this is? She was like what? And then I got in hysterics <pause dur="short"/> and I was like what did you do today <vocal desc="laugh"/> at work <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? Oh I read the obituary of a <vocal desc="laugh"/> complete stranger</u>
<u n="735" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0041">just for shits and giggles</u>
<u n="737" who="S0084">just because  just because  you happened to have the same name as my boss</u>
<u n="738" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s name isn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really</u>
<u n="739" who="S0084">oh it's just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0041">it's just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="741" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="742" who="S0041">like she's been christened with just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's quite nice though isn't it <pause dur="short"/> eve</u>
<u n="744" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> her parents didn't want people to be able to shorten it so she has a</u>
<u n="745" who="S0084">she has a short one</u>
<u n="746" who="S0041">short name</u>
<u n="747" who="S0084">it's nice though <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="749" who="S0084">I don't like many short names <pause dur="short"/> don't like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="750" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="751" who="S0084">bit common</u>
<u n="752" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="753" who="S0084">or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> don't like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> don't like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> either</u>
<u n="755" who="S0084">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>s awful</u>
<u n="756" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="757" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> not pro that</u>
<u n="759" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="761" who="S0084">Don't like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah there's <trunc>g</trunc> a lot of girls just they're just common though aren't they</u>
<u n="762" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0084">that's the problem</u>
<u n="764" who="S0041">that's the issue I have with this</u>
<u n="765" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was very nearly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="766" who="S0041">I like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0084">which is nice <pause dur="short"/> but mum didn't want her to be <trunc>shorten</trunc> not that it is shortening but she didn't want her to be er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="768" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0084">but that's because my dad <vocal desc="laugh"/> wanted to call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from</u>
<u n="770" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Right</u>
<u n="771" who="S0084">from a  from a</u>
<u n="772" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="773" who="S0084">book</u>
<u n="774" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0084">and er so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was very nearly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0041">I like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="777" who="S0084">but they settled on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> so she's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="778" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="779" who="S0084">which is nice</u>
<u n="780" who="S0041">that's a nice name</u>
<u n="781" who="S0084">er and then she was nearly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> they liked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I really like the name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0041">I didn't until I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0084">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="784" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's gutting</u>
<u n="785" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit of a shame actually</u>
<u n="786" who="S0041">she yeah she didn't  she didn't  remind me of a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> she doesn't look like a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> she looks a bit like a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="788" who="S0041">I like the name Ivy and that's a short name</u>
<u n="789" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0041">yeah I prefer older older fashioned names older worldie names <pause dur="short"/> I like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> my cousin's what is it when your cousin has a baby? Second cousin?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0041">well apparently <pause dur="short"/> but I'm saying that it's nephew <pause dur="short"/> so I've got one</u>
<u n="793" who="S0084">nephew <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> so the nephew not that is a nephew is called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> which is quite</u>
<u n="794" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="795" who="S0084">an old-fashioned name <pause dur="short"/> and they um when he was born er he looked so much like my uncle it's not true <pause dur="short"/> which is just because my uncle has a big round face and no hair</u>
<u n="796" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0084">and um a chubby baby face</u>
<u n="798" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> chubby baby face</u>
<u n="799" who="S0084">but her their their my uncle's step-daughter so whatever she is to me <pause dur="short"/> nothing essentially</u>
<u n="800" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0084">that's</u>
<u n="802" who="S0041">A stranger</u>
<u n="803" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="804" who="S0041">this stranger I know</u>
<u n="805" who="S0084">this person that I sort of see at family gatherings <pause dur="short"/> she's had twins <pause dur="short"/> twin boys <pause dur="short"/> and they're called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> awful</u>
<u n="806" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="807" who="S0084">and oh I was gonna say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos that's Laurel and Hardy</u>
<u n="808" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="809" who="S0084">that's not what they're called <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="810" who="S0041">that'd be so funny though</u>
<u n="811" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and something equally as bad</u>
<u n="812" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="813" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> honestly <pause dur="short"/> poor kid <pause dur="short"/> who calls their kid <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> these days?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0041">A masochist probably</u>
<u n="815" who="S0084">A masochist <pause dur="short"/> someone who hates their children</u>
<u n="816" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="817" who="S0084">and life</u>
<u n="818" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0084">I I probably should get in the shower</u>
<u n="820" who="S0041">clean clean your act up</u>
<u n="821" who="S0084">clean all that <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="822" who="S0041">clean all the act up</u>
<u n="823" who="S0084">yes <pause dur="short"/> oh so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was here then? Cos she's taken the rent so</u>
<u n="824" who="S0041">oh has she?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="826" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> she's been around</u>
<u n="827" who="S0084">she is alive <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>e</trunc> and in <trunc>exi</trunc> in existence</u>
<u n="828" who="S0041"><vocal desc="yawn"/> I don't know what to do with myself</u>
<u n="829" who="S0084">um nothing</u>
<u n="830" who="S0041">er yeah <pause dur="short"/> nada</u>
<u n="831" who="S0084">nothing <pause dur="short"/> because it's Friday</u>
<u n="832" who="S0041">nothing compares</u>
<u n="833" who="S0084">are you did you make no plans cos you've gotta work tomorrow?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0084">uh <pause dur="short"/> what a shitter man</u>
<u n="836" who="S0041">do all the work <unclear/> tomorrow</u>
<u n="837" who="S0084">all the work?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0041">all the work</u>
<u n="839" who="S0084">oh huh man alive <pause dur="short"/> well you do have a lambikins to eat so that's exciting <pause dur="short"/> lambie</u>
<u n="840" who="S0041"><unclear/> I'll have a what now?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0084">A lambie</u>
<u n="842" who="S0041">I do have a lambie <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="843" who="S0084">lambie</u>
<u n="844" who="S0041">think I'm gonna have lambie now in my life</u>
<u n="845" who="S0084">do it <pause dur="short"/> I ate mine when I got home</u>
<u n="846" who="S0041">huh <pause dur="short"/> yay</u>
<u n="847" who="S0084">it was pretty exciting</u>
<u n="848" who="S0041">yay</u>
<u n="849" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> oh I just wanna go to sleep</u>
<u n="850" who="S0041">what film are you gonna put on?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="852" who="S0041">hm <pause dur="short"/> lambie</u>
<u n="853" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> something that doesn't test my brain at all would be good</u>
<u n="854" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's probably a good place to start</u>
<u n="855" who="S0084"><vocal desc="cough"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="856" who="S0041">hm</u>
<u n="857" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> now I don't know what we're <trunc>d</trunc> gonna do about take-away <pause dur="short"/> because I've eaten really badly this week <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>l</trunc> well yesterday I went to my dad's and we were gonna have chicken and veg and stuff but his fridge has been freezing all his food</u>
<u n="858" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="859" who="S0084">so he got the chicken out and the chicken was <vocal desc="laugh"/> frozen and he was like right that's not really gonna work is it? No <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> so he had to go to the Co-op and er he brought back pizza <pause dur="short"/> which is fine</u>
<u n="860" who="S0041">love pizza</u>
<u n="861" who="S0084">and delicious <pause dur="short"/> and I hadn't had pizza in ages <pause dur="short"/> and I was thinking about pizza during the week <pause dur="short"/> but we had chips on Monday <pause dur="short"/> so to now have take-away today I might just</u>
<u n="862" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="863" who="S0084">not eat or something tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> but then drinking tomorrow night <pause dur="short"/> stranger danger <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="864" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> given all the cack I've eaten <pause dur="short"/> she says eating lamb <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="865" who="S0084">eating the lambie</u>
<u n="866" who="S0041">yeah I should um I should eat something healthy</u>
<u n="867" who="S0084">never</u>
<u n="868" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Never <pause dur="short"/> not the health</u>
<u n="869" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No</u>
<u n="870" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0084">sausage club this morning <pause dur="short"/> minus <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was very sad</u>
<u n="872" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="873" who="S0084">it was just me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> but I had big breakfast and then didn't have lunch <pause dur="short"/> but I did have a cranberry and orange biscuit and some peanuts <pause dur="short"/> all of which were very delicious <pause dur="short"/> and a banana <pause dur="short"/> but I did have a massive breakfast <pause dur="short"/> so then I came home and ate the lamb</u>
<u n="874" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="875" who="S0084">so I've just basically been pigging out on absolute shite</u>
<u n="876" who="S0041">crap</u>
<u n="877" who="S0084">like apart from the banana and I mean possibly the cranberry and orange but let's be honest it was really just a biscuit <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um <pause dur="short"/> there was nothing healthy today at all</u>
<u n="878" who="S0041">do you know what I had for my tea yesterday?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0084">what did you have for tea?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0041">A whole bag a big bag of Doritos</u>
<u n="881" who="S0084">nice</u>
<u n="882" who="S0041">and a whole tub of fresh salsa</u>
<u n="883" who="S0084">you should've eaten these you maniac</u>
<u n="884" who="S0041">I ate them all</u>
<u n="885" who="S0084">oh good <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> did you eat them?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="887" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="888" who="S0041">bought some</u>
<u n="889" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0041">the entire bag</u>
<u n="891" who="S0084">that's quite good</u>
<u n="892" who="S0041">I just ate half the bag and half the dip</u>
<u n="893" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="894" who="S0041">and then I was on the phone to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for two hours and by one o'clock in the morning I was hungry so I ate the rest of them</u>
<u n="895" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0084">you're an absolute maniac <pause dur="short"/> well I didn't hear you <pause dur="short"/> were you on the phone really late then? Ah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0041">keen <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="898" who="S0084">chatting</u>
<u n="899" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="900" who="S0084">where is he then? So he's not on a boat?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0041">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> he's got a month's holiday</u>
<u n="902" who="S0084">he's been on holiday</u>
<u n="903" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="904" who="S0084">for like three months or something</u>
<u n="905" who="S0041"></u>
<u n="906" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="907" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0084">face <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="910" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="911" who="S0041">he's got a month's holiday <pause dur="short"/> and then he'll get posted around the UK</u>
<u n="912" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="913" who="S0041">Cos he's not going on tour</u>
<u n="914" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="915" who="S0041">apparently <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="916" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="917" who="S0041">and he was on about wanting me to get a hotel room in Nottingham <pause dur="short"/> cos that's half-way between the two of us</u>
<u n="918" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> tempted?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0041">very tempted  very tempted  Um so we toyed around with that idea</u>
<u n="920" who="S0084">lovely</u>
<u n="921" who="S0041">but er I'm a little bit concerned that he is seeing this girl</u>
<u n="922" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="923" who="S0041">which he doesn't seem to give a crap about <pause dur="short"/> which I don't it's nothing to do with me</u>
<u n="924" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0041">just do what I want</u>
<u n="926" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="927" who="S0041">um but he's like it's all very much in jest as in we wouldn't ask the other one if they fancied the other one</u>
<u n="928" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="929" who="S0041">or how how much they liked them <pause dur="short"/> or anything that would have any type of emotion attached to it <pause dur="short"/> because of the very strange situ</u>
<u n="930" who="S0084">cousin situ</u>
<u n="931" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> to which I found out he actually Googled sex with your cousin</u>
<u n="932" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0041">I was like you did what? I said you do realize that that'll be on your computer now and we're not actually related <pause dur="short"/> I mean can you?</u>
<u n="934" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="935" who="S0041">let's back-track a second <pause dur="short"/> you do realize we're not actually related</u>
<u n="936" who="S0084">there's no blood <pause dur="short"/> please not be going there</u>
<u n="937" who="S0041">um and he was like well <pause dur="short"/> he said either way if he'd get on a ship cos apparently if you go in as an officer then you can choose your ship after the year or something</u>
<u n="938" who="S0084">nice</u>
<u n="939" who="S0041">you can nominate somewhere</u>
<u n="940" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="941" who="S0041">and he's got this whole fantasy in his head that because obviously our names aren't the same or anything cos we're not really related then I could nominate to go on his ship <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="942" who="S0084">and you could shag him all the time</u>
<u n="943" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> shag him off <pause dur="short"/> so that's quite amusing</u>
<u n="944" who="S0084">apart from the risk of the old court-martialling or whatever it is</u>
<u n="945" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="946" who="S0084">they do to you</u>
<u n="947" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> apart from that</u>
<u n="948" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="949" who="S0041">um but then he was saying stuff like that he'd googled it <pause dur="short"/> and I was like right okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um now a bit concerned <pause dur="short"/> he said and it turns out anyway eight <vocal desc="laugh"/> eighty percent of Muslims are um married to their cousins anyway <pause dur="short"/> you do realize we're not Muslim either?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="951" who="S0041">like um <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> He was just so funny <pause dur="short"/> he's such a clever dick</u>
<u n="952" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="953" who="S0041">I thought <trunc>s</trunc> what? I was like I want to knock on your forehead and make sure</u>
<u n="954" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="955" who="S0041">there's somebody inside <pause dur="short"/> cos this is not okay</u>
<u n="956" who="S0084">you're not cousins and you're certainly not Muslims</u>
<u n="957" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="958" who="S0084">so</u>
<u n="959" who="S0041">muslims <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="960" who="S0084">all in all everything's fine</u>
<u n="961" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="962" who="S0084">no need to worry <pause dur="short"/> reassuring</u>
<u n="963" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> reassuring to know <pause dur="short"/> thanks for that</u>
<u n="964" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="965" who="S0041">but um er <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he was like but then he kept making comments like not just Muslims that are with their cousin or sleep with cousins but marriage to their cousins</u>
<u n="966" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="967" who="S0041">um and I'm probably reading too much into it but then he was asking about how many people I'd slept with and stuff</u>
<u n="968" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="969" who="S0041">his number's off the scale</u>
<u n="970" who="S0084">uh</u>
<u n="971" who="S0041"><unclear/> hundred and fifty mark</u>
<u n="972" who="S0084">boys in the navy are disgusting <pause dur="short"/> that's gonna be you <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="973" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I've said no <pause dur="short"/> he said  he said  <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you say no now but imagine being pestered all the time  all the time  by all the men <pause dur="short"/> you could choose any single one of them you wanted <pause dur="short"/> it's they just cos they're all trapped on a ship together</u>
<u n="974" who="S0084">and you <trunc>c</trunc> and if you wear the sex top <pause dur="short"/> you'll have to leave the sex top at home</u>
<u n="975" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Don't wear the sex top</u>
<u n="977" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh yeah that's quite bad</u>
<u n="978" who="S0084">you might actually run the risk of Rohypnol in your drink</u>
<u n="979" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> what was I saying to you? Ah</u>
<u n="980" who="S0084">so you're not gonna shag any of them?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm not allowed to shag any of them <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and he was like asking ask he was asking basically where he ranked</u>
<u n="982" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="983" who="S0041">on my scale of <unclear/> sleeping with <unclear/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="985" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="986" who="S0084">that that ranked <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="987" who="S0041">that rankage <pause dur="short"/> which to which he got a percentage</u>
<u n="988" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="989" who="S0041">of top five percent</u>
<u n="990" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="991" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> pretty good</u>
<u n="992" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="993" who="S0041">um which it was quite an awkward conversation for me to have with him <pause dur="short"/> cos it's just</u>
<u n="994" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="995" who="S0041">it shouldn't have really happened and we both want this to happen again</u>
<u n="996" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0041">even though we shouldn't really do it at all <pause dur="short"/> and he was like saying how next time he sees me is obviously gonna be at some family thing</u>
<u n="998" who="S0084">oo</u>
<u n="999" who="S0041">and he said I just don't know how I'm gonna be with you like <pause dur="short"/> I can see it being really awkward</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0041">Cos obviously people say to him have you heard from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? And he's saying no</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0041">Cos he wants to say yes but he's scared <pause dur="short"/> he's second-guessing that they'll</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0041">be second-guessing</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0041">I said they're not <pause dur="short"/> you're in the fricking navy <pause dur="short"/> they know the  they know the  game</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0041">stop overthinking it cos you're gonna make it worse</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0041">um and he was like oh yeah can you imagine next time I see your dad</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1013" who="S0041"><unclear/> And I was like don't even say it <pause dur="short"/> and he was like oh yeah just shagged your daughter and that <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0041">I was like don't even joke about it</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0041">and he said</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0084">man</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0041">do you want me to come down there or something? You know <unclear/> like sexy talking <pause dur="short"/> and he said is that all you see me as? A piece of meat?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0084">he said that to you?</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I wanted to reply like that's all I can ever see you as <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0041">why did you even ask it? I didn't  I didn't  say it <pause dur="short"/> and then he said something like are you seeing anyone at the moment? Er no have you got a boyfriend? And I said I wouldn't say boyfriend <pause dur="short"/> I've been talking to a couple of people</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0084">Possibles</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0041">Possibles <pause dur="short"/> and he was like oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> a couple? And asked me about it <pause dur="short"/> I said no nothing serious just you know <pause dur="short"/> said anyway no boyfriend <pause dur="short"/> not after the last one <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> seriously <pause dur="short"/> men need to man up</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0041">and I was and he said but <unclear/> you know like soppy lovey dovey nah nah can't be doing with that right now</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0041">and he said oh well I'm you know I'm like that <pause dur="short"/> cos he's a really lad's lad type <pause dur="short"/> he said well you know I'm like that when you know when you're in love with someone <pause dur="short"/> basically trying to tell me that he is really very affectionate and very lovely <pause dur="short"/> and not like the part of me that the part of him that I usually see</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0041">when he's with someone <pause dur="short"/> and really kind and and I was thinking like why are you selling this to me?</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0041">why are you selling this idea to me? So</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0041">I don't  I don't  know about that now</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0084">I mean along with the fact that A he's your cousin</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0084">good enough  good enough</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0084">close enough</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0041">close enough <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0084">um and B the comments such as spunk bucket</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0084">all mean he's not a potential boyfriend</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0041">he's definitely not potential boyfriend material</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0041">no way Jose <pause dur="short"/> none whatsoever</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0084">but that is not to say one cannot have fun with one's whatever he is</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think we need to invent a word really</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0041">I don't know what that would be</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0084">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to think about that <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0084">but what so how did you leave things about the hotel?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0041">um he said give me a date and I'll drive down to Nottingham</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0084">nice</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0041">mm which was decidedly the part-way between the two</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0041">initially was Sheffield <pause dur="short"/> and I said yes should we call in and see my dad while we're there?</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0041">and he was like sure</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0084">is Sheffield not really close to Newcastle though? Okay</u>
<u n="1067" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0084">I don't know where it is</u>
<u n="1069" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1070" who="S0084">to me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1071" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0084">to me every is north</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's like me</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0084">so for me</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0041">that everything's south</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0084">all the  all the  towns are here</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0084">all in the north</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0084">of about you know sort of five miles</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0041">that's like me with anything below here</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1083" who="S0041">anything below Cambridge is all together in London <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1084" who="S0084">I've got absolutely no idea <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> positively despairs</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1086" who="S0084">whenever we talk to someone who's you know from somewhere north of London I'm like oh so whereabouts are you from <pause dur="short"/> clare's like don't tell her</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1088" who="S0084">she's got no fucking idea where it is</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1090" who="S0084">there's no point <pause dur="short"/> I've got no clue <pause dur="short"/> she had to tell me that Newcastle's on the east</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> didn't know <pause dur="short"/> well she's from</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0084">Sunderland <pause dur="short"/> but she had to tell me that er yeah that that's where that was</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0041">I feel the need  I feel the need</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0084">draw draw draw the country please</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> so don't really know there's like a bit that comes out there isn't there</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> east anglia</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0041">and that's I think that's like Scotland up there or something</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> so we're gonna pretend that we're about here aren't we</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0084">er no</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0041">this is the <trunc>s</trunc> foot comes out there</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> very very nice <pause dur="short"/> so that's</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0041">that is the bit of Norfolk isn't it <pause dur="short"/> there</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0084">that's Norfolk Suffolk we're that's probably mm if that was there that's probably Leicester <pause dur="short"/> that's London <pause dur="short"/> that's Norwich</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0084">we're probably about here</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0041">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0084">and Newcastle's here <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> newcastles's about here</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> that's all I know</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0041">so that Scottish border's probably about there actually</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0041">but</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0084">fine</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> I don't really know all the whether they're that way or that way <pause dur="short"/> I only know kind of in order as you hit them if you drove up the country</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0041">so the first place you'd hit from us you'd probably hit Peterborough</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0041">so for an hour</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0041">you carry on driving for another hour you hit Nottingham</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0041">you carry on driving oh I've I've got loads and loads of space left <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1127" who="S0041">Peterborough <pause dur="short"/> we'll go Peterborough here</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0041">that's probably a bit closer isn't it <pause dur="short"/> peterborough's probably there <pause dur="short"/> nottingham's probably there</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0041">and then this little bit where the the water comes in</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0041">is Hull</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0041">so between Nottingham here and Hull here in the middle is Sheffield</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0041">so that's where I live <pause dur="short"/> right in the middle</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0041">so it goes us Peterborough Nottingham Sheffield Hull</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0041">Manchester's over that way a bit <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>lee</trunc></u>
<u n="1142" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0041">Leeds is just here</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0041">and then after tut see after Hull I don't really know what comes after that <pause dur="short"/> but from here to here is about three and a half hours</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0084">is it?</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0084">fucking hell</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0041">or <trunc>may</trunc></u>
<u n="1150" who="S0084">that's really far</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0041">yeah or maybe that's three and a half hours from Sheffield <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's really far <pause dur="short"/> from here it's about three hundred miles</u>
<u n="1152" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1153" who="S0041">so it would take me half the time if I drove from here to Sheffield that's half-way between here and Newcastle</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0084">shit man <pause dur="short"/> and that's where you drove to at Christmas wasn't it? Newcastle?</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0041">I drove to Sheffield and then my dad did this route</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0041">so I did this route</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0084">which was two hours?</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0041">and dad did this route <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0084">no two three hours</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0084">two hours to Nottingham <pause dur="short"/> three hours to Sheffield <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's probably takes me about I always leave three hours to get home to Sheffield <pause dur="short"/> but you probably could do it in two and a half</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0084">with your driving <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0084">foot down</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0041">and then from here to here is about the same</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0084">three hours</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0041">two and a half three hours</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0084">fuck</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1172" who="S0084">that's much further than I thought it was gonna be</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er in between</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0084">actually</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0041">there is Manchester at some point <pause dur="short"/> I think it's over that side though <pause dur="short"/> I think it's level with Hull but the other side</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0084">I I think I didn't think that that was lower <pause dur="short"/> I thought that was higher <pause dur="short"/> I thought Sheffield was up there</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0084">er well basically I just think everything's here</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0084">all of the places</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0041">there's Durham here</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0084">are there</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0041">Durham between these two</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0084">and <trunc>y</trunc> then you've got Coventry round there somewhere haven't you?</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0041">oh is that round there? I dunno</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0084">Prr</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0041">Middlesbrough must be somewhere round this point as well</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0084">no it's</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0041">all I know is</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0084">Middlesbrough's near Sheffield isn't it?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0041">is no norther that's near</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Norther</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0041">Norther <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1194" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> We're such retards</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's near Newcastle</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0041">so there's there's Sheffield and then God knows what after that <pause dur="short"/> hull</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0084">Hull <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0041">Leeds</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0084">places you don't wanna go</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hull <pause dur="short"/> leeds <pause dur="short"/> then a bit of a gap</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0041">then you get to kind of Middlesbrough and Durham area <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because that's where the Dales and</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0041">Cos that's where the accents change</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0041">that's how I know it</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0041">so then you hit more countryside and then the accents change from a Yorkshire accent to a what people get confused with a Newcastle accent</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0041">they get really twangy</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0084">oh like <trunc>cou</trunc> County Durham</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0041">and then Newcastle</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then Scotland</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0084">and then the border</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0041">I mean there must be something between Newcastle and Scotland</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0084">sheep</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0041">but in my head <pause dur="short"/> sheep and Scotland</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0084">I don't think there's much <trunc>c</trunc> carrying on up there anyway</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0084">it's fricking freezing <pause dur="short"/> and then Liverpool's over here <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0084">on the coast</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0041"><trunc>L</trunc> Liverpool and Manchester are over here somewhere <pause dur="short"/> dunno dunno <pause dur="short"/> isn't Liverpool near Wales?</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0084">Liverpool is above Wales <pause dur="short"/> so that's that'd be Wales and Liverpool's up there</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0084">because the ferry to Belfast would be back there</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0041">goes from there</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0084">that's why you've got loads of Irish people in Liverpool</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0041">so maybe it goes Manchester then Liverpool</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0084">Manchester's kind of in the middle isn't it</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0084">I mean listen to me <pause dur="short"/> I'm talking absolute shite</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1238" who="S0084">it could be er I mean it could be anywhere</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0041">it definitely takes from Hull to drive to Manchester is on the same road <pause dur="short"/> so er there's a road that goes across country that goes from Hull to Manchester <pause dur="short"/> direct</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0041">Cos I was like Manchester? <trunc>H</trunc> are you kidding me? <trunc>H</trunc> they're miles away from each other <pause dur="short"/> but I think it's about an hour and a half</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> well it's good to know that it's not just my geography</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no mine's cack</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0084">I mean yours sounds pretty good</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0041">oh no everything from down here's London <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0084">well that's fine <pause dur="short"/> because um I dunno the north <pause dur="short"/> I guess you just know <trunc>w</trunc> that was in the washing machine</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1248" who="S0084">Good <pause dur="short"/> I guess you just know what you know</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0084">as it were <pause dur="short"/> so I know the south <pause dur="short"/> and I know the west <pause dur="short"/> cos that's where I've lived <pause dur="short"/> and I know east <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know north</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0041">no I don't</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0084">North of here</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0041"><unclear/> things</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0084">thank you for the um geography lesson my love</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0041">that's that's alright</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1259" who="S0041">so it may be a a trip to the Sheffield</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0084">oo yeah</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0041">maybe I could er incorporate this whole thing with a trip to Nottingham for the birthday and a trip to</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1264" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0041">could all just roll into one</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> never go to work again</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just never go back</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0084">just just don't go <pause dur="short"/> just keep <unclear/></u>
<u n="1269" who="S0041">I was thinking</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> did you  did you  book off the the week off of work when there's bank holidays and then you book three days and you got the week of or something?</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0084">the Easter week? Oh no the June week <pause dur="short"/> the Jubilee?</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0041"><trunc>Ju</trunc></u>
<u n="1274" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did you?</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0041">Cos I thought if I tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to book that off then we could do birthday time at that time</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0084">ah perfect <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's good <pause dur="short"/> although it is half-term week I think <pause dur="short"/> but if we get in there early we can <trunc>s</trunc> book hotels <pause dur="short"/> I mean your</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0084">that shouldn't affect your if we were</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0084">staying somewhere that you could get</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I'll have a look around</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0084">have a little shop</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0041">have a look around</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> shower</u>
</body>
</text>
