<text id="SXGX">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:33:25</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0519 S0520 S0521</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Hunsonby, Cumbria</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>coffee machine, removal and storage costs, politics, Labour leadership, idealism</topics>
		<activity> family chatting in kitchen</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, complaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0519">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Dublin, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith, `</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Recently retired maths teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0520">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead, UK`</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>India/Thailand/UK (Hunsoney</hab_city>
				<hab_country></hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Transcriber, Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0521">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Walsall, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Former role as technical esport of development planning in oil industry</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0519">listen to this <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>e</trunc> I don't know I haven't even looked at the house yet I've <trunc>ju</trunc> and it can't be that good cos it's seven two five</u>
<u n="2" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0519">offering excellent value</u>
<u n="4" who="S0520">seven two five is your budget isn't it?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0519" trans="overlap">we don't like value with no chain located in a truly beautiful and tranquil location set in grounds of just over an acre and ten minutes' drive from <anon type="place"/> village centre</u>
<u n="6" who="S0520">where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0519" trans="overlap">a four-bedroomed three bathroom five reception rooms</u>
<u n="8" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what do you need five reception rooms for?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0519">well we need to two for the piano and accoutrements that's far enough away</u>
<u n="10" who="S0520">two for the piano</u>
<u n="11" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it just means downstairs doesn't it?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0519">mm love it so we'll view on a map</u>
<u n="13" who="S0520">where is <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0519">south Cheshire south west</u>
<u n="15" who="S0521" trans="overlap">very close to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0520">what does it mean by five reception rooms? it's just a <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0519" trans="overlap">five reception rooms it's probably <trunc>ma</trunc> erm a bit modern</u>
<u n="18" who="S0520" trans="overlap">utility and</u>
<u n="19" who="S0519">and other things that we don't want so I'm not going to get over excited</u>
<u n="20" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah erm <trunc>wha</trunc><trunc>wha</trunc> is your budget about seven hundred then? or is it like as in?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no you go normally in England you offer below erm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0520">oh really?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0519">yes so it if you would go up to about say seven fifty or maybe a bit more so that you could come down to seven two five from there</u>
<u n="24" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0521">I've heard this theory before</u>
<u n="26" who="S0519">this is the idea</u>
<u n="27" who="S0520">I've not only heard this theory I've actually seen it in action <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's the ever increasing budget of the house search no but it's a bit different this time isn't it? cos you don't want a mortgage</u>
<u n="28" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="29" who="S0520">or is that a decision?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0519">that's a definite decision yeah that's right</u>
<u n="31" who="S0520">well at least if you live down there you'll keep this house I'll be happy</u>
<u n="32" who="S0519">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="33" who="S0521">if your piano is of low value and you don't mind how it's moved a man and a van should be okay if your instrument is of value either sentimental or instrumental it is wise to use the correct method of transportation we are working blind using this method of booking so if your piano is of high value and you require specialist mover equipment please make this clear <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0520">that's you dad in the second category innit?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0521">yeah extra charges for stairs and obstacles</u>
<u n="36" who="S0520">that's actually a good thing in your house it's probably quite it's quite a dream for a removals company isn't it? cos no no narrow staircases and there's no like weird annoying doors</u>
<u n="37" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it's it's no no double for the piano it's a double door through to the kitchen and a double door out</u>
<u n="38" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0519">to the garden and then you that's your one step</u>
<u n="40" who="S0520">I remember them moving the piano where do I remember that? in Holland maybe from the first to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0519">there was one where the the grand piano came</u>
<u n="42" who="S0520">upside down</u>
<u n="43" who="S0519">on its side on a little trolley</u>
<u n="44" who="S0521" trans="overlap">a trolley</u>
<u n="45" who="S0519">with two little guys in a <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="46" who="S0520">heart attack</u>
<u n="47" who="S0521" trans="overlap">little white van</u>
<u n="48" who="S0519">I was terrified</u>
<u n="49" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah well they're notorious aren't they pianos? for being tricky to move and unhappy to be moved</u>
<u n="50" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0520">you have get it tuned don't you? straight away I also remember the little piano being replaced by the big piano</u>
<u n="52" who="S0519">I know it's funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0520" trans="overlap">how old was I? I was young I was traumatised</u>
<u n="54" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah you were just a little squidge</u>
<u n="55" who="S0520">I remember not enjoying playing the big one for ages</u>
<u n="56" who="S0521">oh oh</u>
<u n="57" who="S0520">cos we were so used to it</u>
<u n="58" who="S0519" trans="overlap">such a different feel wasn't it?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0520">yeah and also you could just kind of go and hide in that little room and play practice and stuff whereas with the grand piano you have to kind of er</u>
<u n="60" who="S0521" trans="overlap">can't hide with the grand mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0520">give a performance every time you sit down</u>
<u n="62" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0520">so what's the er what does it look like?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0519">it's a bit modern and huge rather than you know cosy and</u>
<u n="65" who="S0520">characterful</u>
<u n="66" who="S0519">characterful</u>
<u n="67" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0520">erm the one</u>
<u n="69" who="S0519" trans="overlap">the garden looks stunning</u>
<u n="70" who="S0520">mm that's really nice to have</u>
<u n="71" who="S0519">and the location is fabulous well I don't know that the location is fabulous</u>
<u n="72" who="S0520">I wouldn't want to be that close</u>
<u n="73" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0520">I mean not because of <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0519">it's probably half an hour from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but it's a modern house which is not what we had in mind</u>
<u n="76" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0519">it's a very lovely looking house</u>
<u n="78" who="S0520">you should just start going to see things cos you're not going to be able to tell until you kind of start to erm be there in the flesh and respond to the different types of thing</u>
<u n="79" who="S0519">no you're right</u>
<u n="80" who="S0520">the one that you had a pamphlet of upstairs both of you the favourite one had an amazing kitchen</u>
<u n="81" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0520">it was absolutely beautiful and that's what I imagine and it had it had an Aga though</u>
<u n="83" who="S0519" trans="overlap">me too</u>
<u n="84" who="S0520">which is lovely sounding but nobody wants to cook on it</u>
<u n="85" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no but that no but that they you can even have gas and electric Agas now so you don't know until you</u>
<u n="86" who="S0520">you don't want to be stoking coal into your oven before you cook your baked potato</u>
<u n="87" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no no usually if it has erm an Aga</u>
<u n="88" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I had one in <anon type="place"/> if you remember and er I didn't have a normal cooker so I didn't really use it at all it was just like</u>
<u n="89" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm no that's right</u>
<u n="90" who="S0520">it was a gas Aga though but it was still you know you needed and ancient knowledge of the <trunc>phys</trunc> of the er I dunno physical nature</u>
<u n="91" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah the wisdom of Agas</u>
<u n="92" who="S0520">the wisdom of Agas yeah to get it working I just used the microwave a lot <vocal desc="laugh"/> er you want an option anyway but yeah it was a really nice kitchen it was kind of erm mint a sage colour</u>
<u n="93" who="S0519"><anon type="place"/> road sound rather major doesn't it?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0520">it could be and it couldn't be you know sometimes those are erm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0519">nineteen twenties</u>
<u n="96" who="S0520" trans="overlap">really old</u>
<u n="97" who="S0519">arts and crafts country house with spacious accommodation in six acres with beautiful views</u>
<u n="98" who="S0520" trans="overlap">love mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> is that within the budget?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0519">seven hundred</u>
<u n="100" who="S0520">bargain I mean the good thing is that you don't have a have to <trunc>ha</trunc>have massive house</u>
<u n="101" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0520">you know you can erm you can downsize</u>
<u n="103" who="S0519">mm that's right</u>
<u n="104" who="S0520">and have more land or better quality instead</u>
<u n="105" who="S0519" trans="overlap">what we need is better quality and</u>
<u n="106" who="S0520">layout</u>
<u n="107" who="S0519">bigger downstairs or a studio or a you know something special that it that was close enough to the house so that we could <trunc>ex</trunc> either extend to it with a conservatory or something like that</u>
<u n="108" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0519">and then have the piano room as a sort of garden room separate that would be my ideal</u>
<u n="110" who="S0520">I like the idea as well yeah nice and spread out and the other thing that was nice about that house was the setting the setting was kind of exactly how I imagined your house</u>
<u n="111" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0520">it was mature trees all the way round so you have that really secure feeling</u>
<u n="113" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yes yes that's lovely isn't it?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0520">and the lovely garden and the beyond that obviously nice countryside but the you know it was very kind of enclosed</u>
<u n="115" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0520">erm with the trees and stuff it was really pretty</u>
<u n="117" who="S0521">well it's given our address as north <anon type="place"/> <anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0519">we are in <anon type="place"/> yeah I don't know why don't know why</u>
<u n="119" who="S0520">your address?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0520">thought you were <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0521"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0521">erm it's <anon type="place"/> isn't it? <anon type="place"/> is part of <anon type="place"/>? must be</u>
<u n="125" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="long"/> so have you had any developments with the buyers or are you just waiting for the paperwork?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0519">no tomorrow they're supposed to go and see the house erm er no sorry they're supposed to have a a survey done on the house</u>
<u n="127" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0519">but I did think we would have got the the papers by now it's quite a major er</u>
<u n="129" who="S0520">these estate agents are not the most efficient people I've ever heard of</u>
<u n="130" who="S0519" trans="overlap">pretty slow aren't they?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0520">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>ha</trunc> did you have a survey down before you put it on the market?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0519">you have to have like a a general survey</u>
<u n="133" who="S0520" trans="overlap">general one yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0519">but then they can chose to have something more detailed</u>
<u n="135" who="S0520">mm I can't imagine there's any issues</u>
<u n="136" who="S0519">no er oh in fact for their mortgage apparently they had to erm have a</u>
<u n="137" who="S0520">certain type done</u>
<u n="138" who="S0519">a a survey</u>
<u n="139" who="S0520">construction</u>
<u n="140" who="S0519">probably yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0520">just find lots of birds nesting everywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/> so how's it been with the birds? have they come back?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0519">here?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0520">yeah no</u>
<u n="144" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no no it's been really good</u>
<u n="145" who="S0520">excellent</u>
<u n="146" who="S0519">but <trunc>the</trunc> did we tell you did dad tell you he got like completely free the loft insulated? he just rang the gas company for their advice cos they it it said you know British Gas give advice about lofts and insulation</u>
<u n="147" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0519">of your home and so on and I was like oh for goodness sake you know as I usually am for dad and his erm I you know</u>
<u n="149" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I missed that I missed</u>
<u n="150" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0519">his er free free for nothing bargains</u>
<u n="152" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0519">and the this guy said yes it's free to everybody in Britain the government has decreed it's not means tested</u>
<u n="154" who="S0520">cool</u>
<u n="155" who="S0519">erm and we were just what were thinking we'd do it ourselves but we needed someone to tell us what to put in there</u>
<u n="156" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0519">and two men came and completely re erm lagged the whole loft both sides and then they but what I was why it reminded was I dad had stuffed cloth into all of the eaves to stop the birds being able to get in</u>
<u n="158" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0519">but they said the eaves were there for <trunc>a</trunc>air like there's no air brick and you can get moisture and condensation</u>
<u n="160" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0519">build-up and so you have let some gaps</u>
<u n="162" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0519">so they'd had had to pull it back from stuffed right in and they recommended like wire mesh</u>
<u n="164" who="S0520">to stop the birds from coming in</u>
<u n="165" who="S0519">to stop the birds coming in so erm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0520">well that's good advice isn't it?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but we didn't have any yeah but it was great wasn't it?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0520">that's probably a really smart move in their part cos it's all energy efficiency isn't it?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0519">that's right that's right that's what it's all about isn't it?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0521">so erm I'm just looking and it's about a hundred and fifty the increment in the Edinburgh company's quote for a piano</u>
<u n="171" who="S0519">I don't understand that really increment</u>
<u n="172" who="S0521">well he he he gave me a price with and without piano and then you add tax and insurance to it so I'm I'm sort of thinking if they can if we get a piano company for four hundred</u>
<u n="173" who="S0520">just do it separately</u>
<u n="174" who="S0521">do it separately</u>
<u n="175" who="S0520">I think that sounds wise as well</u>
<u n="176" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0521">what do you think? then you'd be sure that</u>
<u n="178" who="S0519">you've still then got to have that piano delivered</u>
<u n="179" who="S0521">well no they're quoting me prices of four hundredish</u>
<u n="180" who="S0519">for the storage</u>
<u n="181" who="S0521">for everything removal plus storage</u>
<u n="182" who="S0519">nobody's gonna I'm mm I</u>
<u n="183" who="S0521">sorry?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0519">who is quoting you removal and storage erm three hundred miles? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0520">for the just for the piano? do you think that's too low?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0519">and and delivery to your new home I'm talking about maybe that's not so remove it from this home store it for six months and deliver it to your new <trunc>ha</trunc> home all for hour hundred pounds?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0519">I'm very concerned frankly</u>
<u n="189" who="S0520">I like this mentality I know what you mean although if it's three thousand five hundred for the whole house it <trunc>si</trunc> it kind of makes sense to me that that would be the price</u>
<u n="190" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah you'd imagine just the you know we want to hire a van how much was it going to be for us two eejits to hire our own van?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0521">hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="193" who="S0519">a hundred and fifty this is to hire to van and this is not to remove and store and redeliver</u>
<u n="194" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0521">they've got their own vans they don't have to hire them</u>
<u n="196" who="S0519">I know but what I mean is I just want to put it in the context of erm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0520">no but if you put it in the context of the whole house</u>
<u n="198" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it's hardly more</u>
<u n="199" who="S0520">that is like you know where what was it? a web quote or was it a phone quote?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it it's like a lot of it's sort of an agency</u>
<u n="201" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0521">and you you tell the agency what you want to ask for and they distribute it to all of their</u>
<u n="203" who="S0520">oh yeah yeah like a compare dot com almost</u>
<u n="204" who="S0521">and then each each one individually sends in a quote</u>
<u n="205" who="S0520">ah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0521">I've got three for the piano and they're all between four and five hundred</u>
<u n="207" who="S0520">well that must be the case then</u>
<u n="208" who="S0521"><trunc>pro</trunc> if if they do offer a professional service</u>
<u n="209" who="S0520" trans="overlap">if they understood the</u>
<u n="210" who="S0521">and store it in an air-conditioned room then I would</u>
<u n="211" who="S0520">agreed take that out of the equation and then get a good deal on the whole</u>
<u n="212" who="S0521" trans="overlap">prefer that I'd prefer to have that and then take the the best offer for the rest</u>
<u n="213" who="S0520">mm and what else do you have <trunc>st</trunc> in storage the sofas and mattresses beds books</u>
<u n="214" who="S0521" trans="overlap">bookcases</u>
<u n="215" who="S0520">yeah nothing</u>
<u n="216" who="S0521">bedside tables coffee tables</u>
<u n="217" who="S0520">are you going to bring the big coffee table here mum?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0521" trans="overlap">everything except the kitchen really</u>
<u n="219" who="S0520">the one the the main one no it's too big</u>
<u n="220" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="221" who="S0521" trans="overlap">you're thinking of bringing the big one here are you?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="223" who="S0521">no</u>
<u n="224" who="S0520">would be a bit dominating</u>
<u n="225" who="S0519">the little</u>
<u n="226" who="S0521" trans="overlap">dining table dining chairs</u>
<u n="227" who="S0519">the little one the erm one from the gallery is like these sort of oak colour</u>
<u n="228" who="S0520">oh yeah yeah I know what you mean mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0519">and erm the little oak</u>
<u n="230" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah the</u>
<u n="231" who="S0519"><trunc>te</trunc> television table quite a lot of the pictures we may as well hang them here even if we took the others later erm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0520">mm alongside the blobby man there</u>
<u n="233" who="S0519">the blobby tree</u>
<u n="234" who="S0520">Mr Blobby</u>
<u n="235" who="S0519">okay I'll just tell you the erm description of this one not the price situated in a highly sought after location a beautifully presented and extensive I haven't looked at it yet detached family home with character and charm throughout</u>
<u n="236" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0519">landscape private gardens paddocks and stables</u>
<u n="238" who="S0520">paddocks everyone needs a paddock</u>
<u n="239" who="S0521">best buy a few horses</u>
<u n="240" who="S0519">double garage studio and home office</u>
<u n="241" who="S0520">love</u>
<u n="242" who="S0519"><anon type="place"/> is a hamlet with two public houses</u>
<u n="243" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's basically you and the pub</u>
<u n="244" who="S0519">situated within three miles of <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/>'s nice</u>
<u n="245" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I'm shocked how much this pub features in our reckoning</u>
<u n="246" who="S0519">seven miles of <anon type="place"/> and fourteen miles of <anon type="place"/> the award winning village of <anon type="place"/> is renowned for its <trunc>hi</trunc> historic high street which is located blah <pause dur="short"/> erm so I'm just mentioning and that's six nine nine <trunc>n</trunc><trunc>n</trunc><trunc>n</trunc>nine nine nine nine</u>
<u n="247" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I would prefer not to have a paddock actually</u>
<u n="248" who="S0519">so would I</u>
<u n="249" who="S0520">what is the paddock it's just a field</u>
<u n="250" who="S0521">a field for a horse</u>
<u n="251" who="S0520">yeah but it's just a field that you could you know trot about in</u>
<u n="252" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0520">it's just land isn't it?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0521">turn it into a cricket pitch</u>
<u n="255" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you could you could build on it yeah a tennis court of something <vocal desc="laugh"/> you don't have to have a horse on it is what I'm saying luckily you could have one but you</u>
<u n="256" who="S0521" trans="overlap">is that six ninety-nine?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0520">six ninety-nine nine fifty</u>
<u n="259" who="S0521"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0520">how many bedrooms? four</u>
<u n="261" who="S0519">four</u>
<u n="262" who="S0520">four's what you need isn't it? you don't want to be swimming about in a big house either</u>
<u n="263" who="S0519">this website is really awkward to use on an I-device</u>
<u n="264" who="S0520">yeah I would def go with the computer</u>
<u n="265" who="S0521">if you insist on leaving your Ipad in the</u>
<u n="266" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0520">where did you leave it?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0521"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0520">oh mum</u>
<u n="270" who="S0521">least you assume that's where you left it</u>
<u n="271" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0519">I know that's where I left it <pause dur="short"/> I could probably tell you where in the house</u>
<u n="273" who="S0520">I find browsing on the phone is really frustrating</u>
<u n="274" who="S0521" trans="overlap">have you have you got Find Me on your er</u>
<u n="275" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0521">have you got Find Me on your Iphone?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0520">yeah you've got to get the app it beep what</u>
<u n="278" who="S0521" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0519">it looks quite characterful</u>
<u n="280" who="S0520">this SOS signal <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0519">it could be erm a bang your head on the roof kind of house</u>
<u n="282" who="S0520">oh no hate that low beams</u>
<u n="283" who="S0521">why? two</u>
<u n="284" who="S0519">low beams</u>
<u n="285" who="S0520">pokey low beams</u>
<u n="286" who="S0519">we just need somebody to hire the paddock from us that's what we need</u>
<u n="287" who="S0521">oh it's a business opportunity</u>
<u n="288" who="S0519">the conservatory is gross how can you do that to a beautiful house</u>
<u n="289" who="S0521">paddock for hire</u>
<u n="290" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0521">competitive rates</u>
<u n="292" who="S0519">it's a bit sort of box like</u>
<u n="293" who="S0521">bring your own horse</u>
<u n="294" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> horse is not provided well mum could take up horse riding get some wellies</u>
<u n="295" who="S0521" trans="overlap">do is your area of your catchment area Cheshire et al still?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0519">no I I this is just my erm my original square that they send me houses every now and again</u>
<u n="297" who="S0521" trans="overlap">but remind me what the square is</u>
<u n="298" who="S0519">south er north Shropshire south Cheshire</u>
<u n="299" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0521">oh okay</u>
<u n="301" who="S0519">and you know really it's out of date now cos it went up to eight nine five</u>
<u n="302" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mum was <trunc>os</trunc>optimistic</u>
<u n="303" who="S0521" trans="overlap">you're very aspirational aren't you?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0520">well yeah you don't want to be looking at houses that far above your budget cos it'll be depressing</u>
<u n="305" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no but at the time when I</u>
<u n="306" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you didn't know</u>
<u n="307" who="S0519">I didn't know any of this</u>
<u n="308" who="S0520">it was just wishful thinking</u>
<u n="309" who="S0519">we just had a plan</u>
<u n="310" who="S0520">and why not</u>
<u n="311" who="S0519"><anon type="place"/> so now we just zoom there</u>
<u n="312" who="S0521" trans="overlap">where is it? tell me where it is is it near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0519">it's near to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0519">it's very characterful I'm not sure I like the look of the general house oh bloody A51</u>
<u n="316" who="S0521" trans="overlap"><unclear/> ah it's on a main road</u>
<u n="317" who="S0519" trans="overlap">tell me it's not on the A51?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0521">A51 is Whitchurch</u>
<u n="319" who="S0519">nobody's mentioned the A51 so far</u>
<u n="320" who="S0520">yeah they don't tend to this house is conveniently situated</u>
<u n="321" who="S0519">on the A51</u>
<u n="322" who="S0520">on a major road</u>
<u n="323" who="S0521">you can actually see the M6 from the bedroom window</u>
<u n="324" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0520">sometimes you do</u>
<u n="326" who="S0519">highly sought after location cheek of it</u>
<u n="327" who="S0520">well it probably is a highly sought after location I mean it's good if you're communising to be on the A like near a big road isn't it?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no you don't nobody calls the A51 highly desirable</u>
<u n="329" who="S0520">is it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0519">street view is not available that's cos they couldn't stand on the A51 cos the traffic was whizzing by</u>
<u n="331" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="332" who="S0519">wondered why it was looking so nice</u>
<u n="333" who="S0520">is it literally on the road?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0519">it doesn't say so I'll keep going and just get the description of how to get there and it says go down the A51 and Bob'is your uncle</u>
<u n="335" who="S0520">you don't need a</u>
<u n="336" who="S0521" trans="overlap">reminds me of that survey that we had for the for our house and they the comment was erm the gutters were visually inspected from the ground and were found to be satisfactory</u>
<u n="337" who="S0520">what does that mean?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0519">with binoculars it said</u>
<u n="339" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0521">so how how much that actually tells you about the state of the gutters I'm not sure</u>
<u n="341" who="S0520">not a lot mm I personally would hate to be able to hear a road from my house</u>
<u n="342" who="S0519" trans="overlap">me too</u>
<u n="343" who="S0521">yes</u>
<u n="344" who="S0520">that I was retired that is one of the nicest things about this house</u>
<u n="345" who="S0521">we're quite strong on the road noise agreement is there</u>
<u n="346" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's the that is the</u>
<u n="347" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it's so unsettling</u>
<u n="348" who="S0519">the one thing I won't I <trunc>ha</trunc> it devalued our house for me</u>
<u n="349" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0519">in two ways the garden it was too cold but the garden it wasn't enjoyable any more</u>
<u n="351" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0521">there's a slight catch twenty-two of course here</u>
<u n="353" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0521">in order to get to a house you need a road</u>
<u n="355" who="S0519">you need a road</u>
<u n="356" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no there's a road coming to this house as well but do you ever here a road noise?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0519">yeah you here the</u>
<u n="358" who="S0520">you hear the odd tractor you hear more cows that you do anything else I mean that's what I'm saying you can't here the A sixty what have you whatever it is there</u>
<u n="359" who="S0521" trans="overlap">no that's true <unclear/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0520">A66 is it?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0521">A66 yes that's right</u>
<u n="362" who="S0520">erm you know that road noise it's fine even if it's on a little road</u>
<u n="363" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0520">you know that there's occasionally a car trundling along you just don't want that <vocal desc="misc"/> you know like that constant</u>
<u n="365" who="S0521" trans="overlap">well okay we're we're we're quite quite erm we're unanimous aren't we?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0521">unanimous</u>
<u n="368" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0521">about the road noise</u>
<u n="371" who="S0519">absolutely</u>
<u n="372" who="S0520">that's erm disturbing the peace isn't it? or water some I mean in a completely different way running water</u>
<u n="373" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah it's an interesting one that what about water?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0520">it's slightly different</u>
<u n="375" who="S0521" trans="overlap">would that be soothing or disturbing</u>
<u n="376" who="S0520">well some people really like it but I I think to live there</u>
<u n="377" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I wouldn't like rushing water I think that's <trunc>t</trunc> it's too frantic</u>
<u n="378" who="S0520" trans="overlap">on a river yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0521">babbling brooks?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0519">erm a</u>
<u n="381" who="S0520">a little brook</u>
<u n="382" who="S0519">a a tiny little brook would be gorgeous</u>
<u n="383" who="S0521">slight babbler</u>
<u n="384" who="S0519">a little mini babble</u>
<u n="385" who="S0520">mini babbler <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0519">but not a raging torrent</u>
<u n="387" who="S0520">I don't like being too close to the sea for that reason</u>
<u n="388" who="S0521">ah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0519">noisy</u>
<u n="390" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I find it difficult to sleep</u>
<u n="391" who="S0521">the sea well they they give they give our tapes of the sea to relax you</u>
<u n="392" who="S0520">I know it's funny well some people really like it but I find if it's constant shh shh shh it's just slightly a restless noise</u>
<u n="393" who="S0521">mm I know what you mean</u>
<u n="394" who="S0520">but I mean some people yeah they they that's their dream isn't it? there's that house that's on the Eden erm next to <anon type="place"/> Caves that's <trunc>li</trunc> on that</u>
<u n="395" who="S0521">yes</u>
<u n="396" who="S0520">dam and</u>
<u n="397" who="S0519">yes I couldn't cope with that</u>
<u n="398" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that would be much too</u>
<u n="399" who="S0521">the weir</u>
<u n="400" who="S0520">er the weir yeah and it's a lovely looking house and I've seen the family erm I don't think they live there but they come there and erm I've always thought erm it must be really hard to sleep there cos it's quite a strong like it's a bit of a waterfall isn't it?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="402" who="S0519">so that was looking quite interesting until I realised in was on the A51</u>
<u n="403" who="S0520">well you don't know that you could you should ask</u>
<u n="404" who="S0519">I'm pretty sure</u>
<u n="405" who="S0521" trans="overlap">have you established that it's on the A51</u>
<u n="406" who="S0519">I've looked at the view on a map</u>
<u n="407" who="S0521">and</u>
<u n="408" who="S0519">and</u>
<u n="409" who="S0520">that little pin</u>
<u n="410" who="S0519">the pin is on the A51</u>
<u n="411" who="S0521">is that yellow thing the A51?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="413" who="S0521">oh my god</u>
<u n="414" who="S0519">and so you can zoom in</u>
<u n="415" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0519">and you get tiny little roads then showing</u>
<u n="417" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0519">but not for this house it's gets as if it's further and further away from the A51 there's no road to it</u>
<u n="419" who="S0521" trans="overlap">oh my God</u>
<u n="420" who="S0519">so it's on the A51</u>
<u n="421" who="S0521">oh oh</u>
<u n="422" who="S0520">not cool</u>
<u n="423" who="S0519">so that's nay good</u>
<u n="424" who="S0521">dad was showing me the pics from your vacation</u>
<u n="425" who="S0519">yes and I he was me too and it they're lovely and but we have to remember to please turn the setting from two photos to every click</u>
<u n="426" who="S0520">is that what it's doing?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0519">yeah so we it then if you've taken three of the same thing you have to watch it six times</u>
<u n="428" who="S0521" trans="overlap">get six</u>
<u n="429" who="S0520">yeah there was some repetition</u>
<u n="430" who="S0519">zooming in and out</u>
<u n="431" who="S0520">but I was surprised by the Shropshire photos it was really really pretty</u>
<u n="432" who="S0519">it's beautiful isn't it?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0520">mm all the purple heather and</u>
<u n="434" who="S0519">but that's <trunc>so</trunc> a bit south</u>
<u n="435" who="S0520">too far south</u>
<u n="436" who="S0521" trans="overlap">that was south</u>
<u n="437" who="S0519" trans="overlap">from where we would need to live</u>
<u n="438" who="S0520">yeah that doesn't make sense does it?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0521" trans="overlap">north Shropshire</u>
<u n="440" who="S0520">well it makes sense it's fine</u>
<u n="441" who="S0519">the price now makes sense here six nine nine nine fifty</u>
<u n="442" who="S0521">six nine nine fifty brackets A51</u>
<u n="443" who="S0520">would be eight fifty</u>
<u n="444" who="S0521">I wonder whether it makes that much difference</u>
<u n="445" who="S0520">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0519" trans="overlap">oh absolutely huge the number of times you watch a property programme it's huge</u>
<u n="447" who="S0520">is it?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0519">and they say well I'd really like this house but in a different setting</u>
<u n="449" who="S0520" trans="overlap">the road thing is a big deal move it mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0519">and they they just say and then it wouldn't be in your budget</u>
<u n="451" who="S0520">yeah people have to be realistic don't they?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0521">oh my god</u>
<u n="453" who="S0519">it's a huge</u>
<u n="454" who="S0521">another catch twenty-two</u>
<u n="455" who="S0519">that'd be another hundred thou on top if it wasn't on the A51</u>
<u n="456" who="S0520">a hundred thousand maybe not that much</u>
<u n="457" who="S0519">fifty thousand then big it's big</u>
<u n="458" who="S0520">you pay a premium for good location for sure don't you?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah location is</u>
<u n="460" who="S0520">location location location</u>
<u n="461" who="S0519">mm no it looked quite nice</u>
<u n="462" who="S0520">and I mean people who want to move to the countryside it's precisely what they don't want is to hear a road</u>
<u n="463" who="S0519">hear a road</u>
<u n="464" who="S0521">a lot of low flying beams</u>
<u n="465" who="S0520">I don't like low flying beams</u>
<u n="466" who="S0521">have you got to care for my state of my head?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0520">I really don't I just it's so not fun</u>
<u n="468" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="469" who="S0520">to be ducking and I hit my head all over the place in this house</u>
<u n="470" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no I agree</u>
<u n="471" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it is romantic it's romantic having beams everywhere</u>
<u n="472" who="S0520">mm briefly</u>
<u n="473" who="S0521" trans="overlap">but it's</u>
<u n="474" who="S0520">I don't necessarily like how it looks if they're too if it's too beamy either like there's an ideal beam ratio <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0519">no the the a little bit of beamage is nice</u>
<u n="476" who="S0520" trans="overlap">a little bit of beamage but you know there's some places are a bit overboard aren't they?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0521">then you have the faux beams which are just added for show</u>
<u n="478" who="S0519" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="479" who="S0520">no what's that about?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0519" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0521">modern modern editions to make it look supposedly older</u>
<u n="482" who="S0519"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> suggested we had somebody in to erm look at at whether the cross beam in the room upstairs is structural</u>
<u n="483" who="S0520" trans="overlap">this room</u>
<u n="484" who="S0521">he's got a thing about that beam hasn't he?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0519">yeah but it does it goes mean there's quite a bit of that room is half is awkward at to say the very least</u>
<u n="487" who="S0521">you know when they came they moved the bed</u>
<u n="488" who="S0520" trans="overlap">this room or that one?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0521">your room</u>
<u n="490" who="S0520">oh that one yeah you're right it's in a quite an annoying location isn't it?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0521">when they came they moved the bed to the opposite end of the room</u>
<u n="493" who="S0519">no they slept at the opposite end of the bed they couldn't be bothered to move it I don't think</u>
<u n="494" who="S0520">what because of the beam?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0519">they didn't want to be under it</u>
<u n="496" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it's not that threatening is it?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0519">some <trunc>pe</trunc> mm</u>
<u n="498" who="S0520">bit claustrophobic</u>
<u n="499" who="S0519">yeah sleeping under it</u>
<u n="500" who="S0520">I don't notice it at all when I sleep</u>
<u n="501" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I don't notice it but the be where you are you couldn't have two people one each side of the beam you feel like a bit of a barrier</u>
<u n="502" who="S0520" trans="overlap">hallo <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I guess so erm but</u>
<u n="503" who="S0519">but he's right you could</u>
<u n="504" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah it's worth asking</u>
<u n="505" who="S0519">if it's not structural or if there's a</u>
<u n="506" who="S0520">why would it not be structural why would it be there otherwise?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0521">they just put it there for show</u>
<u n="508" who="S0519">no it it was how how it was</u>
<u n="509" who="S0520" trans="overlap">well it's virtually through the middle of the room though isn't it? it's not like near the ceiling it's kind of chest height</u>
<u n="510" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no but but it's <trunc>po</trunc> erm it does go to the wall and onto the bricks but it it doesn't go further</u>
<u n="511" who="S0520">how do you know</u>
<u n="512" who="S0519">well because it doesn't come out the other side</u>
<u n="513" who="S0520">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0519">of the of the wall into the hall into the landing</u>
<u n="515" who="S0520">mm that's true that's true</u>
<u n="516" who="S0519">and so therefore if it's structural it's structural in resting on that wall</u>
<u n="517" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0519">which goes up from the kitchen</u>
<u n="519" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0519">so that must be maybe then a load-bearing wall</u>
<u n="522" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0519">maybe they all are in this house and if and if that's true then maybe you can't do anything about it but it's possible you could have it erm tied in some other way with like a metal tie higher up and take the beam out or something like that</u>
<u n="524" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0519">you don't know but you could ask a <trunc>stru</trunc><trunc>tru</trunc>al engineer to look at it couldn't you?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0521">a Shropshire engineer</u>
<u n="527" who="S0520">a shrupshrual engineer</u>
<u n="528" who="S0519">a ble blah engineer</u>
<u n="529" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0521">well yeah I don't know that's er I'm not sure that's</u>
<u n="531" who="S0520">I mean if you were living here I'd consider it</u>
<u n="532" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="533" who="S0521">this is our little country cottage you know</u>
<u n="534" who="S0519">I know I know I know</u>
<u n="535" who="S0520">got to have some really irritating</u>
<u n="536" who="S0519" trans="overlap">the toilet up there is the next major thing</u>
<u n="537" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0520">I think you've got I think the next major thing is replacing this hideous wall paper</u>
<u n="539" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="540" who="S0520">the seventies theme</u>
<u n="541" who="S0519">the seventies diamond</u>
<u n="542" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0519"><unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0521">seventies paper</u>
<u n="545" who="S0520">seventies is back in fashion but</u>
<u n="546" who="S0519">who would have dreamt of putting this on here?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0520" trans="overlap">only the good parts of it well no one with taste <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0519">painting out the flowers is also an important step</u>
<u n="549" who="S0520">the bedroom flowers?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0519">somewhat</u>
<u n="553" who="S0520">agreed yeah and the skirting I mean now that you mention it now that you've mentioned it I agree with you the skirting would <trunc>idea</trunc> be ideally be white in here</u>
<u n="554" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="555" who="S0520">white skirting and white erm window sills</u>
<u n="556" who="S0519">could work in here</u>
<u n="557" who="S0520">yeah I think so too</u>
<u n="558" who="S0521">erm should I put Harry on?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0521">I'm sure you want to listen to Harry</u>
<u n="561" who="S0520">I'll turn the thingybob off</u>
<u n="562" who="S0519">ah ha ha have you been doing that all that time</u>
<u n="563" who="S0520">yeah got an hour of us babbling on about stuff now</u>
<u n="564" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0520">I have to erm fill in a form which is saying roughly the content of the recording and erm who you are in relation to me not er specifically but in general categories and like indicating who the order of speech and who the people are that's <event desc="music"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's good isn't he <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0521">listen out for the piano here</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
