<text id="SXJW">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:41:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-03-15</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0281 S0355</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker’s home, Brighton.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>news items, food, drinking</topics>
		<activity>friends talking about recent news and present personal situation.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0355">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hove, Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hove, Sussex</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>64 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Business Owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0281">bon appetite old boy</u>
<u n="2" who="S0355">thank you so did you manage to download your other conversations?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0281">upload? yeah I did yeah mm but then I had to upload it to the</u>
<u n="4" who="S0355" trans="overlap">what's what's the difference between downloading and uploading?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0281">well downloading is when you get something from the internet and download it to your computer or</u>
<u n="6" who="S0355" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0281">whatever it is your phone or and uploading is when you've got you've produced something and you you give it to somebody else</u>
<u n="8" who="S0355">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0281">or put it up for somebody else</u>
<u n="10" who="S0355">okay</u>
<u n="11" who="S0281">but the problem I had was that when I did it before my well basically <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> told me how to do it and I wrote it down <pause dur="short"/> but when I got my new computer I found although I didn't realise at the time that the problem was that my phone was not synced or synchronised into my new computer so it was basically just a a question of going to a I think it was settings and just click on something that says synchronise your phone to this computer but the guy had spent two hours trying to figure it out how to do it and didn't didn't know that you know really he was supposed to be a computer expert but we spent all that afternoon you know a couple of hours over two hours trying to figure out how to do it and he downloaded <trunc>I</trunc>Itunes and all the rest of it which I didn't need and didn't want and then had to get rid of it so in the end so I went to Apple shop on the other day on Friday and he said yeah easy enough bom bom bom bom bom <pause dur="short"/> and then I came home and my phone was now synced is now synced to my computer and any any future times I just I put the recordings in and and I can <trunc>acc</trunc> them straight away access them straight away <pause dur="short"/> you know it's like most things isn't it? easy when you know how</u>
<u n="12" who="S0355">gosh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0355">so how many conversations have you recorded this week?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0281">none this month none that's why I want to get a couple done yeah <pause dur="long"/> and I only did a couple of small ones last month <pause dur="short"/> it's only twelve quid but better than nothing <pause dur="short"/> they said that they they planned to continue it on through two thousand and fifteen I thought they were going to finish it June maybe they haven't got enough? <pause dur="short"/> I'd have thought there'd be more people doing it than there are</u>
<u n="16" who="S0355">have you seen America's reaction to us joining the Chinese bank?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0355">what did you make of that?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0281">it sounds a bit like sour grapes you know that they're either miffed that they didn't do it or <pause dur="short"/> think it's it's not on to support you know because of the the special relationship we have with America we're not really supposed to do that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>cha</trunc> erm China called it childish <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but I think America's feeling increasing increasingly threatened by China <pause dur="short"/> not militarily but certainly economically indeed it's been predicted that by twenty thirty China will have overtaken America as the leading economic power in the world what do you think about it?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<u n="20" who="S0355">yes I can see what you're saying <pause dur="short"/> and I tend to agree with you <pause dur="long"/> is China building <pause dur="short"/> a a fleet isn't it? it's commissioned several war ships</u>
<u n="21" who="S0281">have they?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0355">apparently so</u>
<u n="23" who="S0281">it wouldn't surprise me <pause dur="short"/> aircraft carriers I would've thought</u>
<u n="24" who="S0355">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="25" who="S0281">well they've got all those territorial claims haven't they? in South East Asia <pause dur="short"/> those like small island or islands that are disputed with Japan <pause dur="short"/> and there's another dispute going on with the Philippines <pause dur="short"/> it's all about mineral rights really under the sea <pause dur="long"/> mm doesn't look good <pause dur="long"/> and it's as you were saying before <pause dur="short"/> it's man's greed they always want more I suppose if you've got an ever increasing population you've got to plan for it they think they need more natural resources <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> what time are you going to the funeral tomorrow?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0355">going to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s erm I'm arriving there at eleven <pause dur="short"/> and I'm going by bus to his</u>
<u n="27" who="S0281">right where does he live?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0355">in the upper <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="29" who="S0281">it's going to take up most of the day isn't it? all the day</u>
<u n="30" who="S0355"><unclear>oh it shall</unclear> yes yes <pause dur="short"/> I don't do rushing here and there <pause dur="long"/> and then there might be some nice crumpet there you never know</u>
<u n="31" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="32" who="S0355">it's always nice to get them emotional and with their hearts open isn't it? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0281">won't you be in the same ilk?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0355">I shall be the pop star of the <pause dur="short"/> of the funeral I'm doing the eulogy <pause dur="short"/> so I'll obviously attract some groupies</u>
<u n="35" who="S0281">quite rightly too <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> is it being held in a church the ceremony? was she <trunc>relig</trunc>religious?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0355">sorry?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0281">was she religious?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0355">she got drunk religiously</u>
<u n="39" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="short"/> she had alcoholic constipation she couldn't pass a pub</u>
<u n="41" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> very good</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="42" who="S0355">yeah but I I often wondered how she <pause dur="short"/> managed to live the years that she lived</u>
<u n="43" who="S0281">how old was she?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0355">fifty-seven <pause dur="short"/> and er she was an alcoholic bless her but I suspect that that she had a lot of things wrong with her she did she did have a lot of things wrong with her</u>
<u n="45" who="S0281">do you agree with?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0355">euthanasia? yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0281">I was gonna say the lyrics better to burn out than to fade away</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="48" who="S0355">not at the age of sixty-four no</u>
<u n="49" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> when we were young we'd always sing along to the Who's lyrics <shift new="singing"/> hope I die before I get old <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0355">yeah there you go</u>
<u n="51" who="S0281">and then you get old <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes the Who's lyrics hey? they were good weren't they the Who? the pop group the Who</u>
<u n="53" who="S0281">excellent yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> are you not going to help? <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> are you not going to have another one?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0355">I'll let that go down</u>
<u n="55" who="S0281">yeah me too <pause dur="short"/> no that will do me I had bread yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0355"><unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0281">oh well <pause dur="short"/> ah and erm so there's that there's Rolf Harris losing his MBE or CBE and er for kiddy fiddling <pause dur="short"/> and Cliff Richard moving to Barbados</u>
<u n="58" who="S0355">is he?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0281">yeah staying there full time he wants to take</u>
<u n="60" who="S0355" trans="overlap">is there no extradition treaty there?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0281">I don't know about the extradition treaty but he's</u>
<u n="62" who="S0355">there should be it's an ex colony</u>
<u n="63" who="S0281">yes <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> hey I'm going to Las <shift new="normal"/> no that's not it <shift new="singing"/> going to Barbados <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0355">erm so</u>
<u n="65" who="S0281">I expect so many of these stories are gonna come out when he dies</u>
<u n="66" who="S0355">are they?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0281">well I imagine so</u>
<u n="68" who="S0355">you think so <pause dur="short"/> well it makes a mockery of of the system doesn't it? the queen's been giving all these honours to people like Jimmy Saville Archer Jeffery Archer he should have been stripped of his honours he went to prison how can you be a Lord and go to prison and keep your honours?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0281">what was he done for?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0355">lying in court</u>
<u n="71" who="S0281">about?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0355">he's lied he's always lied Jeffrey Archer's always been a liar</u>
<u n="73" who="S0281">financial skulduggery</u>
<u n="74" who="S0355">I don't know he's lied about his qualifications that he's got he's lied about his experience that he's had he's a lying pig <pause dur="short"/> and he's a Tory lying pig</u>
<u n="75" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0355">mm and what else has been in the news <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this week?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0355">what's caught your attention <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0281">not a lot</u>
<u n="80" who="S0355">no? you haven't been watching the news?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0281">not much no <pause dur="short"/> can't remember what was on the news today that's how much effect it had on me</u>
<u n="82" who="S0355">I thought it was one of your favourite topics</u>
<u n="83" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> depends on your mind set I suppose if your mind's totally obsessed with one's own problems you just tend to concentrate on others</u>
<u n="84" who="S0355">right <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> ah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0281">constant pain is it?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0355">constant never goes away I can get comfy in bed and I can go to sleep and then I wake in the night and it's fucking bad <pause dur="short"/> bastard innit? I think that's the answer lose weight</u>
<u n="87" who="S0281">do you want me to try and help you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0355">erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0281">support you</u>
<u n="90" who="S0355">thank you yeah I don't know how but you know really I need a cook</u>
<u n="91" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0355">oh dear</u>
<u n="93" who="S0281">can't supply that one</u>
<u n="94" who="S0355">no there you go</u>
<u n="95" who="S0281">but I imagine there are two areas in quantity and what you eat isn't it?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0355">no it's that's it isn't it? absolutely absolutely no doubt absolutely I don't know why my nails are so filthy I don't know what I've been doing to get my nails so filthy? it must have been that job I did yesterday I need to clip my nails always need clipping and cleaning always they seem to grow</u>
<u n="97" who="S0281">clip round the bloody ear</u>
<u n="98" who="S0355">seem to grow overnight</u>
<u n="99" who="S0281">apparently they still grow when we're dead</u>
<u n="100" who="S0355">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but would that be after cremation or?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> have you got any preference? you're going to be buried aren't you? next to your father</u>
<u n="102" who="S0355">yeah but in a box of ashes if they'd allow me</u>
<u n="103" who="S0281">oh really?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0355">to put those in the grave yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's in the headstone for my name <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0281">I suppose once you're gone it doesn't really make much difference does it</u>
<u n="106" who="S0355">not really <pause dur="short"/> it's for the living</u>
<u n="107" who="S0281">yeah that's right <pause dur="long"/> well I'm going to go and get myself a little bit more veg</u>
<u n="108" who="S0355">yeah go for it mate do it do it do it</u>
<u n="109" who="S0281">won't be a mo</u>
<u n="110" who="S0355">great <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="0281 leaves"/>
<event desc="0355 leaves"/>
<u n="111" who="S0281">right there we go obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has changed his mind having gone off with his plate <pause dur="short"/> so much for cutting down on the amount <pause dur="short"/> does talking to yourself constitute a conversation? <pause dur="long"/> don't worry he'll be back in a minute <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0355">curry sauce and chips that's what I've got curry sauce and chips <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="long"/> so how does how does that Chinese cooking and preparation of the vegetable differ from the preparation erm erm?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0281">well it tends to be all pretty much the same in terms of <pause dur="short"/> cooking nearly everything's fried</u>
<u n="114" who="S0355">in China?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0355">right what like stir fried with a very small amount of oil isn't it?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0281">erm probably <pause dur="short"/> I think traditionally there was being not obese was in <trunc>con</trunc> stark contrast to Westerners but they are starting to to now because of like everybody else they eat masses of erm fast food especially the kids</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="118" who="S0355">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0281">they're following the West</u>
<u n="120" who="S0355">really?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0281" trans="overlap">for good and for bad <pause dur="short"/> well mostly bad I suppose depending on your point of view</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="122" who="S0355">Mother's Day today do they have that in China?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0281">oh yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0355">oh what same day?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0281">I presume so</u>
<u n="126" who="S0355">so it's the end of their New Year now</u>
<u n="127" who="S0281">yeah it's finished everyone is back school is back to back to work</u>
<u n="128" who="S0355">when did when does that finish?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0281">I think erm half way through February</u>
<u n="130" who="S0355">oh right</u>
<u n="131" who="S0281">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went back to school this week so maybe I don't know maybe <pause dur="short"/> most of February so <pause dur="long"/> I'm certainly glad I missed that those bloody fireworks are just incessant and it builds up every day gets a little bit more until the big day and</u>
<u n="132" who="S0355">yes you're not a fan of celebration really are you?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0281">not really no</u>
<u n="134" who="S0355">no</u>
<u n="135" who="S0281">I think it's not the celebration of it that I don't really enjoy I certainly like celebrating as much as anybody but it's the organised celebrations that I I don't like cos <trunc>ever</trunc> well usually everybody is expected to behave in a prescribed manner</u>
<u n="136" who="S0355">which is?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0281">well you have to try and maintain harmony and er <pause dur="short"/> happiness even though you know like as in the West at Christmas time most family feuds'll rekindle themselves don't they at Christmas? so <pause dur="short"/> I think to a certain extent it happens in China as well but not to such a great extent because they don't base all their celebrations on alcohol like we do <pause dur="short"/> and they're also the family value system is they they try and maintain the this thing about harmony which is in my way of thinking just a façade</u>
<u n="138" who="S0355">well yeah it's it's just that's not value that you you consider practising yourself?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0281">well if it I I think that if you're going to do this it should be done as much as you can nearly every day of the year not just in one time of year it's like Christmas</u>
<u n="140" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="141" who="S0281">peace and and love and goodwill for men why is it just at Christmas?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah yeah why is it Christmas? yeah <pause dur="short"/> sure <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0281">but bloody fireworks drive me mad</u>
<u n="144" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="145" who="S0281">cos you can't</u>
<u n="146" who="S0355" trans="overlap">is it the noise you can't stand?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0281">yeah mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="149" who="S0281">amazing peaceful in <anon type="place"/> even where we are in the centre of <anon type="place"/> so quiet</u>
<u n="150" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we're not in the centre really are we? we're not in the <anon type="place"/> or anywhere like that that's the sort of</u>
<u n="151" who="S0281">well I'd say off <anon type="place"/> road's pretty central</u>
<u n="152" who="S0355">yeah I suppose you're right yeah that's true</u>
<u n="153" who="S0281">eleven o'clock at night you can hear a pin drop outside</u>
<u n="154" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="155" who="S0281">in China my god everywhere's buzzing</u>
<u n="156" who="S0355">really? why why do they why do they keep going twenty-four hours do they?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0281">well not twenty-four hours but certainly into the early hours</u>
<u n="158" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0281">yeah they work amazingly hard generally the Chinese</u>
<u n="160" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="long"/> look at that fucking Great Wall they built look at that</u>
<u n="161" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0281">yeah well you can say the same about the Egyptians</u>
<u n="163" who="S0355">yeah and the Egyptians <pause dur="short"/> isis are going to demolish them aren't they? the pyramids</u>
<u n="164" who="S0281">are they?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0355">I think so</u>
<u n="166" who="S0281">they'll have a hard job how would you demolish a pyramid?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0355">dynamite</u>
<u n="168" who="S0281">size of those you'd have to have a hell of a lot of dynamite</u>
<u n="169" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0281">the size of them</u>
<u n="171" who="S0355">yeah Islamic state's going to demolish them</u>
<u n="172" who="S0281">ha</u>
<u n="173" who="S0355">there's no one guarding Tripoli no one's in Tripoli at the moment they can just walk straight in there there's no Americans or English you know defence there <pause dur="short"/> libya they can walk straight in can't they? are the pyramids in near Libya? well it's near Egypt isn't it? ah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0281">painful again?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0355">it's painful all the time</u>
<u n="176" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0355">every waking hour it's painful and probably painful in my sleep it's been going on for months and months now well it's it's it's getting worse and worse</u>
<u n="178" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well you need to start oh god</u>
<u n="179" who="S0355">I'm going to go to the doctor and say look this pain is getting worse and worse and worse</u>
<u n="180" who="S0281">of course when did it start getting worse?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0355">well it gets worse all the time I thought it would go away I thought I had pulled my shoulder it's been about ache or <pause dur="short"/> now it's spreading down my arm it's down into my shoulder I can hardly move it you can see how much I can move it if this arm does the same I'm fucked seriously fucked <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="182" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">take your plates for you?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0355">yes thank you very much</u>
<u n="184" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">thank you <pause dur="short"/> that's great thank you</u>
<u n="185" who="S0355">there you go thank you</u>
<u n="186" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">thank you</u>
<u n="187" who="S0355">ah fuck me <pause dur="long"/> yeah we'll go and see the doctor see the doctor Tuesday</u>
<u n="188" who="S0281">I was going to say mate you can't carry on just</u>
<u n="189" who="S0355">I can't I thought I'd get over it I can't it's getting worse and fucking worse and worse I had to put in some of that gel which was good it's like a chilling gel something like that deep heat or something you know it seems to work</u>
<u n="190" who="S0281">why don't you go tomorrow morning?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0355">well I suppose I could really yeah I suppose I could but I want to wash I want to get myself prepared I've got to get to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s by eleven which means getting out the front door by ten</u>
<u n="192" who="S0281">that's alright you have to be there at half past eight don't you? you're up usually by then</u>
<u n="193" who="S0355">yeah but it's a rush it's <unclear/> I just want to get up slowly wash dress take my time focus prepare myself for a speech a eulogy it may albeit short and erm just rumble off the road get on the bus get to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="194" who="S0281">well it's not exactly to look forward to is it?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0355">well I quite it's for the living isn't it? funerals are for the living they're not for the dead</u>
<u n="196" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="197" who="S0355">er although having said that you don't know you don't know how long</u>
<u n="198" who="S0281">has she got much family?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0355">a sister</u>
<u n="200" who="S0281">is that it?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0355">as far as I'm aware yeah <pause dur="short"/> some people don't have that but she didn't talk to her sister for a long time she certainly didn't tell her she was dying so erm er her sister was a bit miffed and a bit peeved by her erm then <pause dur="long"/> hopefully she'll get over it <pause dur="short"/> so you know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> an alcoholic why did she get swept away on it you know what was that all about? sad isn't it?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0281">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> don't they reckon that some is? I suppose most of it's erm in your DNA that some people are more prone to doing whatever than others</u>
<u n="203" who="S0355">yes yes I mean brief</u>
<u n="204" who="S0281"><unclear/> and suddenly I mean to a greater extent</u>
<u n="205" who="S0355">even if they have a pretty</u>
<u n="206" who="S0281">after after that we had our fair share of pints and booze in general and yet we never got addicted to it</u>
<u n="207" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well there is that there is that <pause dur="short"/> I suppose in my life I have been addicted to booze at various times I remember waking up in the morning and thinking I have to drink erm but</u>
<u n="208" who="S0281">it's a psychological dependence when you start <unclear/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0355" trans="overlap">but I think cos certainly at the end of the day I would just go and have a beer <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear/> you know one beer leads to another I could never just have a beer and feel chilled I'd have to have I'd have to get pissed <pause dur="short"/> and I and at the end when I drank I used to go out by myself go to the pub drink by myself to get pissed and you realise how how miserable that was you see I see other people who are drinkers who go there to drink to get pissed and it's very it's sad very insular to do that isn't it? it's very <pause dur="short"/> so erm yeah so but thankfully I'm not er I don't do that anymore er but I have periods when I when I get pissed very occasionally <pause dur="short"/> think but that that's only happened once in the last years and years I didn't you know years and years and years so er no I agree that there are there are things in your in your genes that can influence that erm you know if that's what they tell us but I think that there are things that er I think there are also psychological reasons why we drink as well</u>
<u n="210" who="S0281">of course</u>
<u n="211" who="S0355">and I don't think it's only just the one thing I think it's and I think you know if you look at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she went out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for a long time and you know I I he wasn't er he didn't treat women nicely erm so you think well she she accepted that but they did row they did have rows but she still went out with him being you know with his with his attitude and everything and I think well <vocal desc="laugh"/> she didn't have much self respect did she you know? erm neither did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> but er you know so I think I think people <pause dur="short"/> I drank for a to try and get some self respect in in a crazy way I mean in and the madness of it is is you when you drink you <trunc>los</trunc> the more you lose your self respect <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0355">it's madness isn't it? sort of weird psychology weird stuff</u>
<u n="214" who="S0281" trans="overlap">especially if you remember everything you did or said</u>
<u n="215" who="S0355">oh thank god I don't I mean I I yeah god terrible <trunc>dr</trunc>dreadful dreadful <pause dur="short"/> yeah well er you know <pause dur="short"/> I blame the society I was brought up in I blame it all for for everything bad that I've learnt I blame it for for giving a man the power sadist to beat a fucking six year old child you know if you that's what Jimmy Saville got put away for <vocal desc="laugh"/> well perhaps not beating but you know and they that was and there were people wanting to bring that back corporal punishment and what corporal punishment does is when you get beaten is it makes you hate the institution hate</u>
<u n="216" who="S0281">that's what the Second World War was</u>
<u n="217" who="S0355">what corporal punishment? <vocal desc="laugh"/> corporal Hitler</u>
<u n="218" who="S0281">corporal Hitler</u>
<u n="219" who="S0355">ah you know what was that all about? <pause dur="short"/> what made him do that? how was he treated as a kid? and I I think we should forgive him I think we should do national things to forgive him to feel sorry for him and to forgive him because if you keep hating something in an idea that's what you can do you keep on hating hating them don't you? just hating the live and er you know Christ came along and does does his thing saying er not to hate</u>
<u n="220" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0355">forgive them you know and er turn the other cheek blah blah blah and that's what you ought to do you ought to have a er national day where we forgive Hitler and see where it went wrong for him</u>
<u n="222" who="S0281" trans="overlap">that would be controversial</u>
<u n="223" who="S0355">well why do we accept hating him and retribution why do we make praise those things? that's in the new the Old Testament isn't it? vengeance is mine sayeth the Lord eye for an eye tooth for a oath well you know look look look where it got the Jews that philosophy</u>
<u n="224" who="S0281">blind and toothless</u>
<u n="225" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><unclear>and look</unclear> yeah here's my boy <vocal desc="laugh"/> well look at where it got them you know <pause dur="short"/> what if you inherit the earth but lose your soul?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0281">are you ready to</u>
<u n="227" who="S0355">forgive Hitler? yes</u>
<u n="228" who="S0281">go back?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0355">I am I forget Hitler I forgive you and I send you my love <pause dur="short"/> for he was a tortured soul <pause dur="long"/> yes I think we should go back and rub jelly and chocolate pudding on my arm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0281">nowhere else <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't turn turn it into</u>
<u n="231" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well your eyes lit up when you said that</u>
<u n="232" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well don't turn it into a perversion <vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="233" who="S0355">going to steal these napkins cos they make excellent <trunc>hand</trunc>handkerchiefs for me during the day <pause dur="short"/> have we finished recording?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0281">erm I think we are just about</u>
<u n="235" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="236" who="S0281">yes and here endeth the first lesson</u>
<u n="237" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="238" who="S0281">right let's mend our way <pause dur="short"/> any good films on tonight?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0355">there could be</u>
<u n="240" who="S0281">okay let's go</u>
<u n="241" who="S0355">I have a huge bag of porn <pause dur="short"/> have you seen that bag of porn that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gave me?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0355">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes on these flat decoration jobs and he finds all this gear like a bottle of gas and some fucking in the loft a bottle of gas some mad paddies had it up there you know they'd been on a welding gang <trunc>ga</trunc> or they'd nicked it and just stuffed it up there but er <pause dur="short"/> he ah he told me he said I found some porn the other day I mean it's bonkers stuff some of it's fucking nuts erm er erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like this one of them it's this I've got literally a bag full a fucking carrier bag full of porn anyway there's one in there that's eastern European woman huge fucking woman ugly fucking woman like that curly hair <pause dur="short"/> in this floral print dress wanking herself off <vocal desc="laugh"/> fucking unbelievable <pause dur="short"/> who the fuck watches this stuff you know? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0281">erm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0355">you've got to be really fucking well you could I suppose <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0281">yes just just up my street <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well okay let's get this show on the road shall we?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0355">right</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
