<text id="SXK4">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:29:13</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-12-31</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0585 S0587</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The Poacher (pub) in Gorse Covert, Warrington. </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics></topics>
		<activity>Best friends catching up (Part 2)  (ANON’s Mum comes in now and again but wasn’t formally part of the recordings…) </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0585">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Warrington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North West England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Warrington</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0587">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Warrington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Warringtonian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Warrington</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>Warrington (20 years) Lancaster 2.5 years)</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0585">so there's me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's why he's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and we call him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> we were say next to each other whilst we whilst we were playing this game and we both dislike the game so we were both like <pause dur="long"/> what are you doing?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0587">where's my <trunc>ph</trunc>phone?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0585">your phone? it's</u>
<u n="4" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0585">mm? I don't know what you're talking about <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were sat next to each other for a while I said why do you bring your own when you just like use mine? ha <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0587"><unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0585">idiot and erm oh god and</u>
<u n="8" who="S0587"><unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="9" who="S0585">and yeah and then and then we were like doing doing ones for each other and we were just like sat there like don't know what to say don't know what to say yeah who? <vocal desc="laugh"/> like what she we say you can't do it without a group of four cos there's too many sensitive people but you know</u>
<u n="10" who="S0587">like you</u>
<u n="11" who="S0585">like I know no cos I'm fine cos I'll I'll happily like if someone says something like that I'll happily like so whatever erm but I still prefer not to I still prefer not to know stuff just cos I prefer that sort of that life</u>
<u n="12" who="S0587">that life?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0585">yeah that life</u>
<u n="14" who="S0587">that's the life I choose to lead</u>
<u n="15" who="S0585">I just prefer I prefer it it's like like so me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got into an argument once and then behind my back <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said something to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like oh why is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> being so annoying about? oh no actually he said why is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> being so pathetic about it? and then erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came and told me and I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you don't just don't tell me cos I really don't care don't tell me cos it <trunc>on</trunc> it's only there it'll only there frustrate me now and so I were like don't don't like I understand what you're doing reporting back to me what people have said but I don't it doesn't help me in any way shape or form</u>
<u n="16" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0585">it just it's just not you know</u>
<u n="18" who="S0587">no</u>
<u n="19" who="S0585">do you need a tissue?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0587">no it's alright I coughed it out</u>
<u n="21" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0587">what? that's the first sneeze I coughed</u>
<u n="23" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0585">mm mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0587">are you taking them away from me?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0585">no I was putting them close close to me so I can just grab them</u>
<u n="28" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah away from me</u>
<u n="29" who="S0585">I I asked if you wanted one I can give you a whole pack if you want one</u>
<u n="30" who="S0587">no</u>
<u n="31" who="S0585">oh you</u>
<u n="32" who="S0587"><unclear/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0585">you're terrible <pause dur="long"/> but</u>
<u n="34" who="S0587"><shift new="singing"/> machine <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0585"><shift new="singing"/> words machine <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0587">machine</u>
<u n="37" who="S0585">oh machine yeah she texted me oh see what am I supposed to say to that?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0587">say erm something like I'm not gonna be speaking today cos my mum told me that I need to</u>
<u n="39" who="S0585">no no I don't think she's ready for jokes about it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0587">oh that's cheeky</u>
<u n="41" who="S0585">no I don't think see this is the thing I have to like pick and choose what I can joke about with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I don't think she'll find that funny I think she'd be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are you serious? and I'll be like</u>
<u n="42" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> too serious <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's serious <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0585">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="44" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's serious</u>
<u n="45" who="S0585">yeah and I guess I guess it would be I would and I don't yeah I guess it would be something that you don't really want to be joked about</u>
<u n="46" who="S0587">yeah fair enough</u>
<u n="47" who="S0585">thank you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0587">well she doesn't know what I'm going to say about her so er</u>
<u n="49" who="S0585">true true this is why I don't tell people like people will be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> mainly she'll be like what's this person said about be behind my back? I'll be like nothing I'm not telling you I won't be</u>
<u n="50" who="S0587">is that one of the things that she asks? has anyone said anything about me behind my back? oh that's a good question</u>
<u n="51" who="S0585">you are you asking that to me?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0585">what do you mean just negative?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0587">no</u>
<u n="55" who="S0585">no well I don't remember everything</u>
<u n="56" who="S0587">I'll have praise as well</u>
<u n="57" who="S0585">you can't er</u>
<u n="58" who="S0587">everything there's a there's an encyclopaedia of what the</u>
<u n="59" who="S0585">what do you? yeah I'm I'm thinking how far we go back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0587">I dunno last week</u>
<u n="61" who="S0585">last week then no no one's really said anything you just they're in conversation if it's like like someone I don't know if if</u>
<u n="62" who="S0587" trans="overlap">I find it weird that I I'm talked about it's not obviously not a lot but that I'm talked about at all</u>
<u n="63" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0587">and I find that weird</u>
<u n="65" who="S0585">yeah I know</u>
<u n="66" who="S0587">we talk about other people but I I I never think that that people say</u>
<u n="67" who="S0585" trans="overlap">so do I yeah yeah same</u>
<u n="68" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did this</u>
<u n="69" who="S0585">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like she she'll be like oh I've told you I've told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about you and I'll be like what? what?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0585">like what have you said about me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know she she was the girl dressed in ivy as as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in her her party</u>
<u n="72" who="S0587">with all the leaves?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0585">yeah and er Poison Ivy that's what she's called I don't she'll be like I've told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all about you I'll be like what what is it? there's nothing to tell</u>
<u n="74" who="S0587">not really no</u>
<u n="75" who="S0585">what have you been saying about me?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0587">yeah I told her about you but just your name not really</u>
<u n="77" who="S0585" trans="overlap">what what have you even said? I know it's like what what would you say then? what do you mean you've told her all about me?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0587">I'm gonna meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0585">exactly it's like what would you say? there's nothing to say quite weird I find that weird</u>
<u n="80" who="S0587">so what's someone said about me?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0585">I don't know there's nothing much there's nothing like I'm trying to think of anything in particular but really <pause dur="long"/> not much it's not much <vocal desc="laugh"/> just sort of in passing do you mean other people? cos I mention you a bit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0587">a bit? when?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0585">er like if if something's like related I'll be like oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did that or something</u>
<u n="84" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did that</u>
<u n="85" who="S0585"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yes someone's been to Africa oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s done that no I don't actually do that I don't do that cos that sounds weird then doesn't it?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0585">that would sound weird if you always said like no I don't really know I'm trying to think but there's there's nothing like</u>
<u n="88" who="S0587">that's rubbish I hope you're like your machine thing is <unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0585">yeah of course it would be er there's nothing negative that I can think of</u>
<u n="90" who="S0587">yeah it's got to be someone stupid to er do that but you know</u>
<u n="91" who="S0585">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0587">it's got to be someone stupid to complain about me in front of you</u>
<u n="93" who="S0585">I'll join in what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0587">shut it oh god nobody ever done this but</u>
<u n="95" who="S0585">I don't talk to anyone who dislikes you so</u>
<u n="96" who="S0587">is that a solidarity thing or?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0585">mm?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0587">is that a solidarity thing?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0585">solidarity? what do you mean?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0587">like if if someone doesn't like me you're like right I'm not talking to you</u>
<u n="101" who="S0585">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0587">oh</u>
<u n="103" who="S0585">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> what?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0587">I think you should adopt that</u>
<u n="105" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I've not I've never met anyone who really talks that bad about you so there you go they're not on my radar anyway people who don't like you I don't know who you're referring to</u>
<u n="106" who="S0587">radar</u>
<u n="107" who="S0585">yeah I don't really know who you're referring to</u>
<u n="108" who="S0587">I <trunc>do</trunc> I I just want to know what someone said about me don't know who don't know when don't know what</u>
<u n="109" who="S0585">I don't think there's nothing in particular there's nothing like big I don't we don't just sit there and like right let's discuss <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0587">right</u>
<u n="111" who="S0585">discuss you in <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos what would we say? it'd be weird that'd be well weird what if what if someone said to you what if like you were sat down and sort of went right let's discuss <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? I know you'd have a lot to say but</u>
<u n="112" who="S0587">right right I thought you'd never ask</u>
<u n="113" who="S0585">yeah no okay wrong person to say really</u>
<u n="114" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well</u>
<u n="115" who="S0585">he'd get all these notebooks out I have so much to say about him</u>
<u n="116" who="S0587">where shall we start eighth of January?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0585">I wrote down <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sounds good doesn't it?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0585">just figured you'd take his name <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0587">I listened to erm Frank Skinner and someone changed their name to erm they don't watch Star Wars and stuff but he said he knew someone once who changed his name to Darth Vader</u>
<u n="121" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0587">erm and he was like why why did you do that? he was like I think someone just told me to do it and I don't really like Star Wars but I did it erm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0587">erm I I forgot the reason why I did it but there actually there was a reason my friend told me to do it for this reason</u>
<u n="125" who="S0585" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0587">and then erm this thing had like a time period and he's like right so you're you're going to you're going to change it back now? and he went erm no I quite like it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0585">quite like it</u>
<u n="128" who="S0587">I'm just going to be called Darth Vader now</u>
<u n="129" who="S0585">quite like it now</u>
<u n="130" who="S0587">but l I didn't even like the movies I just call myself Darth Vader</u>
<u n="131" who="S0585" trans="overlap">just like the name well that's fair enough <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's so funny <pause dur="short"/> no I literally can't remember anything anyone said where it's just been like where it's been about you like in particular</u>
<u n="132" who="S0587">not been talked about ever?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0585">no I can't remember well not to me anyway I literally can't remember anything where it's been like where it's just been like one straight thing like like about your personality or about you</u>
<u n="134" who="S0587">it's personality</u>
<u n="135" who="S0585">it's it's always something like oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can drive oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can drive now</u>
<u n="136" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can drive right erm what</u>
<u n="137" who="S0585">and that's it it's nothing it's not like can't remember anything like that</u>
<u n="138" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0585">sorry sorry to disappoint you</u>
<u n="140" who="S0587">oh I wanted like</u>
<u n="141" who="S0585">I know yeah but I've not got anything</u>
<u n="142" who="S0587" trans="overlap">hot goss</u>
<u n="143" who="S0585">me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> literally don't talk about anyone else really</u>
<u n="144" who="S0587">apart from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0585">even though that was like well god that was like a year ago year ago year and a bit ago now <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> asks me about you guys quite a lot I don't know whether it's like I don't know really why she always asks she asks me a lot about like <pause dur="short"/> yeah she <vocal desc="laugh"/> she's like she's like so in your so your friends at home who would you call your best friend? and I'm like er no I'm like I dunno</u>
<u n="146" who="S0587">oh whatever</u>
<u n="147" who="S0585">no no I don't say it to her</u>
<u n="148" who="S0587">you you just like</u>
<u n="149" who="S0585">I say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0587">oh no</u>
<u n="151" who="S0585">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're such a creep I was like yeah I was like well I guess <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and she was like</u>
<u n="152" who="S0587">I guess <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0585">I guess</u>
<u n="154" who="S0587">that's not a fair <unclear/> that's a oh if I have to</u>
<u n="155" who="S0585">I said that now because I had too many now what has she done?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0587">oh no</u>
<u n="157" who="S0585">I have too many now</u>
<u n="158" who="S0587"><unclear/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0585">ah how many she's had like</u>
<u n="160" who="S0587" trans="overlap">oh now she's going to get your thumbs pounding the screen</u>
<u n="161" who="S0585">she had like three or something erm but yeah she'll ask me stuff like that she she ask she like gets me to rank you all <vocal desc="laugh"/> can I get a tie? no</u>
<u n="162" who="S0587">what? never?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0585">no</u>
<u n="164" who="S0587">what? oh I I've been I guess <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s best friend</u>
<u n="165" who="S0585" trans="overlap">cos you expect it cos you yeah but I've I've said that I guess now because you're here because you're too big-headed about it all so I have to say</u>
<u n="166" who="S0587" trans="overlap">but I know I know I know I'm number one I'm definitely ranked number one</u>
<u n="167" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're so you are <trunc>re</trunc> you're changing now</u>
<u n="168" who="S0587">yes I know who's one</u>
<u n="169" who="S0585">so it's like yeah you and then it's like and then she's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and I'm like yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she's like well who next? and I'm like</u>
<u n="170" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0585">I'm like yeah I guess I guess <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I was like I don't really know I don't really rank you I don't even understand this whole thing and she's like she's like who next? and I'm like oh I can't bothered doing any more <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like no I don't know now</u>
<u n="172" who="S0587">game's over</u>
<u n="173" who="S0585">no yeah I was like I don't know now I was like</u>
<u n="174" who="S0587">run out of friends</u>
<u n="175" who="S0585">problem is I'll be like well you do yours but I I I I don't mean it nasty like I don't mean this in any like weird way at all but she's only got two friends</u>
<u n="176" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0585">ah see I do I don't mean it in anyway but she's only got like two like proper friends at home she said that's what she says to me</u>
<u n="178" who="S0587" trans="overlap">that is quite sad</u>
<u n="179" who="S0585" trans="overlap">she says that so that's not me saying it but she's like you know I've only got two friends and then and I'm not going to rank them and I was like okay well do you not see it's weird you asking me to like rank my friends?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0587">maybe she wants you to talk about your friends so because she doesn't have any friends to think about</u>
<u n="181" who="S0585">mm mm</u>
<u n="182" who="S0587">so she thinks about friends via the proxy of you</u>
<u n="183" who="S0585" trans="overlap">don't say that on tape the proxy of you it's weird like she's cos she's I just found it weird I was like I don't really do that I don't really like think of it in that way but okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> like I don't generally number them but <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know what you want to do but I kind of I kind of feel bad though cos I get the feeling sometimes I don't know cos I'll be like ah my friend's just sent me this and she's like oh who's that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? it's like as in who sent you it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and I'm like oh no she she'll be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I'll be like no no and then she'll like go through she'll be like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? and I'm like no no so like <trunc>hi</trunc> and like oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent me this and then she's like oh right and I'm like</u>
<u n="184" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0585">why do you need to know this? so weird</u>
<u n="186" who="S0587">she said writing it down <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0585" trans="overlap">I know yeah I know yeah why do you need to know? you're just like and then I've got I I can't get rid of this and I don't know how to I'm sure there's a way of getting rid of it but when we're watching stuff on my laptop if I get a Facebook message it pops up on my <trunc>a</trunc> on my actual laptop and it's like oh I hate it cos it's like I'm like er everyone can see it like it's not even anything it won't even be anything much usually it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when I'm on my laptop but then then she pops up in the corner and I'm like I dunno I just think oh that guy <unclear/> some conversation and</u>
<u n="188" who="S0587">yeah I'm sure there's a way</u>
<u n="189" who="S0585">I know and I must I've tried to but there must be something</u>
<u n="190" who="S0587">and the one where it's like erm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0585">oh no that's that never mind</u>
<u n="192" who="S0587">like presentation setting or something so when you're in full screen mode nothing will pop up</u>
<u n="193" who="S0585">okay okay cos yeah we sat <trunc>wa</trunc> we'll be sat watching I'm a Celeb and you're like come on like just just don't like</u>
<u n="194" who="S0587">that'll teach you for watching I'm a Celebrity</u>
<u n="195" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> shut up it's not been like it's but it's the fact that they've read it cos of course they're going to read it cos it's there do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0587">yeah yeah you can like quick before it goes</u>
<u n="197" who="S0585">yeah yeah yeah but I mean it's nothing and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> especially she definitely will read it just cos she'll want to know if it's about her honestly yeah I don't know it kind of annoyed me right so she when she had her argument with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I went down and started chatting to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we didn't mention her at all like nothing at all because I cos I knew there cos I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in the house and I heard her come to the top of the stairs to listen to mine and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s conversation so I made sure not to like mention her at all like not even mention what happened because I want I just wanted to see if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was okay just cos it was an argument they're both gonna be upset like I just wanted to see that but I was like I didn't even ask that because I knew she was like <trunc>at</trunc> I could hear her at the top of the stairs and so after we'd finished like chatting to her I went back to my room and I got a <trunc>messg</trunc> I got a message off <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saying erm er what did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> say about me? and I was like you were at the top of the stairs man like don't pretend you weren't that's why that's why I just I said nothing you know it didn't didn't come up we didn't talk about it genuinely <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't talk about it and erm and then she was like oh no but I heard her say this and I was like she never said that she she's like I heard her saying something about I don't even know what it was but it was something I was like she never never said that I was never never spoke about you never never mentioned you at all and I thought she dropped it and she's like just tell me what she said and I was like</u>
<u n="198" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0585">I was like I can't I <unclear/> I was like I'm not lying <trunc>we</trunc> I'm not lying I don't like this thing that you think I'm lying about this</u>
<u n="200" who="S0587">like you should have said her <unclear/> like order and</u>
<u n="201" who="S0585">yeah I was like I'm not lying we didn't talk about you at all and and I make I mean I don't I don't talk about her very much anyway I know I do here I feel awful actually cos I've been talking about her quite a bit here but at uni I really don't like and especially if she's in the house I'm not mentioning her name cos she'll be like at the door <vocal desc="laugh"/> and so er so I I don't say anything at all erm and it was only when she left the house did I go into <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and say you know are you okay about the you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stuff? and then and that was like the only time and so how I don't know how I just through that I was like not saying anything I was like I'm not talking about you I don't talk about you ever in the house cos I know too dangerous</u>
<u n="202" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0585">too dangerous</u>
<u n="204" who="S0587">you don't er you don't shit where you sleep?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> shit where you eat isn't it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0587">eat ah you don't want to shit where you sleep either</u>
<u n="207" who="S0585">no yeah that's true but at the same time I like I don't talk about either of them in the house I don't talk about like I don't want to talk about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> either even though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> tries to but cos I really like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so and I do really like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I know it probably doesn't sound like it</u>
<u n="208" who="S0587">okay</u>
<u n="209" who="S0585">but it's not twenty-sixteen yet so so</u>
<u n="210" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0585">well my New Year's resolution will be like to be to be better about</u>
<u n="212" who="S0587">to be better?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0585">yeah actually that'll just be my New Year's resolution to be better</u>
<u n="214" who="S0587" trans="overlap">well done what a great resolution that is</u>
<u n="215" who="S0585">I think it is to be better to be better</u>
<u n="216" who="S0587" trans="overlap">no erm it's too broad you're basically</u>
<u n="217" who="S0585">exactly yeah but there's no</u>
<u n="218" who="S0587">but there's no you you like just say to be better you've got no way to improve yourself</u>
<u n="219" who="S0585">yeah I do cos I know the improvements I have to make I just don't want to list them all</u>
<u n="220" who="S0587">well there you go you need to list them</u>
<u n="221" who="S0585">why?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0587">funny</u>
<u n="223" who="S0585" trans="overlap">for who? no</u>
<u n="224" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0585">not funny they're not really funny</u>
<u n="226" who="S0587">what what what's number one three and five?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0585">oh god I haven't I haven't listed them you've just told me to list them so one okay will be to</u>
<u n="228" who="S0587" trans="overlap">rank them they already are ranked</u>
<u n="229" who="S0585">we'll do no cos I'm just thinking now er</u>
<u n="230" who="S0587">strange</u>
<u n="231" who="S0585">shut up</u>
<u n="232" who="S0587">oh</u>
<u n="233" who="S0585">okay so one will be to stop like stop bitching probably be a better <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="234" who="S0587">stop bitching oh what?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0587">like not to me though hopefully</u>
<u n="237" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I'll try and make it less about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in particular actually</u>
<u n="238" who="S0587">okay so more about other people?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0585">no no see I don't mean it like that</u>
<u n="240" who="S0587">you get to balance the you have to address the balance somehow</u>
<u n="241" who="S0585" trans="overlap">no no I don't erm cos I feel awful cos they cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is always like oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you barely bitch and I'm like oh no oh you just don't hear it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0585">I do you just</u>
<u n="244" who="S0587" trans="overlap">it's about you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0585" trans="overlap">you just don't no it's I don't I don't I've not said anything particularly bad about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have I? I haven't not about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0587">see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in my head just are interchangeable so I don't know</u>
<u n="247" who="S0585" trans="overlap">so yeah of course yeah sorry I feel a bit bad cos I keep mentioning them er they we go number two is to stop mentioning <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to you <vocal desc="laugh"/> there you go</u>
<u n="248" who="S0587" trans="overlap">it's alright it's funny though</u>
<u n="249" who="S0585">be funny you don't know them</u>
<u n="250" who="S0587">it's fine to bitch to people I think when they have no idea who they are</u>
<u n="251" who="S0585">that's why I like doing it <trunc>so</trunc>sorry that's why you get it so much</u>
<u n="252" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0585">cos it's it's because at least you don't know them but then it makes them look really bad to you even though they're really nice people so</u>
<u n="254" who="S0587">but I'm probably never going to meet them</u>
<u n="255" who="S0585">no it's true</u>
<u n="256" who="S0587">cos you went to uni that was like so far away</u>
<u n="257" who="S0585">yeah see don't get oh don't get me started on that <vocal desc="laugh"/> maybe that should be New Year's resolution not to think about that <vocal desc="laugh"/> not to like no cos I don't dwell on it anyway</u>
<u n="258" who="S0587">you're having a conversation with yourself I'm not sure</u>
<u n="259" who="S0585">I know I'm not a dweller too much anyway so I think I can leave that</u>
<u n="260" who="S0587">you're a cave dweller</u>
<u n="261" who="S0585">no I dwell on those type of things I would dwell on embarrassing things that happen to me though I dwell on that for a long time</u>
<u n="262" who="S0587">oh what's going on? what are you moaning about?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0585">I don't even know</u>
<u n="264" who="S0587">you're dwelling on this what you what I just said</u>
<u n="265" who="S0585">yeah sorry what what what are you asking?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0587">something about being too far away I said that and you were like oh don't say that</u>
<u n="267" who="S0585">no it's just because I think I've said this at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s but I don't know how drunk you were so</u>
<u n="268" who="S0587">I wasn't very drink</u>
<u n="269" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so erm I was I was just thinking out loud really probably should have said anything actually but okay okay I'll say it</u>
<u n="270" who="S0587">please include me in this conversation</u>
<u n="271" who="S0585">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0587">this tape wants a er a conversation between people not not</u>
<u n="273" who="S0585">yeah see I feel like I'm deep delving too deep for this tape</u>
<u n="274" who="S0587">not at all they've got loads probably going to listen to tapes like</u>
<u n="275" who="S0585">judge me</u>
<u n="276" who="S0587">for a lot a lot of this time it'll be it'll be good for them there some juicy goss</u>
<u n="277" who="S0585">juicy goss I hope they don't know anyone I haven't mentioned any second names so that's fine erm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0587">as if they're gonna facebook them</u>
<u n="279" who="S0585">they might just know them</u>
<u n="280" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0585">no shut up</u>
<u n="282" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0585">erm <pause dur="short"/> sorry I forgot what I was even saying now what?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0587"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0585">okay you're singing now so it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="286" who="S0587">do you know who this is? we'll get back to you in a minute but <pause dur="short"/> er you know Busted?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0585">yeah is it guy on his own or is it Busted?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0587">well no it's not Busted but</u>
<u n="289" who="S0585">oh</u>
<u n="290" who="S0587">Charlie Simpson</u>
<u n="291" who="S0585">I was gonna say the guy on his own the like middle guy that's what his name was the one who's now joined again he like wasn't in it was he? like in the Busted like redo and then he's joined it now</u>
<u n="292" who="S0587">has he?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0585">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0587">yeah so he's a member of Fightstar he's called Charlie Simpson and then</u>
<u n="295" who="S0585" trans="overlap">so he's official <pause dur="short"/> he's officially to back with Busted yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0587">right but he he just released a new album with his like rock metal band</u>
<u n="297" who="S0585">I don't know I don't know but they're back</u>
<u n="298" who="S0587">they're back</u>
<u n="299" who="S0585">they're back it only happened recently but they are back</u>
<u n="300" who="S0587">it it it's probably just a tour though isn't it? not er <unclear/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0585" trans="overlap">yeah oh yeah it's not yeah not forever it must be like a</u>
<u n="302" who="S0587">for the <unclear>longer</unclear></u>
<u n="303" who="S0585">yeah yeah it's like yeah it's like a <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>re</trunc>renew</u>
<u n="304" who="S0587" trans="overlap">must be weird though cos I listened to some of his like Fightstar stuff and it's like proper heavy stuff</u>
<u n="305" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0587">he's like screaming and everything innit?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0587">so it's like he must find it weird</u>
<u n="309" who="S0585" trans="overlap">maybe that that's probably why he left then cos he wanted to do this kind of music can't really do that with</u>
<u n="310" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah well yeah yeah mm <pause dur="short"/> go on then you're saying about being too far</u>
<u n="311" who="S0585">I wasn't it wasn't like being too far away it was just knowing what I know now if I had the choice of universities again I don't think I would have picked <anon type="place"/> I don't think I would be at <anon type="place"/> but obviously I didn't know what I know so can't really like can't really regret it or anything cos it's just so</u>
<u n="312" who="S0587">what because of the distance away from here or because it's got nothing there?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0585">no it's not even I dunno it's it's nothing to do with that it's just it's just I don't think if I knew what I wanted to actually do like if I knew I'd wanted to do like language and linguistics or just linguistics I just don't think I would have picked <anon type="place"/> because I don't think it would have like been on my options if you know what I mean just not for any other reason just because yeah I probably wouldn't have picked it that's all <pause dur="short"/> but obviously I didn't know I didn't know what I wanted to do so <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="place"/> it was <pause dur="short"/> that's all but it's nothing like I don't I don't regret picking <anon type="place"/> there's no like regret there it's not it's just it's just a simple if I had known what I had wanted to do back then I probably wouldn't have picked it that's all it's no like there no like deep like oh my god I've done the wrong thing</u>
<u n="314" who="S0587">existential crisis</u>
<u n="315" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0587">that's good</u>
<u n="317" who="S0585">it's just a simple I probably wouldn't be there I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this and she was like what? where would you be? what would you be doing? I was like dunno who knows?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0587">who knows?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0585">yeah dunno hopefully I would be giving <unclear/> myself in linguistics but probably not at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0585">it's weird when I think about how I got to <anon type="place"/> it's just weird cos it wasn't even a it wasn't even thought through it was too rushed the whole process I found for choosing universities was so rushed that I didn't have time to really like I guess it was just rushed for me because I didn't know what I wanted to do so it was like a mess to pick something when you don't know what you want to do</u>
<u n="322" who="S0587">yeah I remember talking to you and I I remember coming away from it just thinking like I don't I've no idea what she wants to do</u>
<u n="323" who="S0585">no exactly cos I didn't know so</u>
<u n="324" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0585">and so and obviously then I picked a course that I didn't want to do in the end so it's still still ended up in me changing so</u>
<u n="326" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0585">but er it's just weird <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0585">but I guess I guess knowing that knowing how <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'm fine with it now the distance doesn't bother me now in first year it bothered me quite a lot it was tough first year cos I was like it's just it's I guess first year's tough anyway but</u>
<u n="330" who="S0587">yeah I suppose like first year you've been away and it's <trunc>ex</trunc> like exaggerated by the fact that you're so far away from everyone</u>
<u n="331" who="S0585">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0587">I'm pretty sure my first time I came kind of like for a weekend I don't think I needed it because like the back <unclear/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0585">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0587">erm it was nice to come back</u>
<u n="335" who="S0585">yeah yeah I was just jealous cos a lot of people first term went back everyone in fact everyone in my flat apart from me and like that was fifteen people apart from apart from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who obviously didn't go back to America and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who didn't go back to New Zealand but so it wasn't everyone but everyone apart from us three went back saw family went back like for a weekend or something and stuff that was everyone but me from England and I was like</u>
<u n="336" who="S0587">saw me though</u>
<u n="337" who="S0585">and I was like so jealous yeah yeah see that was a good thing that was a good day that yeah oh god you're so annoying see this is what I get this is why can't say it anymore can't say anything good about you cos you just grin at me like that</u>
<u n="338" who="S0587">I like it it's good</u>
<u n="339" who="S0585">course you do</u>
<u n="340" who="S0587">I like I like hearing my greatest hits</u>
<u n="341" who="S0585">greatest hits god you're such a big head</u>
<u n="342" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was so happy when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh it's so thoughtful of you</u>
<u n="343" who="S0585">I know yeah I thought you I I actually thought when I gave you the idea oh he'll take credit for that and I was like oh I'll just leave him I'll just leave it I thought you would have done I I would have just left it I wouldn't have said anything</u>
<u n="344" who="S0587">but I was like I was thoughtful because I asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0585">poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you didn't say that to her did you?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0585">ah what?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0585">you said that to her? I was thoughtful <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because I asked someone else to do the thinking for me</u>
<u n="350" who="S0587">I said I ask asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who I knew would give a good answer</u>
<u n="351" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0587">so</u>
<u n="353" who="S0585">bless her how how she thought that was from you I thought she'd guess straight away that you'd asked me</u>
<u n="354" who="S0587">it it was like she sent a message saying like that so <trunc>tho</trunc> such a thoughtful gift</u>
<u n="355" who="S0585">ah that's so sweet though</u>
<u n="356" who="S0587" trans="overlap">and I sort of like cheers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0585">what did she get you? she was quite happy about what she got you but I forgot to ask her</u>
<u n="358" who="S0587">er well cos it <trunc>ca</trunc> it it was erm due to be delivered fifth of Jan and they went shopping the other day</u>
<u n="359" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0587">I'm pretty sure I told you this last night though</u>
<u n="361" who="S0585">don't think so what?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0587">think I did</u>
<u n="363" who="S0585">what?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0587">erm and then we were going to get some shoes</u>
<u n="365" who="S0585">you didn't tell me this</u>
<u n="366" who="S0587">it was on my list of stuff to get was some shoes and then she was like mm I wouldn't get shoes if I were you</u>
<u n="367" who="S0585">ah bless her</u>
<u n="368" who="S0587">and then she was like yeah that's what I I got you for Christmas</u>
<u n="369" who="S0585">ah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0587">and so erm yesterday she got them well they arrived and then she was like do you want to come round and try them on?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0585">no you didn't tell me this</u>
<u n="372" who="S0587">oh yeah this now is new stuff but</u>
<u n="373" who="S0585">no you didn't tell me any of that</u>
<u n="374" who="S0587">I yeah whatever think I did</u>
<u n="375" who="S0585">no you didn't didn't didn't at all</u>
<u n="376" who="S0587">think I did</u>
<u n="377" who="S0585"><trunc>di</trunc> you didn't I'd remember see I remember information</u>
<u n="378" who="S0587">okay</u>
<u n="379" who="S0585">go on anyway</u>
<u n="380" who="S0587">erm because she found out cos I bought some shoes er like running shoes and she found out that that I was size eight</u>
<u n="381" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0587">but she bought size ten she went come and try them on see if they fit anyway but they didn't so I've seen them I know what they are er she's going to take them back and get a</u>
<u n="383" who="S0585">oh bless her</u>
<u n="384" who="S0587">different size there's something else as well ha but I don't know what that is</u>
<u n="385" who="S0585">oh bless <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0587">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got the <unclear/> as well and I was like yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0585">did she like did she ask about it? ah you did you could have said at least one of them was from you blimey</u>
<u n="388" who="S0587">ah credit where credit's due</u>
<u n="389" who="S0585">no I don't want I don't want it if she's just like thinking that you ah no you should have just said the <unclear/> was you at least</u>
<u n="390" who="S0587">oh yeah I get the <unclear/> you get the</u>
<u n="391" who="S0585">fine you could have had the book I I thought that I was like oh well you'll probably take credit for that I was like I'll leave it</u>
<u n="392" who="S0587">well I wouldn't have <trunc>t</trunc>taken credit for it I think I just would have left it and then she'd just think it was me but then when she started saying about like Corfu or something and I was like I can't I can't bullshit this so I I was just like yeah I have no idea what you're on about you're reading a book? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0585" trans="overlap">you're terrible you could have texted me I would have backed I would have helped you giving you all the information for your lie</u>
<u n="394" who="S0587">no no it was too full-on too soon</u>
<u n="395" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I got this believe she thought it was from you when she opened it</u>
<u n="396" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0585">I would have twigged immediately</u>
<u n="398" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0585">I'd have been like nope</u>
<u n="400" who="S0587">like she was saying what the name of the book was as well and I was like I don't know what the name of the book is she's like you bought it</u>
<u n="401" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0587">it's called After You</u>
<u n="403" who="S0585">it is called After You yeah bless but when I you gave me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s present I was like I was like I'll say I'll say that it you know that you've got it wrong but part of me was like well on this book so just keep it</u>
<u n="404" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would get John Stewart and she's be like erm what?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0585" trans="overlap">she'd be like what who's this guy?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0585">oh</u>
<u n="408" who="S0587">I didn't write it</u>
<u n="409" who="S0585">I know yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0587">must get there</u>
<u n="411" who="S0585">yeah <unclear/> do you know</u>
<u n="412" who="S0587">what? <unclear/> do you want to do that</u>
<u n="413" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0587">oh it did <unclear/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0585">yeah like the last like last like two years ago when you gave me the other one</u>
<u n="416" who="S0587">and I've got that one</u>
<u n="417" who="S0585">yeah you got that one it's something <trunc>e</trunc> Green Eggs and Ham oh no it's yeah Sam-I-Am it's just there it's on the pile <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0587"><unclear/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0585">watch out</u>
<u n="420" who="S0587">I like how it feels this stuff</u>
<u n="421" who="S0585">I know I like it I like it</u>
<u n="422" who="S0587"><unclear/> for a bit write that in in the thing</u>
<u n="423" who="S0585">oh what do you want? do you want an inky pen or a biro?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0587">I I want a pen</u>
<u n="425" who="S0585">I don't know if I should just give you an inky one cos you you write left-handed don't you?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0587">oh okay yeah fine</u>
<u n="427" who="S0585">you smudge erm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0587">am I okay to bend it? you've got to bend it to write in it</u>
<u n="429" who="S0585">do you need something to lean on?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0587">mm <shift new="singing"/> Tuesday's grey and Wednesday too <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0585">yeah that's the only biro I have for when I get like stuff that I can't write on with er my inky pens <shift new="singing"/> break my heart Thursday doesn't even start it's Friday I'm in love <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/> I'm happy she liked it though</u>
<u n="432" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0585">I was going to buy that book but then when you said you'd been out I thought yeah at least then she'll get it <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came in here and she was like how many books do you have? and I was like no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're meant to be a book person like me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0587">oh Harry Potter</u>
<u n="435" who="S0585">yeah I was like you're meant to know you're meant to know what it's like <pause dur="short"/> never mind</u>
<u n="436" who="S0587">never mind</u>
<u n="437" who="S0585">no I was like never mind to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not to you</u>
<u n="438" who="S0587" trans="overlap"></u>
<u n="439" who="S0585">oh are you writing in the cover again?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0585">god you did this last time</u>
<u n="442" who="S0587">what? where am I meant to write?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0585">no never mind fine write in the cover</u>
<u n="444" who="S0587">where's it meant to go?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0585">it's like no never mind just write it whatever <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/> it's so funny there's no in-between with me on Twitter I'm either retweeting really stupid jokes like jokes that are so beyond</u>
<u n="446" who="S0587">yeah I've seen that</u>
<u n="447" who="S0585">have you seen it? or I'm retweeting really serious social issues there is no in-between on my Twitter there's absolutely no in-between what did you see? you saw it last night were you thinking oh I I find them hilarious</u>
<u n="448" who="S0587">I didn't see them last night but I've I've seen them and yeah I like them</u>
<u n="449" who="S0585">oh you like them? well you don't even retweet them you should</u>
<u n="450" who="S0587">how do you know?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0585">because it would tell me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has retweeted your retweet</u>
<u n="452" who="S0587">oh right it would say</u>
<u n="453" who="S0585">yeah see look you've been found out</u>
<u n="454" who="S0587">I've retweeted them all</u>
<u n="455" who="S0585">mm whatever liar <pause dur="short"/> I've actually got erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from uni start following the person that I follow because he thinks they're so funny <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> but I'm gonna all I do that's all I do on Twitter is I look at my timeline and then I search that guy to see if he's said anything else funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0585">yes he done some more tweets <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0587">cool <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0585">done now</u>
<u n="460" who="S0587">that were pretty quick</u>
<u n="461" who="S0585">well forty-three <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know why I find it so funny</u>
<u n="462" who="S0587">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0585">there's a sign saying no harm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0585">what?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0587">funny</u>
<u n="467" who="S0585">well that's my er that's my timeline it's just either really stupid jokes or really serious social issues</u>
<u n="468" who="S0587">well it's er you can have two extremes then that's</u>
<u n="469" who="S0585">I know yeah it's there's no there's literally there is actually no in-between there is absolutely nothing there's all that's all I retweeted and so er</u>
<u n="470" who="S0587">I've considered deleting Twitter</u>
<u n="471" who="S0585">mm?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0587">considering deleting Twitter</u>
<u n="473" who="S0585">oh really? why? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0587">dunno there's quite a lot of tweets that I'd rather not be attributed to my name</u>
<u n="475" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> attributed</u>
<u n="476" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like really old ones that you're like did when you're like fourth year or something it's like</u>
<u n="477" who="S0585" trans="overlap">yeah no yeah just delete them</u>
<u n="478" who="S0587">if I come into the public eye</u>
<u n="479" who="S0585">if I come into the public eye <vocal desc="laugh"/> people going through your tweets</u>
<u n="480" who="S0587">I'd be crucified</u>
<u n="481" who="S0585">that'd be me you would be crucified <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0587">why?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0585">cos I'm there I'm out there in the world my stories would sell for millions</u>
<u n="484" who="S0587"><unclear/> look at him</u>
<u n="485" who="S0585">yeah I have some tweets off you tweets I have some er texts off you that could that could be the end of you</u>
<u n="486" who="S0587">the end of me <unclear/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0585">mm? yeah but I didn't know if I wanted to read it now jeez</u>
<u n="488" who="S0587">what's wrong with reading it now?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0585">I can't really <unclear/> comment look you can write here or</u>
<u n="490" who="S0587">or</u>
<u n="491" who="S0585">or somewhere else or or on the page here</u>
<u n="492" who="S0587">mm what's the point of writing here then?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0585">because it's inside you're not actually meant to write on the cover but never mind</u>
<u n="494" who="S0587">why not?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0585">cos <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wish I'd never said that now</u>
<u n="496" who="S0587">said what?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0585">I <unclear/> what are you going to write? what is that? I'm so smug but that the the one you wrote underneath it looks like I'm so slug</u>
<u n="498" who="S0587">yeah cos I missed out a stick on the U</u>
<u n="499" who="S0585">I'm so slug about it good little slug why do you <unclear/> if you just go write everything I say</u>
<u n="500" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0587">that's funny <shift new="singing"/> when you push it through <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0585">it oh my god I wasn't talking that much</u>
<u n="503" who="S0587">yeah you were <shift new="singing"/> on the back away from you <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0585">I know you'll fill the void for long</u>
<u n="505" who="S0587">well that's what I said at least temporarily</u>
<u n="506" who="S0585">yeah yeah are we all just like woah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0585">you should have just wrote delete as appropriate underneath</u>
<u n="509" who="S0587">what's that thing on your feet? god <pause dur="long"/> are we playing erm roulette?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0585">oh after I've finished this</u>
<u n="511" who="S0587">own</u>
<u n="512" who="S0585">are we playing roulette or battle shots</u>
<u n="513" who="S0587">never</u>
<u n="514" who="S0585">what so you mean never? shut up I'm just calming down after my pizza</u>
<u n="515" who="S0587">calming down what? that was ten hours ago</u>
<u n="516" who="S0585">ten hours ago it riled me up cos</u>
<u n="517" who="S0587">you only ate three quarters of it</u>
<u n="518" who="S0585">I know but I didn't have breakfast that long ago</u>
<u n="519" who="S0587">left all the crusts of them</u>
<u n="520" who="S0585">so did you</u>
<u n="521" who="S0587">no I ate the crusts</u>
<u n="522" who="S0585">you left loads of crust as well</u>
<u n="523" who="S0587">no from the slices that I ate</u>
<u n="524" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0587">I ate the crust I was going to eat your crust that you had nibbled on as well</u>
<u n="526" who="S0585">no you left crust as well so</u>
<u n="527" who="S0587">no I didn't</u>
<u n="528" who="S0585">yes you did I saw you</u>
<u n="529" who="S0587">I didn't</u>
<u n="530" who="S0585">throw it back</u>
<u n="531" who="S0587">no that cos it was stuck to the bottom of the slice I took</u>
<u n="532" who="S0585">oh whatever</u>
<u n="533" who="S0587">it was <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0585">whatever <pause dur="short"/> I can never get rid of Twitter just cos I need that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's the guy who tweets all the jokes</u>
<u n="535" who="S0587">mm well just get a new one</u>
<u n="536" who="S0585">get a new one I don't mind I quite like mine</u>
<u n="537" who="S0587">what do you like about it?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0585">dunno</u>
<u n="539" who="S0587">who are you following just <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0585" trans="overlap">I like my name as well I'd have to be like <anon type="email"/> I don't know how many S's I'd have to add</u>
<u n="541" who="S0587">why do you need a name?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0585">I quite like it though I quite like me <anon type="email"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0587">why?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0585">cos I quite like it cos it's only added one extra S</u>
<u n="545" who="S0587">well done</u>
<u n="546" who="S0585">so I feel quite proud about that I don't have a number after it or anything</u>
<u n="547" who="S0587">call yourself <anon type="email"/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0585">I don't want to delete it why is that so surprising to you? shut up just cos you want to delete yours</u>
<u n="549" who="S0587">what I'm just I'm just surprised that I don't know like to you know like cos even you work at <unclear/> you you don't want to just because your your name you always have your name</u>
<u n="550" who="S0585">quite happy yes cos I have</u>
<u n="551" who="S0587">or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but you could have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> anyway if you got another one like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't gonna disappear</u>
<u n="552" who="S0585">I love that our call him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well</u>
<u n="553" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I just you his his he's only called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he misspelled Johnny</u>
<u n="555" who="S0587">oh right</u>
<u n="556" who="S0585">so he's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but erm it's just funny when just funny when other people say it as well you can have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> anyway</u>
<u n="557" who="S0587">you can have him</u>
<u n="558" who="S0585">yeah I know I know but I just can't be bothered changing it you may</u>
<u n="559" who="S0587">oh</u>
<u n="560" who="S0585">you make <unclear/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0587">no I can't be bothered</u>
<u n="562" who="S0585">does he? you know when you become when you're going to get in the public eye everyone's gonna go through your Twitter feed</u>
<u n="563" who="S0587">it's gonna be soon well</u>
<u n="564" who="S0585">why would you be in the public eye?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0587">I don't know</u>
<u n="566" who="S0585">yeah you do why?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0587">I don't know</u>
<u n="568" who="S0585">if you thought about it you must have an idea why</u>
<u n="569" who="S0587">maybe like there's people who you don't expect to be in the public eyes and then they'll sudden there they are</u>
<u n="570" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0587">I read erm John Watson's <unclear/> public <unclear/> essay book</u>
<u n="572" who="S0585"><unclear/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0587">yeah whatever erm and I remember there my Facebook thing would be</u>
<u n="574" who="S0585">yeah I guess</u>
<u n="575" who="S0587">er <unclear/> people</u>
<u n="576" who="S0585">yep</u>
<u n="577" who="S0587">and I know someone who erm put a tweet when is on the way to erm I forget where it was it was somewhere in Africa</u>
<u n="578" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0587">which is very ignorant of me erm so but she'd put on a thing saying erm I'm going to this place erm I hope I don't get AIDS lol joke I won't because I'm white</u>
<u n="580" who="S0585">right</u>
<u n="581" who="S0587">this is a joke about as you can get</u>
<u n="582" who="S0585">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0587">erm and she she did that before she got on the flight and she turned her phone off</u>
<u n="584" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0587">turned it back on again all these it had been retweeted by loads of people and they were like hating her cos they didn't get the joke but she was joking about her own erm like white erm</u>
<u n="586" who="S0585">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0587">what's it called?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0585">I know I'm trying to think now white</u>
<u n="589" who="S0587">er</u>
<u n="590" who="S0585">privilege</u>
<u n="591" who="S0587">that's it I knew it was a P word</u>
<u n="592" who="S0585">you're a P word <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="593" who="S0587">er and <vocal desc="laugh"/> so yeah and then like people just like slated her and she got like sacked and stuff from her job just because of that</u>
<u n="594" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="595" who="S0587">so</u>
<u n="596" who="S0585">difficult <pause dur="long"/> it is cool because I think <trunc>pe</trunc> well people just get so much abuse on Twitter like I follow I follow an author who follows me he followed me first</u>
<u n="597" who="S0587">really?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0585">yeah he follow that's the only reason I follow him is he followed me first I don't know why but okay</u>
<u n="599" who="S0587">your plug is good</u>
<u n="600" who="S0585">I know yeah I was going to say cos I don't when tweet anything do you can't I can't even accredit it to me like doing stuff cos I really I don't even tweet apart from like</u>
<u n="601" who="S0587" trans="overlap">no maybe he likes the jokes from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0585">I know yeah he must do so he followed me so I followed him back he's called Matt Hague and I have I have I've not I've not read any of his books but I've heard of them and I do intend to read them but but I intend to read a lot of books and erm so he and he tweets quite a bit about one of his books was ten reasons to stay alive and he tweets quite a bit about like you know dealing with depression and stuff not like overly just every so often he'll put out a little thing and then and then the other day he was tweeting about how much abuse he gets like on <trunc>Twi</trunc>Twitter and he was like sometimes really difficult to be on here because you know you don't want to erm you don't want to do this and then and then he's like it's not it's not even the strangers just hating on you or er just you know troll trolls like you know abusing you it's sometimes people that you kind of know like you and and they and they'll say something about you or something and I was like oh must be quite like horrible for people to pay that much attention to your Twitter</u>
<u n="603" who="S0587">I know</u>
<u n="604" who="S0585">that's why I think it's funny if people like pay attention to mine cos it's literally just stupid joke after stupid joke after stupid joke</u>
<u n="605" who="S0587">yeah I think like if it happened to me it would just be so easy to be well fuck doing it</u>
<u n="606" who="S0585">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0587">and I hope <unclear/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0585">yeah but yeah but I really love cos him and and I love you know Patrick Ness I really one of things I really love even though I don't retweet them that much I guess this is my in-between is retweeting authors erm I really love following authors on Twitter really love it cos most of the time they've got something really great to say and er and so I adore it and then when they talk about hate I'm like stop it stop being mean to these lovely authors</u>
<u n="609" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> talk about hate</u>
<u n="610" who="S0585">these lovely people yeah talk about how much hate they get and stuff and how much abuse and I'm just like they're lovely people read their books</u>
<u n="611" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0585">especially J K Rowling I love J K Rowling but she gets pure abuse on Twitter</u>
<u n="613" who="S0587">yeah I can imagine</u>
<u n="614" who="S0585">and it's like so awful but but she always says just such wonderful things that I'm like yes I love you so much</u>
<u n="615" who="S0587">this is like about like erm black Hermione and she's like yeah she was always black</u>
<u n="616" who="S0585">she didn't say that</u>
<u n="617" who="S0587">well yeah but words to that effect but like yeah she was just like</u>
<u n="618" who="S0585" trans="overlap">no she just said she just said I didn't write her as anything she's not in the book she's just described as brown hair and brown eyes</u>
<u n="619" who="S0587">well you could say that about anything I guess cos has she ever said that <trunc>every</trunc> has she ever said they have pale skin?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0585" trans="overlap">oh okay yeah I don't think they are no apart from Voldemort</u>
<u n="621" who="S0587" trans="overlap">surely surely most of the characters are white well yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0585">but yeah yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0587">I'm sure more of the characters aren't erm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0585">yeah I guess yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0587">it's like you can tell that</u>
<u n="626" who="S0585">I don't even know whether she it annoyed me so much people getting annoyed about that</u>
<u n="627" who="S0587">it was strange yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0585">I'm like I'm like no it's nothing to get annoyed about you weirdos it's nothing when they showed it I didn't even <trunc>as</trunc> the first thing I went to even though it doesn't even bother me was like why is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not ginger? cos that is written in the books</u>
<u n="629" who="S0587">oh is he not?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0585">I was like why is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not ginger</u>
<u n="631" who="S0587">he's really old</u>
<u n="632" who="S0585">that's written yeah no yeah I figure maybe he's grown out of his ginger hairs <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I was like</u>
<u n="633" who="S0587">he got so abused</u>
<u n="634" who="S0585">I know I was just like that's the first thing I went to was just like why is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not ginger? that is how he's written <pause dur="short"/> god damn it</u>
<u n="635" who="S0587">he's eleven years old so</u>
<u n="636" who="S0585">but then but then he tweeted being like he's ginger at heart and I was just like</u>
<u n="637" who="S0587">at heart come on</u>
<u n="638" who="S0585">no he isn't</u>
<u n="639" who="S0587" trans="overlap">I reckon they forgot they've gone oh shit he is ginger</u>
<u n="640" who="S0585">yeah yeah cos the whole family is ginger it's just something you can't really get passed</u>
<u n="641" who="S0587">no yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0585">cos the whole Weasley fan <trunc>co</trunc> fan? the whole Weasley Weasley gang is is ginger they're all ginger but never mind <pause dur="short"/> he'll just be a brown-haired kid <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0587">odd</u>
<u n="644" who="S0585">but yeah they are older I think the story is set a bit later</u>
<u n="645" who="S0587">oh okay</u>
<u n="646" who="S0585">I can't remember I honestly can't remember I haven't read it so <pause dur="long"/> but <pause dur="short"/> but everyone thinks it's a sequel prequel and she's like it's not a prequel stop saying that</u>
<u n="647" who="S0587">is it a film?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0585">is it a film or just a play? is it a West End play?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0587">I thought it was a play yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0585">mm is it? she has written it <pause dur="long"/> ah but yeah the same thing was do you know who Idris Elba is? have you watched Luther? or who do you know who Idris Elba is yeah?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0587" trans="overlap">I I know who he is but I don't know what Luther is yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0585" trans="overlap">yeah never mind it doesn't it doesn't matter I just thought Luther might be something you've watched that's all</u>
<u n="653" who="S0587">about him being James Bond?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0585">I think he'd make a fantastic James Bond when I when I</u>
<u n="655" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I thought too</u>
<u n="656" who="S0585">oh right cos cos he's in like when he's in like Luther and stuff and I've seen him in obviously he's good in films but I am like I was like yes he'd be a good James Bond and then a obviously everyone was like oh he's he's too what they say like he's too street and it's like well he is an actor he can act not street but whatever whatever that's a weird thing to say</u>
<u n="657" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0585">weird definitely weird</u>
<u n="659" who="S0587">Daniel Craig's just like never can't do it</u>
<u n="660" who="S0585">I know yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="661" who="S0587">he's too good</u>
<u n="662" who="S0585">yeah I know even though he is like fed up of it now and he's a bit like yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0587" trans="overlap">he just seem to be an arse but I I I understood what he was saying cos you just like like say you you don't have be a marathon <trunc>run</trunc>runner to like do your next one one run a twenty-four miler</u>
<u n="664" who="S0585">yeah it's like the thing is I think he hates the questions you get I think that's the main thing that he hates</u>
<u n="665" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0585">doing which I would absolutely hate cos pretty much they get like when they do those some of those interviews they're in there for like a day aren't they? and they just go to a different room and they're asked the same questions over and over again how that doesn't drive you mad</u>
<u n="667" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0585">I do not know but erm but yeah and and some of the questions he gets cos he's like I've seen him so many times he must get I think he gets quite a lot of like you know sexist questions quite a lot and he and you can tell he just get you can tell if I were him I'd just get fed up of it like he does he does just get fed up of it and then people like slate him on the internet and I'm like oh look he's getting fed up leave him alone</u>
<u n="669" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0585">I don't think this is what he signed up for when he wanted to be an actor I know it's kind of what you have to do it's in your contract you have to go out and you have to like you have to go and promote your film don't you? so</u>
<u n="671" who="S0587">I saw him on Graham Norton and he seemed to be er happy there</u>
<u n="672" who="S0585">yeah I think I think it's fine when you get like when it's Graham Norton when it's like someone who's you know who <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know but someone who's when it's interview it doesn't feel like an interview maybe do you know cos Graham just chats</u>
<u n="673" who="S0587" trans="overlap">I think it yeah yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0585">so but yeah I don't know what you were going to say so I feel</u>
<u n="675" who="S0587">yeah but just cos it's like with other people and</u>
<u n="676" who="S0585">yeah exactly it's more</u>
<u n="677" who="S0587">and he he's not an idiot</u>
<u n="678" who="S0585" trans="overlap">it's not Graham obviously has questions that he does ask but most of the time they go off on a tangent don't they? and they're chatting about other stuff whereas when they're in those like interview rooms the person has a set amount of interview questions that you have to ask and then they don't really like talk about much else</u>
<u n="679" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="680" who="S0585">so like on the red carpet and stuff when he when he's like walking up and they they have questions that you have to ask so so it's not really their fault either but at the same time I'm like poor guy</u>
<u n="681" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0585">poor guy</u>
<u n="683" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="684" who="S0585">like cos like when you hear about everyone who like walks out of like interviews and stuff it's like oh my god</u>
<u n="685" who="S0587">Tarantino</u>
<u n="686" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0587">I'm trying to tell you <unclear/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0585">yeah exactly who who did it recently? did Bruce Willis do one recently or something? someone did one with that guy again you know the guy who interviewed er Tarantino?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0585">something Murphy or something it's something it's something Murphy I think like his like name</u>
<u n="691" who="S0587">I think G begins with a G doesn't it?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0585">I don't know but yeah anyway yeah and then someone walked out of his again erm apparently he's like oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> stop talking about the interviewer</u>
<u n="693" who="S0587">he does seem to be an <trunc>i</trunc>idiot he had an radio interview as well with erm Richard Ayoade as well</u>
<u n="694" who="S0585">yeah yes he did didn't he? but that that was Richard purposely not wanting to like not wanting to follow</u>
<u n="695" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah you feel like it's him again though so it's like</u>
<u n="696" who="S0585">that was good though that I like that cos that's what his whole like Richard's written books that's kind of what his books are about the whole like you know the whole like history of of filming and stuff and <pause dur="short"/> and stuff and and when he used to write for the magazine I used to read it was all about like how ridiculous the industry was <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and stuff so it's kind of not not surprising it's funny though</u>
<u n="697" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0585">it's like Jon Stewart Jon Stewart did a film called Rosewater and er he had to obviously go and promote it like he was <trunc>o</trunc> he came over here actually I watched him on some of the English shows and erm and by the end of it his last one he went on Steven Colbert's like show obviously his friend so it was nice and then Steven started asking him questions and then Jon was just like no Steven what are you doing? and Steven was just like well I have to ask you these questions and Jon was like no not answering any any more <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0585">I came on your show</u>
<u n="701" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0585">it was funny</u>
<u n="703" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0585">oh and he was funny on like the English TV as well cos he was like he was like guys I think I was just after David Cameron had became like PM again and er and he was like you know what you have a shorter process than us but you still get the same crappy results guys and Jon Snow was like yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="706" who="S0585">he's like thank you thank you Jon Stewart for that</u>
<u n="707" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0585">he was like you guys seem to be getting it wrong as well so <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> ah I miss him miss him man I miss watching him five days a week four days a week</u>
<u n="709" who="S0587">oh</u>
<u n="710" who="S0585">I do I miss him I miss him</u>
<u n="711" who="S0587" trans="overlap">oh no read his book</u>
<u n="712" who="S0585">yeah I will</u>
<u n="713" who="S0587" trans="overlap">you'll be fine</u>
<u n="714" who="S0585">I will</u>
<u n="715" who="S0587">he's done that erm <pause dur="short"/> there's like another book that he's done well that he's actually done</u>
<u n="716" who="S0585">yeah is it</u>
<u n="717" who="S0587">summat Earth</u>
<u n="718" who="S0585">oh okay no phew was gonna say oh phew I don't know why I'm phewing cos you did get it but I've got one of his of it's there erm what is it? erm books of naked people or something and it's his essays just a collection collection of his essays</u>
<u n="719" who="S0587" trans="overlap">oh okay no</u>
<u n="720" who="S0585">no Earth yeah he's done Earth he's done another one as well the daily but that's not just him that was The Daily Show like the writers on The Daily Show as well</u>
<u n="721" who="S0587">okay</u>
<u n="722" who="S0585">he's done Earth and he's done another one yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0587">but like I don't know if if his Earth it seems to be like some of it's good some of it's bad</u>
<u n="724" who="S0585">yeah I've seen some I like read like clippings of it and stuff and some of it is quite it's it's very satirical it's all like completely satirical so I guess it's your taste really isn't it?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0587">mm I suppose he just like it doesn't flow I guess and it's just like a dicky analysis</u>
<u n="726" who="S0585">mm I did wonder how like how he did pardon me how he did a book like that cos</u>
<u n="727" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="728" who="S0585"><unclear/> I don't know how he yeah I don't know but</u>
<u n="729" who="S0587">I hope that's better just cos it</u>
<u n="730" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0587">it's better innit?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0587">er yeah the er autobiographer seemed to well biographer seems to be pretty clued up on</u>
<u n="734" who="S0585">oh yeah yeah cos she's obviously done like Steven as well</u>
<u n="735" who="S0587">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0585">should be good I'll enjoy it</u>
<u n="737" who="S0587">should be</u>
<u n="738" who="S0585">see books are always the best present to get</u>
<u n="739" who="S0587">mm? oh when I get them like I really enjoy them so</u>
<u n="740" who="S0585">what did you get <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0587">er</u>
<u n="742" who="S0585">it's not er what's this?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0587">er er The Tale of Dueling Neurosurgeons I think it's called</u>
<u n="744" who="S0585">oh yeah you've told me about this actually you have you told me about this? when did I last see you? I dunno</u>
<u n="745" who="S0587">I think it might might have been by text</u>
<u n="746" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="747" who="S0587">maybe but yeah that's what I'm reading</u>
<u n="748" who="S0585">but yeah I think you've mentioned it</u>
<u n="749" who="S0587">she tells it in like like the first chapter was about well it's it's all split up into sort of explaining different parts of the brain but through different historical events</u>
<u n="750" who="S0585">right</u>
<u n="751" who="S0587">like things sort of like duelling opinions like of neuroscientists like there's one in erm like the fourteen hundreds erm</u>
<u n="752" who="S0585">you told me has someone has something like though their eye?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0587">oh yeah that's the French French king erm</u>
<u n="754" who="S0585">how how why have you told me this?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0587">Henry the second I think yeah he was jousting and then erm the joust sort of went up into his eye</u>
<u n="756" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0587">didn't pierce well it it pierced his skull but it didn't hurt his brain but it was the impact that it his brain hit his the back of his skull</u>
<u n="758" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0587">and sort of like turned to mush erm and then he died slowly from like infection and stuff</u>
<u n="760" who="S0585">mm mm</u>
<u n="761" who="S0587">erm but it it's like how we now know what we do now because the neuroscientists that looked at him then</u>
<u n="762" who="S0585">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0587">recorded what was wrong with him and then they saw his brain like oh that must have been like his vision part which lives in the optical lobe</u>
<u n="764" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0587">that sort of stuff it's pretty cool to sort of</u>
<u n="766" who="S0585">yeah <pause dur="long"/> interesting yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0587">mm it's good that it's not just like a all sort of like <unclear/> it's all like a story it's not</u>
<u n="768" who="S0585">yeah yeah I like them yeah that's what I liked about like You Know How cos it wasn't</u>
<u n="769" who="S0587">no</u>
<u n="770" who="S0585">it was his story so it wasn't like so it was kind of told as a story but it was like it wasn't yeah cos I like I like first person narration as well</u>
<u n="771" who="S0587">massive hands</u>
<u n="772" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> alright creep</u>
<u n="773" who="S0587">he does he's got massive hands</u>
<u n="774" who="S0585">what at the back there's a picture on the back? I can't remember it</u>
<u n="775" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah yeah oh have you got the book here?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0585">I've not seen it no cos you've got it</u>
<u n="777" who="S0587">have I? yeah he's got massive hands like I reckon they're like one and a half of his head <pause dur="short"/> definitely that's why he was a surgeon</u>
<u n="778" who="S0585">massive hands you read why he's a surgeon and it wasn't I look down at my massive hands that's why I became surgeon to be fair the way he became a surgeon wouldn't be like wouldn't we wouldn't be able to do it today not in this country</u>
<u n="779" who="S0587">no cos he didn't know what to do did he? so it's like ah I'll just</u>
<u n="780" who="S0585" trans="overlap">he just went and he just dropped out and then went back and well that's maybe if you you really put your mind to it you might be able to</u>
<u n="781" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="782" who="S0585">put the years in but I don't think you'd be able to be a surgeon like I when we went down to <anon type="place"/> ah so interesting like where we had Christmas like just the four of us there's like no arguments or anything we're all just chatting about whatever and then you always go to and then you add the more family you add I find like the more arguments you get you get like</u>
<u n="783" who="S0587">yeah I remember those <unclear/> now though</u>
<u n="784" who="S0585">it's not it's not like really bad arguments they're never like it's it's just sort of debates I guess but but their views are really different so when I went down to <anon type="place"/> we only went there was only me my dad and my brother went cos mum stayed here with the dog and so and then obviously they're quite I dunno it's so interesting cos it's my dad's sister and er it was my dad's who was there was my dad's sister and her husband <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his partner er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's from Hungary and erm and I'm he dropped out of school like when he was younger cos he's a bit of a hippy and he now lives in in America and like he does seem like a bit of a hippy <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's got like braided hair and stuff and erm it's so interesting though cos my like my dad's like he's kind of if I had to put him on a political scale I think he's more left however compared to me he's not you know what I mean? like I'm way more left than he is I guess</u>
<u n="785" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0585">and then when I down there it's like aunt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> completely right and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s completely right I think that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I can't I don't quite understand cos I don't know him enough to to place him so and so there's like arguments on climate change cos we have climate change deniers in our family and erm yeah and erm er no it's a struggle that one cos I <trunc>y</trunc> cos that one's just such a struggle for me cos I was like I was like there's like seven billion people on the planet how can you think we're not having an effect? I just don't understand like that view I'm like how you can think it?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0587" trans="overlap">mm and also it it it shows that they blatantly just like just ignored any evidence or chosen not <unclear/> it</u>
<u n="788" who="S0585">the thing is cos he's not completely but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a bit of a one he's not completely like he <trunc>un</trunc> but he said he said have you not seen the data? the earth is for all the years the earth has warmed up and then cooled down warmed up cooled down warmed up cooled down he's like I'm not denying that the earth's not warming up but it's done that for all the years and it's going to come down and then everyone and then it got into the argument of and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like but no it's the rate of increase the rate of increase we're going up way faster than we should in recent years so they had a whole massive argument about it and I'm just I'm sat there most of the time until until I like chime in every so often but to be fair it was like it was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and my dad against <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s partner from Hungary so to be fair it was like uneven anyway so I was I was like I can't be bothered chiming in cos they're saying my argument for me but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> turned to me and she's like I love it I I you know your brother needs to tell your dad you should join in and I was like I was like no I've got to steer this on the way back home I'm not I'm not joining in and she's like oh I love it he's challenging he's oh your brother's proper challenging your dad that's how it should be and I'm like yeah but he's wrong <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="790" who="S0585">and then and then cos cos she's like another like climate change denier and I was just like great I'm just going to sit here</u>
<u n="791" who="S0587">but I'm not sure if it was a good argument because I guess the data that we know from <unclear/> is is over millions and millions of</u>
<u n="792" who="S0585">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0587">that when it's happened in fifty we don't have that position to know what happened back then</u>
<u n="794" who="S0585" trans="overlap">yeah yeah exactly yeah and it's stuff like that and then I don't cos I like cos I understood cos he was just like like why the heat? like what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying and I was like and I understood them maybe yeah and I was like then I was like but there's no denying that we're I just don't understand how you could be naïve enough to say like oh we're not having an effect of course we're having an effect it's like</u>
<u n="795" who="S0587">yeah they can see a massive difference</u>
<u n="796" who="S0585">like completely <trunc>ev</trunc> nearly everything we do is like unnatural</u>
<u n="797" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0585">so I was like okay but never mind</u>
<u n="799" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no one's been burning er fossil fuels like they</u>
<u n="800" who="S0585">mm mm but yeah so er so it was interesting and then er it was all awkward cos they live in America <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and so they always and they hate Americans so <pause dur="short"/> yeah and erm after they were like commenting on all like oh Americans do his and Americans do that and I'm like they're not that bad though <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're not that bad and cos like all the race stuff's been happening over there they're like you know it's so serious the stuff and we feel like they don't you know it's <trunc>be</trunc> it's got to the point where it's like do they even like white people? and I was like it's not about you though is it?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like it's not about you I don't understand that and then they and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said erm he was this was when I chimed in cos I was like <unclear/> taking this er he he was like you know it's fine to be gay be gay be gay but don't shove it in our faces and I was like oh like like well you shove er like heterosexuality in everyone else's faces and he was like no never done that and I was like not about you <vocal desc="laugh"/> not about you I don't care if you've not done it personally</u>
<u n="803" who="S0587">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0585">fucking hell</u>
<u n="805" who="S0587">fucking hell</u>
<u n="806" who="S0585">and I was like I was like not about you though is it?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0585">he was like yes but it feels like they don't like us anymore and I'm like it's not about you</u>
<u n="809" who="S0587"><unclear/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0585">I know yeah I'm like stop you what are you on about? stop it he says why? it's like this way doesn't work cos you guys always think that it's about you</u>
<u n="811" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said it as well I went out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other day and we were talking about Uber taxi</u>
<u n="812" who="S0585">oh yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0587">and this must be quite a lot of Uber taxi people are erm well they're they're Asian men with beards</u>
<u n="814" who="S0585">oh right I thought you were</u>
<u n="815" who="S0587">it happens to be the case</u>
<u n="816" who="S0585" trans="overlap">wanting to talk about something else</u>
<u n="817" who="S0587">no er</u>
<u n="818" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just I had a conversation with my dad and he was like you can't use Uber drive drive divers are poaching normal taxi drivers people and I'm like can't really poach someone at at airport though can you? it's just where you go to pick people up you can't claim the airport as yours but never mind carry on anyway sorry it's not about that clearly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="819" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no erm yeah and then it then he turns up and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sees him and then she she goes ah oh my god and she starts laughing and he's like ah good look with the terrorist and I was like</u>
<u n="820" who="S0585">to you? did she say that to you?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0587">yeah and I was like see you later</u>
<u n="822" who="S0585">yeah like</u>
<u n="823" who="S0587">not getting into this</u>
<u n="824" who="S0585">no yeah</u>
<u n="825" who="S0587">hardcore</u>
<u n="826" who="S0585">ah no</u>
<u n="827" who="S0587">had to get away from her</u>
<u n="828" who="S0585">yeah don't like no don't like that</u>
<u n="829" who="S0587">they're getting married did I say it?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0585">yeah yeah you told me cos we were <trunc>sa</trunc> we were talking well I was maybe you weren't listening then erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> we said they that they must have got engaged like in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0587">aye</u>
<u n="832" who="S0585">cos I <trunc>rem</trunc> I remember you telling me when they got engaged</u>
<u n="833" who="S0587">yeah that was</u>
<u n="834" who="S0585">I remember you being like no actually I won't say it then</u>
<u n="835" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0585">you <vocal desc="laugh"/> you <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're just funny funny now you're like I I'm not going on my own you you're coming with me if if I got to their wedding and I was like okay</u>
<u n="837" who="S0587">my dad's going now so it's alright</u>
<u n="838" who="S0585">no no but I remember that <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0587">don't want to go like it was just like</u>
<u n="840" who="S0585">you should you can invite them I'd like to go to Barbados</u>
<u n="841" who="S0587">no you you can go</u>
<u n="842" who="S0585">no I'll stay</u>
<u n="843" who="S0587">that would be so awkward</u>
<u n="844" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="845" who="S0587">hi I'm here for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="846" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="847" who="S0585">I'm here on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s behalf</u>
<u n="848" who="S0587">yeah representative</u>
<u n="849" who="S0585" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="850" who="S0587"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in da house</u>
<u n="851" who="S0585">I don't think he'd pay for me to go and then give you <trunc>so</trunc> give you your money so</u>
<u n="852" who="S0587">might</u>
<u n="853" who="S0585">doubt it <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="855" who="S0585">no it's cos I remember cos I I must <trunc>re</trunc> I remember conversations quite well but I remember you were like cos you didn't want to go to their wedding and you were like and oh yeah and I was like well I was like well if you don't do it straight away you don't get married straight away you were like really?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0585">I was like yes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> listen to me</u>
<u n="858" who="S0587">I'm pretty sure it it's at least like within a year</u>
<u n="859" who="S0585">mm?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0587">it's always like usually in a year isn't it?</u>
<u n="861" who="S0585">sometimes but I I think mainly but I was like I was like I think you said that to me at the time and I was like sometimes it can be you can be engaged for god knows how long years and years and years</u>
<u n="862" who="S0587">what comedy is like they're sort of engaged just like forever?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0585">comedy? like what? like a film or a TV show?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0587">TV show I think</u>
<u n="865" who="S0585"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="866" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0585"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the office</u>
<u n="868" who="S0587">yeah yeah ah they're engaged for like I don't know</u>
<u n="869" who="S0585">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah yeah I think it just gets to a point where after a few years you don't want to tell someone how long you've been engaged for cos people just presume that it's not going to happen then</u>
<u n="870" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0585">so mm quite sad</u>
<u n="872" who="S0587">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0585">like that's why I find it weird that they they've got engaged now but it's like when are you going to afford a wedding? like you know the people I said my friends <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got engaged it's like how when are you going to afford it?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0587">like our age?</u>
<u n="875" who="S0585">a year older I know she is I don't know if he is a year older but he seems similar age</u>
<u n="876" who="S0587">okay</u>
<u n="877" who="S0585">so mm?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0587">great</u>
<u n="879" who="S0585">I know but then er</u>
<u n="880" who="S0587">it's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps saying I'm like</u>
<u n="881" who="S0585">I I feel awkward when</u>
<u n="882" who="S0587">I do feel very awkward</u>
<u n="883" who="S0585">cos he's like</u>
<u n="884" who="S0587" trans="overlap">I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like definitely years since they've been together</u>
<u n="885" who="S0585" trans="overlap">he's like how can you <trunc>s</trunc> yeah I'm like oh don't say that don't say that I</u>
<u n="886" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="887" who="S0585">I just feel awkward in myself that's why I can never be one of those people who goes up to a couple and is like oh when are you getting married? who can you how can you say that to a couple? oh no</u>
<u n="888" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah cos he</u>
<u n="889" who="S0585">how can you say that? cos you don't know you don't know their situation you know nothing and it's like how can you say that?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0587">you could spark like someone to go home and like well when is this going to happen? and then</u>
<u n="891" who="S0585">exactly spark a <unclear/> exactly cos it can it can fester</u>
<u n="892" who="S0587">a week <trunc>la</trunc> yeah a week later you could could be on the street</u>
<u n="893" who="S0585">exactly like I don't understand how people can say stuff like that and they don't I'm like oh god how can you how can people comment? it's like when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like erm was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? it might be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually and they were like ah we want someone to have a baby oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're closest to it he and I'm like oh god don't say stuff like this</u>
<u n="894" who="S0587">unless she really she wants a baby as well or?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0585">I know yeah no I don't know it's just I just find it awkward I'm like er I don't want to make</u>
<u n="896" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0585">cos I don't want to make anyone uncomfortable and I'm like</u>
<u n="898" who="S0587">I just sit there and grin when <unclear/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0585" trans="overlap">yeah you're such yeah you're a creep though you're like yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="900" who="S0587">exactly I I I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just like just trying to think of what to say don't say anything just sort of laugh it off</u>
<u n="901" who="S0585">yeah yeah don't make it like serious <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah bless</u>
<u n="902" who="S0587">five years though it already says it five years</u>
<u n="903" who="S0585">yeah she like <unclear/> my flatmate who like plans has planned when she wants kids and stuff and planned when she wants to get married and things and it's like well <pause dur="long"/> but loads of people say that now they're like oh I want I want kids and like before I get to thirty like everyone well not everyone quite a few people I know say that</u>
<u n="904" who="S0587">that means like if you're that way you got like nine years to like sort it out</u>
<u n="905" who="S0585">to sort it out that's not that's okay though that's not really what I was thinking oh but yeah I don't think that's a short I don't think that's okay <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it I don't he'll be like no <unclear/></u>
<u n="906" who="S0587">no yeah but like it's like daunting innit?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0585">daunting</u>
<u n="908" who="S0587">all the years I've got to sort out</u>
<u n="909" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="910" who="S0587">who I'm going to live with the rest of my life and have a kid with them</u>
<u n="911" who="S0585">you don't have to you don't have to plan it all but that's what they all they've done anyway</u>
<u n="912" who="S0587">they have</u>
<u n="913" who="S0585">mm?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0587">I'm just thinking about if I was going to plan it but I don't know</u>
<u n="915" who="S0585">oh right yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I <unclear/> when she's alright just talk about it her like quite cool yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't even want a kid</u>
<u n="916" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no kids</u>
<u n="917" who="S0585">cos that's what she said she asked me and I'm like I don't have any desire I don't creep me about a little</u>
<u n="918" who="S0587">creeps you out?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0585">yeah plus plus I'm too selfish nine months that's it's at least obviously nine months is carrying the thing</u>
<u n="920" who="S0587" trans="overlap">creeps you out? the thing</u>
<u n="921" who="S0585">and then then you've got to take time off work afterwards and it's like</u>
<u n="922" who="S0587">well it's it's a life sentence</u>
<u n="923" who="S0585">yeah and at least at least those at least three years of your life and nine months and you're in <trunc>pret</trunc>pretty uncomfortable pretty uncomfortable state</u>
<u n="924" who="S0587">mm it's a while</u>
<u n="925" who="S0585">and er and then the next like at least three two years two three years you've got to be there nearly twenty-four seven for this thing kid</u>
<u n="926" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="927" who="S0585">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="928" who="S0587">effort innit?</u>
<u n="929" who="S0585">effort innit <pause dur="short"/> no I'll adopt</u>
<u n="930" who="S0587">it's like what reminds me of you? <pause dur="short"/> I quit at the <unclear/> New Year's</u>
<u n="931" who="S0585">oh dear</u>
<u n="932" who="S0587">hang on a sec</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="933" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="934" who="S0587"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="935" who="S0585">drink?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0587">yeah chocolate</u>
<u n="937" who="S0585">what?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0587">chocolate</u>
<u n="939" who="S0585">what are we doing are we doing the shots then or? <pause dur="short"/> I'll get a drink as well cos then I can like drown it drown it down</u>
<u n="940" who="S0587" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah peach schnapps</u>
<u n="941" who="S0585">peach schnapps it it's so sweet though but yeah it's probably best it's probably the best one for shots</u>
<u n="942" who="S0587">oh yeah I can't <unclear/> is this real <trunc>pe</trunc>peach schnapps though is it?</u>
<u n="943" who="S0585">yeah is it?</u>
<u n="944" who="S0587">not like the last one</u>
<u n="945" who="S0585">what do you mean the last one?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0587">the last one was just like paint thinner with a bit of peach in it</u>
<u n="947" who="S0585">paint thinner with a bit of peach in it? what what have you been drinking?</u>
<u n="948" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> with you</u>
<u n="949" who="S0585">don't think it was</u>
<u n="950" who="S0587">it was</u>
<u n="951" who="S0585">paint thinner with a bit of peach in no way</u>
<u n="952" who="S0587">er? <pause dur="short"/> you can't <unclear>grab</unclear> this anywhere</u>
<u n="953" who="S0585">oh god don't put it in there oh actually we can put it in there cos it still spins doesn't it?</u>
<u n="954" who="S0587">no</u>
<u n="955" who="S0585">does it not?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="957" who="S0585">oh does it okay you can put in there I was going to say you don't want to make a mess</u>
<u n="958" who="S0587">told you</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="959" who="S0585">told you <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> right I'll take it out and find put something to it in</u>
<u n="960" who="S0587">erm <pause dur="short"/> what? take it</u>
<u n="961" who="S0585">go take it go take it in to the kitchen and put and fill the drinks</u>
<u n="962" who="S0587">ah I just got</u>
<u n="963" who="S0585">I know yeah I wondered what you were doing you don't have to come with me though you know you can sit here and talk to the microphone</u>
<u n="964" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="965" who="S0585">whilst I'll rig this</u>
<u n="966" who="S0587">no don't rig it</u>
<u n="967" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="968" who="S0587">bloody hell</u>
<u n="969" who="S0585">I know should we even be doing this now?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0587">no I don't care</u>
<u n="971" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="972" who="S0587">start the New Year</u>
<u n="973" who="S0585">start the New Year it's like ages off isn't it?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0587">no it's twenty minutes</u>
<u n="975" who="S0585">it's not twenty minutes off liar</u>
<u n="976" who="S0587">it is</u>
<u n="977" who="S0585">oh god where did that time go?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0587">I know</u>
<u n="979" who="S0585">she's she's drunk five</u>
<u n="980" who="S0587">five</u>
<u n="981" who="S0585">so I'm like blimey you are doing well</u>
<u n="982" who="S0587">oh</u>
<u n="983" who="S0585">I'm like five what? but okay okay so you get a number and spin it round and then what are we doing?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0587">you get a number?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0585">you pick a number spin it round and then what are we doing?</u>
<u n="986" who="S0587">okay erm</u>
<u n="987" who="S0585">if it lands on your number you drink or?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0587">I think it</u>
<u n="989" who="S0585">or is that too gonna be too difficult? cos I don't think we'll ever get easily</u>
<u n="990" who="S0587">shall we just do red and black?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0585">yeah okay yeah yeah but what we've got two balls there so what if it is it just if any of them land?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0587">no I think we should just do one</u>
<u n="993" who="S0585">there's four shots of vodka in there</u>
<u n="994" who="S0587">ah you didn't what?</u>
<u n="995" who="S0585">yeah you told me to do you told me to do</u>
<u n="996" who="S0587">yeah isn't that like yesterdays?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0585">well there's four shots of vodka in there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I don't know cos I span it round quite a few times I actually don't know where they are the rest are peach schnapps</u>
<u n="998" who="S0587">I hope like that one's not vodka</u>
<u n="999" who="S0585">no honestly the vodka ones so you might be able to guess cos I didn't fill them up that high cos I've got to drink this too you know? but they're not it's twenty-one percent vodka it's not</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0587">is the toffee thing?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0585">it's yeah it's the toffee fudge vodka in there and marshmallow the marshmallow one smells really nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0587">okay I'm gonna do a little schnapps check</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0585">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> you'll go first <pause dur="short"/> mm am I going to get a thing or are you just updating your story?</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0587">no I don't do the story</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0585">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0587"><shift new="singing"/> you want me to you want me to <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1007" who="S0585">oh crap where did that go?</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0587">did you lose the ball?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0585">only the second one it's fine the first one's on there you're spinning go on</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0587">no you first</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0585">no I said you first already so</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0587">er</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0585">pick a pick a <trunc>col</trunc> no you put the ball on afterwards so you drop the ball on</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0587">you do the ball</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0585">me?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0585">okay well what what colour?</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0587">er black <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0585">red you hit red what are you whinging about?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0587">oh I about what to do</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0585">I was going to say you don't drink if you get</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0587">okay</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0585">is that okay?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0587">well this is like guessing that would be <unclear/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0585">I know yeah but it's up to you</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0587">mm I that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1027" who="S0585">oh yeah really</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0587">okay so you have to get it right</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0585">oh you do it for me then</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0587">no I'll do it</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0585" trans="overlap">oh no now I do it okay erm mm <trunc>r</trunc><trunc>r</trunc>red <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1032" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what?</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0585">good thing I had a back up one</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0587">it spat it out</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0585">where is it?</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0587">red or</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0585">oh black okay don't know if I can get this one out</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1039" who="S0585">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> watch it</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0587">watch you er black</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0585">oh god</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0587">is <unclear/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0585">no it's meant to go round the side all the time we've been doing it wrong <pause dur="short"/> yay <trunc>sh</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc>shot</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0587">I've got to do a it means you have to do</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0585">no just just do a shot <trunc>do</trunc> I don't I can't be bothered looking for the numbers on them so</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0587">no but like like same colour</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0585">oh okay yes yeah pick a pick a black one</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0587">ah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0585">ah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0587">I'm scared of the ones with less in it like cos you want to go for them but you said like might have vodka in it</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0585">oh</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0585">is it actually?</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0587">yeah it's definitely not peach</u>
<u n="1055" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1056" who="S0585">is it actually?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0587">it's the toffee innit?</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1059" who="S0587">ah I don't want it</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0585">don't be a wimp you're not allowed to do this</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0587">what the thing I took on the sat chat was erm trying to avoid the voddie got it first time</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm so happy that means it's one down for me</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0587">oh my god</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0585">and you flashed I would say you flashed yourself</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1066" who="S0585">creep <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1067" who="S0587">got it first time</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> such a baby</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0587"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1070" who="S0585">go on oh I can avoid the marshmallow one is it that bad? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1071" who="S0587">dunno</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0585">see look at you all that whinging for nothing but it wasn't even that bad</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0587">no it was okay</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0585">are you okay now then?</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0587">yeah right let's do it</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0585">with your theatrette</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0587">let's do it man</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0585">there we go okay okay oh well erm er black <pause dur="long"/> yes</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0587">I was like I was like</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0585">superman superman go on I spin it but go on <pause dur="short"/> go on you have to pick a colour idiot</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no er black <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1082" who="S0585"><pause dur="long"/> you didn't even pick anything yes yes this is so good I love this game this is like me and battleships last year battle shots</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0587">yeah you did all of them</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0585">yeah right schnappys schnappys</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0585">I know where you are now it's so sweet guess at least it doesn't get your gag reflex but it is like so sweet</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0587" trans="overlap">yeah that's the good thing about it</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0585">red</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0587">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1090" who="S0585">I know I spilled it the peach schnappys ah no wait no I didn't get red ah yes</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0587">ah you said black</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0585">no I said red don't try and don't try and do this go on pick a colour then</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0587">black</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0585">I love this come on give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a shot another one</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0587">what if I get all the balls?</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0585">I know this is gonna be so good if you choose black</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0587">ah</u>
<u n="1098" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1099" who="S0585">oh yes did you say could? loving loving</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0587">ah got a peachy</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0585">ah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1102" who="S0587"><unclear/> ah</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0585"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you know who Greg Davies is? the really tall man comedian</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0585">he said have you seen in like one of his</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0587">say my name</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0585">say what?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0587">say my name properly</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0585">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1110" who="S0587">it's you</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0585">yeah yeah well that's okay I was just going to tell you this quick have you seen in one of his things he was like I don't you might have seen this but he was like when he was talking about he was when he was a teacher and he was like a kid came in and he was like why are you late? and the kid was like sorry sir I was living living la vida loca he was like can't say much to that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1112" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/> faggot</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0585">I know yeah I thought it was funny okay erm oh I go red <pause dur="long"/> come on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1114" who="S0587">oh for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0585">yes this game is so good yeah</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0587">right black is gonna be</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0585">come on black you always pick red and it's <trunc>al</trunc> maybe it's rigged for</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0587">it's not I don't <trunc>pi</trunc> I always pick red oh green so I guess I dunno two shots</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0585">bugger off</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0587">erm I dunno I dunno what that is</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0585">I'm kind of just ignoring zero</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0587">okay I can do that</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0585">I'll give you okay</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0587">I got it</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0585">erm fine fine why are you going again or?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0587">no</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0585">yeah you can go again</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0587">no thanks</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0585">fine so I chose red last time so black <pause dur="long"/> come on do me do me well</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0587">did you put that track?</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0585">ah yes this game is so good <pause dur="long"/> do you mind fixing it no no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1132" who="S0587">as long as you don't slob on it right red</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0585">red oh <pause dur="long"/> oh well done oh I don't know why I'm well done-ing you you didn't do anything er okay now I'm going black</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0587">oh dangerous dangerous game</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0585">oh yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1136" who="S0587">oh what?</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0585">oh my god this game is so good I should I should take up erm bloody maybe yeah I should take up gambling you do you say black?</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0587">mm take up gambling but you always get it wrong</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0585" trans="overlap">mm think I should yeah just go the opposite of what I feel yes do a <trunc>sha</trunc><trunc>sha</trunc>sha =<trunc>sha</trunc>shot</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0587">ah this is definitely rigged</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0585">I have haven't done anything don't don't know how I could rig it <shift new="singing"/> de de de de de de de de de de de <shift new="normal"/> are you okay? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1142" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0585">yep okay erm red it's weird I try and not do a pattern but there's only two to choose from so it's quite difficult</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0587">the fact is it's always black</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0585">it's always black oh no no I've got one okay I'm trying to see which still have water which still have er fluid in</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0587">well you always have to get all the reds cos I've not had a red</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0585">schnappys</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0587">oh what?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0585">I can't get away from the sweetness</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0587">yeah it is quite</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0585">I don't think I can be drinking it all night but</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0587">it's quite tarty <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1153" who="S0585">ah it's so sweet afterwards ah man</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0587" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah man</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0585">ah man er is it yeah do I oh yeah do I put it in go on</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0587">erm black</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0585">what the hell? I'm trying to think of what they say but yes but erm maybe my luck's gonna run out of what you know like the people say? the real like wheelers like they de de de black and white pretty sure they say something</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0587">do they?</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0585">yeah I didn't even choose a colour red</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0587">I don't know if they do what can they say?</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0585">they do say something but it's it's more like it's not like fast it's just telling you</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0587">what?</u>
<u n="1163" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1164" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="1165" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I've stuck cos I didn't want to come in again</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0585">it's fine you can come in</u>
<u n="1167" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I've stuck oh god I've stuck stuck</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0587" trans="overlap">he's quite <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0585">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s done it as like a shine in your face thing</u>
<u n="1170" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh I've stuck I've I've stuck that pudding of yours in the microwave and it's bloody ice cream isn't it? I've just put it it's not melted or anything but it's like</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0585">I was just like but the microwave's not on so it's alright</u>
<u n="1172" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I know but it's once it's defrosted you're supposed to leave it in the fridge</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0585">oh right</u>
<u n="1174" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">tea's in the refrigerator so yeah so I've put it in the fridge anyway</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0585">are we going to have the champagne at? at may as well open the champagne</u>
<u n="1176" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I don't know do you want to?</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0585">yeah well we're not going to open it any other time so it was for my birthday</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0587">was it?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0585">yeah but we didn't open it on my birthday so</u>
<u n="1180" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">if you want to if you want to I won't say no cos I've got now the</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0585">look at your shots hey</u>
<u n="1182" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I won't say no cos I've put I don't just drink it on its own now</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0587">oh don't you?</u>
<u n="1184" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I have to put erm cranberry or stuff in like that</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0587" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="1186" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">cos otherwise it just goes straight to my head mind you I had some Stella I'm not I'm not drunk but I feel as if I've had a drink with the Stella</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0585" trans="overlap">drunk with my mate Stella Stella cos we'll all sing when I hear that though yeah so I said red <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> telling me like fifty-two come on <trunc>dis</trunc>disarray of <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1188" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1189" who="S0585">does she mean just one or?</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0587">I guess so that's pretty fun</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0585">yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0587">pretty</u>
<u n="1193" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">chilled for half an hour</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0585">pardon</u>
<u n="1195" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's not been chilled do you want me to chill it for half an hour?</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0585">no can't chill it for half an hour we've only got eight minutes</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0587">maybe in the freezer might be er</u>
<u n="1198" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0585">just shove it in the freezer for for eight minutes</u>
<u n="1200" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0585">okay wait do I spin? no you spin and I go on</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0587">er red</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0585">that was a poor spin</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0587">I think you just landed on it</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0585">yes</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0587">oh what?</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0585">I didn't know thought so</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0587">that is rigged that is</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0585">how how is that rigged? how could I do that?</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0587">rigged</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0585"><shift new="singing"/> de de de de de de de de de de de <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1212" who="S0587">ah no it's not the marshmallow it's the toffee one as well is that the twenty-one though?</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0585">yeah they're both twenty-one they're both like I thought you're not holding your nose this time look at you go ah</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0587">oh god</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0585">oh no do you need a cup? do you need a cup <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0587">no</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she just said happy New Year's to me disarray of you're fucked <unclear/> you're fucked are you okay? are you going to live?</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0585">happy New Year's happy <vocal desc="laugh"/> over to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1220" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1221" who="S0585"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah man that is funny okay black <pause dur="long"/> oh ah damn it</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0587">yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0585">not yeah yeah you pussy</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0587"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1225" who="S0585">ah man</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0587">spelt it right</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0585">I know yeah happy New Year's why has she said that to me? why is she eight minutes ahead? okay oh I'm scared now is that one that one you've drank all that one do I just pick any colour or do I have to go with red?</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0587">you have to go with red</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0585">black has it got to be black?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0587">er black then</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0585">I drank that one damn it I'm scared now</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0587">that black one is <unclear/></u>
<u n="1233" who="S0585">no</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0587">it's definitely peach though that one</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0585">oh no this is like the one <unclear/></u>
<u n="1236" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0585">marshmallow one</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0587">it's about time you had one</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0585">yeah really scared okay ah the marshmallow's quite nice tasting isn't it?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0587">the marshmallow's better than the toffee one</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0585">I smelt the I smelt more the marshmallow when I smelt the bottles I smelt the marshmallow more than the toffee fudge like I could smell like more flavouring for the marshmallow maybe the marshmallow's not quite twenty-one</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0587">mm</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0585">I don't know which one I read the twenty-one percent off</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0587">okay it's my go</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0585">it smells quite nice I'm going to have a drink of that</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0587"><unclear/> get to me</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0585">oh am I doing it? yeah sorry yeah</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0587">red then <pause dur="long"/> tasty black</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0585">I feel like we need to keep time feel like we're going to miss it</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0587">yeah we might miss it</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0585">just about</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0587">how long have you been recording for?</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0585">mm</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0587">how long have you been recording for?</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0585">so since five minutes past eight</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0587">ah three hours ah yes</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0585">do you want me to stop it now?</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0587">yeah we can stop it now actually</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0585">thank god cos</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
