<text id="SXLD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:12</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-04-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0392 S0398</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>politics</topics>
		<activity>Grandson’s visit to grandma’s  house</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0392">
				<exactage>15</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Newcastle-upon-time</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern/Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Full-time education</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0398">
				<exactage>87</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>80_89</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Darlington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern (Co Durham/Yorks)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bagby near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0392"><anon type="place"/> it says here only had a majority of three hundred and thirty-two votes last time around does that tend to change do you think in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="3" who="S0392">yeah cos they're at they sometimes want to be in <anon type="place"/>  <unclear> as well I suppose</unclear></u>
<u n="4" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0392">and er what do you think about <anon type="place"/> will they?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0398">it would be very narrow</u>
<u n="7" who="S0392">is it?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0398" trans="overlap">very narrow I would think</u>
<u n="9" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0398" trans="overlap">it fluctuates</u>
<u n="11" who="S0392">does it?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0398">yes and erm <pause dur="short"/> yes I <trunc>th</trunc> it can be very <pause dur="short"/> it's a lady mind so I would like to see</u>
<u n="13" who="S0392" trans="overlap">oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0398">yeah I would like to see</u>
<u n="15" who="S0392" trans="overlap">so all the best for her then?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0392">is she standing again this time do you think?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes and she is a young woman</u>
<u n="19" who="S0398">yeah because <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> for us isn't standing is she?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0398" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> well I think they've actually kicked her out haven't they?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0392">they have yeah I could easily see this place like UKIP doing well here</u>
<u n="22" who="S0398">no I don't agree there</u>
<u n="23" who="S0392" trans="overlap">no you not think so?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0398">no no</u>
<u n="25" who="S0392">no</u>
<u n="26" who="S0398">not in an affluent place</u>
<u n="27" who="S0392">actually no you're right yeah <pause dur="short"/> there is a lot of money around here this will be one of the safest seats over at <anon type="place"/> and here</u>
<u n="28" who="S0398" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="29" who="S0392">yeah they are very erm <pause dur="short"/> it just shows you it tends to be the cities go Labour and then the countryside goes blue doesn't it? if you ever look at</u>
<u n="30" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="31" who="S0392" trans="overlap">a lot of the time yeah <pause dur="short"/> all will be revealed will you be staying up?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0398">yes I stay up until the er the first one <trunc>come</trunc> in comes in is Sunderland</u>
<u n="33" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0398">I believe <pause dur="short"/> but the Scottish ones don't come in to the next day</u>
<u n="35" who="S0392">don't they? what time does Sunderland usually come in at?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0398">er about <pause dur="short"/> it is just before midnight</u>
<u n="37" who="S0392">oh right they like to get it counted quickly then</u>
<u n="38" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="39" who="S0392">yeah well they tend to go Labour anyway so I wouldn't</u>
<u n="40" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0392">imagine there's much dispute there <pause dur="short"/> they will be one of <trunc>the</trunc> they will be one of the safest Labour seats actually will they?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0398">yes I would definitely think so</u>
<u n="43" who="S0392">yeah <pause dur="long"/> and then do they all sort of? is there a bit of a gap before the next ones or does that?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes but not too bad one follows pretty quickly after but not that quickly</u>
<u n="45" who="S0392">okay I see <pause dur="short"/> and who is it at Sunderland now do you know? it <trunc>says</trunc>  oh here we are <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is Sunderland oh</u>
<u n="46" who="S0398">yes I knew it was a lady but she hasn't been very <trunc>prom</trunc> prominent at all</u>
<u n="47" who="S0392" trans="overlap">mm no they will change all the boundaries again soon</u>
<u n="48" who="S0398">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0392" trans="overlap">because <trunc>the</trunc> they like to do that don't they? <pause dur="short"/> when do you get your postal vote?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0398">I er just got another one sent this morning for the local elections</u>
<u n="51" who="S0392">of course</u>
<u n="52" who="S0398" trans="overlap">and one for general elections and I think it it tells me when it will be about another fortnight before they</u>
<u n="53" who="S0392">oh okay I would like to see what the the sheet looks like with everyone on</u>
<u n="54" who="S0398">it's in the kitchen</u>
<u n="55" who="S0392">oh</u>
<u n="56" who="S0398">yeah because er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me yesterday they've sent another one out and I just accepted that and I thought what a waste but when I look I've got a second one today but it is for local</u>
<u n="57" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0398" trans="overlap">er so erm I <trunc>h</trunc> haven't checked the dates on it whether they are voting on the same day?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0392" trans="overlap">I think they either do get us <pause dur="short"/> we may as well if we are going to be there doing one</u>
<u n="60" who="S0398" trans="overlap">mm well yes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0392">we may as well do the other at the same time yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0398">but then again older people might get might get a bit confused</u>
<u n="63" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah oh of course yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm what turnout? what do you think that will be like? <pause dur="short"/> does it tend to be high or low?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0398">I think it'll be it will be the older people that'll go out and make the effort</u>
<u n="65" who="S0392">yep</u>
<u n="66" who="S0398">I would like to see more younger people</u>
<u n="67" who="S0392">cos there are a lot of people who can't make their mind up</u>
<u n="68" who="S0398" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yes</u>
<u n="69" who="S0392">and will just say no</u>
<u n="70" who="S0398" trans="overlap">there's a lot of people who can't be bothered</u>
<u n="71" who="S0392">yeah that's not good</u>
<u n="72" who="S0398" trans="overlap">but I am pleased that younger people in schools are taking</u>
<u n="73" who="S0392">yeah because our school have had the candidates in</u>
<u n="74" who="S0398">yes and younger people are getting more involved in politics</u>
<u n="75" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0398">which is a good thing</u>
<u n="77" who="S0392" trans="overlap">that's what we want you can see here there's more younger MPs as well it is not all the same</u>
<u n="78" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0392">mm then because in the Scottish referendum there was quite a high turnout there</u>
<u n="80" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="81" who="S0392">with a lot more younger people getting involved</u>
<u n="82" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="83" who="S0392">which was a good thing</u>
<u n="84" who="S0398"><pause dur="short"/> well yes it is their future</u>
<u n="85" who="S0392">exactly I don't think we'll see something like that anymore for a long time whether it's in or out <vocal desc="misc"/> cos that the Wales woman was saying that she wanted something similar to that for Wales sometime</u>
<u n="86" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="87" who="S0392">she says there's no reason we can't be friends but different countries that's what she says <pause dur="short"/> she came across quite well last night</u>
<u n="88" who="S0398" trans="overlap">she <trunc>came</trunc> I think the I think the woman <pause dur="short"/> most women these days that's involved in politics I think are very good</u>
<u n="89" who="S0392" trans="overlap">she was a nice person that <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="91" who="S0392">and that fella afterwards said that Nicola Sturgeon won the Scottish they say</u>
<u n="92" who="S0398">really</u>
<u n="93" who="S0392" trans="overlap">most people think she performed the best</u>
<u n="94" who="S0398">oh I don't know who were <trunc>s</trunc>saying oh cos there was no mention of it in today's paper but I think</u>
<u n="95" who="S0392" trans="overlap">I think all the</u>
<u n="96" who="S0398" trans="overlap">they are all the same</u>
<u n="97" who="S0392" trans="overlap">all the polls say something different really you can't tell can you?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0398">I felt sorry for them standing all the time</u>
<u n="99" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="100" who="S0398">they must have been tired</u>
<u n="101" who="S0392">they got a break halfway through</u>
<u n="102" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="103" who="S0392" trans="overlap">but apart from that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0398">yes yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0392" trans="overlap">but that wasn't long either just a few adverts</u>
<u n="106" who="S0398">erm <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc>everything goes very nice explaining what they were doing and what they</u>
<u n="107" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0398">were wanting to do</u>
<u n="109" who="S0392">are there anymore debates or is that?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0398">I've no idea</u>
<u n="111" who="S0392">I think there was one that they were going to have a three</u>
<u n="112" who="S0398">like they did last time</u>
<u n="113" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="115" who="S0392">but er Cameron didn't want to have one on one with Miliband that's why they had that thing the other week</u>
<u n="116" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="117" who="S0392">where Paxman just gave them the questions</u>
<u n="118" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes Miliband came over alright but er I don't think he has what it takes</u>
<u n="119" who="S0392">no</u>
<u n="120" who="S0398">to be</u>
<u n="121" who="S0392">it will be really close to call</u>
<u n="122" who="S0398">yeah absolutely I think his brother was the better of the two</u>
<u n="123" who="S0392">at speaking to people appealing to people yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes and he was a big favourite of Tony Blair's because the night that Tony Blair flew flew down</u>
<u n="125" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0398">when he knew he was in he took er <pause dur="short"/> his brother were in that night</u>
<u n="127" who="S0392">what happens? what happened to David Miliband?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0398">he's he went over to the <trunc>Ameri</trunc> over to America</u>
<u n="129" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0398">and he did quite a bit there but apparently he is getting more friendly now with his brother</u>
<u n="131" who="S0392">oh that's good</u>
<u n="132" who="S0398" trans="overlap">there's a possibility he might be coming back but I don't know whether</u>
<u n="133" who="S0392" trans="overlap">cos if</u>
<u n="134" who="S0398" trans="overlap">it would be as a politician</u>
<u n="135" who="S0392">is he going to be standing in the as an MP?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0398">I don't well not at the moment no because that would makenews wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0392">yeah it would so he won't be in the Cabinet then?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0398" trans="overlap">I think he was <anon type="place"/> it was that way I know</u>
<u n="139" who="S0392">he was somewhere around there wasn't he? yes</u>
<u n="140" who="S0398">and this er er because we stayed up that night</u>
<u n="141" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0398">when he said who was taking down</u>
<u n="143" who="S0392">because <anon type="place"/> now is <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0398">oh right</u>
<u n="145" who="S0392">it says here I'm seeing if there's any other people that I recognise on here <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is quite famous from <anon type="place"/> isn't he?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0392">but he is not standing this time <pause dur="short"/> erm like ours isn't standing this time and she's quite oh William Hague obviously he's really well known within</u>
<u n="148" who="S0398">yeah but he's retiring isn't he?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0392" trans="overlap">he's retiring as well</u>
<u n="150" who="S0398">he's been there since he was about 16 hasn't he?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0392" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0398">in politics</u>
<u n="153" who="S0392">yeah he was <pause dur="short"/> but he was the leader at one point wasn't he?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0398">yeah but then I don't think he had what it takes either</u>
<u n="155" who="S0392" trans="overlap">nah his people didn't like him nowadays it's got to be somebody who comes across well on the TV hasn't it?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0398">yeah and you have got to have personality and lacking passion</u>
<u n="157" who="S0392">not good</u>
<u n="158" who="S0398">no</u>
<u n="159" who="S0392">it could be then if you took away the podiums it could be any of the same people speaking</u>
<u n="160" who="S0398">yeah yes</u>
<u n="161" who="S0392">it is not how it used to be</u>
<u n="162" who="S0398">I once went to a a meeting outside and the mayor-elect the council was beaten <pause dur="short"/> by a socialist</u>
<u n="163" who="S0392">gosh I bet that was big news</u>
<u n="164" who="S0398">and people screamed it had never not been known before and they were delighted</u>
<u n="165" who="S0392" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0398">but if that passion is lacking</u>
<u n="167" who="S0392">it is that yeah people just yeah <pause dur="long"/> lack of <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> it says here that <anon type="place"/> they've done a whole page on how it could prove crucial in the fight for control</u>
<u n="168" who="S0398">right</u>
<u n="169" who="S0392" trans="overlap">or it is quite marginal</u>
<u n="170" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="171" who="S0392" trans="overlap">it could define the election <pause dur="short"/> and they've got this fella called <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> going against <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who I presume is the Labour one?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0398">he is a young fellow I believe</u>
<u n="175" who="S0392">he looks like it yeah I'm looking at the result from last time gosh it was very close very close indeed <pause dur="short"/> mind you back then the BNP were standing I don't think they will be having any at all</u>
<u n="176" who="S0398">will they not?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0392">I can't well I can't see them having many</u>
<u n="178" who="S0398">no</u>
<u n="179" who="S0392">because they haven't been on any of the</u>
<u n="180" who="S0398">no</u>
<u n="181" who="S0392">no they're finished they've all migrated to UKIP now I think</u>
<u n="182" who="S0398">I think UKIP will get quite a few votes but</u>
<u n="183" who="S0392">I can't see them taking too many seats though</u>
<u n="184" who="S0398">no I can't but er</u>
<u n="185" who="S0392">mainly around the south east like in Kent and right on the</u>
<u n="186" who="S0398" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="187" who="S0392">where they have got a couple now on the estuary</u>
<u n="188" who="S0398" trans="overlap">and it is immigration there isn't it <trunc>tha</trunc> that get the votes when you get the votes there</u>
<u n="189" who="S0392">that seems to be the <pause dur="short"/> watching him last night he seemed to that was his only policy wasn't it? really whenever he spoke it was about health tourism or something like that</u>
<u n="190" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="191" who="S0392">the turnout at Stockton was sixty-seven point four percent last time around</u>
<u n="192" who="S0398">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0392">I <trunc>don't</trunc> I think that will probably go down if anything</u>
<u n="194" who="S0398">possibly yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0392">it will be interesting to see what the weather's like because that can have a big effect on</u>
<u n="196" who="S0398">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0392">mm because if it is raining people don't want to go outside</u>
<u n="198" who="S0398">and they've got to have people ready to give lifts to elderly people who want to vote that can't go and vote because</u>
<u n="199" who="S0392" trans="overlap">oh that's a good idea</u>
<u n="200" who="S0398">yes and <trunc>I</trunc> I saw it happen once</u>
<u n="201" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0398">and er the Labour man <pause dur="short"/>er  <trunc>I</trunc> I was looking for I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s plans</u>
<u n="203" who="S0392">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0398" trans="overlap">and said well you send somebody around</u>
<u n="205" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0398" trans="overlap">and I was very disillusioned he didn't</u>
<u n="207" who="S0392">because you can vote by proxy as well can't you? send someone in</u>
<u n="208" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="209" who="S0392">I'd never</u>
<u n="210" who="S0398" trans="overlap">but that was</u>
<u n="211" who="S0392">I'd never trust someone to do that</u>
<u n="212" who="S0398" trans="overlap">that was quite a few year ago but there was no proxy voting then</u>
<u n="213" who="S0392" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="214" who="S0398">and it was the Labour people that wanted to go especially older ones and erm he didn't and that particular fellow I forget his name now he was he was elected a Member of Parliament and he was only there for I think it was a month but I can't remember his name I don't know what happened</u>
<u n="215" who="S0392" trans="overlap">mm I remember last time around the UKIP candidate for this constituency died and so our constituency waited months</u>
<u n="216" who="S0398">ah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0392" trans="overlap">after before it was revealed do you remember that?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0398">no I don't remember that</u>
<u n="219" who="S0392">ah well you wouldn't have noticed because you had a postal vote but the people who went to the station</u>
<u n="220" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="221" who="S0392" trans="overlap">had to go a couple of weeks after because they had to fix up who was going to be his replacement and then adopt him and everything</u>
<u n="222" who="S0398">right</u>
<u n="223" who="S0392" trans="overlap">to see if he was alright and then <pause dur="short"/> we all had to wait a bit and it wasn't until a few weeks after until they actually released who had won</u>
<u n="224" who="S0398">right</u>
<u n="225" who="S0392">obviously it were no surprise but it was interesting to see the result</u>
<u n="226" who="S0398">now we had a man <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> he was a councillor for a lot of years a very good man he did a lot of good work and erm he asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would he help that night? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was home from university would he help?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0398">and he said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> enjoyed going around and he was telling people who needed cars and er the practical side of it</u>
<u n="229" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0398">and erm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0392" trans="overlap">and then there's all the people who count up the votes as well</u>
<u n="232" who="S0398"><trunc>absolut</trunc> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who is now an MP</u>
<u n="233" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0398">I think he got in that night</u>
<u n="235" who="S0392">did he?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0398">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0392">how do they count them up? do they put all the ones for the same party on a pile?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0398"><trunc>I</trunc> I've only seen pictures</u>
<u n="239" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0398"><trunc>I</trunc> I would love to be in there</u>
<u n="241" who="S0392" trans="overlap">because there must be some mistakes sometimes</u>
<u n="242" who="S0398">I would like to be there to get get the atmosphere</u>
<u n="243" who="S0392">ah yeah it would be good</u>
<u n="244" who="S0398">I would love that you know it would be</u>
<u n="245" who="S0392">because I remember when they were voting for the London mayor</u>
<u n="246" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0392" trans="overlap">they kept having recount and recount and it was changing so there must be a lot of mistakes because they were recount recount recount</u>
<u n="248" who="S0398">yeah and they are counting late at night as well</u>
<u n="249" who="S0392">yeah and if if you were a biased counter you could either just slip one of the opposition underneath no one checks it do they?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0398">no I suppose they don't no I wouldn't have thought of that but yes I suppose yes</u>
<u n="251" who="S0392">I mean there would massive fines and everything if you did do that</u>
<u n="252" who="S0398" trans="overlap">and I think it is a good idea the polling stations are always closed at nine o'clock they are closing at ten now</u>
<u n="253" who="S0392">ah that's good yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0398">and that gives <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> time to</u>
<u n="255" who="S0392">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0398" trans="overlap">run up he is always the last one because he is late in from work</u>
<u n="257" who="S0392">yeah cos there'll be a lot of people who vote cos I've seen people people <unclear/> turned away didn't they sometimes or is that?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0398">and there used to be terrific queues</u>
<u n="259" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0398">and the people on the door as you went to vote were usually people that were employed by the council</u>
<u n="261" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0398" trans="overlap">in the offices and that and they took your name and that</u>
<u n="263" who="S0392">because there's <pause dur="short"/> at <anon type="place"/> there's those two people who sit there all day long the clerks</u>
<u n="264" who="S0398" trans="overlap">they do they do make a change because I knew</u>
<u n="265" who="S0392">oh do they?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0398" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who used to work there he er he used to say he was always on a morning shift</u>
<u n="267" who="S0392">I see yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0398" trans="overlap">but he enjoyed doing it</u>
<u n="269" who="S0392">because when I've called in with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on the way to school</u>
<u n="270" who="S0398">ah yes</u>
<u n="271" who="S0392" trans="overlap">we've always gone in quite early and seen them there</u>
<u n="272" who="S0398">right</u>
<u n="273" who="S0392">and then going in with my dad at night or on the evening</u>
<u n="274" who="S0398">but young people must be encouraged to go and vote</u>
<u n="275" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah what do you think about voting at sixteen?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0398">I agree with it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0398">especially when they are being educated at school with these people coming in the MP in <anon type="place"/> is regularly in at school</u>
<u n="279" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0398">and I <trunc>c</trunc> no she was not er yes she erm <pause dur="short"/> she is in at school and also one of the councillors whose husband was the Euro MP</u>
<u n="281" who="S0392">oh yeah because you see them in the the paper don't you?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0398">yes but she is really keen</u>
<u n="283" who="S0392" trans="overlap">good</u>
<u n="284" who="S0398">and she is always in at school and I notice pictures and names too of her children</u>
<u n="285" who="S0398">yes</u>
<u n="286" who="S0398">are also always on when she is up there discussing politics</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
