<text id="SXNE">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:30:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0661 S0662 S0663</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Grandma’s flat, Sale, Cheshire</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Films, family, cooking, cars, work, bikes</topics>
		<activity>Having a cup of tea with mum and grandma</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0661">
				<exactage>30</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Manchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Mancunian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0662">
				<exactage>91</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>90_99</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Withington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Mancunian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Sale</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>56</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0663">
				<exactage>56</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sale</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Sale</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>56</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Sales</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0663">I'm a bit neanderthal with regards to what I've seen and what I haven't seen so some of things erm</u>
<u n="2" who="S0662">sit down there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0663">are actually is that recording now?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0663">oh it is okay so some of the films like Pulp Fiction <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to have a poster on his wall Pulp Fiction didn't you?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0661">yeah think I've still got it actually <pause dur="short"/> trying to think where it is it used to be we had it up in the flat and then we had it up in our old house <pause dur="short"/> cos it's quite a gangster film with shooting and stuff and I had a poster of <unclear>pointing a gun at</unclear></u>
<u n="7" who="S0663">yeah and that was John Travolta wasn't it? he was in that wasn't he?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0663">so I remember cos I remember this poster on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wall but I was just saying I've hardly seen any Quentin Tarantino so</u>
<u n="10" who="S0661">had the box set of do you remember? it's the there was the three at the time that were his main films there was Reservoir Dogs which was his first one</u>
<u n="11" who="S0663" trans="overlap">Pulp ah yeah is that violent as well?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0663">right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0662">oh yes <unclear>it would aye</unclear></u>
<u n="15" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>yeah think that</unclear> came out in about ninety-two ninety-one nineteen ninety-two</u>
<u n="16" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0662">made a fuss about didn't it? that it was a bit violent?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0661">yeah yeah I think at the time I would've been seven</u>
<u n="19" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0661">but er <unclear>read about it yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="21" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0663" trans="overlap">thank goodness you didn't watch it you didn't watch it did you?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0661">when I was seven?</u>
<u n="24" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0661">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0663" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>no very good</unclear></u>
<u n="27" who="S0663">well I wouldn't've given you permission</u>
<u n="28" who="S0661" trans="overlap">unless you took me</u>
<u n="29" who="S0663">no I didn't and I wouldn't've given you permission to watch it either</u>
<u n="30" who="S0661">there was no downloading back in them days</u>
<u n="31" who="S0663">no god</u>
<u n="32" who="S0661">erm then there was Pulp Fiction</u>
<u n="33" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0661">about ninety-five I think that was and then there was another one called Jackie Brown as well</u>
<u n="35" who="S0663">no I don't know Jackie Brown</u>
<u n="36" who="S0661" trans="overlap">have you seen that? you'd probably like Jackie Brown it's less violent erm but it's it's got a lot of like soul music in it which is really good</u>
<u n="37" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh right oh no I'll have to say I'll have to say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah I'll watch Jackie Brown then because</u>
<u n="38" who="S0661">mm it's</u>
<u n="39" who="S0663">well I mean the he said he said Pulp Fiction's a good story he said it's got that</u>
<u n="40" who="S0661" trans="overlap">it just it's still <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah plot</u>
<u n="41" who="S0663">he said it's got three stories interwoven into into the</u>
<u n="42" who="S0661">yeah yeah Pulp Fiction's really Pulp Fiction was my favourite film for a very long time</u>
<u n="43" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm oh</u>
<u n="44" who="S0661">Quentin Tarantino was one of my favourite directors but erm since then he's <trunc>d</trunc> he's done a film every two or three years and they're always very violent there was there was one erm there was one about the about the Nazis erm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0661">which was really over the top violence but that's what that's what he does and that's what he's very good at he's broken all these records for the most use of fake blood in films and stuff like that and</u>
<u n="47" who="S0662" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="48" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0661">Kill Bill that was another one</u>
<u n="50" who="S0663">oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I should need to watch that as well</u>
<u n="51" who="S0661">think that's really good and that's <trunc>ba</trunc> it's kind of there's all these homages to like the old erm like Bruce Lee films</u>
<u n="52" who="S0663">kung fu they're kung fu though aren't they? they're martial arts they're not you know <unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<u n="53" who="S0661" trans="overlap">and yeah yeah yeah and so there's a girl in that that wears a yellow <trunc>ja</trunc> yellow like jumpsuit like Bruce Lee used to wear and she has a katana sword and lots of lots of blood <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0662" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="55" who="S0661">it's very good</u>
<u n="56" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well that's the thing I mean although you know it's fake blood it's still quite gory to watch and</u>
<u n="57" who="S0661">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="58" who="S0663">unless it's really relevant to the plot and I mean we don't use guns in the UK and I just think do you know what? I really don't wanna see people having their heads blown off it's really <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's <trunc>r</trunc> it's <trunc>r</trunc> so <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so if I'd been at I'd if I don't know no I think I was I just</u>
<u n="59" who="S0661">well Jackie Brown is more of a it's still it's more of a heist type film</u>
<u n="60" who="S0663">right</u>
<u n="61" who="S0661">there's still bits of violence but it's no it's nowhere near as gory as erm like Reservoir Dogs or <pause dur="short"/> er Hateful Eight</u>
<u n="62" who="S0663">right but you enjoyed The Hateful Eight? well you thought it was a good film</u>
<u n="63" who="S0661">yeah yeah I thought it was brilliant</u>
<u n="64" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was</u>
<u n="65" who="S0661"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really liked it as well erm she just has this problem staying awake in in dark rooms late at night</u>
<u n="66" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0662"><unclear><vocal desc="laugh"/></unclear></u>
<u n="68" who="S0661">especially for long films</u>
<u n="69" who="S0663">cos three hours it was three hours long</u>
<u n="70" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="71" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0662">oh that's too</u>
<u n="73" who="S0663">it's too long</u>
<u n="74" who="S0661">I usually struggle with films that are long but Quentin Tarantino's er I'll always watch them they're just</u>
<u n="75" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="76" who="S0662">well I erm I think a lot of the things you know on on TV that I watch</u>
<u n="77" who="S0661" trans="overlap">my they're my favourites</u>
<u n="78" who="S0662">are two hours and sometimes I think oh it's even that's too long</u>
<u n="79" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0662" trans="overlap">remember when when my mother used to babysit for us and we'd come back and we'd say you know and she'd say it's it's too long two hours and I begin to feel the same like two hours is long and but that's not necessarily a film it's just erm <pause dur="short"/> how can you say? like Lewis or erm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0663">oh an <trunc>e</trunc> like an episode of a of a series</u>
<u n="82" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="83" who="S0663"><unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<u n="84" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0662">like John John Judge John Deed you <unclear>know that even er</unclear> but you know Martin Shaw surely?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0661"><unclear>haven't seen the before</unclear> one?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0663" trans="overlap">Martin he he used to be the Bodie and Doyle in The Professionals that was a series that was probably nineteen seventies</u>
<u n="88" who="S0662" trans="overlap">that's right that's right</u>
<u n="89" who="S0663">and</u>
<u n="90" who="S0662">you'd never recognise them would you?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0663" trans="overlap">Martin Shaw</u>
<u n="92" who="S0662">he had lots of curly hair <unclear>yes</unclear></u>
<u n="93" who="S0663" trans="overlap">now he's gone on and done quite a lot more hasn't he?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0662">oh yes yes</u>
<u n="95" who="S0661" trans="overlap">is he <trunc>co</trunc>? did he do comedy acting?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0663">no</u>
<u n="97" who="S0661">oh I don't know who he is</u>
<u n="98" who="S0663" trans="overlap">don't not really does</u>
<u n="99" who="S0662">and it's been a <trunc>w</trunc> a long time ago but this last fortnight it's been on and I've you know found it in the erm in <unclear>preview</unclear> things you know looked through there <unclear>and</unclear> <trunc>co</trunc>cottoned on to it so it was on every night and it's only just finished this week and it's all it's really all about erm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0663">cos he's a high court judge isn't it?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0662">yes and and Jenny Seagrove's like his love interest and she's a barrister and it's their on-off affair as well and gets them into bother and you know then they whoever they've caught you know he's doing and and the others because he's kind of erm more outspoken and does different things that they don't like him doing erm and he's always got women on the go and these others you know that are kind of erm one's a home secretary and the other one was interfering and there it was trying to pull him down they want to get him off the circuit you know cos they don't like him and so on and he's always one step ahead and he always wins in the end you know so erm it's good but er that's been on now that's it but <pause dur="short"/> I I I like the court scene thingies all of those you know</u>
<u n="102" who="S0663" trans="overlap">they're very clever aren't they? very cleverly written</u>
<u n="103" who="S0662">yeah yeah yes they're very good</u>
<u n="104" who="S0663" trans="overlap">when you think about <vocal desc="cough"/> having to know the background</u>
<u n="105" who="S0662" trans="overlap">but that's two hours I don't mind that cos I</u>
<u n="106" who="S0663">no</u>
<u n="107" who="S0662">cos I think it's good</u>
<u n="108" who="S0663" trans="overlap">it keeps you <trunc>int</trunc> it keeps your holds your interest</u>
<u n="109" who="S0662">yeah depends what you're watching doesn't it?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0661">yeah mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0662">but I wouldn't watch probably what you watch</u>
<u n="112" who="S0661">probably not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0662">I've probably not heard of them you see I mean</u>
<u n="114" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0662">I was mentioning erm Martin Shaw in and then I think he's coming into something soon you know cos he's oh and he did another one that was erm <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>w</trunc> he was a policeman in the North and it was so funny he had a sidekick and they were from the North and they did sound funny and they were and they it was in the days when everybody was smoking you know erm and they had this Northern accent and it seems it's funny then really to hear him talking like he did with this young fellow that was his you know he was training him up sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> depends what you like <trunc>s</trunc> <unclear>you know</unclear></u>
<u n="116" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah yeah right shall I put the kettle on? <unclear>anyone want</unclear> tea?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0663">I was just gonna say</u>
<u n="118" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh I thought you might</u>
<u n="119" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0662">I thought you might</u>
<u n="121" who="S0663">yeah <unclear>that's</unclear></u>
<u n="122" who="S0661"><unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0662">there's some cake there and there's some biscuits which I don't know if they've gone soft or not you'll have to tell me</u>
<u n="124" who="S0663">well well I've just brought the end of a <unclear/> yesterday when I say I cooked I'll use the term loosely I think actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ended up cooking the steaks cos I'd said I'll cook er and <pause dur="short"/> I ended up saying when he got here oops still haven't done my shopping can we go to Tesco? so we went to to do the food shopping <pause dur="short"/> and I bought some steak cos he likes steak erm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I like steak</u>
<u n="126" who="S0663">pardon?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0661">I like steak</u>
<u n="128" who="S0663">you like steak well he's just you know when you <unclear>go out</unclear></u>
<u n="129" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I think everybody does but <trunc>i</trunc> you never know how people like it do you? that's the thing</u>
<u n="130" who="S0663" trans="overlap">I <trunc>kn</trunc> I don't think I cooked <trunc>st</trunc> I can't remember when I last cooked steak</u>
<u n="131" who="S0662">no</u>
<u n="132" who="S0663">and I didn't even cook it last night cos he did it but</u>
<u n="133" who="S0661">but he did cos you wouldn't've let him have it how does he have it? medium rare or?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0663">actually no he <trunc>d</trunc> he probably has it medium</u>
<u n="135" who="S0661">does he?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0663">and I just said give him</u>
<u n="137" who="S0661">do you have yours well done? <unclear/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0663" trans="overlap">then I just said give me the smallest one and normally I would grill it but he got it with a pack of sort of garlic butter or whatever it happened to be <pause dur="short"/> so we we <trunc>w</trunc> we</u>
<u n="139" who="S0662" trans="overlap">had it in a frying pan and</u>
<u n="140" who="S0663">were frying it yeah so we just did roasted</u>
<u n="141" who="S0661" trans="overlap">it was nice to fry them</u>
<u n="142" who="S0663">yeah yeah it was actually very it was tasty</u>
<u n="143" who="S0661">nice to treat yourself every now and again</u>
<u n="144" who="S0663">well it it it wasn't bad at all when I think about it and I mean I shouldn't obviously have gone to the supermarket for steak I was initially in my dreams which is <trunc>w</trunc> how I live my life really I intend to do all this stuff I was gonna go to the butcher's I was gonna go to <unclear/> erm I was gonna buy a couple of steaks and then I thought I'll go and get my some veg and what have you <pause dur="short"/> so I ended up buying a bag of pepper so we had <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> just did roast new potatoes and peppers and onions and then I deep fried some mushrooms so that was what we</u>
<u n="145" who="S0661">er mushrooms</u>
<u n="146" who="S0662">er mushrooms</u>
<u n="147" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0663">well you know how I love mushrooms so and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> likes mushrooms as well</u>
<u n="149" who="S0662"><unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0663" trans="overlap">so there we go so there you go so that's so I got when we were in Tesco erm again <unclear>yeah</unclear> so bad buying all this stuff from the supermarket but we'd got erm a roulade of of Sicilian lemon roulade so I said cos he said you don't like lemon do you? so I said yes I do</u>
<u n="151" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0663">said I thought Sicilian lemon</u>
<event desc="sound of mobile phone ringing"/>
<u n="153" who="S0663">is that?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0661">it's er the plumber but I'll ring him later</u>
<u n="155" who="S0663">oh right erm so we bought this Sicilian lemon roulade so that was <unclear/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0662" trans="overlap">was that nice?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0663">yeah and bizarrely this is so bizarre cos I've never said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as far as I'm aware <pause dur="short"/> that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s parents were Sicilian</u>
<u n="158" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0663">and when we when we went last Saturday night to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="160" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0663"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had done the cooking cos you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> retired now</u>
<u n="162" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="163" who="S0663">I don't know if you do</u>
<u n="164" who="S0662">I thought you were going to say because he's a chef and I thought oh I'm sure he's not a chef oh</u>
<u n="165" who="S0663">no he <trunc>w</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="167" who="S0663">he <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's an <trunc>I</trunc><trunc>I</trunc>IT specialist</u>
<u n="168" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0663">and he <trunc>u</trunc> he cooked a lasagne and he'd done it in a traditional cos if I if I do lasagne I can't remember again when I last cooked a lasagne so I</u>
<u n="170" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm I didn't I used to cook them for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he liked it</u>
<u n="171" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0662">used to make them all the time then but</u>
<u n="173" who="S0663" trans="overlap">put it all together with all the sauce</u>
<u n="174" who="S0662" trans="overlap">but I still didn't like them much</u>
<u n="175" who="S0663">well I I do like them</u>
<u n="176" who="S0662" trans="overlap">it's just the flavours you see that's all it is I'm not used to</u>
<u n="177" who="S0663">well</u>
<u n="178" who="S0661">used to make it all the time for us when we lived with you</u>
<u n="179" who="S0663" trans="overlap">I I did yeah but I used to</u>
<u n="180" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0661"><unclear>lasagne's</unclear> <trunc>h</trunc> nice and healthy with a</u>
<u n="182" who="S0663">salad yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0661" trans="overlap">and some tear and share</u>
<u n="184" who="S0663">yes tear and share bread we've not bought that for a while but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> made me</u>
<u n="185" who="S0662" trans="overlap">what's that?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0663">a lasagne one Mother's Day tear and share bread you put it in the oven and it's just it's all covered in cheese <unclear>all the <trunc>t</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="187" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I did?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0663">you made one for me yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0661" trans="overlap">did I?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0663">it was Mother's Day and it was two thousand and twelve yeah and you made</u>
<u n="191" who="S0661" trans="overlap">two thousand and twelve</u>
<u n="192" who="S0663">yeah you came round and you made you made this lasagne and you <trunc>d</trunc> I think it <trunc>w</trunc>was it a recipe that you'd got online? I don't know if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had done it but you came with his phone did you not remember this?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0661">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0663">how can <unclear/> I remember it I tell people about it sometimes cos</u>
<u n="195" who="S0661" trans="overlap">two thousand and twelve? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0662"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well that's just</u>
<u n="197" who="S0663" trans="overlap">you don't even remember and and he came and he had the recipe on his phone and he had all the ingredients and he'd cooked it all and and it was lovely</u>
<u n="198" who="S0662">where did the bread come in? <unclear>this day</unclear></u>
<u n="199" who="S0663" trans="overlap">no the that was that was when I used to do it when when they were younger</u>
<u n="200" who="S0662">oh oh</u>
<u n="201" who="S0663">but he he it was it was mother for Mother's Day and</u>
<u n="202" who="S0662">and did you just buy just buy er just buy the erm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0662">thank you <unclear>you</unclear></u>
<u n="205" who="S0663" trans="overlap">you buy the er lasagne sheets? thank you very much <unclear>and just yeah you made them</unclear></u>
<u n="206" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the sheets?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0663">and that but he'd he'd put everything together and made all the did it he did it all from scratch</u>
<u n="211" who="S0661">yeah does ring a bell actually</u>
<u n="212" who="S0663">you did cos you</u>
<u n="213" who="S0661" trans="overlap">two thousand and twelve?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0661">seems like longer than that that's that wasn't very long ago was it?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0663">no it was and I just <unclear/> tell you oh <unclear>I can</unclear> tell you again how I er</u>
<u n="217" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no <unclear/> I mean I can eat it and but it's just the slippiness of the pasta I mean I watched Dinner Date you know bet you've never seen Dinner Date have you?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0661">Dinner Date no</u>
<u n="219" who="S0662">well it's where <pause dur="short"/> one <pause dur="short"/> a <trunc>gir</trunc> the girl's the one that's going to be looking for somebody er sort of seriously and</u>
<u n="220" who="S0661">oh yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0662">they show her five <trunc>m</trunc>menus and she picks three of them</u>
<u n="222" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0662">and</u>
<u n="224" who="S0661">I think I have I think I've seen that</u>
<u n="225" who="S0662" trans="overlap">and then she goes out</u>
<u n="226" who="S0663">goes for three different meals</u>
<u n="227" who="S0662">yeah and they they do the cooking and the blokes you know? mean they <trunc>m</trunc>mostly know what they're doing erm but there are people on there that don't like mushrooms and</u>
<u n="228" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0662">and the girl's saying that to the camera mushrooms you know and he's in the kitchen and she oh I didn't say I didn't like mushroom and she you know and then they when it comes like this pile of mushrooms on the side and and she <trunc>sai</trunc> I forgot to say you know but er mostly they they they these days you see boys go to uni and they learn to cook don't they more? so there are more than they used to do well some of the things they do you know and some of these girls are screaming and jumping about you know they put like a a pan on and then they shove something on it and it and then it sparks all over them they're jumping about and they're really silly you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well they pick them ones cos it makes good TV doesn't it?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0662">I suppose so I suppose so and then at the end of course for the <trunc>th</trunc> after the three evenings they she has to choose which one to go out with on a date where she doesn't have to cook so and then er they're talking</u>
<u n="232" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well nobody has to cook they both they just go out to a restaurant don't they?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0662" trans="overlap">they go to erm <pause dur="short"/> yes he picks one of the three</u>
<u n="234" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0662">and the other two there's a</u>
<u n="236" who="S0663">well it's either a him or a her that's doing the choosing isn't it? so there's one time it might be a girl that's choosing and another time it might be a guy</u>
<u n="237" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah that's right <pause dur="short"/> yes yeah or sometimes two blokes</u>
<u n="238" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0662">as well it <unclear/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh right oh so they've had gay couples as well</u>
<u n="241" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0663">oh well I'm sure they will do <unclear/> to ensure that</u>
<u n="243" who="S0662" trans="overlap">erm and then they go out for a meal to a restaurant you see but you see him knocking on the door with a <trunc>bu</trunc><trunc>bu</trunc> er bunch of flowers and the other two have opened the thing you know with a <unclear>cherry</unclear> thing on the top and and they <trunc>c</trunc> and it's erm these are these you know what you get from the supermarket that you put in the microwave?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0662">and sometimes they say oh lovely my favourite they say or they look and they say oh crumbs and you see some of them they just stick it into the bin you know</u>
<u n="246" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0662">or you see them putting it in the microwave and then they sit eating it and they say well I thought he'd've picked me really but never mind erm er good luck to him you know if he picks er</u>
<u n="248" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0662">whoever he picks good luck you know and then you see them having their meal and how they're getting on then they talk to them separately and and they <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> say what they think you know</u>
<u n="250" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0663">cos at the end it just says there's a little thing that comes up that says</u>
<u n="252" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>just</unclear></u>
<u n="253" who="S0663">they had another date doesn't does it say they had a they or they didn't or they're still not said or they're both still single or whatever they said</u>
<u n="254" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they're going <trunc>s</trunc> out steady or something like that they say as well</u>
<u n="255" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0661">lived happily ever after</u>
<u n="257" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0662"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I often wonder whether they get paid and I mean some of them you can see they're really silly I'm thinking what is that bloke thinking you know? I <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="259" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well do you think they just do it? I don't know if they actually get paid cos you have to apply to join these things as far as I'm aware</u>
<u n="260" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0662">supposed to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0663" trans="overlap">do you want this meringuey thing or not?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0661">oh you got a meringuey thing?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0663">well I brought this I was saying about this roulade that I got this <unclear/> <unclear>and lemon</unclear></u>
<u n="265" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>are we having it today?</unclear></u>
<u n="266" who="S0662">oh we're open to offers</u>
<u n="267" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well well it's <unclear/> it'll have to cut into three it's not</u>
<u n="268" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I thought you <unclear>ate it</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> what's this? leftovers?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0661">alright alright</u>
<u n="271" who="S0663">do you not want leftovers?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0661">no I'll have leftovers</u>
<u n="273" who="S0663">you'll have leftovers you'll have leftovers won't you?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh yes anything that's like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0661">so I was thinking about the other day do you remember when er at Scouts we made a spaghetti bolognese and you came into the Scout hut you <trunc>a</trunc> you er I think you and dad and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came into the Scout hut</u>
<u n="276" who="S0663">good lord did we? did we? and you see there's me having a <trunc>m</trunc> I'm having a memory lapse now</u>
<u n="277" who="S0661">yeah cos this er for a badge cooking badge or summat in Scouts <unclear>must've been</unclear></u>
<u n="278" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah I suppose so yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0661">and er I remember being in the kitchen in that little hut making a meal and you came and ate it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0663">oh I seem to vague I'm vague vague memories but that must've been a long time ago for me to</u>
<u n="281" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0663"><unclear>cos could be something</unclear></u>
<u n="283" who="S0661" trans="overlap">cos I remember the old one don't remember the <vocal desc="laugh"/> the more recent one</u>
<u n="284" who="S0663">oh my goodness how strange cos I remember doing something was it my Brownie or Guide cook's badge? and I had to go along to somebody's didn't I have to make <trunc>s</trunc>?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><unclear><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></unclear></u>
<u n="286" who="S0663">didn't I? you shouldn't <unclear>actually</unclear> mention it <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc>was was I <unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><trunc>i</trunc>it's a this is a the least least the <trunc>lea</trunc> person that I dislike at church</u>
<u n="288" who="S0661">oh yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0662">you know the dentist that used to be at the corner of <anon type="place"/>? well the original dentist you probably won't remember <unclear/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <trunc>rec</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s recording this mum</u>
<u n="291" who="S0661">it's alright</u>
<u n="292" who="S0662">oh no</u>
<u n="293" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0662">I thought he'd switched off</u>
<u n="295" who="S0661">which er? is that the dentist we used to go to?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0663">well <trunc>y</trunc> originally you went there I think didn't you?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah yeah long long time ago that</u>
<u n="298" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well didn't you say she'd she'd mellowed a little bit? and didn't you say she was erm?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0662">oh she's making a right <unclear/> right now</u>
<u n="301" who="S0662" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0662">I'm got not in joining in anymore</u>
<u n="304" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0662">I've given up</u>
<u n="306" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0662">I remember when we we lived on on <anon type="place"/> road <pause dur="short"/> and your dad was recording something or other and I was in the kitchen and he was recording what I was saying and when I heard it back I was appalled <pause dur="short"/> thought it sounded <pause dur="short"/> not exactly like Coronation Street but not far off you know?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0662">oh I said switch that off and get rid of it that's</u>
<u n="312" who="S0661">what was he recording that for?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><unclear>just shut up now</unclear> just <trunc>d</trunc> not for anything particular and I think I was just the fall guy you know?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0661">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0662" trans="overlap">say something so <unclear>we could</unclear> hear if it works or whatever</u>
<u n="316" who="S0663">well I think we all don't sound like we think we sound when</u>
<u n="317" who="S0662">no I don't know</u>
<u n="318" who="S0663" trans="overlap">we record it so</u>
<u n="319" who="S0661">no I think it's cos the sound resonates in your in your head</u>
<u n="320" who="S0662">maybe maybe <pause dur="short"/> but I can't tell you while that's recording now what I was gonna tell you about</u>
<u n="321" who="S0663">well you'd have to just make sure you think about it and say it later</u>
<u n="322" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh that looks nice thank you</u>
<u n="323" who="S0663">well it is actually it's quite it's quite <unclear>young lady you know yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="324" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm good</u>
<u n="325" who="S0662" trans="overlap">this card that I'm supposed to be writing <unclear>I dunno what erm</unclear></u>
<u n="326" who="S0663">Tesco Finest so it's er if you like slightly more erm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0662">I'm getting used to Tesco I mean I always call Tesco but I mean I only went to Sainsbury's because I like I prefer parking on the flat and not going round that horrible concrete</u>
<u n="328" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well I I think Sainsbury's is is quite expensive I went in the other day for some bits and pieces and <unclear>everything</unclear> seemed to be more expensive than a <trunc>norm</trunc> it normally is anywhere else so <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>and whether <trunc>S</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="329" who="S0662" trans="overlap">what was more expensive? anything?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0663" trans="overlap">Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="331" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="332" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm I mean I like it I like the store and it's a nicer shopping experience but</u>
<u n="333" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0663">everything seemed to be more expensive to my mind</u>
<u n="335" who="S0661">yeah they have more erm like two for two pound and stuff like that rather than just discounting the prices</u>
<u n="336" who="S0663" trans="overlap">just buy something on their own yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0661">mm Tesco's Finest steak dinners</u>
<u n="338" who="S0662">well</u>
<u n="339" who="S0661">very posh</u>
<u n="340" who="S0662">lovely</u>
<u n="341" who="S0663" trans="overlap">not really it was just me making an effort because</u>
<u n="342" who="S0661" trans="overlap">pushing the boat out</u>
<u n="343" who="S0663">I often buy that two for ten dining two for ten pounds from Marks And Spencer's which is really</u>
<u n="344" who="S0661" trans="overlap">that's good that</u>
<u n="345" who="S0663"><trunc>c</trunc> it is good have you done that?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0663">mm and you get a bottle of wine as well</u>
<u n="348" who="S0661" trans="overlap">it's a bit limited what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can have from it</u>
<u n="349" who="S0663">of course yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0661" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="351" who="S0663">well mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0661" trans="overlap">she she can't have lasagne either so we've not had lasagne for a long time</u>
<u n="353" who="S0661" trans="overlap">although actually I think</u>
<u n="354" who="S0661" trans="overlap">of course cos it's got wheat in it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0661">I think we've got I think someone I think her grandma gave us some gluten-free lasagne sheets</u>
<u n="356" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="357" who="S0661">years ago</u>
<u n="358" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0661">must've gone off by now</u>
<u n="360" who="S0663">not used them?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0661"><unclear>they're probably good</unclear> actually yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0663">well <vocal desc="cough"/> there's a they do a paella which is nice I've had that a couple of times</u>
<u n="363" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0663"><unclear>but it's been</unclear></u>
<u n="365" who="S0662" trans="overlap">what? a what?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0663">paella Marks And Spencer's do this dining two for ten pounds</u>
<u n="367" who="S0662">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0663">you can have <vocal desc="cough"/> you get</u>
<u n="369" who="S0662">but don't you get wine <trunc>wi</trunc> it as well?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear>you</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah a free bottle of wine so you get a main course a side dish</u>
<u n="371" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0663">a dessert and a bottle of wine for ten quid which is very good value</u>
<u n="373" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0662">I see them advertised but</u>
<u n="375" who="S0663">mm <pause dur="short"/> they're very good <pause dur="short"/> so I've had the paella trying to think what else we've had I think there's been a nice lasagne erm <unclear>well there's</unclear></u>
<u n="376" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I think we've had it once actually</u>
<u n="377" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0661">can't remember what we had</u>
<u n="379" who="S0663">erm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0662">but when they they used to do these on this Dinner Date sometimes you know they're dishing it up and there's a plate with so much you know erm pasta <pause dur="short"/> oh and it looks <pause dur="short"/> you just think how could I manage to eat that?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0663">well I suppose if you if you give people too much and they feel obliged to eat it <pause dur="short"/> that's <pause dur="short"/> you should let people help themselves so if you got a dish in the middle they can serve themselves from you can have a small portion and they well almost and <trunc>the</trunc> and then they can help have some more what I was saying about this lasagne that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> made back to the</u>
<u n="382" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0663">last Saturday</u>
<u n="384" who="S0661"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="385" who="S0663">erm <pause dur="short"/> it was cos I was really worried thinking oh my goodness she didn't say at all is there anything you don't like to eat?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0662">who was this?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0663"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0662">oh yes</u>
<u n="389" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0663">so</u>
<u n="392" who="S0662">did she ask you beforehand?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0663">ask what?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0662">is there anything you don't?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0663" trans="overlap">no that's what I'm saying she didn't ask so</u>
<u n="396" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="397" who="S0663">I was only a bit worried cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s hopeless with vegetables and I thought</u>
<u n="398" who="S0661">is he?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0663">yeah and I just thought oh no I hope <pause dur="short"/> I hope it's not something that</u>
<u n="400" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0663" trans="overlap">we'd be noticeably <trunc>s</trunc> you know that people will notice that he didn't have any vegetables you didn't have any vegetables but there you go</u>
<u n="402" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0663">the lasagne was was <pause dur="short"/> traditional <pause dur="short"/> italian lasagne I it had chopped eggs in it and ham in it so he said</u>
<u n="404" who="S0662">ah right</u>
<u n="405" who="S0663">it's just like his mum makes and so he was <vocal desc="laugh"/> he was he was and it so it was Italian style which is a bit</u>
<u n="406" who="S0662">was it nice?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0663">very nice it was lovely</u>
<event desc="sound of mobile phone humming"/>
<u n="408" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0661">I'll have to give that a go</u>
<u n="410" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0661">chopped eggs <unclear>in lasagne</unclear></u>
<u n="412" who="S0663" trans="overlap">in fact I think <unclear><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said</unclear> was it?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0661" trans="overlap">is it like Parmesan or something?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0663">no it was</u>
<u n="415" who="S0661">not Parmesan what's it called?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0663">erm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0661">that fancy ham that we have <unclear/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0663">oh no</u>
<u n="419" who="S0661"><unclear/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0663">Parmesan's cheese</u>
<u n="421" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>er</unclear> yeah I know</u>
<u n="422" who="S0663">erm it you mean the raw stuff?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0661">er maybe</u>
<u n="424" who="S0663">Parma ham?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0661">Parma ham Parma ham</u>
<u n="426" who="S0663">I <trunc>d</trunc> no I no I don't know cos it was all cooked anyway so</u>
<u n="427" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>mm</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> mm was it nice though?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0663">it was nice and I think it was a Jamie Oliver recipe</u>
<u n="429" who="S0661">mm mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0663">so then we all had the conversation about Jamie Oliver's thirty minute meals</u>
<u n="431" who="S0661">really?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0663" trans="overlap">not that I've made any thirty minute meals but everybody has</u>
<u n="433" who="S0661" trans="overlap">they don't take thirty minutes</u>
<u n="434" who="S0663">and <unclear>doubtfully</unclear> that was the whole <pause dur="short"/> that was the whole thing was that they don't take thirty minutes</u>
<u n="435" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0663">everyone loves Jamie Oliver and they're more than happy to do his meals but they don't take thirty minutes</u>
<u n="437" who="S0661">yeah they are nice though er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made a few <pause dur="short"/> not made them for a long time actually but some of the dishes are really</u>
<u n="438" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0661">creative and original</u>
<u n="440" who="S0663">well I think this lasagne dish was out of <trunc>th</trunc> out of there so maybe</u>
<u n="441" who="S0661" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="442" who="S0663">cos he did like a tour didn't he? and he did an Italian</u>
<u n="443" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="444" who="S0663">thing so</u>
<u n="445" who="S0661">we've got a ticket a voucher actually for his erm Jamie's Italian in <unclear>you know</unclear> in <anon type="place"/> the restaurant?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="448" who="S0661"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s er auntie <pause dur="short"/> gave us for <trunc>Christ</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> er for Christmas</u>
<u n="449" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh that's nice is that the one on <anon type="place"/> street?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0663">yeah I believe it's nice</u>
<u n="452" who="S0661">yeah <unclear>it'll be good</unclear></u>
<u n="453" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I so when we went to Brighton we saw I think it was the first time we'd actually seen cos that's going back a few years but <vocal desc="cough"/> it was the first time we'd seen his his actual restaurant we ate somewhere else as it happens but</u>
<u n="454" who="S0661">what his er his fancy one? is that where it is?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0663">well there's one there is one in Brighton</u>
<u n="456" who="S0661" trans="overlap">or the Jamie's Jamie's Italian?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0661">oh okay er cos there there's a few of them there's a couple in London and but he does have a proper gastro whatever restaurant as well</u>
<u n="459" who="S0663">oh right okay</u>
<u n="460" who="S0661">you know where he works and</u>
<u n="461" who="S0663">oh where he actually hangs out?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="463" who="S0663">and cooks or directs people to cook</u>
<u n="464" who="S0661">think so yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0663">mm cos I mean I like Jamie Oliver he's and he's a he's he does champion</u>
<u n="466" who="S0661" trans="overlap">pukka</u>
<u n="467" who="S0663">good causes doesn't he? with</u>
<u n="468" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0663" trans="overlap">regards to diets and <unclear>looking at</unclear> dietary sugar <unclear>at the moment</unclear></u>
<u n="470" who="S0661" trans="overlap">that's what he's on about mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0663">at school meals he did some good work</u>
<u n="472" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0663">erm to try and alter the <pause dur="short"/> way that people sort of perceive school meals but it's about having the children choose the right things which is very hard <pause dur="short"/> when you're there and it's lunchtime and you're hungry and you fancy the chips</u>
<u n="474" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0663">erm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0661">used to eat a lot pizza and</u>
<u n="477" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0661">used to eat a lot of pizza and chips and garlic bread</u>
<u n="479" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm very nice that</u>
<u n="480" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0661">at school</u>
<u n="482" who="S0663">you did? did you? <trunc>g</trunc> I don't think I knew what you ate at school</u>
<u n="483" who="S0661">oh you never took an interest did you?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0662"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what you I can't hear</u>
<u n="486" who="S0663">he's talking about school meals and</u>
<u n="487" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="488" who="S0663"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he used to eat a lot of pizza and garlic bread <pause dur="short"/> and what? chips?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0661">chips gravy <pause dur="short"/> turkey burgers</u>
<u n="490" who="S0663">mm <pause dur="short"/> well that's it and you don't have that choice do you when you?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0661" trans="overlap">very unhealthy</u>
<u n="492" who="S0663">you don't you can't choose for your children you can't say I insist that you have the salad at lunchtime cos they don't want it do they?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0661">unless you give them a packed lunch and don't give them any money</u>
<u n="494" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well we did do that <trunc>fir</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> we did you did have packed lunches didn't you for a long time?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0661">mm <unclear>that's the kind of thing</unclear></u>
<u n="496" who="S0663">I'm not surprised <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><unclear><vocal desc="laugh"/></unclear></u>
<u n="500" who="S0663">I have a packed lunch and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> insisted the same thing every day and I just sometimes people say oh aren't you healthy? and I think yeah but</u>
<u n="501" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="502" who="S0663">here I'm healthy</u>
<event desc="sound of buzzing"/>
<u n="503" who="S0663">cos I've made sure that I only take cottage cheese</u>
<u n="504" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0663">my Ryvita</u>
<u n="506" who="S0662">uhu</u>
<u n="507" who="S0663">my fruit and nuts</u>
<u n="508" who="S0662">well I think you do get into a habit don't you? with them <trunc>a</trunc>and then it quite often</u>
<u n="509" who="S0663"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0662">I used to find that after so long I mean for ages and ages they used to have Ryvita and</u>
<u n="511" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0662">cheese on it and whatnot and thought nothing about it then but when I think now I think god</u>
<u n="513" who="S0663" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0662">how I kept eating that for ages but I think I I think I'm a bit like that now with things</u>
<u n="515" who="S0663">but Ryvita have you can now buy Ryvita in lots of different formats so</u>
<u n="516" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh yes I suppose so</u>
<u n="517" who="S0663" trans="overlap">it it's more exciting than it ever was and I'm just on my quest to buy Longley Farm cottage cheese cos <vocal desc="cough"/> it's so much nicer than all the supermarket sloppy cottage cheese that they do</u>
<u n="518" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0663">and if I ever run out and I can't get to a supermarket that has</u>
<u n="520" who="S0662">do you do without?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0663">Longley Farm well I I've had a</u>
<u n="522" who="S0662">would you like to switch that <unclear/> on?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="524" who="S0662">you know cos <unclear/> forget my</u>
<u n="525" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0662">eventually that's probably when I fall <trunc>n</trunc> asleep and</u>
<u n="527" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well <unclear>just</unclear> take I'm not surprised</u>
<u n="528" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0663">it's tropical temperatures do you just turn it off at at the plug? or do you turn it off?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0662">just switch it off on the plug just</u>
<u n="531" who="S0663">right</u>
<u n="532" who="S0661">are your radiators okay at the moment? they coming on at the right times and warming up?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0662">oh yes</u>
<u n="534" who="S0661">just a bit of a boost is that</u>
<u n="535" who="S0663">oh have you got a camper van T-shirt?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="537" who="S0663">ooh</u>
<u n="538" who="S0662">a what T-shirt?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0663">oh it's not a camper van it's a VW Golf T-shirt</u>
<u n="540" who="S0662">I was gonna say that's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0661" trans="overlap">oh yeah it's a Golf?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="543" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0663">isn't that the one that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes? the mark one?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0661">she does yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so that <trunc>T</trunc>T-shirt was influenced by <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I think <unclear>it was her</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah she might've bought it me can't remember</u>
<u n="548" who="S0663">well she possibly did <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="549" who="S0661">maybe</u>
<u n="550" who="S0663">and that's the only car I've ever heard her ever <trunc>men</trunc> <trunc>e</trunc>ever heard her mention</u>
<u n="551" who="S0661">but erm think she's going off the idea of a Golf now</u>
<u n="552" who="S0663">okay</u>
<u n="553" who="S0661"><unclear>maybe</unclear> something something a bit more realistic cos I'm <trunc>a</trunc> probably gonna have to buy a car at some point this year</u>
<u n="554" who="S0663">are you? is yours?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0661" trans="overlap">when ours packs in</u>
<u n="556" who="S0663">oh right</u>
<u n="557" who="S0661">at the moment it's like got booked it in on Wednesday again cos it sounds like a boy racer car at the moment</u>
<u n="558" who="S0663">oh no but you've just paid lots of money out haven't you?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0661" trans="overlap">it's mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="561" who="S0661">it's a <unclear>bit shame</unclear></u>
<u n="562" who="S0663">is it worth it?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah that's a shame</u>
<u n="564" who="S0663">is it worth it? to spend more money</u>
<u n="565" who="S0661">depends how much it is to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well why don't you ring <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0661">cos he's too far away</u>
<u n="568" who="S0662" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0662">what? to tell you what?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0663">well no it's because I'd spent money</u>
<u n="571" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0663" trans="overlap">it was just <trunc>aft</trunc> just before they went to New Zealand wasn't it?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0663">erm and they paid <unclear>didn't</unclear> you pay about five hundred pounds you know to to get?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh god that's that's an enormous amount isn't it?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> well <pause dur="short"/> to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0662" trans="overlap">you expect that hundred and twenty or something don't you of? <trunc>s</trunc> like you know but</u>
<u n="578" who="S0661">yeah that was including the MOT and service</u>
<u n="579" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="580" who="S0663">but but then you were hoping it would last you a year weren't you?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0663">but it might now</u>
<u n="583" who="S0662">I <trunc>d</trunc> to me I don't think it <vocal desc="cough"/> it doesn't seem to be well I mean <trunc>ba</trunc> perhaps a good thing it doesn't seem to push you know like erm</u>
<u n="584" who="S0663">I know but I think it's probably from a business point of view for <trunc>d</trunc> it probably doesn't do him</u>
<u n="585" who="S0662" trans="overlap">it sort of says</u>
<u n="586" who="S0663">he probably doesn't <trunc>d</trunc> he's lovely he's absolutely lovely and he's been brilliant with you mum and and I I've no complaints at all it's just the fact that</u>
<u n="587" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes I know that</u>
<u n="588" who="S0663">you can lose touch with you</u>
<u n="589" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I've never complained about what he's charged or anything cos I'm sure</u>
<u n="590" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh not at all not at all I just think you just lose touch with him sometimes and I think he he kind of but he would come and he would do it and he usually would pick your car up from your <pause dur="short"/> he'd he'd pick it up from home and it's just</u>
<u n="591" who="S0661">it's too far out far afield for him to come and pick it up</u>
<u n="592" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0661">it's too far to for him to come here to drop it off and</u>
<u n="594" who="S0663">yeah <unclear>I know</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="cough"/> yeah so</u>
<u n="596" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I've done it a few times it's just when there's a garage at the end of our road it's just so convenient</u>
<u n="597" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0663">I know I do you <trunc>th</trunc> do you think they're okay though?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0663">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay fair enough <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0662">you see for the <trunc>maj</trunc> generally speaking if I say <vocal desc="cough"/> you you know could you come and look? erm he'd sort of push it in at lunchtime you know that sort of thing and which is fair enuogh it doesn't really matter to me at all</u>
<u n="602" who="S0663">well he's handy cos he lives locally isn't he?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0662">yes yes yeah <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear>he is</unclear> and he he's he's been very good hasn't he?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0662">oh yes he has he has</u>
<u n="606" who="S0663">oh but we got we went to try your car didn't we? we got in we got in well <pause dur="short"/> we we <unclear/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0662" trans="overlap">we did both get in actually and</u>
<u n="608" who="S0663">we did actually eventually</u>
<u n="609" who="S0662" trans="overlap">you got in the passenger seat <pause dur="short"/> and I got myself in the driving seat</u>
<u n="610" who="S0663" trans="overlap">driver's seat</u>
<u n="611" who="S0662">when we when you moved the seat forward <vocal desc="laugh"/> this happens every time but I always forget to remind anybody you know <vocal desc="cough"/> they get in it and they put the seat to suit them and then when they finish they <trunc>t</trunc> forget you know?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0663">they forget</u>
<u n="613" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0662">erm and then the <trunc>pr</trunc>problem</u>
<u n="615" who="S0663">well the key</u>
<u n="616" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I couldn't use the blooming <trunc>ha</trunc>handbrake could I?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0663">no well to start off with the key well it's completely dead anyway but the key erm the key wouldn't open the door so that was</u>
<u n="618" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0663">the <trunc>fir</trunc> is that the <trunc>f</trunc> your first sign that the battery's dead yeah?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0661" trans="overlap">cos the battery's gone</u>
<u n="621" who="S0663">erm so then I said well we'll undo the door</u>
<u n="622" who="S0662">with the key</u>
<u n="623" who="S0663">er with key which so we we undid the door and then mum got in so you were able to get in weren't you?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0663"><vocal desc="cough"/> and then of course it wouldn't start wouldn't turn over cos the battery's dead <pause dur="short"/> so <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0662">totally blank on the <pause dur="short"/> on the dashboard</u>
<u n="627" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0663">erm but then I got in cos we were messing with the handbrake weren't we? because you couldn't do the handbrake <unclear>could you mum</unclear>?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah I couldn't even get the but then <vocal desc="cough"/> that happened once at at <anon type="place"/> shops and erm I couldn't get out I was <trunc>st</trunc> somebody came and parked right up against me and when I came back to the car I couldn't get I I I was concerned you see and was sort of dithering a woman came by and she said are you having trouble? she said er would you like me to get it out for you? and I just said alright and she got it out and then she got into her car and shot off and she'd put the handbrake on and I couldn't get it off and so of course I she backed me out and there I was blocking like two or three people this is at <anon type="place"/> and then an elderly couple came and I just shouted to the bloke and I just said can you help me? and oh yes cos you know because you're old and you're a woman you see they like it and I said I can't get the handbrake off and he said there you are you know like at the petrol station if I have any trouble there the blokes come and they say there you are petal</u>
<u n="630" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="631" who="S0662"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and I say thank you</u>
<u n="632" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0662">it works all the time it really does</u>
<u n="634" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0662">but it was it <vocal desc="laugh"/> but you see you erm it was on the when you got in the car</u>
<u n="636" who="S0663">well I undid it didn't I? and then I put it back on again</u>
<u n="637" who="S0662" trans="overlap">you managed it</u>
<u n="638" who="S0663">and</u>
<u n="639" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0663">then you couldn't do it but then I I put it on</u>
<u n="641" who="S0662">not so <trunc>f</trunc> tight</u>
<u n="642" who="S0663">a little well quite slack <unclear>by</unclear> the way that that's</u>
<u n="643" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah you see I like I was telling the <trunc>s</trunc> consultant on Friday it's nothing to do with my leg this was me telling about my fingers and whatnot and he looked at them all said yes yes yes and I sort of said to him I said even switching a light on you know on switches I said it's difficult but I mean he doesn't want to know about my fingers really you know</u>
<u n="644" who="S0661">does he not?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0663">well he's he's an orthopaedic man</u>
<u n="646" who="S0661">right</u>
<u n="647" who="S0663" trans="overlap">I mean he's very very he's lovely isn't he? he's really nice really nice</u>
<u n="648" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm you get the handshakes and all you know yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0663" trans="overlap">Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> he's <trunc>fa</trunc> he's really nice</u>
<u n="650" who="S0661" trans="overlap">oh Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0662">and a couple of gooks with him honestly a boy and a <trunc>gi</trunc> a boy and a girl haven't they? and then they <trunc>c</trunc> well and he he he said you don't mind? and I said no and I said</u>
<u n="653" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well they must've been training but</u>
<u n="654" who="S0662">I said good morning to them they both stood there and looked at me as though I was stupid you know</u>
<u n="655" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear>they just said things</unclear></u>
<u n="656" who="S0662">and then lastly I was talking occasionally when I thought it was suitable kind of I'm telling him and then sort of looking at them I got not a pip out of either of them not even a you know?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0662">they must be terrified of him or else <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was their first day or</u>
<u n="659" who="S0663" trans="overlap">think they no they're probably just terrified of the patient and terrified of the whole concept of thinking about operating on people or whatever they're training to do <unclear>well</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0662" trans="overlap">well I should think by by the time oh I don't know I don't know how far along the line they're going remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s grandson you know he'd been in the theatre hadn't he? <trunc>t</trunc> into his second year was he and? oh he was he's enjoying it and he's decided that's what he's going to do surgery</u>
<u n="661" who="S0663" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>ah</unclear></u>
<u n="662" who="S0662">erm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0663"><unclear>back to</unclear> Quentin Tarantino how I just couldn't I <unclear>couldn't couldn't cope</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0662" trans="overlap">and he was loving you know and it's <pause dur="short"/> even though like he said you know he said it was only</u>
<u n="665" who="S0663"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0662">kind of you know holding on to this limb or whatever it was and and she said that when they <trunc>f</trunc> when they're finished for the day he said erm she that the others you know trot off home quite quickly but he stays behind and asks questions and helps to put stuff away and all that you know and he's really lapping it all up yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well that's lovely it's that's really good he's obviously got the enthusiasm and he's</u>
<u n="668" who="S0662" trans="overlap">he's full of enthusiasm</u>
<u n="669" who="S0663">yeah he's</u>
<u n="670" who="S0662">if it lasts till he becomes a doctor <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="671" who="S0663">well no but that's that's good that he's he's keen and that he's <trunc>in</trunc> he wants to</u>
<u n="672" who="S0662" trans="overlap">it is</u>
<u n="673" who="S0663">he's interested and he wants to do that that's</u>
<u n="674" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="675" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0663">cos it's a long training lot of long time in training isn't it understandably?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="679" who="S0663">but mum went because I was working on Friday and I couldn't get I couldn't change it</u>
<u n="680" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0663">erm mum went in the the you rang for the ambulance <trunc>did</trunc> you know <trunc>bef</trunc> she'd booked the ambulance to take her so she had a little adventure on Friday didn't you?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0661" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="683" who="S0662">oh it was great I were</u>
<u n="684" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> was it?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0662">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> well they rang the bell and erm no I don't know who rang the bell cos I <trunc>d</trunc> I didn't eventually I said I'll come down and I came down and somebody must've let them in and then erm as she walked me to the car to the ambulance he was putting the step down and what have you and she said erm yes she said somebody said to us oh have you come for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know who it was that had said</u>
<u n="686" who="S0663"><trunc>some</trunc>somebody let them in</u>
<u n="687" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> cos they were a bit confused</u>
<u n="688" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="689" who="S0662">because on the on my notes I'd got</u>
<u n="690" who="S0663">it didn't</u>
<u n="691" who="S0662">it hadn't got an apartment number it'd just got</u>
<u n="692" who="S0661">oh right</u>
<u n="693" who="S0662" trans="overlap">number thirty so they didn't know which to press you see I thought I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s away anyway but everybody presses number one you see if they're stuck so poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she said</u>
<u n="694" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="695" who="S0662">don't ever buy a flat flat number one don't</u>
<u n="696" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="697" who="S0662">but you see she likes to look at everything doesn't she? and looks at all the bins and I'll do it for you you know?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0663">she is the bin police she actually is the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/> which is fine cos we do the right thing don't we with the bins? we're actually really good with our recycling but</u>
<u n="701" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0663">yeah which is yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0662" trans="overlap">so we had we went to <anon type="place"/> they said there's only you and erm another lady at <anon type="place"/> well <anon type="place"/> it's like other like <anon type="place"/> it was enormous went we went <trunc>or</trunc> I didn't <trunc>rec</trunc> apart from you know the main road and the <anon type="place"/> centre sort of thing I didn't recognise anywhere in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="704" who="S0661">oh right</u>
<u n="705" who="S0662">loads and loads of streets and <trunc>s</trunc>semis all over you know turn into this street and the bins are out and into this street and round the corner and then you think oh they'll be stopping in a minute and and they drive a bit further and then they turn left and right and and they eventually stop at the right spot and and he went he got out cos she sat with me chatting and he drove and he went and knocked at the door and the door opened and a face came and said something and then she shut the door then disappeared and he stood around and then she came out a minute or two later and she said er oh hello and all this and you know quite she's been in every hospital in <anon type="place"/> she says and around and so she got in and introduced herself and she was American she's lived here thirty-five years and</u>
<u n="706" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0662">she said what was my name? and I said oh she said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said oh there's not many get that one right cos she'd be middle-aged you know</u>
<event desc="sound of bird chirping"/>
<u n="708" who="S0662">and er so I said what's your what's your name? and she said erm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>is that the budgie?</unclear></u>
<u n="710" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0662"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she said my parents come from the <trunc>R</trunc>Ukraine and she said people forget the A on the end but the they they I said they call you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yes but mine's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="713" who="S0662">I said right so <pause dur="short"/> she talks all the way to the hospital we were ages getting to the hospital I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe</u>
<u n="714" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0662">when we came back</u>
<u n="716" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm yeah it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="717" who="S0662" trans="overlap">with this young woman that drove us back in her car erm was just straight up <anon type="place"/> road and straight round the roundabout <anon type="place"/> road and home you know home territory sort of thing</u>
<u n="718" who="S0663">oh they'll've just gone a different route won't they? because</u>
<u n="719" who="S0662" trans="overlap">heavens above oh it was ages</u>
<u n="720" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0662">just about got there just about quarter past ten which was my time you know? but coming back then erm she picked me up and it was so near and I'd <trunc>te</trunc> so they put erm salt down outside that entrance and number one entrance there and I <unclear>remember</unclear> looking at that and talking about that and the next minute she said here we are and looked up and there was this car with all sorts of colours so I don't didn't have time to see what it said on it but it was obviously sprayed for you know for what it would be</u>
<u n="722" who="S0663" trans="overlap">transportation <unclear>colours</unclear> that sort of a yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes that's right but she was nice and it was a nice car but heck it was <trunc>he</trunc> not very good to get in the back seat she opened it and</u>
<u n="724" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="725" who="S0662">cor there wasn't much room at all and I said oh I said <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc><trunc>ho</trunc> I'll see how we go and I said is it any better if I get in the front? and she said no so</u>
<u n="726" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0662">she had to kind of</u>
<u n="728" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0662">I got as far as I could and she had to get hold of my foot and lift my right one in and then lift my left one in and then after that she she fastened my seatbelt and that was it so the next thing we went to the <trunc>n</trunc> place where this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> where she'd been and I thought I bet it's her we're picking up now and sure enough out she comes from the place ah my friend hello hello hello</u>
<u n="730" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0662">can you hold a stick? and can you? can you hold my coat and then I can perhaps see if I can't manage to cos she was a big woman <trunc>c</trunc>can't <trunc>man</trunc> cos I'd have to do the seatbelt er she got in and you know we <trunc>ha</trunc> she talked all the way</u>
<u n="732" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="733" who="S0662">all down <anon type="place"/> road and I'm looking at the at <trunc>ev</trunc>everything else and she's waffling on about <pause dur="short"/> about New York and yes New York she liked she liked New York yeah yes but er and the driver said I want to go to New York when it's New Year's Eve and all this and</u>
<u n="734" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0663">Times Square isn't it? is it the big?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="737" who="S0663">it is a big celebration isn't it the <pause dur="short"/> times Square?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0662" trans="overlap">it is I think isn't it?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0663">I think they drop the</u>
<u n="740" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0663">there's a big</u>
<u n="742" who="S0661">big ball on a stick</u>
<u n="743" who="S0663" trans="overlap">ball isn't there that they drop?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0662">there's a what?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0663"><trunc>in</trunc> there's a like a ball in</u>
<u n="746" who="S0662">oh right</u>
<u n="747" who="S0663" trans="overlap">that that drops and</u>
<u n="748" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="749" who="S0663">and</u>
<u n="750" who="S0661">on top of a building</u>
<u n="751" who="S0663">pardon?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0661">is it is is it on top of a building or is it?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0663">yes I think yes it is</u>
<u n="754" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="755" who="S0663">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0661">I've heard they have to you have to queue up from sort of <pause dur="short"/> midday</u>
<u n="757" who="S0663">to get a space in Times Square</u>
<u n="758" who="S0661" trans="overlap">to yeah to be able to see it and you're not allowed to leave so you can't</u>
<u n="759" who="S0662">ah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0661">go to the toilet or anything like that</u>
<u n="761" who="S0663">oh so you can't really drink much</u>
<u n="762" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="763" who="S0663">not really that much fun is it then if you can't really <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0661" trans="overlap">sounds pretty pretty <unclear>bad yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="765" who="S0663" trans="overlap">have a nice cup of coffee</u>
<u n="766" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0663">and some nice sugary food <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0662">said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that would be a nice job for her that erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>t</trunc>taking people and dropping them off and coming back you know</u>
<u n="769" who="S0663" trans="overlap">it's a nice a nice erm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="771" who="S0662">but the only thing I mean it works fine and I'm quite happy now so if I have to do it again I'll I'll know because I had to be <pause dur="short"/> the appointment was quarter past ten but I had to be ready for eight o'clock you see cos</u>
<u n="772" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="773" who="S0662">so course there I am ready before eight o'clock and had to wait till about quarter past nine twenty past nine when they came</u>
<u n="774" who="S0661">oh really?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0662">not that it mattered I mean as long as you're ready that's all that matters really isn't it?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0663" trans="overlap">just depends how many people they've got to pick up and where from</u>
<u n="778" who="S0662">that's right</u>
<u n="779" who="S0663" trans="overlap">cos obviously if they're driving all around the area and if they're driving around <pause dur="short"/> starting at eight o'clock they're they're in the mid of</u>
<u n="780" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0663">mid</u>
<u n="782" who="S0662">it was just the <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="783" who="S0663" trans="overlap">rush hour traffic <unclear>still you have to</unclear></u>
<u n="784" who="S0662" trans="overlap">it's just waiting cos</u>
<u n="785" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0662">but you know there's only by the time you know it was <trunc>t</trunc> I'd finished there was only about five people left waiting and she was <trunc>d</trunc> wiping the names and things off the boards and everything they were all obviously getting ready to close down for lunch I suppose and er so then I had to tell them at the desk <pause dur="short"/> that they hadn't got a number <vocal desc="sigh"/> of the flat and she said oh no I haven't have I? and then she said oh well anyway you're discharged today so right so then they another one came and said <trunc>y</trunc>you do know don't you? black girl she said er nurse she said you do know that you've got quite a wait she said you could wait up to two hours I said well so be it you know I that's it and so on so</u>
<u n="787" who="S0663">did you wait about an hour did you <trunc>s</trunc> then?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="789" who="S0662">yes about an hour</u>
<u n="790" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="791" who="S0662">but by this time the ones that were left you see they were all getting quite agitated because they were so late you know?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="793" who="S0662">you know what it's like when you go in there's lots of people there and then they all keep going in and out in and out and nobody calls your name and <pause dur="short"/> there's a couple <trunc>o</trunc>opposite to me and she was chinwagging to her husband about <pause dur="short"/> obviously she was fed up and what they doing about her? I'm going to ask and he's tried to shut her up you know and saying no don't go and ask don't go I I'm going I'm going to going to see and she took off and came back I don't know what she said to him but <pause dur="short"/> he was looking at his watch and she was saying but you will manage to <trunc>b</trunc> get get home before you're ready before you're due to work won't you? and you know the usual sort of pattern I suppose</u>
<u n="794" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah people are watching the clock</u>
<u n="795" who="S0662">anyway eventually they got seen and they came back and as she came back she went <vocal desc="sigh"/> cheerio and off she went and then two minutes later she came back and she said erm where do you live? so I said <anon type="place"/> she said cos my husband said would you like him to take you home? you know so I said well thanks that's very kind but I said I better not upset the system you know better just wait so she said <unclear>go on then</unclear></u>
<u n="796" who="S0663" trans="overlap">that wasn't it wasn't it kind though? I thought that was really cos people normally just</u>
<u n="797" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="798" who="S0662">cos they were fed up they'd been there all morning you know and</u>
<u n="799" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0662"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0663">people are kind aren't they? you know you just think that there are sort of</u>
<u n="802" who="S0662" trans="overlap">ready to get home</u>
<u n="803" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0662" trans="overlap">but your dad would've done that you see</u>
<u n="805" who="S0663" trans="overlap">he would've absolutely absolutely</u>
<u n="806" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm ah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0663">the kindness of strangers</u>
<u n="808" who="S0662">and course the telly goes on and so you've all got your head turned like <trunc>i</trunc> this you know getting neck ache watching Escape to the Country and</u>
<u n="809" who="S0663">reading the subtitles cos you can't hear it or <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>but</unclear> how's work been this week for you?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0661">er it's been alright yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0663">have you started your new <pause dur="short"/> job yet?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0663" trans="overlap">ooh oh cos you was that your meeting in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0661">yeah yeah that's the first one</u>
<u n="815" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="816" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0662">in the picture now</u>
<u n="818" who="S0661">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah so erm yeah did a day of that on Tuesday so I'm splitting my time between that new job two days a week and the FA three days a week</u>
<u n="819" who="S0662">oh that's probably good isn't it like that?</u>
<u n="820" who="S0663">well it's variety isn't it?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah it was yeah I think it's good</u>
<u n="822" who="S0663" trans="overlap">I think and it also keeps erm</u>
<u n="823" who="S0662">yes</u>
<u n="824" who="S0663">it keeps you kind of</u>
<u n="825" who="S0662">in the link with what you've been doing</u>
<u n="826" who="S0663" trans="overlap">in with a <trunc>f</trunc>foot in each camp</u>
<u n="827" who="S0662">yes</u>
<u n="828" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0663">good experience and</u>
<u n="830" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0663">erm <pause dur="short"/> you're working with different people as well?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0661">yeah yeah yeah it's good</u>
<u n="833" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm so how how is the new? are you just sort of getting your head around the new <pause dur="short"/> position?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0661">yeah yeah and er tomorrow I've gotta hand over some <trunc>s</trunc> some of the old <pause dur="short"/> older stuff that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to do</u>
<u n="835" who="S0663">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0661" trans="overlap">now he's left</u>
<u n="837" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="838" who="S0661">so I kind of was doing <pause dur="short"/> did a bit of in the lead-up to Christmas I called him before and now someone else is gonna do that cos I'm doing other things and then erm er between tomorrow some point tomorrow and Tuesday I'll be doing a bit more of an intro into this new job and then <pause dur="short"/> wednesday Thursday Friday I'll be in <anon type="place"/> again doing EFA for three days</u>
<u n="839" who="S0663">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0661"><unclear/> to put it out like that</u>
<u n="841" who="S0663">but it's easier for you to get into <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0661">yeah it's easier than getting to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="843" who="S0663">do you still cycle or do you go in <pause dur="short"/> on the train?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0661" trans="overlap">no it's <trunc>diff</trunc> you get the train cos it's <pause dur="short"/> I have got access to the they have showers and stuff and lockers but</u>
<u n="845" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="846" who="S0661">I can access the showers with my key but I can't <pause dur="short"/> there's no free lockers without a locker</u>
<u n="847" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh no no</u>
<u n="848" who="S0661">I can't fit enough stuff in my bag I'd have to <trunc>t</trunc> I'd have to take like my shoes and my suit</u>
<u n="849" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="850" who="S0661">then just leave them there all the time</u>
<u n="851" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="852" who="S0661">just bring like my shirts and stuff but</u>
<u n="853" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="854" who="S0661">without a locker I can't it's too much stuff it doesn't fit in my bag so I can't really do it</u>
<u n="855" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="856" who="S0662">no</u>
<u n="857" who="S0661">and I cos I've got that at <anon type="place"/> at the <anon type="place"/> office</u>
<u n="858" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="859" who="S0661"><unclear/></u>
<u n="860" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="861" who="S0662">how long does it take you to go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0661">erm well I drove</u>
<u n="863" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="864" who="S0661">er in a hire car and it was about</u>
<u n="865" who="S0662" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="866" who="S0661">cos it's it was at <anon type="place"/> which is erm off you see it you drive past it when you go on the M6 so it's not in the centre of <anon type="place"/> it's a bit out</u>
<u n="867" who="S0662">uhu</u>
<u n="868" who="S0661">erm and it's a bit difficult to get to on public transport but it took about a good two hours cos in the traffic</u>
<u n="869" who="S0662">ah</u>
<u n="870" who="S0663">see that's the problem isn't it? no matter where you go the traffic is er is so heavy</u>
<u n="871" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah yeah you got <trunc>f</trunc> to find that out when you get there I suppose</u>
<u n="872" who="S0663" trans="overlap">so did you enjoy driving the hire car because?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0661">yeah it was nice for a change</u>
<u n="874" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0663">something that well goes without making a noise and</u>
<u n="877" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it was a Vauxhall</u>
<u n="878" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="879" who="S0661">Astra</u>
<u n="880" who="S0663">oh right okay they're quite nippy aren't they? the <trunc>Vau</trunc></u>
<u n="881" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah it was one point six as well so it was pretty good</u>
<u n="882" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="883" who="S0662" whoConfidence="low">mm mm</u>
<u n="884" who="S0661">but erm yeah I've been <trunc>look</trunc></u>
<u n="885" who="S0662" trans="overlap">good</u>
<u n="886" who="S0661">been looking at something like a <pause dur="short"/> ford Focus or a maybe a Fiesta</u>
<u n="887" who="S0663">Fiesta were when I was looking for mine Fiesta were the top small car</u>
<u n="888" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0663">erm I was looking on What Car? <trunc>What</trunc>What Car? yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0662" trans="overlap">were they?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0663">yeah erm yeah yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum has a Fiesta doesn't she?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0661">mm she got a Corsa</u>
<u n="893" who="S0663">oh maybe that she doesn't then <vocal desc="laugh"/> it looks like a Fiesta it's a Corsa scrub that erm but yeah Ford Fiesta there's a lad at work who's who has a Ford Fiesta and he he <trunc>thin</trunc> he loves his but he he got the kinda top of the range and spent a lot of money on</u>
<u n="894" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="895" who="S0663">on the on his Fiesta but</u>
<u n="896" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="897" who="S0663">he he really likes it but they did win the the sort of the award or whatever that</u>
<u n="898" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0663">when I was looking for mine</u>
<u n="900" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="901" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="902" who="S0662">cos I remember the Fiesta because erm</u>
<u n="903" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear>think he</unclear></u>
<u n="904" who="S0662">er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had <pause dur="short"/> a Fiesta when she first learnt to drive and I thought <pause dur="short"/> you know it's a long time and I mean I've been <pause dur="short"/> I've been left thirty years so it's a long time ago and how many you know different Fiestas have they <pause dur="short"/> made over the you know the updating and whatnot? and I don't know what they're</u>
<u n="905" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="906" who="S0662">what they're like now</u>
<u n="907" who="S0663">well it's <unclear>erm</unclear></u>
<u n="908" who="S0661" trans="overlap">they're bigger than they used to be</u>
<u n="909" who="S0662">yes</u>
<u n="910" who="S0663">erm I we we've had this conversation in fact I did with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's got the Fiesta because I was saying small cars are not as small as they were it's like the</u>
<u n="911" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="912" who="S0663">Yaris used to be a small car</u>
<u n="913" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="914" who="S0663">it's now a bigger Yaris than it was before</u>
<u n="915" who="S0662">oh is it?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0663">and your Fiestas your Renault the Renault the Renault Clio</u>
<u n="917" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="918" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="919" who="S0663">is now a bigger Renault Clio so whatever you buy that's a small car</u>
<u n="920" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="921" who="S0663">it's not actually that small but</u>
<u n="922" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="923" who="S0663">then if you do need <trunc>m</trunc> quite a lot of motorway driving maybe a little bit bigger</u>
<u n="924" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="925" who="S0663">might be</u>
<u n="926" who="S0661" trans="overlap">well that's what I thought I <trunc>d</trunc> I that's why I wanted a either something on along the lines of a Golf</u>
<u n="927" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="928" who="S0661">which well Golfs are too are too expensive for what they are plus this whole cheat device</u>
<u n="929" who="S0662"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0661">scandal</u>
<u n="933" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="S0661">is a bit off-putting as</u>
<u n="935" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="936" who="S0661">as well so maybe a <trunc>F</trunc> maybe a Focus or like a Seat Leon you know that kind of slightly bigger</u>
<u n="937" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have just bought a Leon</u>
<u n="938" who="S0661" trans="overlap">body shape <pause dur="short"/> have they?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0663">yeah they have cos I was saying oh it has the engine of a Volkswagen doesn't it? cos it does doesn't it?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0661">is the whole the whole thing chassis the all the Seat <pause dur="short"/> volkswagen and Audi are all essentially the same car</u>
<u n="941" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah they do <pause dur="short"/> they do</u>
<u n="942" who="S0661">for the sort of from the little hatchbacks to the saloons</u>
<u n="943" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0663">cos I was saying I was saying this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about the Volkswagen and then he said yes but he said Audi are in that group and he and he <trunc>s</trunc> cos he has an Audi and</u>
<u n="945" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="946" who="S0663" trans="overlap">and it just must <trunc>m</trunc>mean that at some point if Volkswagen have been up to whatever they've been up to</u>
<u n="947" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="948" who="S0663">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="949" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="950" who="S0663">cheat <trunc>n</trunc> well it's it's about it's about the emissions isn't it? it's about giving incorrect <unclear>scores <trunc>adj</trunc></unclear> adjusting the computer to</u>
<u n="951" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="952" who="S0663">saying that their emissions are better than</u>
<u n="953" who="S0662" trans="overlap">well I bet they've lost a lot of you know potential customers</u>
<u n="954" who="S0661">well yeah</u>
<u n="955" who="S0662">people will go won't they?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0663">well it'll be it'll be very very bad for business very bad for business but</u>
<u n="957" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes it will</u>
<u n="958" who="S0663" trans="overlap">but Volkswagen are such a sought after</u>
<u n="959" who="S0662">yes yes that's right</u>
<u n="960" who="S0663" trans="overlap">car and everybody loves the Golf in fact the Golf was the number the people's car did you see the James May?</u>
<u n="961" who="S0661">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="962" who="S0663">that you see that tells you to</u>
<u n="963" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm oh really?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0663">to buy a Volkswagen Golf cos everybody wants a Volkswagen Golf but if you want a GTI those are the ones that people want to steal off you so</u>
<u n="965" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="966" who="S0663">it's probably not good to have a GTI unless you really want to have that engine erm <pause dur="short"/> and I like the Scirocco if I was just choosing a little bit of a <pause dur="short"/> sporty type car</u>
<u n="967" who="S0662" trans="overlap">so who makes that?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0663">Volkswagen</u>
<u n="969" who="S0662">it's a Volkswagen one?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm and I was</u>
<u n="971" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="972" who="S0663">telling I was telling <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she said she's gonna get herself another car and well they've got this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got the <trunc>Le</trunc> <trunc>Se</trunc>Seat Leon but she was saying that they were talking about a <pause dur="short"/> oh no I'm gonna say a erm not a Kia what are the? Skoda and so</u>
<u n="973" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="974" who="S0663">she was just saying she said she said I'm not having she cos they don't really worry that much about well she she <trunc>w</trunc> said I'm not having a Skoda and that because the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they'd had a a Skoda and and it was supposed to be a very very good you get more for your money definitely definitely <unclear>out of it</unclear></u>
<u n="975" who="S0662" trans="overlap">well I thought it <trunc>w</trunc> I thought Skodas were all a joke you know?</u>
<u n="976" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="977" who="S0663">well that's what I'm saying <trunc>i</trunc> they're not very cool so I actually said</u>
<u n="978" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0663">I said cos I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s car was a was a very nice car but what what I'm saying is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just sort of suddenly thought right no I am not having an uncool <trunc>ca</trunc> so I said no I said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't have an uncool car so we had a conversation then about what was a fairly cool car to have you see</u>
<u n="980" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="981" who="S0663">so she was thinking something along the lines of a Volkswagen but she said they were expensive she we were talking about the Polo and the Golf and said she said the same thing they're expensive they don't want another Seat because they've already got one so she wanted something</u>
<u n="982" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="983" who="S0663">and she said that she'd had a Scirocco cos I said I don't like the Sciroccos <vocal desc="laugh"/> I said what about one of those? so she said I've had one in the past she said but</u>
<u n="984" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="985" who="S0663">and</u>
<u n="986" who="S0662" trans="overlap">are they expensive? are they high are they high? er</u>
<u n="987" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> they'd</u>
<u n="988" who="S0662">er</u>
<u n="989" who="S0663">be high insurance group I think and I think that's what because I was when I was looking it was kind of I was like mm a little bit well I mean I <trunc>w</trunc> I probably wouldn't've bought one because it would've been the <trunc>expens</trunc> er expensive insurance and</u>
<u n="990" who="S0662" trans="overlap">but you were talking about the Yaris weren't you for quite a while?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0663">well I was because I do like the Yaris</u>
<u n="992" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="993" who="S0663">and the Yaris in fact if you if you're looking for reliability er Honda and Toyota</u>
<u n="994" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0663">are the most what did I say? yeah <trunc>Hon</trunc> no sorry Honda and Nissan but <trunc>T</trunc>Toyota are</u>
<u n="996" who="S0661" trans="overlap">most of most of the Japanese sort of you know Eastern <unclear>companies</unclear></u>
<u n="997" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah I'd <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="998" who="S0662">but Honda were were erm <pause dur="short"/> very well-known long ago I I remember everybody you know well at that stage they were talking about Japanese engines were so so</u>
<u n="999" who="S0663">reliable</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0662">yes yes</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0663">well my cousin's got the Jazz and but and she likes the car but she's now saying not that she just she just said <pause dur="short"/> I do and I like hers cos it's got the glass it's got the panoramic roof which is lovely <pause dur="short"/> however it is more of an older person's car and she's now saying she wish she'd got something a little bit more</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0662">modern?</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0663"><trunc>tr</trunc> <trunc>m</trunc> well not not modern cos it was a brand new car but</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0663">little bit more cool is what I mean trying to move back to cool cool now so</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>I would be</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> is worry about what miles you get to the gallon and things like that</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well no you do it's all in the mix but then you also want to enjoy driving it</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0663">you spend a lot of money on it and <pause dur="short"/> you also don't necessarily want <pause dur="short"/> something that's considered to be very very uncool because <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0662">depends how much money you've got doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>reputation er as well</unclear></u>
<u n="1013" who="S0663">yes absolutely yeah this is it</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0662">what did he say?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0663">he's got you got a reputation to protect which is why I would say</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0663">I mean Ford Focus are very erm reliable I would've thought</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0662">that's a Ford isn't it the Focus?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0663" trans="overlap">it is Ford and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s had one for years and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s had one and you know they they do like theirs very much but I would've said again like the Honda Jazz it's an older person's car</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0661">a Focus?</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0661">you think?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0662">it probably sounds to me like a</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0663" trans="overlap">I kinda that's that's that's my image but</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0662" trans="overlap">like a like a Ford ordinary you know dead <trunc>s</trunc> dead standard</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc>nothing <trunc>s</trunc> not not that <trunc>s</trunc> not that special</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0662" trans="overlap">ordinary car you know not</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0662">don't worry about what it looks you know if it's cool or otherwise the sort of car that people would <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>b</trunc> say was reliable and they could you know drive all over with it and not worry about</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well I suppose nobody wants to mug you for the keys <pause dur="short"/> particularly</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0661" trans="overlap">well it the new models have they do <trunc>sport</trunc> really sporty ones now and</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0663">do they?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0661">they were on Top Gear there was this they called it the er</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0661">the ASBO cos it was this bright orange thing</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0662">what was that? <unclear/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0663"><unclear><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friend</unclear></u>
<u n="1044" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they Top</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0662" trans="overlap">they what?</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0661">Top Gear called the <trunc>For</trunc> the Ford Focus the ASBO</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0661">you know <trunc>ant</trunc>antisocial behaviour erm</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1050" who="S0662">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0661">cos it was a bit of a a bit of a boy racer car <pause dur="short"/> so a bit a bit like the er comparable to like a Golf GTI or a Honda Civic Type R you know a more of a <trunc>s</trunc> racier type car</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well I did look at the Honda Civic and I do like the Honda well I I like I like the Honda Civic have you thought about a Honda Civic?</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0661">yeah I like I like it as well erm but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't like it but then when I pointed to one the other day <pause dur="short"/> I think she got it confused with another car</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0663">well I would definitely look at one of those I did go and sit in one</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0661" trans="overlap">the problem is the</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0663">the only thing that I found was I didn't I wasn't sure visibility was that great so</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0661">it's got that bar across the back window hasn't it?</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0661" trans="overlap">that's I probably wouldn't like that</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0663">and also there there's to me the bonnet sloped off and I couldn't see the front of the car</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0663">and that I didn't I didn't particularly like so but I do like the</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0663">I like the look of the car I think it's a <trunc>d</trunc> I mean I would just say go and sit in one drive one don't don't don't make a hasty choice go and drive a few cos I think you tend to go</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah well</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0663">you tend to go and you find something and you think oh yes this will be okay but</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0662">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0663">you don't do enough</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0663">looking about researching and <trunc>dri</trunc> test driving</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0661">yeah well I'm just</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0663" trans="overlap">cos</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0661"><trunc>l</trunc> gonna look for something secondhand actually pretty cheap and</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh definitely <pause dur="short"/> well have you er there's</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0661" trans="overlap">the only thing I really want is like a DAB radio I'm not <trunc>r</trunc> not like <trunc>l</trunc> overly bothered really about whatever else</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0663">no what about <anon type="place"/> have you looked on that?</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0661" trans="overlap">as long as it's cheap</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0662">that's where erm</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0661">where's that?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0663">yeah er</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0662"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got hers from there but if you what <trunc>w</trunc> if you click on cos I think I looked at everything I went until I was dizzy looking at cars but if you go onto the <anon type="place"/> site <pause dur="short"/> I think they still call it <anon type="place"/> erm</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0661">where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0663">it's <anon type="place"/> so <anon type="place"/> way</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0661">okay</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0663"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0662">yeah and they advertise as well don't they?</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1089" who="S0662">like most of them do they advertise</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0663">mm they do</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0663">and if you can actually click on a car and they <trunc>g</trunc> the <trunc>dri</trunc> they they'll show they do a little video of it of</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0661">is that where you got yours from?</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0663">no no</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0661">no</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0663">I got mine from erm <anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1097" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0663">so that was er that was a nice experience wasn't it? that was lovely</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0661">yeah I remember that guy did did the the videos and stuff</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0663">yes cos I sent you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the video didn't I so?</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0663">they do they do the he'd made that video himself hadn't he? but</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0663">if you go on the</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0661" trans="overlap">well I've not really looked around much</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0663" trans="overlap">if</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0661">I've only looked on Auto Trader to <trunc>s</trunc> just to see what kind of thing er</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0662">give you an idea of price ranges and things</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah cos what I'm trying</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0661">what you know the only thing I'm really bothered about is having a DAB radio so I can listen to 6 Music</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0661">and like anything else will just be so many streets ahead of what I've got now it doesn't really matter</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0661">it's not massively you know my car doesn't have air conditioning</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0662" trans="overlap">update the</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0661">or a beepy key fob</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0661">and those are the probably the three <trunc>thing</trunc> only three things that I'm bothered about other than</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0661">you know not not getting a Honda Jazz <unclear>so</unclear></u>
<u n="1123" who="S0663">but why <trunc>d</trunc> yeah I know</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0661">or something like that</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0663" trans="overlap">er why don't you?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0663">why don't you well well just have a look and you'll what happens is you find you can look at a say a particular sort of if I if you want a I don't know Honda Civic particular engine <pause dur="short"/> do you want petrol? do you want diesel? do you want manual? do you want automatic? do you want erm what size engine do you want? and then</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0663">they will show you everything they've got in that range and you can click on it you think yeah I want a I dunno a red one so you click on and they'll so you pick your car and then what happens is <trunc>y</trunc> they they've done a video of every car they've got so</u>
<event desc="sound of beeping"/>
<u n="1130" who="S0663">therefore you click on it and and it shows you they drive it out and they tell you all about it you see so</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0662" trans="overlap">what's that noise?</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0663">it's quite nifty</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I'll have to have a look</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0663">do have a look</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0663">and I was quite impressed I was <trunc>r</trunc> and look on What Car? and read reviews</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0661">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0663">because when I was looking at mine what I <trunc>w</trunc> by the time I'd finished as I say I did it till I was dizzy but there's like a little there's a Mini forum so <pause dur="short"/> I was looking on this Mini forum that you can buy you can go onto two different ones one is for <pause dur="short"/> very old Minis like <pause dur="short"/> vintage whatever erm and then the other one was for newer sort of <trunc>v</trunc>versions or whatever so whatever subject you want to discuss I mean I didn't join in I just read other people's write-ups but if you wanted to say</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0663">what about cos at one point I was looking at one with a glass roof and I went on to see about what people were saying about glass <trunc>r</trunc></u>
<u n="1142" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0663">about panoramic rooves and and somebody had had trouble with it and then I thought mm maybe not because if I have trouble it could be a really expensive thing to fix and I also didn't want a cabriolet because I didn't want because again <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had had trouble with hers and it was very expensive</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0661">what's a cabriolet?</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0663">you know the soft top</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0661">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0663">so therefore that was a massively expensive thing and she got it</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0663">done for a a a reasonable price but it's still a lot of money</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0662">who was this?</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0663"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she had her</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah so</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0661">I probably wouldn't get much use of it other than a couple of days of sunshine <unclear>or something</unclear></u>
<u n="1155" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well exactly I mean there so there are certain</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0661" trans="overlap">oh I've heard that the UK has has the most convertibles per capita in the world or something</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0662">really?</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0663">well that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0661" trans="overlap">shows shows what an optimistic country we have <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1160" who="S0663" trans="overlap">isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0662">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0663">absolutely so the what's the point? and also you <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="1163" who="S0662" trans="overlap">just <unclear/> and be American</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0663">you can't you can't wash it</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1166" who="S0663">like you can't you've gotta have your special treatment and stuff for your roof</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0663">you can't just wash it like you can wash a normal car so</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0663">to me that</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0663">there were lots of negatives for that I mean <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1173" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0663">if we suddenly get tropical you know we can think you might consider it but there's no point is there for the number of sunny days that we have these days?</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0662" trans="overlap">but if you see these programmes and and <vocal desc="cough"/> these housewives of Beverley Hills or whatever and sometimes I put that on <pause dur="short"/> at teatime and obviously you know they they're all <pause dur="short"/> they you know they're all so well off and you you know they drive up to somebody's mansion and they're all the <trunc>s</trunc> they're all different but they're all the same <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> huge and course as you know Americans call the garden the the back yard and you look at the back yard and it's you know acres of beautiful trees and everything and they get out of a they come in a car and or they go visiting somebody else's house and they just step out of the car and <trunc>s</trunc> you know some shadowy figure some bloke's there to remove it and they don't even acknowledge the fact that somebody's opened their door or somebody's driven them there at all you know</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0661">no</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0662">they're very erm</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0662">everything to hand you know</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0662">and there's another one on now er by the they're looking for I've forgotten what they call it the <trunc>s</trunc> the upper fixers or something and the <trunc>h</trunc> the houses that've been run down and they go round and there they are and along the side everything they talk about they keep showing a if the kitchen's going to be pushed out you know twenty feet or whatever you know they put a little thing down showing what it would look like and then then at the side they keep putting the the dollars you know like that's six six and a half thousand dollars for that bit and then fifteen dollars fifteen thousand dollars just to alter that and so on and so forth and</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0662">you know it's a real er after a while you get <trunc>f</trunc> sick of it but there they are you know like money's no object whatsoever</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0662">you know they think</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0663" trans="overlap">the Fixer Uppers?</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0662">that's it what did I say?</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0663">upper fixers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1189" who="S0662"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did I?</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1191" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I think I was thinking upper class</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1193" who="S0662">oh that's right have you seen that?</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0663">no I haven't no it was just a cos that's what</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0662" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0663">that's a term isn't it? fixer upper? isn't it? isn't</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0662" trans="overlap">is it? I suppose it's</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well it kind of is because it's a <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1199" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I suppose yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0663">slang for</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0662">and then they want a mirror and you see six blokes carrying a mirror you know to put on that wall and <pause dur="short"/> and I really I mean they could obviously it wouldn't suit the rest of them because the people that they mix with they're all the same you know they're all all in the same and really when it's the housewives that are on they're out they're either out for lunch or they're out for a a meal with the husbands and everybody else</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well they probably don't I bet they're all dead thin and they don't eat very much a lot of them</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0662" trans="overlap">they are dead thin all of them</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0663">cos er all their dining out mustn't they mustn't have three courses and</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0662">no oh they mustn't</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0663" trans="overlap">cos otherwise they would be</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0662">they mustn't</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0663">overweight</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0662">but you know it's all er and the nannies and <pause dur="short"/> and then like if they're having a do all you know the two or three chefs there doing all little dinky things you know to eat and</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0662">all of that and the so on but when they meet together there there's like usually for the whole thing that keeps coming on there's probably half a dozen of them that are all supposed to be friends and the way they go on about one another and in the end it's I suppose it's good television they're they're falling out you see and then they're saying is Sonia coming? and er well I <trunc>d</trunc> I did invite her but if she comes well if she doesn't well I'm well I <trunc>sh</trunc> I won't be coming you know? and they're backbiting like that and that's what they're like</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0662" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1215" who="S0662"><unclear>well see the</unclear></u>
<u n="1216" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well yeah but that's airing your airing your that's just your life in public is it just because people want their fifteen minutes of fame?</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0662">I don't know</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0663">I can't understand why would you want to show that to the world unless you just want to show off? why would you want people in your home?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0662">I don't know</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0663" trans="overlap">with cameras <trunc>u</trunc> <trunc>j</trunc> you know?</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0662">it's a big ego I suppose</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0662">cos there must be thousands of people who would go on it I'm sure</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0663">yeah definitely I suppose they just want to show off <unclear>for the</unclear> people</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0663">but no <unclear>I would never do that</unclear></u>
<u n="1227" who="S0662" trans="overlap">and then at the end of the series they have a they get together when they sit in this you know like semi-circle and work in the middle with all the questions that people have contacted them you know to ask <pause dur="short"/> would you please ask such a body you know why she'd why she did such and such to so-and-so? and why did you fall out with? I didn't I never ever said and then there's three on each side of him and they're all having their you know all getting worked up saying and he's trying to kind of get onto the next question and say no no no no well <trunc>pro</trunc> well no well she probably didn't mean that you know and now some so-and-so's rang in and what about such a body what? why did he do such and such you know? <trunc>h</trunc>how they can do it and they all they're all dressed up you know in all like off the shoulders sort of sort of dresses that you don't see many people you know in the middle of the afternoon wearing or not like we'd think of as like going to a a ball or something like that but</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0663">they must dress up for the camera</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0662">and they're all blonde and their hair's all down to here <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1230" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1231" who="S0663">maybe it's a uniform</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1233" who="S0662"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1234" who="S0663">I don't know</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0662">anyway</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh what's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gone to London for? that was what I was gonna ask you</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0661">she's erm meeting the er project team for a festival called er Brainchild festival in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1238" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh what's that all about then?</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0661">er she's volunteering and she's <unclear>helped lumped</unclear> in with the design team</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0663">oh fabulous</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0661">so</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0663">so is it a music festival or an arts festival or?</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0661">er bit of both I think</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0663">right and when is it?</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0661">July something</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0663">July something?</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0661">yeah one weekend in July</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0663">oh very good</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0661">so she got the coach at nine o'clock took about five hours to get down there</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0663">what? this morning?</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0663">oh what? where was the coach going from?</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1254" who="S0663">so er did <trunc>sh</trunc> did you take her in or does she?</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0661">yeah I gave her a lift</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>o</trunc> er five o'clock this morning?</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0661">no nine o'clock</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0663">oh I thought you said five I thought</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0661">it's a five-hour</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0662">it's a five-hour <unclear/></u>
<u n="1261" who="S0663" trans="overlap">five-hour sorry</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0663">that's me <trunc>d</trunc> my brain's just not clicked in so</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0661">erm</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0663">nine o'clock this morning five-hour so she won't get there till one</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0661">yeah and then the meeting was three I think three till five</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0663">okay and then</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0661" trans="overlap">and she's on the coach back now and</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0661">gets in about quarter to eleven I think</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0663">oh poor lass well good for her for doing it</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0661">yeah it's a long way to go</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0663" trans="overlap">for making that that's a whole day out of your life isn't it? ten hours on a coach</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> for a two-hour meeting</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0663">for a two-hour meeting could it not have? could they not have done it on Skype?</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0662">well people would've been from all over perhaps were they <trunc>t</trunc>? I mean is this why it took so long were they picking up people perhaps?</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear>well it</unclear></u>
<u n="1278" who="S0661" trans="overlap">they're all from London <pause dur="short"/> no they all just they hadn't the rest of them are from in and around London <pause dur="short"/> so she just wanted to get involved and they were quite impressed that she'd made the</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0661">effort to go <trunc>d</trunc> all the way down</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0663">I think that's very impressive</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0661">yeah but most of the work can be done</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><trunc>sh</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> up here?</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0661" trans="overlap">while she's up here <pause dur="short"/> and she's got her studio space <trunc>w</trunc> in that college where she can work on whatever <unclear/> thing</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah that's good that's <unclear>so will that?</unclear></u>
<u n="1286" who="S0662" trans="overlap">well it's a space that she's got to work in <pause dur="short"/> that she <trunc>n</trunc> she's <trunc>d</trunc> she's there now anyway like?</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0661">yeah she went she's been there for a few weeks now</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0663">has she been erm <trunc>be</trunc> able to store what she's working on there as well or can it she doesn't have to bring it home every night?</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but she does</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh that's good</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0661">drive there so she's <pause dur="short"/> can take whatever she needs and bring it back or whatever</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0663" trans="overlap">if she wants well that's good</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0663">good so she's quite happy is she?</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0661">yeah yeah she's doing really well</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0663" trans="overlap">good <unclear/> good good</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0661">apart from the she's working at a er place called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1300" who="S0663">yes you said they hadn't given her enough hours and</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0661">er been up and down then she's worked she worked <trunc>yest</trunc> last night erm and Friday day so she's got a few hours but she</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0663">oh right</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0661">she wants to get something a bit more local and different cos it's</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes that would be useful wouldn't it? mm</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0661">yeah going from college to town and</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0661">then I mean that'd be easier if she could get <unclear>bring</unclear> into</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0661"><trunc>r</trunc> so she is on the lookout for something a bit more convenient</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0663" trans="overlap">something more local well that's good because then if she does and she <trunc>se</trunc> she finishes late at night it's easier to get home isn't it?</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0661">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0663" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0663">it you know you you don't worry about sort of having to walk to the train or bus</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0663">well the train's quite good isn't it but?</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0661">the train's good but they're er late night they're only like once an hour and they don't run very late so last night she finished after the train had finished so</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0663" trans="overlap">so she had to get the bus?</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0663">I mean you are on a quite busy bus route</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0661" trans="overlap">but then we don't <pause dur="short"/> we're quite far about twenty minute walk to the bus stop</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0663">well that that was was gonna say even though it goes through the the road down like <anon type="place"/> road whatever it</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0661">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0663"><trunc>y</trunc> when she gets off she it's it's a bit of a walk at whatever time in the morning isn't it? so</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0663">that's not so good</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0661">no</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0661">bit of a pain but usually she cycles but she's had three punctures in less</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="gasp"/> three oh no</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0661" trans="overlap">in about a week <pause dur="short"/> well she had <trunc>o</trunc> she had one and she had to she was late to work and she had to take her bike on the bus and then there was traffic and everything and it was horrible</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0663"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1335" who="S0661">and then she got the train home and had repaired it and then by the morning the repair just failed so had to put a new inner tube in and <vocal desc="laugh"/> then she got another <trunc>pu</trunc>puncture in the new inner tube</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0663">no oh that's so disheartening isn't it when she makes such an effort? I mean you both</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0663">you're both very good at at cycling but even so</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0661" trans="overlap">when I took it out it was one of these cheap ones from Wilkos so I think maybe that's why cos it'd just it had this like loads of little holes along the end in it</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0661">couldn't even repair it</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0661">so I ordered a better quality couple of inner tubes off the internet</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0663">right</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0661">today</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0662" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0663">I know but it's so it's disheartening isn't it? because I mean that's</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>it is</unclear></u>
<u n="1350" who="S0663">you're <trunc>d</trunc> you're cycling to work not just to save money but for health reasons as well</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0663">but then</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0663">you're spending your wages back in inner tubes and it kind of it's a bit counterproductive isn't it?</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0661" trans="overlap">well I had a couple of weeks <pause dur="short"/> last year where I must I must've had like nearly ten punctures</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0663"><vocal desc="sigh"/> oh</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0661">just I was = I was on the verge of giving up cycling it was <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1358" who="S0662" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0663">oh right</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0662">you know</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0663">I</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0661" trans="overlap">so annoying</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0663">well I would've done <unclear>coward</unclear></u>
<u n="1365" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I think it was just some shrapnel that was in <anon type="place"/> park that kept going anywhere</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0662">ah</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0661">but it's so it's hard when you're going that far to <trunc>j</trunc> keep</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0662">mm mm</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0661" trans="overlap">you know <unclear/> grounded</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><trunc>i</trunc> well <trunc>i</trunc> you can't if you <unclear>move</unclear> your eyes on the ground you're not looking round you are you?</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="1372" who="S0663">and and it's really important to be safe so</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0661">but my new bike's a bit <pause dur="short"/> a bit better because it's thinner tyres than my mountain bike which has flatter tyres so I think there's less chance of it actually hitting something</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0661">and the tyres are harder which I dunno maybe that makes them more resilient or maybe that makes them more resilient or maybe that <unclear>means er</unclear></u>
<u n="1376" who="S0663">is it a road bike did you say?</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0663">so it's</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0661"><unclear>well</unclear></u>
<u n="1380" who="S0663">yeah okay cos you can get the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1381" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I've been having these erm I'm getting this pain in my elbow</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0663">oh that's not that's not</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0661" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0663">the shock of</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0661">I don't know if it's the lack of suspension and I'm not used to taking shocks on my arms</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0661">the different seat <trunc>positi</trunc> the hand position going from that to that</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0663">mm?</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0661">also leaning forward</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0662" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0661">which means my arms are overstretched and I've got more weight of my backpack on my arms than I would have when I'm sat like that</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0661">or maybe the bike's too big for me and I'm stretching further than I should be</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0661" trans="overlap">or a combination of all of the above</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0663">oh no so</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0661">so I don't know if I'm getting like <trunc>te</trunc> give myself tennis elbow or</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well I was just gonna say you'll end up with tennis elbow is the one</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I was gonna say tennis elbow mm</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0663">and then you'll end up with support straps unless you put the support straps on when you're cycling but I don't know if that will help</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0661">well it shouldn't it shouldn't happen I just need to fix whatever's going wrong but erm</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0663">so if you're not <unclear/> the suspension on your</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0662" trans="overlap">you'll have to keep your eye on it and see</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0663">no</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0661">cos it's a new bike I've got er they they said bring it back in a couple of months and they'll have a look over it just to make sure everything's alright</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0661">but I think because I've tried I've rode I tested one bike</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0661">and waited nearly six months to get it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1410" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh and they sent you another they said it <trunc>w</trunc>wasn't available</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I know then it's just got yeah so many so many delays they're just like gotta just just give me a different bike so I picked one</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0661">that was very <trunc>s</trunc> very similar but made by a different company and they said what <trunc>si</trunc> what size do you want? and it was fifty-four centimetres on this one so I'll give you fifty-four centimetres on this one <pause dur="short"/> I was like yeah sounds good <pause dur="short"/> didn't test ride it erm but I don't when I test rode it I don't know what I'm should be feeling because it's so different and I'm not used to it</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1415" who="S0663" trans="overlap">it's different to to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1416" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes you <unclear>put it down to</unclear></u>
<u n="1417" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I wouldn't how would I know if it's uncomfortable? cos it is uncomfortable because it's different</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0661">and when I looked at the size guides <pause dur="short"/> on the internet for the old bike and the new bike</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0661">they're both fifty-four centimetres so you think they're the same size but</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0662">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0661">I they're not because the frames are different shapes like different geometries</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0662">oh right</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0661" trans="overlap">so one size bike</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0663">is not you don't</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0661" trans="overlap">in one brand might be different to another one</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc> is different</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0661">so the size guide they have these on the internet you can get the size guide for your for your height</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0661">you should have be on the size bike</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0662">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0661">and fifty-four was right on the old one but it's not right on the new one</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0663">oh no</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>which <trunc>sh</trunc></unclear> I should be on a smaller bike</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0663">oh no</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0661" trans="overlap">according to that <pause dur="short"/> so really <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d</trunc> I think I've I did a bit of research and people on forums saying <trunc>s</trunc> they'd been mis-sold</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0661">the right <trunc>s</trunc> the wrong size bike and they just really it's your responsibility you I should've checked it you know? if I</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0662" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0661">think it's comfortable I'm the customer and I bought a bike and it's my fault really but when I take it in to for them for them to check it</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0661">I'll just ask them and I'll say you know <pause dur="short"/> what do you think about my position on the bike? cos the size guide it's</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah five foot seven should be on a fifty-two inch fifty-two centimetre bike not a fifty-four</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0661">and just ask them you know did you not check <vocal desc="laugh"/> or anything or?</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0661">but I think there might be some options whether you can I <trunc>s</trunc> I've not actually had chance to look myself yet but maybe just pushing the seat forward or something or</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0661">moving the handlebars up or even replacing the drop bars with some flat bars might help</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0663">unlike I've done with mine well that I did a very very long time ago cos mine's a racing bike and and I had originally it came with drop handlebars but I've just had the standard handlebars put on it because</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0663">I wouldn't want to have have my head down I want <trunc>h</trunc> I want to have my head up when I'm cycling so that would be an easy well I don't <trunc>s</trunc> how <trunc>e</trunc>easy it is but that was that's that's an option</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah the only thing is I think it might be expensive cos I might have to get new brakes as well cos I the the brakes are special drop handlebar brakes like well you probably have the same mm</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm pff must've done but I kinda can't remember now</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0663">so long ago</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0661" trans="overlap">just a just a bit of a pain really</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0663">no it is definitely</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0663">will you find it easier to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1467" who="S0661" trans="overlap">but no cos I'm not even I'm not even riding it every day</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no you've got to keep your you've got to keep your eye on it haven't you? to see how</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0661">well yeah</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0662">how often it happens and how long are you driving before it cycling before it hurts or what you know it</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0661">it doesn't hurt when I'm cycling it's <pause dur="short"/> it's kinda when</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0662" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0661">it's like I've got my drink bottle that hurts like gripping</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0661">so which is a I've read about tennis elbow that's one of the symptoms so</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0661">and then this this arm's not as bad but well this arm wasn't at all but then it was mostly this one but then since started a bit as well you know it's <pause dur="short"/> well I'm not <trunc>e</trunc> not I'm only riding it like one or two days a week</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0661">erm</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0663">well somebody at work <unclear>had to try cycling a period</unclear></u>
<u n="1482" who="S0662" trans="overlap">and do you find the <trunc>r</trunc> other days you're not it doesn't affect you?</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0661">no it's well I've can <trunc>f</trunc>feel it</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0662" trans="overlap">it you'd get yeah</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0661">I imagine if it'd be worse if I was riding every day</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0661">I think next weekend that's <trunc>pr</trunc> take it in and see what they say</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0661">see if they can <pause dur="short"/> sort me a deal if they've not <pause dur="short"/> sold me the right bike or something like that</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0663" trans="overlap">how long have you had the bike?</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0661">er got it <trunc>br</trunc> weekend after we came back in December</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0663">right well</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0661" trans="overlap">so it was only about less than a month well bit over a month</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0663">well why don't you see if because somebody I know bought a bike from <pause dur="short"/> and took that back and I think cos it's within a period of time that they guarantee this particular cycle place I can't tell you what it's called <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0661">oh right</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0661">yeah I'll erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'll see what they say</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0663">or or or look up and see what their <pause dur="short"/> sort of</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0661">what their policy is</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0663">policy and</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0663">that or whatever <pause dur="short"/> cos sometimes it's like anything isn't it? it's <pause dur="short"/> you know if you've bought a coat that's a bit big it doesn't really matter does it? I mean you just think oh silly me or I've lost a bit of weight or whatever it's not the end of the world but if it's affecting your health and your joints then</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0663">it's really important and it's not a good thing <pause dur="short"/> and also if they've got specialist knowledge which they should have</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0662">yeah they know about it</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0663">they should then know that if you've had a fifty-four frame and you you then go into a different model that they suggested or whatever that that they should know that that is not the right one or they should</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0663">have that background knowledge to be able to say <trunc>y</trunc> well actually you need to go down a size in that because it's a different frame and it's set up differently or whatever</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0662">and you've got to try all over again haven't you to see how it is? cos I <vocal desc="cough"/> remember me having tennis elbow</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0663">well I was gonna say I sort of vaguely remember but</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0662" trans="overlap">twice</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0662">and they thought it was it was because erm you know you're carrying heavy shopping they <trunc>s</trunc> he said</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0662">used to go on <pause dur="short"/> in the car to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1523" who="S0663">good heavens</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0662">to this particular osteopath who was supposed to be very good</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0663">right</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0662">your daddy used to go as well <trunc>ke</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>k</trunc> he got something in his fingers or <trunc>u</trunc> playing rugby you know?</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0663">right</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0662">and but</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0663" trans="overlap">so <unclear/></u>
<u n="1530" who="S0662" trans="overlap">eventually erm I remember on the one occasion me sitting on the edge of the like the bed like me sitting on the edge and him sitting there and he was a big chap <pause dur="short"/> erm and he just sort of got hold of my arm <pause dur="short"/> and gave a great big tug which he didn't sorta say this is gonna hurt or anything</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1532" who="S0662">but it did and and then it was okay</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0663">really?</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0661">oh right</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm and we went to one before that erm <pause dur="short"/> in <trunc>cor</trunc> the <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> and he wasn't particularly nice and he did it and I remember going <trunc>t</trunc> whilst I was there going into the shops and shopping and thinking well oh they're not really interested cos it hurts and the next day it was still hurting and I rang him up and said and he was quite short with me and he said you were in my <trunc>s</trunc> my surgery less than twenty-four hours ago and er you can't expect it to be <pause dur="short"/> totally you <trunc>n</trunc> carry on and it'll be and it was</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0663"><unclear>how mm</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>osteop</trunc>osteopathy is a</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0662">mm you don't hear much about them now do you?</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0663" trans="overlap">a good <pause dur="short"/> mm you don't hear you don't hear very much but</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0662" trans="overlap">it's all physio now isn't it? seems to be</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well mostly cos it's kinda recognised isn't it? but I don't know are</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0663">osteopaths not considered <unclear>another thing</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no anyway eventually had cancer and died</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0662">I didn't need him again as as it happened I didn't</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0663" trans="overlap">oh but I know</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah but erm I do remember that I don't know how he'd had perhaps it was through the rugby club that somebody knew I don't I don't know</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0662">but when something hurts you see it hurts doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0661">yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1552" who="S0662">it it's you know it's quite debilitating really</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0662" trans="overlap">really get you down</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0663">well I hope I hope you get sorted love really do</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm getting on a bit now I need to be careful</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0663">pardon?</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0661">I'm getting on a bit now I need to be careful</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0662"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1560" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1561" who="S0662">oh god</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0661"><trunc>thir</trunc>thirty now</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0663">prime age for <pause dur="short"/> whatever</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1565" who="S0663">don't know just prime age <pause dur="short"/> and I've listened and listened and listened to all the programmes about David erm Bowie</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0661">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0663">this week</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0662">David Bowie</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0661" trans="overlap">I listened to a really good one</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0662">is he a <trunc>w</trunc> er er pop erm musician?</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0663">yeah he died he died last yeah</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0661" trans="overlap">yeah he was</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah but it didn't <unclear>go in <vocal desc="misc"/></unclear> I mean obviously heard about the other one</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0663">Alan Rickman?</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0662">no heard about him the other one <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> what's he called?</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0663">I don't know</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0662">oh you know the one that it was on all the time and people complained that the BBC had <pause dur="short"/> given it far too much time <pause dur="short"/> you know the very very famous one</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0661">another one?</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0663">musician? this week</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0662">no a singer <pause dur="short"/> well it was a musician</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0663">singer that's died this week?</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0662">yes why can't I think of his name?</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0663">oh <unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="1585" who="S0661">David Bowie?</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0663">cos it was Bowie it's er there's only David Bowie that</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0662" trans="overlap">Bowie Bowie</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0663">yeah that's what we're talking about</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0662">I thought you said <trunc>say</trunc> I thought you said Dave Berry</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1591" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1592" who="S0662">cos I've never heard of him <pause dur="short"/> you were talking about</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1594" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1595" who="S0662">him that they'd just said he's been on too much</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1597" who="S0662"><unclear>er</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> married to <pause dur="short"/> iman</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0663">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1599" who="S0662">I know that much anyway</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0661"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1602" who="S0662">I dunno how many millions he made when he sold whatever he sold and <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>know all of that</unclear></u>
<u n="1603" who="S0663">oh god</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0661">oh</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0663">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no that's that's that's just yeah that has made me laugh but yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1606" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1607" who="S0663">yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent me a WhatsApp message on was it Monday morning?</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0663">yeah to say have you and I thought heard what? no I haven't and I'm I'm really <pause dur="short"/> shocked and</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0663" trans="overlap">what a shame because nobody knew he was ill he had cancer didn't he?</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> he had</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0663" trans="overlap">he was only <unclear>he's only</unclear> just had his sixty-ninth birthday and he'd released his</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0663">latest album only a couple of days</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0663">well he'd released it on his birthday hadn't he I think?</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm on a Friday</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0663">erm yeah and then he died on the Sunday</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0662" trans="overlap">there's an awful lot of them gone recently hasn't there? <trunc>s</trunc> you know we seem as though we've had</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0661"><unclear><vocal desc="sigh"/></unclear></u>
<u n="1622" who="S0662">you know notice on the telly about different</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0663">there's been quite a lot of people that have died this month</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0661" trans="overlap">both sixty-nine died of cancer</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0662">who?</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0661">Bowie was sixty-nine died of cancer and so was Alan Rickman</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0663" trans="overlap"><unclear>sixty-nine</unclear> Alan Rickman</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0661">sixty-nine cancer</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0661">and er</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0663">that's</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0661">the week before there was er a guy called Lemmy who was a guitarist er in or bassist in Motörhead</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0663">yeah no I'd heard I'd heard yeah I'd heard about him how old was he?</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0661">he was seventy odd I think</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0663">right <pause dur="short"/> mm gosh</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0662">well there's been quite a lot of the old film stars as well you know the old ones you know that I would appreciate but <pause dur="short"/> and they like you know eighty-five or ninety-two or you know film directors and</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0663" trans="overlap">was there one just recently? yeah</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0662">I mean some of them their names don't really always mean very much do they?</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0663">but then they mention the films that they've directed or whatever and then you think oh right yeah I know</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes yes <pause dur="short"/> and they're more important than the stars really aren't they? but <pause dur="short"/> they you don't get <trunc>t</trunc> their name do you? you don't recognise them the same as the</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0663">no</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0662">people</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0661">did listen to a really good show on 6 Music this afternoon it's <trunc>w</trunc> a while back it was and it was about <pause dur="short"/> bowie's er Bowie's heroes and his influences</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0661">and it's people from the Chicago <trunc>ar</trunc> rhythm and blues</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0663">oh really?</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0661">singing <pause dur="short"/> and stuff like that yeah</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0663">oh</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0661" trans="overlap">and <unclear>now</unclear> played loads of old interviews that he'd done</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0663">he's really</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0662">that's</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0663">he's really well-spoken isn't he? and he's he's erm</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0662" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> good yes he is yes</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0663">cos he was he's he was born David Jones wasn't he?</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0663">and</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0663">er you know I went to the exhibition we went to the Bowie exhibition in erm Melbourne when I was in Australia</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0662">oh really?</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0663">because I <trunc>d</trunc> well I didn't</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0662">he was quite a nice singer from what what I saw</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0663" trans="overlap">he was very very good very talented</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0662" trans="overlap">what I saw</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0663">he wrote all his own material didn't he?</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0663">he's was really yeah and very diverse as well and</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0662">yes yes</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0663" trans="overlap">groundbreaking and and everything very very good</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0663">he had lots of his costumes there and</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0663">yeah and</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0662">oh</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0663">lots of erm interviews you could hear interviews you could hear <pause dur="short"/> obviously his music and yeah and album covers and</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0662" trans="overlap">a lot of them seem to have gone through the rock and roll and the drugs and whatnot haven't they? and they've kind of kicked and then you know become more famous afterwards and</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0662">as they've got older even</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0662">I mean such a lot of them say about what they did you know then <pause dur="short"/> as it goes on you they they come <pause dur="short"/> they've given all that up and <pause dur="short"/> you know are doing fine with <pause dur="short"/> whatever else they've done</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0663" trans="overlap">they've settled down and grown up and got on with their life <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1688" who="S0662">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0663">no it's it is but he was he was quite like I mean he is an icon isn't he? and I think</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0663">it just is very sad cos obviously he's very talented and and</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0663" trans="overlap">you know it's ended early and and yet</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0662">and also you didn't hear an awful lot about him did you?</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0663">well he was a very private man and <trunc>w</trunc> that's why I think nobody knew he was ill</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0661" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0663">because</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0662">mm</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0663">he'd kept his private life private which is fine and <pause dur="short"/> you know but it's just it's</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I think they're the wise ones that do</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0662">keep out of the limelight</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0663">yeah</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0662">aren't they?</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0663">very sad that</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I mean look at all these blokes that have gone to prison you know and they've like Max Clifford and all <pause dur="short"/> the rest of them that more serving sentences and whatnot and you know they've made such a lot of money haven't they out of other people and whatnot and? <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0663" trans="overlap">but then that's not it's not about that it's about the fact they've <trunc>d</trunc>done something wrong and that they</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no I know but</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0663">have been if you like erm</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0662">found out?</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0663">they've probably <trunc>you</trunc> well they've <trunc>be</trunc> yeah they've obviously been found out but they've used their position probably to take</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0662">yeah</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0663">advantage of situations and</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0663">that's what's really bad and other people can be famous and they can be talented and they they just use their talents and they use their</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0663">the funds that they've made not all of them obviously but they to help erm</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0662" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0663">and they do a lot of charity work and then</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes they do</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0663">so that's there's that's there's a nice side to it isn't there? there's a</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0663">and I think that's that's the best part about</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0662">yes if you've got money</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well celebrity being a celebrity is that you can actually use it to help</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0662" trans="overlap">help people</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0661">use it for good</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0663" trans="overlap">other people yeah and you can use it to</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0662" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0663">erm forward a cause</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes because they use your name it helps yeah</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0663" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0662" trans="overlap">cos you see Barbara Windsor's been given a <pause dur="short"/> a dame hasn't she?</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0663">yeah she has yeah</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0662" trans="overlap">and you see people grumbling about that but</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0663">well she's done a lot of charity work hasn't she?</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yes and that's what what they said she</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0663" trans="overlap">that's why she's that's what she's gained it for isn't it?</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0662">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0663">I mean they don't give it them just for being an actress do they? they give it</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0662">no</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0663" trans="overlap">they give them a erm they award them a</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0662">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0663">title because of work they've done</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0663">charity work it's not <pause dur="short"/> it's not about them being a</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0662">no</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0663">a good actress cos that's just somebody being good at their job isn't it?</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0662">I know yeah it's another world isn't it?</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0663">mm of course</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0662">than the average <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1753" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely we yeah yeah they're not average people are they?</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0662">not really no</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0663">but then there's a lot of erm I suppose a lot of people that have been <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what can I say? named and shamed that have <trunc>y</trunc> kind of had a lot of <pause dur="short"/> not respect for necessarily but you know when you think that they've been a big part of</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0662" trans="overlap">but you always thought that they were nice and they</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0663">yeah they'd been a big part of</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0662" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like you'd be surprised if it was Terry Wogan wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0663" trans="overlap">like when you were were growing up <pause dur="short"/> yeah but you just know full well it wouldn't be would you? cos he's a decent man you know and and</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0662" trans="overlap">you know you <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0663">at the end of it all there are some really decent people out there who have</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0662">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0663">done lots and lots of good and then there are various like</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0662" trans="overlap">and it's good when they do them on the telly when they do these things about people</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0662">and they give them all awards and they're people you don't know</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0663">oh yes</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0662" trans="overlap">like headmistresses send a school around and</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0663">yeah that's lovely</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0662" trans="overlap">and people I think the ones that that deal with all the disabled ones are the ones that need <pause dur="short"/> recognising don't they?</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0663">definitely well they they just well it's about them putting in time or <trunc>th</trunc> about the fact that they do their job</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0662">well</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0663">really really well and they're very very committed and that they take it seriously and go <trunc>ab</trunc>above and beyond to to make sure people <unclear>lead better lives</unclear></u>
<u n="1774" who="S0662" trans="overlap">well they do don't they? they seem to do they seem to do those sort of people</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0661">just realised your chair's still in the bathroom when we moved it in at Christmas</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0662">I know well</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0661" trans="overlap">do you need do you need it in here? do you want me to move it <unclear>up</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0662" trans="overlap">no well I don't use it really</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0661">you don't use it?</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0662" trans="overlap">do I?</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0663">I think it's in there wasn't it because you it was a bit in the way and <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0661" trans="overlap">we just we moved it on Christmas Day</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0662" trans="overlap">well I think it was it was Christmas Day really wasn't it that was?</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0663" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0661">do you want?</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0663" trans="overlap">well <trunc>th</trunc> she's got a perching stool in the other bathroom</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0661">okay</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0663">so</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0661">so it's</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0663">you don't well you can have it back of course you can but you've not mentioned needing it <pause dur="short"/> I've just brought that chair back today <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1792" who="S0662">I was going to ask you to do it so</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0661" trans="overlap"><unclear>does that make you yawn?</unclear></u>
<u n="1794" who="S0663">I said I I can do that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1795" who="S0662" trans="overlap">I said to her <unclear>but</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so she brought it</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0663"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1797" who="S0661">mm <unclear>it would</unclear></u>
<u n="1798" who="S0662" trans="overlap">thought it would be heavy</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0661">alright I'll get these washed up</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0663">right</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0661">have you finished with this?</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0662">yes</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0661">yeah</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0662">yes I have <pause dur="short"/> I'm busy thinking I ought to write this card because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to take it</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0663">oh yeah I was just gonna drop them off and and er</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0662" trans="overlap">when she goes</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0661">what are the cards for?</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0663">oh did you did you turn that off <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0661">er not yet no</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0663">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear>those cards are</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum's died</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0661">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0663">mm</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0663">so we just writing cards and I said I'd drop them off because she's in a state of distress <unclear>when I</unclear> talked to her a couple of times and I was going to go round but she wasn't <pause dur="short"/> don't think she was up to receiving visitors so well not</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0663">visitors but I I she's at she's at her daughter's at the moment</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0661" trans="overlap">was she ill or? <pause dur="short"/> what happened?</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0663">erm <vocal desc="sigh"/> she she was <trunc>sh</trunc> it was fairly sudden</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0661">mm</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0662">but she's been ill on and off</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0663">she's she's had some ups and downs in recent times erm and she's been really unfortunate</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0662" trans="overlap">ups and downs yes</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
