<text id="SXPD">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:08:19</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Football, fast food.</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking while watching football on TV</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">what's the score?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">I dunno uh I think it was <pause dur="short"/> I think Cardiff are winning but I just I was just channel hopping and they um <pause dur="short"/> it was like they ran they had a really good run like he ran all round the goalie like they thought he was offside so <trunc>ev</trunc> all the other team like put their hand up for offside but like he just ran past the goalie and it like literally went past the post by about two millimetres</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">ah so it was  it was  uh very spectacular?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">I don't even know what the <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know what this game is though like <pause dur="short"/> is it the League Cup or something? I don't even know what the League Cup is</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> league Cup semi-final Cardiff versus Crystal Palace</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">I didn't even <pause dur="short"/> but what like <trunc>w</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> they've changed it so many times like what was the Coca Cola Cup was that the FA Cup or something different?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">uh that was the League Cup I think the Coca Cola was the league one and <pause dur="short"/> fA FA was always FA wasn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037">was it? Is it not the something FA Cup like the sort of</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well maybe but you don't sort of need to say that do you?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">I dunno</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115">but there was the <pause dur="short"/> there was like the Autoscreen one or something</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Like Pott's Pies? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0115">auto Windshield <pause dur="short"/> yeah and the I mean <pause dur="short"/> but <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037">anyway</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">the Auto Windscreens one or whatever it was I think that was like uh</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's the <trunc>Car</trunc> Carling Cup as well what was that?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">wasn't there a Leyland DAF Cup or something?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">Don't be silly <pause dur="short"/> there's was no Leyland DAF Cup was there?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037">I'd like it if there was <pause dur="short"/> what would be the most inappropriate thing for there to be like an FA Cup named after? Like fags or something</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115">well they they do that in you know in snooker don't they have that Embassy Snooker uh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">oh is that where that comes from? That just shows my ignorance</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">uh and of course uh Formula One is uh is famous for uh</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">there look Middlesborough's first and only major trophy success <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0115">when was that? The hundred and twenty-eight years ago</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Middlesborough hasn't wasn't even invented a hundred and twenty-eight years ago probablies</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah just about uh just about yeah I think they were actually</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's Steve McClaren that's who</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah no um <pause dur="short"/> uh this was <pause dur="short"/> uh Birmingham winning the uh <pause dur="short"/> birmingham winning the the League Cup uh against Arsenal <pause dur="short"/> I think I watched that one actually last year</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">ah yeah you did yeah I remember watching that <pause dur="short"/> and you were like yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">top Of The Shocks <pause dur="short"/> this this is the <trunc>s</trunc> that was the section of Top Of The <trunc>Shock</trunc> that was number one on Top Of The Shocks Birmingham City beating uh Arsenal in the  in the  League Cup</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037">but like</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">which ranks after the FA Cup but I think there's there was an <trunc>e</trunc> there was an even another cup that I think was that was a bit lower</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037" trans="overlap">more rubbish?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">but I think that was the one that I think Birmingham won a while ago <pause dur="short"/> where you  where you  you only entered it if you were in like the um one of the lower like if you were in then the third division or below</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm <trunc>n</trunc> obviously not that up to date <pause dur="short"/> I think I was football like for life after that whole like working at the <anon type="place"/> thing</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">oh uh</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">like the pies the pie aspect</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">yeah well that was you know that was enterprising and you know I mean it was industrious like you uh you were working at age when did you start that?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037" trans="overlap">just was a bit <trunc>uns</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I was enterprising <pause dur="short"/> um well you were supposed to be sixteen but I wasn't sixteen I just said I was and like they weren't bothered <pause dur="short"/> and they didn't check <pause dur="short"/> although I'm sure they had me National Insurance number so they should probably have <pause dur="short"/> well who knows <pause dur="short"/> it was all a bit dodgy</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah best  yeah best  left unsolved really <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they used to put the pies <pause dur="short"/> like the pies like if they didn't sell them they used to just put them in a box and then put them in a cupboard and then the next week just like crack the pies back out and then put them in the warmer and be like doo dee doo</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115" trans="overlap">scandalous yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">because if somebody got like ur um like a bad belly from eating a dodgy pie you would never know cos like I suppose a lot of the blokes and that who go to football and eat those horrible pies like would've had twenty pints of beer anyway so <pause dur="short"/> they would never think d'you know what that was a bad pie</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037">like people would laugh wouldn't they if they said that?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">yeah I think there wasn't probably much in the pies apart from sort of potatoes was there or?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> like sawdust and like</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> well I never  I never  had a I I never went to a football match I've never had a football pie so uh</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hooves and that <pause dur="short"/> ahh need to rectify that</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">what are they like?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037">well they <trunc>s</trunc> they <trunc>bra</trunc> they branched out</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is it just like the ones you get in the chippie?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">um yeah more or less but they branched out like <pause dur="short"/> obviously this is like more than ten years ago but I remember like they introduced a new like a chicken tikka pie <pause dur="short"/> and um everyone was like chicken tikka pie why do I want one of them? Like cos people used to just be like Give us a pie luv <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037">and then you'd be like Oh what flavour do you want? And they'd be like Meat <pause dur="short"/> so no <vocal desc="laugh"/> they didn't they was didn't really sell very well</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well in the chippie you know it used to be steak and kidney or uh</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115"><trunc>chick</trunc> uh chicken and mushroom or something <pause dur="short"/> um I mean Gregg's obviously got the  got the  steak bake and uh cheese cheese and onion pie <pause dur="short"/> but uh if you and then there's Cornish pasty  Cornish pasty  which is mainly potatoes in a cut in squares or cubes I should uh with peas and a very small amount of mince</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ugh kidneys <pause dur="short"/> a <trunc>kid</trunc> d'you like kidneys? Oh yeah cheese and onion pie <pause dur="short"/> I remember when I first <trunc>we</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah Cornish pasties are always quite like peppery though aren't they?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115">yeah really loads of like like it's just white mainly white pepper but also</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">they are very like quite <trunc>s</trunc> quite hot aren't they?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">they are</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">but not like chilli hot sort of pepper hot</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> peppery <pause dur="short"/> like tickle your nose</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um yeah so uh you uh worked at the Stadium Of but it wasn't called that then was it or?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037">yeah yeah no <pause dur="short"/> come on <pause dur="short"/> I'm not that old</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh were you? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I dunno I don't know uh when it changed</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I worked at the stadium <pause dur="short"/> but it was it wasn't hadn't been open that long though <pause dur="short"/> to be fair <pause dur="short"/> but anyway</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> uh we <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah so uh <trunc>f</trunc> um I was gonna say another <pause dur="short"/> there was a lotta tobacco sponsorship in the old days uh <pause dur="short"/> formula One was um <pause dur="short"/> was heavily uh</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but football's <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah Formula One loads</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">I I think it's it's banned now isn't it but used to be really heavily banned uh heavily sponsored by uh</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I <pause dur="short"/> d'you think they'll ban like? D'you think they'll ever ban like MacDonald's sponsoring things?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037">you know because they've <trunc>b</trunc> they've banned cigarettes <pause dur="short"/> or like you know alcohol?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no because MacDonald's are sneaky you you know they uh there's a  there's a  quote for you uh</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">they they uh well they don't just sell unhealthy food do they? Some of the  some of the  things they sell are actually like salads and that like a MacSalad or something</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I suppose</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">although I haven't been to MacDonald's for a very long time so <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I haven't <pause dur="short"/> I can't even remember <pause dur="short"/> actually I do remember it was that time d'you remember when me brother had been round and we were really hungover and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like Oh stop at MacDonald's and then the car got beached on like one of those like weird concrete things and I couldn't get it off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> oh that was  oh that was  just a really bad moment wasn't it um?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">it was funny <pause dur="short"/> looking back</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115">just uh</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037">but no I haven't been to MacDonald's for absolutely ages like</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">Don't actually remember um</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">but do they sell  do they sell  these um</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">some diving there <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't even know if I even like it that much like I remember when I'd broke me arm and I'd been to the hospital with me nana and grandda for like a hundred hours or whatever</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">and then me grandda was like Come on love <pause dur="short"/> let's go for a treat <pause dur="short"/> And I was like grandda I just wanna go home <pause dur="short"/> and he was like Come on <pause dur="short"/> Like cos he blatantly just wanted to go to MacDonald's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">and like he was like I'll take you for a nice treat let's go to MacDonald's I was like yay</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">well I never  I never  used to get driven to MacDonald's when I was that sort of age</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037"><trunc>N</trunc> I'm <trunc>b</trunc> this was when I was twenty-one and I'd broken my arm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">you're not listening</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">uh sorry yeah I was sorta watching the uh TV sorry</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">no it's alright <pause dur="short"/> um yeah yeah I mean I I don't really like it I don't even know</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">hang on</u>
</body>
</text>
