<text id="SXQU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:39:52</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0189 S0192</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Brother's kitchen, Bedford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cooking, working out, food preparation, cleaning, childhood, travelling</topics>
		<activity>Cooking with my brother</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0189">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Artworker</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0189">so when we cook is this from memory?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0192">yeah this is actually a recipe I just made up</u>
<u n="3" who="S0189">oh</u>
<u n="4" who="S0192">and I normally do it with lamb and but we have beef so <pause dur="short"/> and I don't normally do mashed potatoes stuffed peppers but there's potatoes and there's peppers so <unclear/> consider doing it with rice but then I had to buy rice and <unclear/> we've already got potatoes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0189">when I do potatoes with curry for like the customer I get lazy with peeling them if they're small potatoes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0189">cut them and boil them</u>
<u n="8" who="S0192">it's a bit of a pain in the bum</u>
<u n="9" who="S0189">is it that bad? and then with the skin on them</u>
<u n="10" who="S0192">erm depending on what you're eating if I just had mashed potato I'd actually prefer it with skin on it but not all of the skin I'd probably cut off like half of the skin and then when I mash it it's got the skin in it it's good it's got more flavour and then the more nutrients are usually in the skin <unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0189">yeah but surely it's like a darker colour?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0192">yeah well like what I'm making today I probably I don't want to leave any of the skin and the mash potato I'm going to make with erm ginger and red onions and erm <pause dur="short"/> maybe a bit of nutmeg</u>
<u n="13" who="S0189">sounds good <pause dur="short"/> ah <unclear>where is the skin</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0192"><unclear/> I like these bowls</u>
<u n="15" who="S0189">ah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0192">they're really nice</u>
<u n="17" who="S0189">I don't actually like those ones that much this is my favourite</u>
<u n="18" who="S0192">because they're difficult to clean?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like these ones</u>
<u n="20" who="S0192">which ones? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0189">these big ones</u>
<u n="22" who="S0192">ah yeah they're cool <pause dur="long"/> nice how mum would always leave this terrible pan</u>
<u n="23" who="S0189">yeah I know</u>
<u n="24" who="S0192">I guess they cooked last night we should've washed up <pause dur="short"/> oh you did wash up you left it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0189">huh?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0192">you washed up last night didn't you so I guess you left it</u>
<u n="27" who="S0189">ah yeah I left that one <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the sink soaking</u>
<u n="28" who="S0192">it doesn't soak <unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0192">I never really wash up at home <event desc="sound of banging"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0189">does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do the wash up?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does it</u>
<u n="33" who="S0189">oh <pause dur="short"/> do you dry? or do you just leave it drain?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0192">we just leave it drain <unclear/> I'd rather cook or do something else</u>
<u n="35" who="S0189">cooking's more interesting</u>
<u n="36" who="S0192">erm I do wash up though I mean quite often as well I'm cooking when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not around and then I if I have to wash up things as I go along so although she claims that I never do any washing up that's actually a lie I do a bit of washing up just not the same as she does</u>
<u n="37" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0192">but then she never cooks</u>
<u n="39" who="S0189">does she never cook?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0192">no not really <pause dur="short"/> she's cooked on occasion when she has like wanted to she's wanted to do something special for everyone but</u>
<u n="41" who="S0189">so she knows how to cook</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0189">she just chooses not</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and I mean saying she never cooks is a lie because she always cooks with me she's like <foreign lang="fre">sous</foreign> chef</u>
<u n="45" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0192">I'm in charge of like well I just go along with the recipe I know what's going on but I just tell her what to do you know <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0189">oh</u>
<u n="48" who="S0192">she's good at making she's good at baking and she like makes the bread and stuff <pause dur="short"/> did you get on with her?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0189">with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0189">yeah she's cool <pause dur="short"/> like whenever you weren't around and we were together we we'd chat</u>
<u n="52" who="S0192">you got along?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0189">she's a nice girl <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0192">this is just a pain in the arse this <unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0189">you should use the metal</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192">yeah I was using it I think I'm just going to leave that for now and have another go <pause dur="short"/> another day</u>
<u n="59" who="S0189">it's going to need doing though eventually</u>
<u n="60" who="S0192">oh this thing</u>
<u n="61" who="S0189">yes <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of banging"/> so when you're in <anon type="place"/> and you go in to the gym <unclear/> like what was your routine to <pause dur="short"/> build muscle?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0192"><unclear/> said I didn't really put on much muscle <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0189">no you you did because when you left you were kind of skinny and then you came back and you were quite buff <unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0189">and then you went travelling erm to India or no it was to</u>
<u n="66" who="S0192">it's the last time I came back I was kind of muscly</u>
<u n="67" who="S0189">no the last time when you came back from erm America South America you were <unclear>real skinny</unclear></u>
<u n="68" who="S0192">but now I'm more muscular</u>
<u n="69" who="S0189">well also yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0192">I can't get much bigger it's kind of sad doesn't matter how much I work out this is just about as big as I get I don't eat protein shakes or anything I don't I guess I just ate more probably this is just my natural build</u>
<u n="71" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0192">but like when we're travelling a lot I wasn't really eating that much and I was doing a lot of exercise so that was probably not a natural <unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0189">yeah so like how much exercise were you doing?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">right the <trunc>la</trunc> the last year or two?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0189">just like when you were in your peak</u>
<u n="76" who="S0192">four to five hours a week</u>
<u n="77" who="S0189">that's quite a lot</u>
<u n="78" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0189" trans="overlap">is that ah every day or every other day?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0192">I tried to do weekdays and I do an hour a day</u>
<u n="81" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0192">erm but I mean at my peak it could have been more because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I would go in the last year not the most recent year but the year before we were going hiking every other weekend and when you go hiking you're doing like six hours of exercise like in one go</u>
<u n="83" who="S0189" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0192">it's not as strenuous as like you know weights or something but it's not it's not too easy so I don't know but on average i'd say four to five hours a week probably go running once or twice or hiking and then go to the gym a couple of times</u>
<u n="85" who="S0189">so you do ah free weights at the gym?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0189">that's what I need to do <pause dur="short"/> I've got to sign up to a gym at uni ah if I sign up before I go it's like ten percent cheaper</u>
<u n="88" who="S0192">ah it's cheap anyway isn't it?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0189">it's not that cheap it's cheap compared to like a <unclear>don't know what</unclear></u>
<u n="90" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the one in <anon type="place"/> was cheap I know it was like a hundred and eighty pounds for the whole year or something</u>
<u n="91" who="S0189" trans="overlap">yeah it's about the same <unclear>again</unclear></u>
<u n="92" who="S0192">that's well cheap</u>
<u n="93" who="S0189">it is cheap</u>
<u n="94" who="S0192">I mean it's less than a pound a day</u>
<u n="95" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> considering</u>
<u n="96" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's still a hundred and eighty quid but</u>
<u n="97" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0192">I mean even if you go twice a week <pause dur="short"/> how much would that cost you to go twice a week? it's like fifty pence a go or something isn't it?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0192">no no no sorry</u>
<u n="101" who="S0189">no it would be more</u>
<u n="102" who="S0192" trans="overlap">fifty-two weeks so fifty-two goes into a hundred and eighty about three and a half times</u>
<u n="103" who="S0189">uhu <pause dur="short"/> it's still cheap if I ah go to the gym and I'm going to want to go quite often</u>
<u n="104" who="S0192">but you're not going to be there all the weeks are you? how close is the gym to where you're living?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0189">ah I don't know <pause dur="short"/> er I'd imagine it's near the <anon type="place"/> area because that's where the all the sports are</u>
<u n="106" who="S0192">yeah worth finding out</u>
<u n="107" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0192">for sure</u>
<u n="109" who="S0189">erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0192">right so the first thing we need to do is get the bread <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0189">are we going to need a saucepan?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0192">we're going to need a whole bunch of things but not immediately do you want to help me with the bread?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0189">yeah sure</u>
<u n="114" who="S0192">could've made breadcrumbs <pause dur="short"/> because we're going to make meatballs so did you ever make meatballs?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0189">nah I didn't</u>
<u n="116" who="S0192">or burgers or anything? have you ever made a burger?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0189">ah maybe once</u>
<u n="118" who="S0192">it's the same kind of thing really <pause dur="short"/> so we want some crusty bread the bread I bought the cheapest stalest looking bread so that's what you want <pause dur="short"/> and then I'm going to put some erm <pause dur="short"/> on top of the mashed potato as well</u>
<u n="119" who="S0189">okay</u>
<u n="120" who="S0192">with the breadcrumbs <pause dur="short"/> that will probably be enough give me one more slice <pause dur="short"/> I don't like that wooden chopping board</u>
<u n="121" who="S0189">why?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0192">I feel like it the germs kind of stay on it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0189">yeah I don't actually chop on this do you know? <unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0192">I mean I'll use it I haven't got a problem <unclear>it's just</unclear></u>
<u n="125" who="S0189">saying that I don't actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0192"><event desc="sound of machinery"/> oh its powerful they are too small aren't they I just think they need a better chopping board I don't see the problem with chopping on this surface <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> how good is this blade <unclear>though</unclear>? this food processor</u>
<u n="127" who="S0189">it's good enough</u>
<u n="128" who="S0192">it's quite small though isn't it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0192">sure we're going to have to do it in stages alright first things first do you want to help me de-crust? is there a bowl as well? where's like a big bowl?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0189">I'll take all the breadcrumbs <unclear>away</unclear></u>
<u n="132" who="S0192">may need to <unclear>be</unclear> bigger than that</u>
<u n="133" who="S0189">really? <unclear/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0192">do you want to help me de-crust?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0189">yeah sure</u>
<u n="136" who="S0192">so just take the crust off of these</u>
<u n="137" who="S0189">so we're only wanting the crust?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0192">no we don't want the crust</u>
<u n="139" who="S0189">oh why did you buy crusty bread then?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0192">I mean can you buy a loaf of bread without the crust?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0189">you can</u>
<u n="142" who="S0192"><unclear>how's</unclear> that?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0189">they sell it they just chop the crust off</u>
<u n="144" who="S0192">ah never seen it?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0189">ah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0192">never heard of it</u>
<u n="147" who="S0189">I'm pretty sure that Hovis and all them do that</u>
<u n="148" who="S0192" trans="overlap">ah that this was like forty pence or something i've been quite impressed since i've come home about how cheap the food is it's not cheap cheap but like you go in Lilds it's pretty cheap compared to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0189">where are we putting? have we got to break up this?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0189">I'm just joking with you <pause dur="short"/> well the thing is you're going top</u>
<u n="152" who="S0192" trans="overlap">this is some shitty bread</u>
<u n="153" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0189">this one's really dry</u>
<u n="156" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0192">it should be dry a loaf of bread <unclear/> you don't want it to be ah you don't want it to be like nice</u>
<u n="158" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the problem with cheap bread is that they make it very very quickly so it hasn't actually it's not really bread</u>
<u n="159" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="160" who="S0189">in a traditional sense</u>
<u n="161" who="S0192">what's the traditional sense?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0189">well I think like they use enzymes to partially break down the bread so it's easier to digest</u>
<u n="163" who="S0192">oh ok</u>
<u n="164" who="S0189" trans="overlap">but these are really manufactured and just not good</u>
<u n="165" who="S0192">I try not to eat much bread</u>
<u n="166" who="S0189">yeah me too</u>
<u n="167" who="S0192">in general I never <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I never bought a loaf of bread in <anon type="place"/> really <trunc>k</trunc> we'd eat tortillas a bit though a little bit</u>
<u n="168" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0192">I prefer corn tortillas though <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0189"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0192">what's so funny?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0189"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0192">they're tasty</u>
<u n="174" who="S0189">when you're complaining about that I know that wasn't <trunc>co</trunc> oh yeah that was corn</u>
<u n="175" who="S0192">what?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0189">the the crap we've got in the freezer</u>
<u n="177" who="S0192">no that's quorn with a Q Q U O R N it's like some weird I'm not even sure what that is</u>
<u n="178" who="S0189" trans="overlap">ah ok</u>
<u n="179" who="S0192">corn as in like corn you know maize they use it to <event desc="sound of banging"/> <pause dur="long"/> there's something wrong here</u>
<u n="180" who="S0189"><unclear/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0192"><unclear>cool</unclear> erm <pause dur="short"/> okay so we got the breadcrumbs</u>
<u n="182" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0192">now what I normally do with these is make a bunch like I've just done now it's just too much and then I freeze it <pause dur="short"/> so I put in in a bag</u>
<u n="184" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0192">so then I just take a handful and then I leave it</u>
<u n="186" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0192">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0189"><event desc="sound of banging"/> that keeps for a while?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0192">yeah I mean once you've frozen it it will keep for six months</u>
<u n="190" who="S0189">you could use it quicker than that</u>
<u n="191" who="S0192">right cool a lot of breadcrumbs should we quickly clean this side <pause dur="short"/> just wipe this shit off <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0189">what are you going to do if you submit your recordings and they're like ah actually this one has swearing in it we can't take it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0192">can't accept it</u>
<u n="194" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0192">ah shit <unclear/> but it's just a word isn't it? linguists aren't particular about the words that they use</u>
<u n="196" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0192">mum have like a Dustbuster thing actually is that this?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0189">yes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0192">I'll just <unclear>cane</unclear> it <event desc="sound of machinery"/> <pause dur="long"/> good idea</u>
<u n="200" who="S0189">uhu</u>
<u n="201" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="202" who="S0189">what's?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0192">hands clean?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0189">yeah what's next?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0192">right <pause dur="short"/> right you can make the sauce if you want while I make the burgers?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0189">sure</u>
<u n="207" who="S0192">first thing we want to do is make ah let's make the burgers should we just do everything together?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0189">okay</u>
<u n="209" who="S0192">this is going to take a little bit longer than <unclear>one hour</unclear> you cool?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0189">yes</u>
<u n="211" who="S0192">you got time?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0192">like an hour or something? <pause dur="short"/> right now I need an even bigger bowl like a really big bowl like a mix</u>
<u n="214" who="S0189"><unclear/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0192"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> go on</u>
<u n="216" who="S0189">that one that I showed you a minute ago is that big enough? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0192"><vocal desc="misc"/> not really is there not like a big mixing bowl somewhere? mum and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not have one?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0189">I've got bigger bowls in here</u>
<u n="219" who="S0192">hang on a minute there might be something in here yeah there's a mixing bowl in here <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <event desc="sound of banging"/> oh it's a salad spinner oh weird do they ever use it?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0189">they just got <event desc="sound of banging"/> they've used it yet</u>
<u n="221" who="S0192">oh it's got a weird little spike in the middle</u>
<u n="222" who="S0189">no good I'm just going to get a big bowl out here <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0192">just the bigger the bowl <event desc="sound of banging"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0189">here you go</u>
<u n="225" who="S0192">you got one? is it ridiculous? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0189">it's too big <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0192">cool right do you want to chop <pause dur="short"/> an onion or two? <pause dur="short"/> they've got some old onions here maybe if you could de-peel these onions? that'd be great where's the knife? need to get some air in here <event desc="sound of packaging"/> it's a really nice temperature outside</u>
<u n="228" who="S0189">yeah it's good today <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0192">which one is the real knife?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0189">this one <pause dur="long"/> chop up</u>
<u n="231" who="S0192">there's a cleaver here <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0189">erm this is the one I'm allowed to take to uni so I might as well get good at it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0192">oh you're allowed to take?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0189">well the other knives they use</u>
<u n="235" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0189">so this one <unclear>will do</unclear> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0192">I take it they don't keep the eggs in the fridge?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0189">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0192">cool <pause dur="short"/> only like a little more I guess a cup will do <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0189">ah man <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0192">what's wrong with it?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0189">a massive piece of shell went into it</u>
<u n="243" who="S0192">oh <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0192">okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0189">how finely chopped do you want these?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0192">not at all they're going to be blended</u>
<u n="247" who="S0189">okay</u>
<u n="248" who="S0192">just chop them into little bits not like too small just so they fit in the blender <pause dur="short"/> whisk the egg <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0189">that's loud</u>
<u n="250" who="S0192">yeah that is so loud isn't it? <event desc="sound of whisking"/> they can hear you out the window <pause dur="long"/> cool</u>
<u n="251" who="S0189">was that just one egg?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0189">oh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0192">probably should have just used the egg white whatever where's the light in here is this it? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0189">we've got a light here <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0192">oh nice</u>
<u n="257" who="S0189">yep</u>
<u n="258" who="S0192">very good you got any olive oil?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0189">ah yes</u>
<u n="260" who="S0192">light olive oil</u>
<u n="261" who="S0189">the one behind the <unclear/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0192">cool</u>
<u n="263" who="S0189">these are ready to go in the blender</u>
<u n="264" who="S0192">right stick them in the blender then</u>
<u n="265" who="S0189">does it matter that there's still bread there?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0192">no not really because the <unclear/> is going to go in there so <pause dur="short"/> so we're going to stick the onions in the blender <pause dur="short"/> with a little bit of olive oil <pause dur="long"/> and <pause dur="short"/> we don't need garlic that'll be alright <pause dur="short"/> right next thing you can do is erm chop some parsnip</u>
<u n="267" who="S0189"><unclear>sure</unclear></u>
<u n="268" who="S0192">right hang on one second are you ready?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0189">uhu</u>
<u n="270" who="S0192">okay so we've got the onion have you got the parsley?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0189">yeah I'm working on it</u>
<u n="272" who="S0192">cool and add the onion to this so just blend the onion up until it's nice and fine <pause dur="short"/> and this is the same kind of recipe <trunc>yo</trunc>you can use for burgers</u>
<u n="273" who="S0189">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0192">not dissimilar at all <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0189">so taking the egg just makes it all stick together</u>
<u n="276" who="S0192">yeah then the breadcrumbs the egg sticks it together but it also makes it a bit <pause dur="short"/> sticky for the breadcrumbs <unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0192">we're gonna want this blender again in a bit <pause dur="short"/> to make the sauce <pause dur="long"/> the blender is a bit small we're <unclear>going to have to</unclear> do the sauce in stages this said fruit processor or something <unclear/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0189">I don't know</u>
<u n="280" who="S0192">I think it's called a fruit processor</u>
<u n="281" who="S0189">what's the difference?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0192">this is a blender it blends</u>
<u n="283" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0192">whereas processors it like chops it differently</u>
<u n="285" who="S0189">oh</u>
<u n="286" who="S0192">so these are more heavy duty than these they'd make a smoothie and something else in this very cool what else are we going to put in this? <pause dur="short"/> put a bit of cumin? do you like cumin?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0192">put in the cumin in there maybe bit of paprika</u>
<u n="289" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">is that paprika?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0189">Does it matter if there's a few stalks in it?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0192">no mate just chop it up as small as you can</u>
<u n="292" who="S0189">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0192">put in a bit of salt and pepper <pause dur="short"/> do you enjoy cooking?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0189">yeah I like it <pause dur="short"/> when it works and I make a nice meal</u>
<u n="295" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> comes out tasty it's annoying when you go to all that effort</u>
<u n="296" who="S0189">and it's rubbish</u>
<u n="297" who="S0192">oh this tastes like crap</u>
<u n="298" who="S0189">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0192">where would the salt and pepper be bro?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0189">ah salt and pepper <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0192">oh forgot there was a lid on it <pause dur="short"/> oh can I get this to work? <pause dur="short"/> there's some big chunks of pepper corn coming out now <unclear/> what is this? pink Himalayan salt?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0189">it's good salt</u>
<u n="303" who="S0192">is it yours?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0192">you've got like the fanciest salt around</u>
<u n="306" who="S0189">uhu <pause dur="long"/> now I'm quite hungry</u>
<u n="307" who="S0192">have you not eaten anything?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0189">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0192">you can take a break and then grab some food</u>
<u n="310" who="S0189">there's not really much to grab</u>
<u n="311" who="S0192">is there not? we've got apples</u>
<u n="312" who="S0189">yeah I might have some fruit</u>
<u n="313" who="S0192">there's yogurt <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> there's bacon <pause dur="short"/> there's a couple of sausages</u>
<u n="314" who="S0189">well how long do you think this is going to take to cook?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0192">going to be a little while but you can do that while I'm getting on with something else</u>
<u n="316" who="S0189" trans="overlap">this is for dinner isn't it? not lunch</u>
<u n="317" who="S0192">yeah this is for dinner</u>
<u n="318" who="S0189">I'm going to have to do lunch then</u>
<u n="319" who="S0192">cool <pause dur="short"/> what are you going to do for lunch?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0189">don't know yet maybe do an omelette</u>
<u n="321" who="S0192">I had a sausage sandwich earlier it was good there's two more sausages left if you want</u>
<u n="322" who="S0189">maybe</u>
<u n="323" who="S0192">ah there's plenty of bacon <pause dur="short"/> I bought another whole pack of cheese <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty good for two quid</u>
<u n="324" who="S0189">that's pretty big</u>
<u n="325" who="S0192">yeah man</u>
<u n="326" who="S0189">alright is this cut up enough?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0192">yeah man sure looks good</u>
<u n="328" who="S0189"><event desc="sound of chopping"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0192"><unclear/> cool so stick it in here</u>
<u n="330" who="S0189">okay do you want to do that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0192">yeah cool <pause dur="short"/> nice cleaving now put a bunch of breadcrumbs in there <pause dur="short"/> and then just mix it all together basically until we get the brain</u>
<u n="332" who="S0189"><vocal desc="laugh"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> sounds pretty disgusting</u>
<u n="333" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah tastes good though <pause dur="long"/> you don't want to impress your mates with some eh burgers? yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0189"><unclear/> not buying them</u>
<u n="335" who="S0192">oh definitely <pause dur="short"/> burgers are never cheap though you have to use so much meat</u>
<u n="336" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0192">five hundred grams should be enough for the three of us shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0189">I can eat five hundred grams on my own</u>
<u n="339" who="S0192">yeah but I mean we're having quite a lot of sauce and we're going to have some peppers with mashed potatoes though <pause dur="short"/> do you think this might be enough?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0189">ah should be okay</u>
<u n="341" who="S0192">got me worried <pause dur="long"/> I'm sure there'll be enough food <pause dur="short"/> there'll be quite a few meatballs here <pause dur="long"/> I want to cook a rendang with you at some point</u>
<u n="342" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0192">I was tempted when I go over Dad's to see if he's got any lemongrass and <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0189">I think he will do</u>
<u n="345" who="S0192">because if he has and I think he has then we might be able to do one before we go</u>
<u n="346" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit expensive though buying your beef <pause dur="short"/> I need like some proper steak <pause dur="short"/> you know just buy like pre-cut beef chunks <pause dur="short"/> or does that have to be very tender meat?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0192">erm it's you don't really want it to be very chewy but I mean if we left it for a day it'd be alright <pause dur="long"/> right where's the big frying pan?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0189">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0192">is that as big as it comes? is there no other ones? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0189">we've got a wok if that'll do?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0192">no I need flat</u>
<u n="352" who="S0189">right it's flat as it comes</u>
<u n="353" who="S0192">is that all there is? <pause dur="short"/> you don't have the bigger ones no? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0189">erm do we have one in the eh <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0192">nope</u>
<u n="356" who="S0189">must have taken it with them</u>
<u n="357" who="S0192">they've taken it?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0189"><unclear/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0192">oh bugger that's no good</u>
<u n="360" who="S0189">unless you can wait <unclear/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0192"><unclear>yeah I might have to</unclear> what's that one at the back? the wok? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0189">yeah that's no good <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0192">yeah so you're making bacon?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0189">I'll do bacon eggs I'll put some veg in and make some kind of omelette <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0192">cool <pause dur="short"/> right so we've got the brain</u>
<u n="366" who="S0189">what do you think of the tea?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0192">yeah it's good I like it actually got the brain good good</u>
<u n="368" who="S0189">it does look like a brain</u>
<u n="369" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it does doesn't it? every time I make it I'm like it's the brain <pause dur="short"/> and now for meatballs you just want to make them into balls <pause dur="long"/> so you excited about going to uni?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0189">yes time's going to fly by down there</u>
<u n="371" who="S0192">it really is going to fly by isn't it?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0192">it's good that you've got your accommodation agreement</u>
<u n="374" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0192">that's a relief it's quite exciting when you get that kind of information</u>
<u n="376" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was more exciting when I got accepted</u>
<u n="377" who="S0192">yeah well when you got back? when you got back from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0189">yeah and I got <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0192">did you get the grades you were hoping for in the end? what was your final grade?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0189">ah like ninety percent</u>
<u n="381" who="S0192" trans="overlap">ah I need that celery mate</u>
<u n="382" who="S0189">all of it?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0192">yeah I need all of it</u>
<u n="384" who="S0189">oh bugger</u>
<u n="385" who="S0192">I didn't know you were going to use it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0189">no I don't have to use it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0192">erm no I don't you can use the stalk</u>
<u n="388" who="S0189">one?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0192">yeah use one how much does that leave me with? there's no leaves on this thing is there what's that all about? how much does that leave?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0189">you've got like ah four stalks</u>
<u n="391" who="S0192">okay yeah you can use one is that alright?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0192">well I'm glad I caught you <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>particularly</unclear> you didn't want to cook me any food</u>
<u n="394" who="S0189">you can have some of this if you want?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0192">you might want to stick an extra rasher in you know I did have a sausage sandwich but it was about three or four hours ago</u>
<u n="396" who="S0189">I'll just put a bunch of eggs in I'm going to make this how I make it it's not especially tasty</u>
<u n="397" who="S0192">ah I'm sure it's good mate</u>
<u n="398" who="S0189">I actually mix it in with rice as well</u>
<u n="399" who="S0192">cool whatever you've made if I could just have a little bit of it I'll be pleased</u>
<u n="400" who="S0189">right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0192">what's your favourite thing that you cook?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0189">probably the curries at the moment</u>
<u n="403" who="S0192">yeah?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0189">when they go well they're quite nice</u>
<u n="405" who="S0192">I need chilli now to make a proper proper sauces once you know how to do it it's easy you just need the ingredients</u>
<u n="406" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0192">and once you buy a pack of tamarind you only need a little bit so you've got like loads of tamarind</u>
<u n="408" who="S0189">yeah I did try and <unclear/> <event desc="sound of banging"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0189">like that special galangal or whatever it's <trunc>cal</trunc></u>
<u n="411" who="S0192" trans="overlap">galangal</u>
<u n="412" who="S0189">galangal</u>
<u n="413" who="S0192">as I said just replace it with erm ginger</u>
<u n="414" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0192">it's basically the same thing it's a type of ginger</u>
<u n="416" who="S0189">it's just a special type of ginger?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0192">but it still tastes fine I could never get peanut oil you know or coconut oil</u>
<u n="418" who="S0189">coconut oil is easy to get here</u>
<u n="419" who="S0192">yeah it's not in erm <pause dur="short"/> it's not in <anon type="place"/> for some reason <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why <pause dur="long"/> oh it's looking good how often do you eat celery then?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0189">erm <pause dur="short"/> well whenever we have it like sometimes I'll buy it but mum usually puts celery in stock</u>
<u n="421" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0189">and I think it's kind of tasty so</u>
<u n="423" who="S0192">it is tasty isn't it?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0189">sometimes I'll have leek as well</u>
<u n="425" who="S0192">yeah leek's good <pause dur="short"/> I've noticed in England they don't have the leaves</u>
<u n="426" who="S0189">no</u>
<u n="427" who="S0192">like they cut the tops and the heads off</u>
<u n="428" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0192">in Korea and I I found one day do you like cilantro? coriander?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0189">yeah kind of</u>
<u n="431" who="S0192">I googled one day I didn't have coriander and I was like what could you use instead of coriander? and this guy <trunc>t</trunc> said on this website to use the leaves of celery</u>
<u n="432" who="S0189">oh</u>
<u n="433" who="S0192">and I started doing it it's really flavoursome cos normally actually when I make this meatballs dish I don't use the stalks of celery I use the leaves</u>
<u n="434" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0192">with a bit of the stalk they're quite pungent</u>
<u n="436" who="S0189">I've never tried it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0192">it's good and they don't sell them here so <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> pointless <pause dur="short"/> you're gonna be well sought after when you go to uni surely</u>
<u n="438" who="S0189">why cos I?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0192">travelling mature student knows how to cook</u>
<u n="440" who="S0189">perhaps we'll see</u>
<u n="441" who="S0192">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="442" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0192">if you get out there and start cutting up real ingredients and stuff <unclear/> these nineteen-year-old children are gonna be</u>
<u n="444" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0192">really impressed</u>
<u n="446" who="S0189">people grow up pretty quickly at uni they all come in with their Pot Noodles</u>
<u n="447" who="S0192">yeah basically <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't cook when I went to uni it was my mate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that showed <trunc>y</trunc> have you met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0189">yeah I have</u>
<u n="449" who="S0192">he showed me like er he lives in <anon type="place"/> by the way</u>
<u n="450" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0192"><unclear/> he showed me a can of chopped tomatoes and said <pause dur="short"/> better learn how to cook <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0189">yeah our our parents never taught us to cook</u>
<u n="453" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="454" who="S0189"><unclear/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0192">it's a terrible life skill not to not to teach you</u>
<u n="456" who="S0189">it's cos they couldn't cook</u>
<u n="457" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0189">plain and simply <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0192">if you can't cook how are you gonna cook someone else teach someone else to cook</u>
<u n="460" who="S0189">exactly</u>
<u n="461" who="S0192">you can't</u>
<u n="462" who="S0189">that's why we never learned ambition from them</u>
<u n="463" who="S0192">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> mum said the other day she was a bit upset you kind of had a talk with her in the car or something</u>
<u n="464" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0192">what was that all about? told her she was a bad parent or something?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0189">no I wasn't saying that I was just saying like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> how do I go into it? erm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0192">well don't talk about it if you don't want to <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0189">we were having a discussion like about childhood and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and things like that</u>
<u n="469" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0189">and I was saying to her how like she never taught me to cook or er because she was never ambitious like we didn't really get pushed to be ambitious either</u>
<u n="471" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="472" who="S0189">and like I was like well you can't really teach kids things that you yourself do not possess and I suppose I was just having a bit of a moan <pause dur="short"/> about my childhood</u>
<u n="473" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0189">or whatever cos er we had a lot of shit <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0192">we had a lot of good things as well though</u>
<u n="476" who="S0189">we had some good things yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0192">I mean we did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up until the divorce like mum tried hard she did she may have done some things wrong but she tried hard every time</u>
<u n="478" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0192">so no you can't say that she didn't try</u>
<u n="480" who="S0189">I know she I'm pretty sure that she always did what she thought was best</u>
<u n="481" who="S0192">mm but like erm what you were talking about with being ambitious? I'm actually glad personally that our parents didn't push us too much because I have friends now that they don't really have a very adult relationship with their parents because they <trunc>tr</trunc> still treat their parents like parents because their parents have always been in possession of them and they've always told them what to do and all that kind of thing</u>
<u n="482" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0192">whereas like I dunno <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I have never felt any pressure so whatever we do they're proud of us whatever we achieve we've done well</u>
<u n="484" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0189"><unclear/> so it can go both ways <pause dur="long"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="486" who="S0192">just obviously obviously you can tell your mum how you feel obviously but just remember that she'll carry that</u>
<u n="487" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0192">she'll remember it</u>
<u n="489" who="S0189">but the thing is like through a lot of my childhood I was depressed</u>
<u n="490" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0189">like after they'd split up and I didn't really have a good time <unclear/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean you say a lot of your childhood but they split up when you were thirteen or twelve?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0192">you were a man by the time you were eighteen so</u>
<u n="495" who="S0189">yeah I know <trunc>b</trunc>by the time I was eighteen I was okay but like <trunc>thr</trunc>through school after that</u>
<u n="496" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0189">like things went bad and then they never really got better <pause dur="short"/> but I'm sure like a lot of that was through my own choices and decisions</u>
<u n="498" who="S0192">yeah well it's a combination isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> but I mean you definitely became more introvert once <pause dur="short"/> they split up</u>
<u n="499" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0192">but now you're out the other side now and you just have to be pleased that you came out the other side</u>
<u n="501" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0192">you're okay <pause dur="long"/> cos it could've erm could've been worse</u>
<u n="503" who="S0189" trans="overlap">it took me time like <unclear/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0189">for me to get my shit together</u>
<u n="506" who="S0192">but that's alright everyone does things at slightly different ages I was lucky I personally at the time it happened I could've gone one of two ways I could've just spiralled out been some <pause dur="short"/> fuck up in <anon type="place"/> pretty much</u>
<u n="507" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0192">erm but thankfully I didn't I went to uni and it helped quite a bit <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="509" who="S0189">it's just I didn't have any direction <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0192">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> but that is your own fault to a certain degree</u>
<u n="511" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0192">in the west it's up to us isn't it the parents can't tell you what to do and I'm sure if mum had told you and the thing is mum did try and <trunc>cour</trunc> and encourage you plenty you forget of all the clubs that mum tried to sign you up to and all the things that she tried to do to get you out of your room you can't just blame her for that you didn't want to and you didn't want to come out</u>
<u n="513" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0192">you were addicted to the computers it's an addiction no one blames you for that because you used it as a crutch I <unclear>didn't get addicted</unclear> to things as we all know</u>
<u n="515" who="S0189">where's the? erm <pause dur="short"/> where's the can opener?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0192">it should be in that drawer there <pause dur="long"/> I don't know can you use this this doesn't look like a normal can opener</u>
<u n="517" who="S0189">you have to open it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="518" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0192">what a retard <pause dur="long"/> did she get upset?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0189">a little bit</u>
<u n="521" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean don't worry about it I've said some horrible things <pause dur="short"/> over the years so problem is one thing I've learned you can't really take that back and they do remember it <pause dur="short"/> but it's fair to say how you feel <pause dur="short"/> but just bear in mind that how you feel is also your perception and she has her perception</u>
<u n="522" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0192">does bother me that she seems to be making some of the same mistakes with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he watches too much TV <pause dur="short"/> for my liking and eats too many <trunc>sug</trunc> too much sugar</u>
<u n="524" who="S0189">they try and control it like</u>
<u n="525" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I know they do</u>
<u n="526" who="S0189"><unclear/> like what they did there is a lot better <unclear>now kids eat</unclear> nothing but sugar</u>
<u n="527" who="S0192">no it's crap <pause dur="short"/> it's really bad actually <pause dur="short"/> I'm not the biggest fan of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the way she kind of lives her life you think she'll have any more children? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0189">probably <pause dur="short"/> I hope not but</u>
<u n="529" who="S0192">hope they don't like divorce or anything that's just going to be another wrecked family <pause dur="short"/> it's not on <pause dur="short"/> but what can you do?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0189">you can't do anything</u>
<u n="531" who="S0192">it's people's life to live isn't it? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0189">people's mistakes to make <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0192">yeah and they'll keep making them that's smelling good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's healthy hearty <pause dur="long"/> have you decided if you're going to kickboxing or not?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0189">yeah I will do</u>
<u n="535" who="S0192">what time are you? are you going to eat then when you get back?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0189">might just have a snack first <pause dur="short"/> depends what time you want to eat</u>
<u n="537" who="S0192">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going to pick me up at like half five <pause dur="short"/> I doubt we're going to eat before half six seven</u>
<u n="538" who="S0189">okay will I sort my own myself some food then?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0192">are you done with this chopping board? can I chop some lemons?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0189">ah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0192">yeah if you're not</u>
<u n="542" who="S0189">I can peel some mushrooms and eh</u>
<u n="543" who="S0192" trans="overlap">ah shit you put mushrooms in it <unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0189">do you not like mushrooms?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0192">no I'll pick around them <unclear/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0189">well I'll put them away then</u>
<u n="547" who="S0192">I mean most no no put them in most of this is yours anyway I'll just have <pause dur="short"/> if you could spare maybe a quarter or a third?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0189">yeah sure <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0192">say that I did have a sausage sandwich but it was a while ago <pause dur="long"/> did you have anything for breakfast?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0189">I've had two bananas today that's it</u>
<u n="551" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0192">so with this sauce now I'm just going to add in raw tomato and blend it in with the onion and raw garlic stuff like that I mean if you just give me another chopping board I could <unclear/> cleaning or whatever <pause dur="long"/> onions ever make your eyes water?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0189">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="555" who="S0192">badly?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0189">never badly but it's unpleasant</u>
<u n="557" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0189">you don't like mushrooms at all do you?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0192">no but that's fine I mean if you can leave them bigger so I can quickly pick them out I mean I get around mushrooms all the time but if if you like make them really <trunc>s</trunc>small</u>
<u n="560" who="S0189"><unclear>It'd look rubbish</unclear></u>
<u n="561" who="S0192">I can eat them but I don't I just choose not to <pause dur="short"/> depends on the mushroom some are less pungent than others</u>
<u n="562" who="S0189"><unclear/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0192">you can do it quarters that's fine <pause dur="short"/> it's still fairly big but it's a quarters isn't it just don't like douse it <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0189">these need using or they're going to go off because I don't think you're going to use them</u>
<u n="565" who="S0192">no <pause dur="short"/> never going to happen did you ever see those ones in <anon type="place"/>? they're like the long thin white ones? come in a big bunch</u>
<u n="566" who="S0189">I saw the mushrooms that are kind of like jellyfish</u>
<u n="567" who="S0192">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> they've got so many different types there actually</u>
<u n="568" who="S0189">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0192">kind of ridiculous <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> so do you reckon the summer's coming to an end?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0189">we seem to be lucky with the weather today but I think summer's almost over</u>
<u n="571" who="S0192">is September normally nice? I don't remember</u>
<u n="572" who="S0189">it's okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0192">not terrible</u>
<u n="574" who="S0189">no <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0192">oh this is one thing I don't miss <pause dur="short"/> unpeeled garlic <pause dur="short"/> it's always peeled in <anon type="place"/> doesn't come in a in a clove like this <pause dur="short"/> quite a great idea but I mean is there a machine that does that? seems a bit difficult to peel garlic</u>
<u n="576" who="S0189">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'll show you the way that they showed me in ah <anon type="place"/> to peel</u>
<u n="577" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0189">well <unclear/> that big one but <pause dur="short"/> man these are huge <unclear/> these ones</u>
<u n="579" who="S0192">you just squish it</u>
<u n="580" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0192">yeah thanks <pause dur="short"/> bang</u>
<u n="582" who="S0189"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0192">easily done <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0189">it seems to work</u>
<u n="585" who="S0192">yeah it does oh something's gone in my eyes now <pause dur="long"/> I reckon the garlic here is stronger <pause dur="short"/> you don't need a bigger knife to do this banging thing with <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0189">you need a big chopper</u>
<u n="587" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how far are we off until eating?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0189">soon</u>
<u n="589" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah nice <pause dur="short"/> anything with eggs <pause dur="short"/> it's nice that we managed to have some time to ourselves</u>
<u n="590" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0192">kind of worker out alright <pause dur="long"/> oh</u>
<u n="592" who="S0189">I wonder how long it's going to take them to get to eh to <anon type="place"/> by car?</u>
<u n="593" who="S0192">yeah I know when are they meant to be there by?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0189">I feel sorry for them</u>
<u n="595" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0189">that's going to be so boring</u>
<u n="597" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's not actually that long though when I asked them how long the actual journey was I was quite surprised I thought it would be longer once they're over the ferry it's about seven hours' drive</u>
<u n="598" who="S0189">that's not too bad</u>
<u n="599" who="S0192">no seeing as I mean it's like a five hour drive to <anon type="place"/> so actually they should be there soon shouldn't they?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought it would take a lot longer than that</u>
<u n="601" who="S0192">yeah I thought so too <pause dur="short"/> but maybe I'm wrong <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure he said that to me but you would think it would be like six hours just to get through <anon type="place"/> wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0189">mm and then they've got to get down to southern <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0192">I don't rightly know</u>
<u n="604" who="S0189">oh no I don't think I've got any rice <pause dur="short"/> got that sticky rice</u>
<u n="605" who="S0192">just have it without <pause dur="short"/> it's got to be good <unclear/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0189">yeah it's just not <unclear/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0192"><unclear/> put some more eggs in it</u>
<u n="608" who="S0189">I've put three in already</u>
<u n="609" who="S0192">I mean I could eat two eggs I'm sure you can eat three eggs couldn't you? <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0189">gets really eggy though</u>
<u n="611" who="S0192">yeah it's lovely</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
