<text id="SXRR">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:02:13</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0046 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Work, dating, clothes</topics>
		<activity>Friends cooking and eating dinner, chatting, watching a movie</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0046">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Labourer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0084">it's so upsetting <pause dur="short"/> just leave it to fester love</u>
<u n="2" who="S0041">fester</u>
<u n="3" who="S0084">fester <pause dur="short"/> uncle Fester</u>
<u n="4" who="S0041">erm <pause dur="short"/> fork?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0084">to shovel the food?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0041">to shovel <pause dur="short"/> shovel the food</u>
<u n="7" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> genius <pause dur="short"/> is that your dinner? Oh the fish is in the oven</u>
<u n="8" who="S0041">no I've got the fish for next for second dinner <pause dur="short"/> so I'm going to have a slice of eggy bread for first dinner and then then it'll be time for second dinner which seems fine</u>
<u n="9" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mhm <pause dur="short"/> mm seems sensible</u>
<u n="10" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at work likes to talk to me now</u>
<u n="11" who="S0084">yeah just tell that you hate her</u>
<u n="12" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> the thing is I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knows that I hate her</u>
<u n="13" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> do you have a pained expression on your face every time she talks to you?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> erm but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes her either <pause dur="short"/> I think it's just cos she's so tedious <pause dur="short"/> like it takes her so long to talk as well that you're just like oh fucking shut up <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s much more patient with her than I am</u>
<u n="15" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0041">so when we're both we both have to play the game of just nod and she might stop speaking soon and realise that she's the only one that's been talking in this conversation</u>
<u n="17" who="S0084">yeah those people never get the hint though do they?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="19" who="S0084">is she the older one that's got the kids? No</u>
<u n="20" who="S0041">no kids <pause dur="short"/> she's old though <pause dur="short"/> well not super old <pause dur="short"/> she's fifty this year</u>
<u n="21" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0041">well no you're thinking of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0041">she's on team Amy though</u>
<u n="25" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh my God <pause dur="short"/> amy <pause dur="short"/> let's speak about her</u>
<u n="27" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0041">has gone down to <pause dur="short"/> what has she gone down to? mm <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember the name of the place but we'll say it's <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> don't know</u>
<u n="29" who="S0084">somewhere west</u>
<u n="30" who="S0041">somewhere <pause dur="short"/> no it's just somewhere that I don't know of</u>
<u n="31" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="32" who="S0041">or like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0084" trans="overlap">but you don't know <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh okay</u>
<u n="34" who="S0041">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> somewhere <pause dur="short"/> she's gone there cos their erm sales manager <pause dur="short"/> director of sales has just walked out and they've been one sales manager down for like eight weeks or something so they're really behind on their quotas <pause dur="short"/> so basically as a favour <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> has pimped her out to go and help them out for two weeks or something</u>
<u n="35" who="S0084" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0041">erm I mean I'm the only person that knows that that's the part of her personal development plan to go and work in a cluster cos she just works for <pause dur="short"/> she's a sales manager for a hotel</u>
<u n="37" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0041">usually sales managers manage a couple of hotels so she's had a really easy ride of it</u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">oh that's interesting</u>
<u n="40" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm and obviously her targets are easy to get cos we do all the work and she just takes credit for it</u>
<u n="41" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> can't blame the girl for trying</u>
<u n="42" who="S0041">whereas <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> really she's been really smart about it because if you work for a cluster as opposed to just one hotel then you don't get to speak to the conference team and find out all the insider gossip and try and work around them <pause dur="short"/> you're just left to your own devices and the conference team won't talk to you because they don't won't you poaching their clients</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="44" who="S0041">so that's how she's ended up being so good</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0041">but she's basically passed it off to everyone else as if they've requested her to go and sort it out <pause dur="short"/> so she's looking after a cluster <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> what a douche</u>
<u n="47" who="S0084">she's a nob</u>
<u n="48" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084">well at least that gets her out your hair for two weeks</u>
<u n="50" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> it just pisses me off hearing her say it because she's not particularly good at her job <pause dur="short"/> she just is getting on the back of everyone else</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0041">she's been in sales for a year and a half</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">is that it? She's already a sales manager</u>
<u n="54" who="S0041">mhm <pause dur="short"/> that's what I mean <pause dur="short"/> had she not worked at our hotel she wouldn't have a chance</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0041">her figures aren't high enough <pause dur="short"/> her contacts aren't high enough</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0041">she's just been fortunate</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> it basically is just <trunc>ri</trunc> right place right time <pause dur="short"/> and don't rock the boat too much</u>
<u n="60" who="S0041">mhm <pause dur="short"/> which I mean is great for her and if she's a nice person you'd be like fucking hell <pause dur="short"/> great</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084">yeah but it still doesn't seem fair though if you're the in a different department and that option isn't available to you and you're working your arse off for little credit</u>
<u n="62" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> so she's winning <pause dur="short"/> she basically gets targeted on bedrooms as well as conference <pause dur="short"/> but if she overhears me landing a big deal she muscles in</u>
<u n="63" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> really?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0041">and she's like that <pause dur="short"/> oh do you want me to contact them and ask them about Business Cub <pause dur="short"/> and I'm like no <pause dur="short"/> cos I know she's only doing it to make friends with them and then she'll make them one of her accounts <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0084">bitch</u>
<u n="66" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="67" who="S0084">there's no sense of like unity then is there</u>
<u n="68" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no not at all <pause dur="short"/> and I mean I can't get angry because I don't have accounts that are my own so there's no benefit to me having them but I just resent her reigning the credit for just jumping on at the last minute</u>
<u n="69" who="S0084">yeah fair enough <pause dur="short"/> well it's it's it you're getting on with anyone that's not really pulling their weight you know if you're getting paid a decent salary or is getting credit for something that they isn't justified <pause dur="short"/> like isn't through hard work or their hard work <pause dur="short"/> somebody else's</u>
<u n="70" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> and she hasn't done a <pause dur="short"/> she did a  training like I did the first week I got there <pause dur="short"/> yet  have we got  have we got room for a conference on this day? And I'm thinking you should know how to check that yourself <pause dur="short"/> that's part of your job <pause dur="short"/> but she'll <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I mid doing something and even Simon now says if you've got any enquires send it to the <trunc>i</trunc> in box</u>
<u n="71" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0041">and we'll get to it when I get to it <pause dur="short"/> we're busy now</u>
<u n="73" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0041">Cos she just says it <pause dur="short"/> she'll start speaking <pause dur="short"/> expect you to drop what you're doing and check availability for her when actually she should be able to check it for herself</u>
<u n="75" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0041">and we have to put contacts together for her when she should be able to do a contract herself <pause dur="short"/> it's a button <pause dur="short"/> it's just it's a tedious time consuming job</u>
<u n="77" who="S0084">she doesn't want to do it</u>
<u n="78" who="S0041">so she doesn't want to do it <pause dur="short"/> yeah we can't say no cos then we're cos we're reactive sales so she'll be supporting the sales team</u>
<u n="79" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> what a nober</u>
<u n="80" who="S0041">she's just doing it to be <pause dur="short"/> it it's just feels like whenever she does something it's to get something <pause dur="short"/> she never <pause dur="short"/> if we  if we  needed something she'd never help us but she expects our help all the time</u>
<u n="81" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0041">and that's another thing <pause dur="short"/> she dropped <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in it</u>
<u n="83" who="S0084">yeah?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0041">Cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the GM has started this new thing where he's saying <pause dur="short"/> he started like a secret club <pause dur="short"/> I don't really understand what the hell's going on</u>
<u n="85" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and there's a few people in the hotel basically that are working on this <trunc>il</trunc> on the PE team and I don't know what the hell that is <pause dur="short"/> but he's basically driving revenue within the hotel <pause dur="short"/> so both <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she's Sales manager and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because he's a financial controller to see if it's financially viable</u>
<u n="87" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for some reason <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s in on the game <pause dur="short"/> maybe because he's they're trying to develop him</u>
<u n="89" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0041">so <unclear/> proof that he can manage <pause dur="short"/> and they've been on this stupid team erm to drive revenue in the hotel</u>
<u n="91" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="92" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not on the team but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did the usual and basically recruited loads of people to do the work for her <pause dur="short"/> one of them being <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stupid enough to say yes I'll help <pause dur="short"/> and I did warn her</u>
<u n="93" who="S0084">she is a douche</u>
<u n="94" who="S0041">yeah and she said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said no now I've just said I'll help with the restaurant lunches because that goes on our banqueting revenue so win win</u>
<u n="95" who="S0084" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="96" who="S0041">so there's a big massive <pause dur="short"/> there's a big presentation tomorrow that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are supposed to be doing to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is the regional sales director that's come in <pause dur="short"/> real big cheese <pause dur="short"/> as far as we're concerned he's the closest to head office that we ever see</u>
<u n="97" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so he's come in <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fucked off and been pimped out and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s said that he's too he's he's too shy to do the presentation so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> fell on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="100" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got to do a massive presentation tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> something that she's not been involved in <pause dur="short"/> doesn't have a clue and has literally got some slides <pause dur="short"/> and she was like what? And he's prepare him to ask you for questions about meetings <pause dur="short"/> and she's like what the fuck? Cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fucked off and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will come back and say well I don't know if I can help cos I wasn't in the last meeting</u>
<u n="101" who="S0084">oh what a nob</u>
<u n="102" who="S0041">yeah she's so  she's so  bad</u>
<u n="103" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0041">and it works for her career like being that type of person is great for sales</u>
<u n="105" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0041">Cos you pass the buck <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to do anything and you just reap the benefits so really she's doing really well</u>
<u n="107" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0041">but I just can't understand how you could be that awful <pause dur="short"/> that that selfish to you people your supposed to work with <pause dur="short"/> and so two faced</u>
<u n="109" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't feel like you're part of a team <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> you must think for them <pause dur="short"/> erm why do you get job satisfaction from that?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0084">you couldn't pay me enough <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously that's why they pay people really well in sales cos I think money does turn you <pause dur="short"/> and some people who are only interested or only motivated by money then great then sales is for you but in terms of like your own emotional development I think it just stunts you because you've basically just got to be out there for yourself and you know to sell whatever it is that you your commodity or whatever it is against anybody else</u>
<u n="112" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm er I'm not pro <pause dur="short"/> not pro that</u>
<u n="113" who="S0084">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> this is a good idea</u>
<u n="114" who="S0041">I just thought of something</u>
<u n="115" who="S0084">what did you think of?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I wonder if there's some type of sexy underwear <pause dur="short"/> you know like my zip up</u>
<u n="117" who="S0084">oh where can we get that from?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0041">from <trunc>Tri</trunc> Triumph to go under the dress <pause dur="short"/> like if it was gold</u>
<u n="119" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0041">and you even if you could see it <pause dur="short"/> as long as it looks pretty</u>
<u n="121" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> we do need to go to Triumph <pause dur="short"/> do you want to do some birthday shopping on your birthday?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0041">yeah I love birthday shopping <pause dur="short"/> that will be nice <pause dur="short"/> we could go and do some birthday shopping and then go for a little drink</u>
<u n="123" who="S0084" trans="overlap">have a little drink somewhere</u>
<u n="124" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that will be my favourite <pause dur="short"/> I love shopping</u>
<u n="125" who="S0084">shopping and drinking</u>
<u n="126" who="S0041">always a winner</u>
<u n="127" who="S0084">and birthday</u>
<u n="128" who="S0041">I really want to open my ring <pause dur="short"/> kate dropped it off <pause dur="short"/> dad left it with her <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0084">oh how exciting <pause dur="short"/> did he wrap it?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I really want to open it but I haven't <pause dur="short"/> it was close</u>
<u n="131" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Really?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0041">it nearly got opened <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> I haven't opened it</u>
<u n="133" who="S0084">but it will be here for Saturday <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="134" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0084">are you going to just wear it for best</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="138" who="S0041">I want to wear it all the time but I can't wear it for work <pause dur="short"/> it's too showy <pause dur="short"/> but erm I'll wear it at the weekends <pause dur="short"/> I want it if I wasn't at this job I would wear it all the time</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">it's to go here <pause dur="short"/> so this one will go on this finger</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="142" who="S0041">and it will go next to the gold band <pause dur="short"/> when you see it you'll realise it it should go next to the gold band</u>
<u n="143" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0041">yeah I really want it <pause dur="short"/> I really want it on</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084">lovely <pause dur="short"/> precious</u>
<u n="146" who="S0041">and this one was for eighteenth and this one was for Christmas of twenty first and that one's for the twenty fifth</u>
<u n="147" who="S0084">perfect</u>
<u n="148" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="149" who="S0084">go Dad</u>
<u n="150" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just really like it cos it's not it's really unique like it's not you can tell somebody has spent a lot of time making it and it's the only one that's been made</u>
<u n="151" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> mm mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0041">like the clasps are on show and they shouldn't be and it's not finished perfectly</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0041">it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> and you'll never get lapis lazuli set on gold ever</u>
<u n="155" who="S0084">you never get what sorry?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0041">the stone it's lapis lazuli <pause dur="short"/> it's like er this colourish <pause dur="short"/> maybe a bit darker <pause dur="short"/> but you never get it set on gold <pause dur="short"/> you're like amber's usually set on silver</u>
<u n="157" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0041">which is why this is a er sapphire <pause dur="short"/> not a not amber cos I couldn't get amber</u>
<u n="159" who="S0084" trans="overlap">not amber <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well that's interesting isn't it <pause dur="short"/> why do they do that then?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0041">they do it with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well <pause dur="short"/> my three favourite stones because I think they're semi precious</u>
<u n="161" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Okay yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0041">really <pause dur="short"/> they're not like diamonds or rubies or this on silver <pause dur="short"/> and I had a look the only place in England I've I know where you can get the lapis lazuli set on gold is a place in London but it makes custom jewellery so you're talking like two hundred pound a pop minimum</u>
<u n="163" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0041">bloody buggers</u>
<u n="165" who="S0084">but then  but then  it would be just your own <pause dur="short"/> just your own secret ring <pause dur="short"/> all secret things have secret times</u>
<u n="166" who="S0041">of secret wonderfulness</u>
<u n="167" who="S0084">that everyone would be really jealous by <pause dur="short"/> so who have you actually invited for Saturday then?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0041">erm <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> I I just actually want you <pause dur="short"/> emily <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yourself</u>
<u n="170" who="S0041">that's fine by me</u>
<u n="171" who="S0084">that's more than enough</u>
<u n="172" who="S0041">that's enough people for me to</u>
<u n="173" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0041">Cos I I mean I sound like I don't like being around people <pause dur="short"/> I do like being around people</u>
<u n="175" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0041">it's just that I always hate it when you have to herd people around <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? And</u>
<u n="177" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0041">if someone goes to the toilet and then three people go to the toilet and there's four of you stood and whereas if it was a small group then you would be with people the whole time <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="180" who="S0041">so I think I'll text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> nick <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then I thought but then I thought if I text them then I've got to invite <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0041">and</u>
<u n="183" who="S0084">yeah cos I thought you weren't going to invite any of them cos then at least that's safe</u>
<u n="184" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then I thought well isn't it a bit mean of me not to invite <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0084">well if you're going to invite any of them then yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="187" who="S0084">it's a tough one though because you shouldn't <trunc>ha</trunc> feel dictated to on your birthday <pause dur="short"/> you should just invite the people that you want to invite</u>
<u n="188" who="S0041">yeah I mean if it was just her then fine but she doesn't go anywhere on her own <pause dur="short"/> she always invites  And I do like</u>
<u n="189" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right and you've met him?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0041">yeah yeah he's nice <pause dur="short"/> but also they're not really <pause dur="short"/> although they're not old they behave like they're old <pause dur="short"/> like she's only thirty-four but she would never go clubbing <pause dur="short"/> she would never go into a club <pause dur="short"/> never</u>
<u n="191" who="S0084">really? Is that because she's never really liked it or she's just got old?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0041">just got old <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's her type of thing <pause dur="short"/> and I feel like if I invited her she'd probably come for drinks first somewhere and then go which is fine</u>
<u n="193" who="S0084" trans="overlap">naff off <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0041">in fact what I might do is maybe tomorrow at work say we're gonna go out on Saturday</u>
<u n="195" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0041">we're gonna probably have some drinks at the hotel first <unclear/> before we decide where we're gonna go <pause dur="short"/> so if anybody wants to join us</u>
<u n="197" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0041">and then at least no one feels like they have to</u>
<u n="199" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that sounds fine cos if we're gonna be in the hotel anyway <pause dur="short"/> I guess we have to think about timings</u>
<u n="200" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0084">Cos if we were <pause dur="short"/> I suppose the good thing is if we do all the shopping in the week we don't have to worry about shopping on Saturday cos shopping on Saturday is a bitch</u>
<u n="202" who="S0041">yeah and we can start the <unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and we can <pause dur="short"/> exactly we can just chill out during the day <pause dur="short"/> we don't have to panic</u>
<u n="204" who="S0041">yes and do the nails</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084">yeah do the nails <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> pamper</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041"><unclear/> and we can sit and moisturise and <unclear/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">mm all that stuff <pause dur="short"/> all that good stuff and like not have to rush <pause dur="short"/> I mean it depends whether you need to pick up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or or whatever <pause dur="short"/> or pick up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or whether they just come straight here or meet us in town or</u>
<u n="208" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think they can do that on their own</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084">Cos it's your birthday <pause dur="short"/> well yeah I mean you're not their mum <pause dur="short"/> have you <trunc>invi</trunc>?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0041">I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will have a problem at all <pause dur="short"/> it's just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> whereas if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is coming surely <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can give <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a life through</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084" trans="overlap">baby <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> if he's coming from <anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> where does the love of his life live?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0041">I don't know</u>
<u n="213" who="S0084">is she going to come?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0041">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> to be honest I I don't really mind if she does or not because I don't think  I don't think  she'll <pause dur="short"/> I think she'll be nice <pause dur="short"/> if she likes him she must be quite a nice person</u>
<u n="215" who="S0084">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="216" who="S0041">oh no I forgot about this devil lettuce</u>
<u n="217" who="S0084"><event desc="sound of laughing"/> It's risky</u>
<u n="218" who="S0041">I mean it is dying now I must admit it's on it's last legs</u>
<u n="219" who="S0084">it's a risky business <pause dur="short"/> I've got salad in the fridge <pause dur="short"/> not the one with the death lettuce <pause dur="short"/> not the one that will kill you <pause dur="short"/> a new one</u>
<u n="220" who="S0041">the lettuce of death <pause dur="short"/> what time do you think we should go out then?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0084">erm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0041">what time do you think is appropriate time?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0084">be at the hotel for seven do you think? It depends if you want to eat <pause dur="short"/> I mean the thing is if we're here during the day</u>
<u n="224" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yea I was going to say <pause dur="short"/> you're supposed to feed people</u>
<u n="225" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="226" who="S0041">Cos I I'm I'm not really one for like eating and then drinking cos then I'll feel full and I'll feel flat</u>
<u n="227" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it depends what time you go out <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> well that's what I was going to say <pause dur="short"/> if we're here during the day we can eat you know a meal at lunch time or something sizable at lunchtime and then we can just pick in the afternoon</u>
<u n="228" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we could <trunc>ha</trunc> make a little buffet</u>
<u n="229" who="S0084">make a little buffet <pause dur="short"/> finger buffet</u>
<u n="230" who="S0041">yeah with the Italian hams <pause dur="short"/> I love the Italian hams</u>
<u n="231" who="S0084">and prawns with chilli sauce</u>
<u n="232" who="S0041">and prawns with chilli sauce</u>
<u n="233" who="S0084">Cos I have prawns and we can  we can  get the chilli sauce cos we have chilli</u>
<u n="234" who="S0041">we can make a good chilli sauce or buy the chilli sauce <pause dur="short"/> we have that <pause dur="short"/> yeah that would be nice <pause dur="short"/> and I suppose we could always say to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know we're going to be in all afternoon getting ready <pause dur="short"/> we're going to move for the hotel for about seven</u>
<u n="235" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0041">or leave here at seven say <pause dur="short"/> so there for half past</u>
<u n="237" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> come around if you want to or meet us there</u>
<u n="238" who="S0041" trans="overlap">come around if you want to or meet us there</u>
<u n="239" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0084">Cos that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got to get the bus if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't coming here she might to decide to just meet us in town rather than get the bus to town and get another bus from town to here</u>
<u n="242" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I think I might say to her as well cos obviously we're going to need to get some bubbly in</u>
<u n="243" who="S0084">yes</u>
<u n="244" who="S0041">obviously erm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0084">that will need to happen</u>
<u n="246" who="S0041">it's that I I want to be able to enjoy having a drink <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't I can't get too drunk before I put my face on but if I did my make-up earlier on so my make-up was kind of done for five <pause dur="short"/> then</u>
<u n="247" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos then we'll just be pottering around and topping up and whatever <pause dur="short"/> just make sure we don't look like David Dickinson before we go out</u>
<u n="248" who="S0041" trans="overlap">nail painting <pause dur="short"/> nail painting <pause dur="short"/> I can do that at the last minute <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking <unclear/> taking my nail polish off and I quite like it with just the tip done</u>
<u n="249" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> really nice</u>
<u n="250" who="S0041">I mean I don't know how you do that because I just was picking my nail polish off and that happened by accident</u>
<u n="251" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="252" who="S0041">but erm you know</u>
<u n="253" who="S0084">we could  we could we could  attempt <pause dur="short"/> we could make some little erm er markers</u>
<u n="254" who="S0041">guides</u>
<u n="255" who="S0084">some guides</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="256" who="S0041">erm yeah so what I could do is erm make a list of all the things I need</u>
<u n="257" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0041">and then on Friday when I get paid go and pick the stuff up in my lunch break and or after work because I finish at five</u>
<u n="259" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah that's true</u>
<u n="260" who="S0041">and then <pause dur="short"/> cos I can always <pause dur="short"/> if I go into <pause dur="short"/> if we're going into town on Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> if I decide on those shoes or whichever shoes I decide on really <pause dur="short"/> I can always say would you put these on hold for me and I'll come and collect them on Friday</u>
<u n="261" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0041">they're not going to mind are they</u>
<u n="263" who="S0084">well the shops <pause dur="short"/> you'll have to be careful because the shops might close at five if that's when you finish</u>
<u n="264" who="S0041">on Friday?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0084">yeah I don't know what time the shops in town close <pause dur="short"/> some close at five <pause dur="short"/> some close at six</u>
<u n="266" who="S0041">could go in my lunch</u>
<u n="267" who="S0084">you could go in your lunch <pause dur="short"/> cos if you're just collecting then that's not an issue is it <pause dur="short"/> you're not choosing</u>
<u n="268" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll choose the ones I want and then</u>
<u n="269" who="S0084">yeah then you'll have to cart them around on <trunc>F</trunc> Wednesday</u>
<u n="270" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0084">yes yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0041">Cos if I choose choose other things <pause dur="short"/> underwear and my shoes</u>
<u n="273" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0041">I do have a little gold handbag <pause dur="short"/> but it's fallen to pieces but it's my favourite <pause dur="short"/> which would go with that <pause dur="short"/> I might have to replace that</u>
<u n="275" who="S0084">yeah mine died <pause dur="short"/> I had a really nice one</u>
<u n="276" who="S0041">do you think I can wear the <trunc>go</trunc> the orange dress for the wedding or do you think that's a bit inappropriate for the wedding? If I get a white blazer with it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0084" trans="overlap">for the wedding <pause dur="short"/> yeah that would look really nice <pause dur="short"/> cos you could <pause dur="short"/> oh no you can't wear tights can you <pause dur="short"/> you can wear stockings though <pause dur="short"/> hold ups or the ones that stick to your leg</u>
<u n="278" who="S0041">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0084">I mean the only thing is once they go you look like Nora Batty</u>
<u n="280" who="S0041">yes that is an issue <pause dur="short"/> because by the time it's reception time</u>
<u n="281" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Cos then <unclear/> They can come off</u>
<u n="282" who="S0041">they can come off</u>
<u n="283" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0041">if I get a quite like a a white off white blazer</u>
<u n="285" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0041">and wear <pause dur="short"/> I've got some little gold heels that are sandals but they're only this high so they're more acceptable wedding wear during the day</u>
<u n="287" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah that's the thing</u>
<u n="288" who="S0041" trans="overlap">so if I get a gold bag at least that will go with the gold sandals for the wedding</u>
<u n="289" who="S0084">yeah for wedding</u>
<u n="290" who="S0041">and the gold one to <unclear/> your heels</u>
<u n="291" who="S0084">lovely</u>
<u n="292" who="S0041">that could be a winner <pause dur="short"/> that could be a winner <pause dur="short"/> erm I'm afraid I'm going to need to see your pink dress again</u>
<u n="293" who="S0084">oh my dress</u>
<u n="294" who="S0041" trans="overlap">and the new dress</u>
<u n="295" who="S0084">and the new dress</u>
<u n="296" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> well that's definitely an option <pause dur="short"/> erm I <trunc>re</trunc> yeah cos I like that pink dress and I have only worn it once</u>
<u n="298" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I love your pink dress</u>
<u n="299" who="S0084">and it did look nice with the tan</u>
<u n="300" who="S0041">the tanage</u>
<u n="301" who="S0084">and obviously that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>la</trunc> that was the last time I went out <pause dur="short"/> out out <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> but you know <pause dur="short"/> got really dressed up and that's what I wore so it feels like that's all I own <pause dur="short"/> and it was with the same people <pause dur="short"/> it was with you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it doesn't really matter <pause dur="short"/> and it's a nice bright colour <pause dur="short"/> you could say it was of a spring colour so</u>
<u n="302" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I was saying to Eve about not being able to find a suitable dress and she said erm well what's Liz wearing?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0041">and I said she'll probably wear the pink one but it's it's a spring it's a really nice formal dress that could be either a winter one or a summer one</u>
<u n="305" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0041">I mean you could wear that dress in July</u>
<u n="307" who="S0084">yeah I suppose that's it is quite versatile <pause dur="short"/> like because again you could probably wear it with different coloured accessories <pause dur="short"/> like obviously when I wore it in the winter I wore it with the black</u>
<u n="308" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0084">but maybe I need to get some silver things or gold things</u>
<u n="310" who="S0041">some silver or some gold yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0084">erm I think I'm seeing one of the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>' on Friday</u>
<u n="312" who="S0041">right that's exciting</u>
<u n="313" who="S0084">he has three motorbikes <pause dur="short"/> he works in <pause dur="short"/> this is the one who works in the international sale</u>
<u n="314" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="315" who="S0084">the thing is I fear that their personalities might get confused like I might <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to get it really clear in my mind that the artist isn't <trunc>g</trunc> get confused with the motorbike guy</u>
<u n="316" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="317" who="S0084">Cos I might say stuff to him that is for the other guy <pause dur="short"/> but that's fine</u>
<u n="318" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="319" who="S0084">but that's just the risk you take <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="320" who="S0041" trans="overlap">which I can understand seeming as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are different names and I I still have the terror that that's going to happen</u>
<u n="321" who="S0084">yeah yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I did put a photo for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> motorbike guy cos I I haven't erm got photos for the other one yet cos we only just started chatting <pause dur="short"/> okay so this is</u>
<u n="322" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> see <pause dur="short"/> I think photographs help</u>
<u n="323" who="S0084">my concern is he is wearing his jumper around his shoulders which is a bit of a  thing to do</u>
<u n="324" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> he looks nice</u>
<u n="325" who="S0084">he looks quite nice <pause dur="short"/> he's six foot two and he he's got three motorbikes and this is</u>
<u n="326" who="S0041">I like six foot two <pause dur="short"/> that is like my perfect body</u>
<u n="327" who="S0084">Cos it's not too  it's not too  like with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's really actually quite intimidating like the relations with him <pause dur="short"/> you'd feel a bit your there's your perfect Adonis body and here's my wobbly body</u>
<u n="328" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I really need to see it again <pause dur="short"/> that was a hot bod</u>
<u n="329" who="S0084">it's nice isn't it</u>
<u n="330" who="S0041">I want to bite it <pause dur="short"/> I want to bite it</u>
<u n="331" who="S0084">yeah cos he's got like proper proper pecks and stuff so</u>
<u n="332" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0084">it's quite good <pause dur="short"/> it looks like quite a nice body <pause dur="short"/> erm he lives with his mum and dad because he works <pause dur="short"/> his office is in <anon type="place"/> so he works from home but he <trunc>ha</trunc> he owns a house which he rents out cos there's no point because he's away a lot of the time cos he travels a lot which is perfect really <pause dur="short"/> he's never gonna be here so that's good</u>
<u n="334" who="S0041"><event desc="sound of laughing"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0084">erm but he doesn't live <pause dur="short"/> his parents live in some village near St <pause dur="short"/> ives <pause dur="short"/> actually it might even be <anon type="place"/> erm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0041"><trunc>Tho</trunc> those places</u>
<u n="337" who="S0084">those places that are called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="339" who="S0084">so I think if he comes to <anon type="place"/> on Friday I said he can't stay here for obvious reasons just mainly because you know I might not like him</u>
<u n="340" who="S0041">mhm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0084">erm so he's gonna get a hotel</u>
<u n="342" who="S0041">fine</u>
<u n="343" who="S0084">so he should do that <pause dur="short"/> he's gonna book it at some point <pause dur="short"/> erm and we might go <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s because I've never been to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s yet</u>
<u n="344" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0084">and he says he's been a few times <pause dur="short"/> he said it's alright <pause dur="short"/> we'll go there <pause dur="short"/> and then I don't know <pause dur="short"/> we might go out for a couple of drinks after maybe <pause dur="short"/> it depends what he's like but you can't really tell can you <pause dur="short"/> you can never really tell</u>
<u n="346" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="347" who="S0084">he's he's pretty keen <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> don't know do you</u>
<u n="348" who="S0041">it's so hard to read somebody isn't it <pause dur="short"/> like if you meet them you'll know within ten minutes but you've got that ten minutes</u>
<u n="349" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0041">you've got to wait for <pause dur="short"/> that's the annoyance</u>
<u n="351" who="S0084">yeah and it could go either way <pause dur="short"/> mm that's some interesting hair <pause dur="short"/> crazy hair <pause dur="short"/> how's the fish wrap?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0041">er awesome</u>
<u n="353" who="S0084">Good <pause dur="short"/> nice and salty</u>
<u n="354" who="S0041">I do like the loads of salt yes <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> fish finger</u>
<u n="356" who="S0041">the thing is I'm a bit dubious about signing up for dinner</u>
<u n="357" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a lot of commitment isn't it if you don't like  if you don't like  each other which is why we'll meet for a drink first because every <trunc>ev</trunc> everyone could then make it an excuse you know my legs just fallen off <pause dur="short"/> I'm really sorry</u>
<u n="358" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> there could be an emergency <pause dur="short"/> the unions on fire</u>
<u n="359" who="S0084">the unions on fire <pause dur="short"/> erm my housemates leg is falling off so I have to take her to hospital</u>
<u n="360" who="S0041">mhm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0084">etcetera etcetera</u>
<u n="362" who="S0041">I mean I think all first dates should have a ten minute cap</u>
<u n="363" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0041">like enough for you to finish one drink and then you get to say yes or no <pause dur="short"/> and if one says yes and one says no then you call it a day</u>
<u n="365" who="S0084">no hard feelings</u>
<u n="366" who="S0041">mhm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0084">but it's always going to be hard feelings <pause dur="short"/> like there's always going to be a oh that smarts</u>
<u n="368" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0084">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> I mean <unclear/> and I used to say we'd like to invent something where you could just like if you walking down the street you could have like a clicker or a buzzer and if someone you fancy walked past you would just buzz and then they would get the buzz and then they would look over and if they like you they would buzz back and then then winner</u>
<u n="370" who="S0041">and then if not no</u>
<u n="371" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah if not yeah carry on <pause dur="short"/> carry on your merry way <pause dur="short"/> no harm done</u>
<u n="372" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0084">I mean it's all  it's all  based on appearances obviously but then most of this thing is <pause dur="short"/> you know internet dating is isn't it <pause dur="short"/> you you only message <pause dur="short"/> I never message anybody</u>
<u n="374" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mhm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="375" who="S0084">and you probably you would presume that they only message you based on what you look like <pause dur="short"/> not really what you say about yourself</u>
<u n="376" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I noticed yesterday on Plenty of Fish <pause dur="short"/> I thought something had gone wrong <pause dur="short"/> so I went on there and loads of girls pictures came up instead of boys and I was like</u>
<u n="377" who="S0084">oh hilarious</u>
<u n="378" who="S0041">erm and all all the girls all that came up had all got like fake hair <pause dur="short"/> like really fake big hair <pause dur="short"/> their boobs out <pause dur="short"/> the face really close with big colour lipstick on like</u>
<u n="379" who="S0084">is that what they all look like?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0041">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0084">Cos I suppose that's the thing cos you don't know what the other girls look like because you wouldn't ever be erm staring at them would you</u>
<u n="382" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> they're not normal photographs like ours</u>
<u n="383" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="384" who="S0041">yeah like you know my witch photograph?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0084" trans="overlap">they're just <unclear/> Yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0041">worse than that <pause dur="short"/> flirtiness and they're all like it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0084">oh my God <pause dur="short"/> just really fake</u>
<u n="388" who="S0041">really fake <pause dur="short"/> really like could have been a photographer that took it</u>
<u n="389" who="S0084">oh my God</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> fake eyelashes <pause dur="short"/> oranged up</u>
<u n="391" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">boobs out <pause dur="short"/> hair done</u>
<u n="393" who="S0084">oh God</u>
<u n="394" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0084">delete</u>
<u n="396" who="S0041">yeah delete</u>
<u n="397" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> horrible <pause dur="short"/> I think that's it <pause dur="short"/> I think because some of the messages that I've had from fellas the who they message you and they say oh you you know you seem like a really genuine person and you think well you don't know me <pause dur="short"/> but if if just from that a few of those few conversations that you seem quite a genuine person you do wonder what the other girls on there are like</u>
<u n="398" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0084">or what you know that other fellas do you know most of the fellas are to be honest</u>
<u n="400" who="S0041" trans="overlap">there's lots of filthy girl as well</u>
<u n="401" who="S0084">well there probably are <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0041" trans="overlap">filth pots</u>
<u n="403" who="S0084">well I think cos a lot of people are using things for cheating <pause dur="short"/> don't they</u>
<u n="404" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0084">so erm yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0041">I never thought of that</u>
<u n="407" who="S0084">I had one guy who was really weird <pause dur="short"/> he had a did I tell you he had a fake photo and then he went mental when I  when I  said it was a bit strange <pause dur="short"/> he was he went bananas <pause dur="short"/> it like the guy in the photo <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't a like anyone famous it was just a and it didn't overly look like a model <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't look at it and go oh well that's a fake <pause dur="short"/> he did look like a nice guy and you couldn't really get that much of a look at him because he was behind a camera <pause dur="short"/> he was taking a photo <pause dur="short"/> just looked like a nice guy <pause dur="short"/> and then we're chatting away and he's like oh by the way that's not me in the photo <pause dur="short"/> and I thought oh oh well okay fine <pause dur="short"/> he's just like oh you know I respect I want my privacy to be respected <pause dur="short"/> I was like okay well you're on a dating site but fine okay <pause dur="short"/> just don't put a photo just put erm ask me for a photo message or whatever <pause dur="short"/> he was like oh well whatever <pause dur="short"/> and then it turned out that that's like a forty-five fifty year old guy <pause dur="short"/> really unattractive <pause dur="short"/> really unattractive <pause dur="short"/> and I was and I just thought well you've really sort of duped people here</u>
<u n="408" who="S0041">what the fuck? Yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0084">yeah it was really unfair <pause dur="short"/> it's really rude for you to do that cos</u>
<u n="410" who="S0041">waste somebody else's time</u>
<u n="411" who="S0084">yeah and he was like oh well you know that's all girls say that and you know I'm not just here for sex <pause dur="short"/> and I was like well neither am I but it's going to happen <pause dur="short"/> your appearance is going to have an impact on my decision whether I would meet you or not</u>
<u n="412" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0084">you know I'm here to meet a fella for a good time and maybe more <pause dur="short"/> I'm not necessarily here to make friends with people <pause dur="short"/> because I've got friends <pause dur="short"/> you now I wouldn't come on a dating site just to meet meet friends</u>
<u n="414" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0084">so he really took <pause dur="short"/> he really found it surprising that I was annoyed and I was just <pause dur="short"/> he was right I'm going to block you now because you're really weird <pause dur="short"/> he said that to me <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like okay</u>
<u n="416" who="S0041">fucking weirdos</u>
<u n="417" who="S0084">so I reported him as abuse</u>
<u n="418" who="S0041">I would totally done that</u>
<u n="419" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0041">I was talking to a guy once who called me and I was on the phone to him for about an hour or something</u>
<u n="421" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0041">erm just chatting away <pause dur="short"/> he seemed pretty normal erm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0041">easy enough to get on with <pause dur="short"/> bit too flirty like naughty flirty <pause dur="short"/> I was a bit like mm this is a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> don't really know you at all</u>
<u n="425" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0041">but fine</u>
<u n="427" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0041">it wasn't too much <pause dur="short"/> and then he was like oh do you want to go for a drink? I was erm well you know <unclear/> day off and all that</u>
<u n="429" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0041">erm but yeah fair enough <pause dur="short"/> when? You know when are you thinking?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0041">anyway <pause dur="short"/> he says oh there's something I've got to tell you first <pause dur="short"/> I was like what? He was like oh that photograph's not me</u>
<u n="433" who="S0084">erm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0041">and he'd had me on the phone for an hour <pause dur="short"/> I was like what the fuck? Are you taking the piss?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0084">Jesus</u>
<u n="436" who="S0041">and he was like no <pause dur="short"/> erm but the job that I work in erm which he couldn't tell me about <pause dur="short"/> I'd not asked but until this point came up <pause dur="short"/> you know I deal with the public cos I work in like a shop erm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0041">so I work in like retail and people see me all the time and so I don't want my colleagues know I'm on here or people that come into the store to ask my advice to know that it's me on here <pause dur="short"/> and I was like okay fine so do that same thing so ask for a picture</u>
<u n="439" who="S0084">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0041">Don't put a fake one on there and leave me talking to the fake person for an hour <pause dur="short"/> and he said yeah but you wanted to meet me for my personality <pause dur="short"/> you know I've not lied <pause dur="short"/> anything I've said to you has not been a lie <pause dur="short"/> I said no but the whole  the whole  conversation was built on fake foundation because that's the choice you make when you've decided to talk to someone</u>
<u n="441" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="442" who="S0041">at least I don't  I don't  think particularly think I'm superficial I just think because it's  because it's  internet dating you do base your decision on luck because you don't know them</u>
<u n="443" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah cos you haven't got an awful lot to go on else else have you so</u>
<u n="444" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0084">yeah I just think it's really mean <pause dur="short"/> it's really mean to just use someone else's photo that you've just found on Google Images or something you know</u>
<u n="446" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he thought it was me being ridiculous and I was like no piss off</u>
<u n="447" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0046">hi ladies</u>
<u n="449" who="S0084">hiya</u>
<u n="450" who="S0041" trans="overlap">hiya</u>
<u n="451" who="S0046">how are we doing?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0041">Good</u>
<u n="453" who="S0084">Great <pause dur="short"/> you?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0046">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0084">how's your tooth?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0046">it's alright <pause dur="short"/> it's me neck that hurts again</u>
<u n="457" who="S0041">how's work?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0046">boring</u>
<u n="459" who="S0084">why?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0046">it's just <pause dur="short"/> they were just taking me around stuff that you need to do and things like that</u>
<u n="461" who="S0084">it takes a while to get bedded in doesn't it</u>
<u n="462" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so especially in a big factory like that as well</u>
<u n="463" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0046">you know there's two hundred and eighty employees there</u>
<u n="465" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0041">I just think you don't  you don't  really know what the jobs like till like the three month point</u>
<u n="467" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's alright <pause dur="short"/> I I don't hate <pause dur="short"/> don't get me wrong I don't hate it <pause dur="short"/> you know and I like  I like  the fact that I can see people that I know as well <pause dur="short"/> you know that's that's the whole point in like group inductions and things like that</u>
<u n="469" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="470" who="S0046"><unclear/> people so that that's definitely good <pause dur="short"/> but if I was just employed on my own you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm it's quite daunting isn't it</u>
<u n="472" who="S0084">when it's a big staff like that</u>
<u n="473" who="S0046">yeah just thrown in the deep end but you know that that's alright <pause dur="short"/> they seem a good bunch of lads anyway <pause dur="short"/> there's one security guard there that's twenty-one and he just doesn't give a damn</u>
<u n="474" who="S0084">that's a bit young isn't it?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0046">he he well he's a student at AIU and he he's just there for the money <pause dur="short"/> he just really doesn't care</u>
<u n="477" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0046">so he just <pause dur="short"/> you know he seems like a good lad</u>
<u n="479" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="480" who="S0046">you know out of work but as far as work goes he doesn't do a lot <pause dur="short"/> as far as I can see</u>
<u n="481" who="S0084">well they'll probably weed him out quite quickly like security surely that's not going to be okay</u>
<u n="482" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0046">he he's he's just he he does what he needs to do basically <pause dur="short"/> he just doesn't go looking for it like I do</u>
<u n="484" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0046">you know but</u>
<u n="486" who="S0041">fine</u>
<u n="487" who="S0046">you know each to their own <pause dur="short"/> you know he's just there to earn a bit of pennies that's all</u>
<u n="488" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0046">what do you think of your doors then <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0041">very nice</u>
<u n="491" who="S0046">I like them <pause dur="short"/> I like them indeed</u>
<u n="492" who="S0041">they're very nice</u>
<u n="493" who="S0046">and they open</u>
<u n="494" who="S0041">yeah which is a winner</u>
<u n="495" who="S0046">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's all good</u>
<u n="496" who="S0041">can you see my dress from there?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0046">the one hanging up?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0041">it's my birthday dress</u>
<u n="501" who="S0046">is it?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0041">yeah we just bought it</u>
<u n="503" who="S0046">ah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0041">flirty number <pause dur="short"/> bright orange</u>
<u n="505" who="S0046">where did you get that from?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0041">er Dorothy Perkins</u>
<u n="507" who="S0046">ah good old DP</u>
<u n="508" who="S0041">yeah well I had a look in town and I couldn't find anything I liked and then I went in a Dorothy Perkins store with a boutique stuff so</u>
<u n="509" who="S0046">so did you get it from the leisure park I mean <trunc>re</trunc> retail park?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cool <pause dur="short"/> cool cool cool <pause dur="short"/> I've watched all three Underworlds today</u>
<u n="512" who="S0041">Good?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose</u>
<u n="514" who="S0041">I'm not convinced</u>
<u n="515" who="S0046">the story line is wicked <pause dur="short"/> the story line <pause dur="short"/> it it was only until I got to the third one that I thought you know even without Kate Beckinsale in the third one I was like yeah yeah this is  this is  a good story line you know they they've really covered their tracks quite well</u>
<u n="516" who="S0084">she's not in the third one?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0046">no</u>
<u n="518" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="519" who="S0046">Cos I don't</u>
<u n="520" who="S0084">is she in the forth one?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think the third one was released in cinemas you see</u>
<u n="522" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="523" who="S0046">which is probably why she wasn't in it <pause dur="short"/> but all the original cast were in the third one apart from Kate Beckinsale</u>
<u n="524" who="S0084">is that the one with the vampires <pause dur="short"/> and and the werewolves and the Vikings</u>
<u n="525" who="S0046">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0084">yeah I have seen them <pause dur="short"/> I have one or two of them <pause dur="short"/> I quite like it actually</u>
<u n="527" who="S0046">yeah it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0084">did I remember they dig up the old vampire and he's in the ground in the big house and he comes out the ground and he's like eight hundred years old and they've got to ask him a question?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0046" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> they don't really dig him up <pause dur="short"/> basically it takes another vampire's blood to raise him</u>
<u n="530" who="S0084">oh yeah that's it</u>
<u n="531" who="S0046">and it</u>
<u n="532" who="S0084">but they're not supposed to <pause dur="short"/> they raise him early or something yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0046">yeah they raise him like a century early just so Kate can release this news that she's <unclear/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no no no no no</u>
<u n="535" who="S0046">oh have you not seen it?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="537" who="S0046">oh okay</u>
<u n="538" who="S0084">yeah I quite liked it actually</u>
<u n="539" who="S0046">yeah I'm going to watch the forth one now <pause dur="short"/> the new one</u>
<u n="540" who="S0041">I'm really full now</u>
<u n="541" who="S0046">what did you have for dinner?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0084">accidentally ate all the food</u>
<u n="543" who="S0041">accidentally ate all the food</u>
<u n="544" who="S0046">oh dear</u>
<u n="545" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I had a slice of eggy bread and then I also had a fish finger wrap</u>
<u n="546" who="S0046">oh dear</u>
<u n="547" who="S0041">so it's not a lot of food <pause dur="short"/> let's be honest</u>
<u n="548" who="S0046">well I had one of those microwave meals today <pause dur="short"/> dead impressive</u>
<u n="549" who="S0041">Good</u>
<u n="550" who="S0046">dead impressive</u>
<u n="551" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="552" who="S0046">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I chopped it up like a little baby though <pause dur="short"/> which is <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> me chopping it up</u>
<u n="553" who="S0041">baby mush</u>
<u n="554" who="S0046">but it it went down alright</u>
<u n="555" who="S0041">Good</u>
<u n="556" who="S0046">and I didn't realise it was spicy so I took a big mouthful of it and because I just I literally just run it round my mouth and swallow <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't do that</u>
<u n="557" who="S0041">spice your face off</u>
<u n="558" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0046">I coughed my guts up <pause dur="short"/> yeah it wasn't pretty but it was nice nonetheless</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">Good <pause dur="short"/> I need to put my phone on charge <pause dur="short"/> oh yes that guy that was texting me on Saturday</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah the one that was <trunc>d</trunc> none stop wasn't it</u>
<u n="562" who="S0041">yeah yeah he's like really on the ball all the time like give us a break <pause dur="short"/> give us a breather</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041">which leads me to believe that perhaps he's not quite the type of</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084">it sounds like he's not got a lot going on in his life if he can text you all the time</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041">yeah yeah well he's had <pause dur="short"/> he had the weekend the off and he had today off so maybe tomorrow will be different although he didn't text me today until about half six</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041">so <pause dur="short"/> that's fine</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="570" who="S0041">erm he's going to Orlando next month with his friends which you can only afford to do if you live with your mum and dad</u>
<u n="571" who="S0046">mhm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0084">oh is he a baby?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> twenty-six <pause dur="short"/> twenty-four <pause dur="short"/> twenty-six</u>
<u n="574" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> and what does he do?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0041">er what do you call it? Like a grounds man at like a golf place <pause dur="short"/> I don't really know what that entails but I I think just grass cutter</u>
<u n="576" who="S0084">grass cutter</u>
<u n="577" who="S0046">there's a  there's a  lots of grounds men at the golf course and their them just cutting grass</u>
<u n="578" who="S0041">alright <pause dur="short"/> well in my head he cuts grass and you know does sand</u>
<u n="579" who="S0046" trans="overlap">but yeah he basically cuts grass and maybe <unclear/> weed as well I would have thought</u>
<u n="580" who="S0084" trans="overlap">trims the trees</u>
<u n="581" who="S0041">he does something <pause dur="short"/> he does he cuts the grass and trims the trees yeah <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="582" who="S0084">and makes the holes nice</u>
<u n="583" who="S0041">makes the holes nice and fills the sandpit up</u>
<u n="584" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0041">I'm sure that's about what happens</u>
<u n="586" who="S0084">mhm <pause dur="short"/> feeds the ducks on the pond</u>
<u n="587" who="S0041">feeds the ducks</u>
<u n="588" who="S0046">building a sandcastle</u>
<u n="589" who="S0084">he's got a pretty sweet job</u>
<u n="590" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0084">build sandcastles yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0041">build sandcastles <pause dur="short"/> so it's pretty cushy in the summer <pause dur="short"/> not so good in the winter</u>
<u n="593" who="S0084" trans="overlap">drive the buggy around</u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">golf buggy <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="595" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">erm he seems quite nice but then I I I asked the question of you know what's the longest relationship you've been in?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">eight years</u>
<u n="599" who="S0046">wow</u>
<u n="600" who="S0084">and he's twenty-four</u>
<u n="601" who="S0041">twenty-six I think</u>
<u n="602" who="S0084">jeebus</u>
<u n="603" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> which leaves eighteen to twenty-six doesn't it</u>
<u n="604" who="S0084">yeah basically he's just <trunc>bl</trunc> split up with the girlfriend</u>
<u n="605" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> which may also explain the trigger happy texting</u>
<u n="606" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0041">so I was a bit like mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0084">suspicious</u>
<u n="609" who="S0041">yeah I think a little bit cling <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="610" who="S0084">Jesus Christ</u>
<u n="611" who="S0041">so he was like oh do you wanna go out for a drink? Fine <pause dur="short"/> erm do you want to see me before or after my holiday? And I'm thinking before because I'm not waiting all that time in case you're a weirdo cos the majority of chances you're a weirdo</u>
<u n="612" who="S0084">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0041">erm fine er are you free this week? He says oh I'm off work tomorrow if that's any good as in today <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh fine I don't finish work till six <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm busy in the evening <pause dur="short"/> I was like so when were you thinking I was going to be able to see you?</u>
<u n="614" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0041">and he was like oh yeah I didn't think that through properly <pause dur="short"/> no probably not <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0084">oh dear</u>
<u n="617" who="S0041">fine <pause dur="short"/> then</u>
<u n="618" who="S0084">brainiac</u>
<u n="619" who="S0041">I was like well I'm not free Wednesday or Thursday cos that's the date with the other guy</u>
<u n="620" who="S0084">yep good</u>
<u n="621" who="S0041">erm who by the way looks like a child <pause dur="short"/> have I showed you the picture?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0084">ah no where's the current picture</u>
<u n="623" who="S0041">yeah I've got it on Laurie <pause dur="short"/> I'll show you <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah so and I'm not free on Saturday cos well that's celebratory day <pause dur="short"/> and he was like erm well what time are you working Saturday <pause dur="short"/> obviously I didn't tell him it was celebratory day <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh I'm not working it's birthday party day so you know I'll I'll be going out from kind of ten in the morning</u>
<u n="624" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="625" who="S0041">and he was like oh erm okay well you know we'll we'll work something out <pause dur="short"/> I was like yeah fine don't worry <pause dur="short"/> I've got to go <pause dur="short"/> I've got to sleep bye <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="626" who="S0084" trans="overlap">bye bye bye</u>
<u n="627" who="S0041">the he trumps up ah actually as it happens after to going to football on Sunday night <pause dur="short"/> erm might be going to <anon type="place"/> for drinks on Saturday <pause dur="short"/> oh you know <pause dur="short"/> that's convenient</u>
<u n="628" who="S0084">so you said that you're going out Saturday night and now he's like yeah and by the way I'm out on the tiles</u>
<u n="629" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I was like oh right and how's that? And he said oh well we're playing a football match in <anon type="place"/> on Saturday so the lads are just gonna take the stuff get changed shove the kit in the van and come out</u>
<u n="630" who="S0084">er where are they gonna get washed?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0046">changing rooms</u>
<u n="632" who="S0041">well <pause dur="short"/> at the changing rooms</u>
<u n="633" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say <pause dur="short"/> back of the van</u>
<u n="634" who="S0041">so they're all gonna get out <pause dur="short"/> get <pause dur="short"/> finish football <pause dur="short"/> shower up and go out</u>
<u n="635" who="S0084">so they're gonna start drinking at like two in the afternoon?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0041">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I didn't really ask And I was like oh right where do you usually go? And he said to be honest I've not been out in <anon type="place"/> for about four four or five years erm I usually go to</u>
<u n="637" who="S0046" trans="overlap">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> definitely convenient that you're going out as well</u>
<u n="638" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0041">to erm <anon type="place"/> or whatever else he's from I don't know <pause dur="short"/> somewhere <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> don't' know I can't remember</u>
<u n="641" who="S0084">he's from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0041">can't remember</u>
<u n="643" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> suspicious</u>
<u n="644" who="S0041">he's from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="645" who="S0084">not another one from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0041"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> he's the same one</u>
<u n="647" who="S0084">he's the one from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0041">he's the one from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0084">erm</u>
<u n="650" who="S0046">and were we right on where it was?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0041">mm mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0084">it's actually I saw it on the map today <pause dur="short"/> it's on the way to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="654" who="S0084">I saw it on the map when I was getting the <anon type="place"/> route</u>
<u n="655" who="S0041">yes I know exactly what you're getting to with <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="656" who="S0084">my <unclear/> was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0046">it's right under <anon type="place"/> isn't it</u>
<u n="658" who="S0041" trans="overlap">what else?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0084">er <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's next to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> which I don't know where that is but I found it on the map</u>
<u n="660" who="S0046" trans="overlap">no <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> I think there's a <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="661" who="S0041">I know where <anon type="place"/> is</u>
<u n="662" who="S0046">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0084">it's the <anon type="place"/> if that helps</u>
<u n="664" who="S0041">yeah of course no</u>
<u n="665" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0046">m11</u>
<u n="667" who="S0084">oh the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0046">I thought you should <pause dur="short"/> I thought <anon type="place"/> was the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0084" trans="overlap">the M11  the M11  comes down like this</u>
<u n="671" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0084">and Biggleswade is over there <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0084">Cos <anon type="place"/>'s here and <anon type="place"/>'s here and we're there</u>
<u n="675" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I don't know any of those <pause dur="short"/> I don't know any of those places</u>
<u n="676" who="S0084">blah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0041">yeah <unclear/> So I was like oh right <pause dur="short"/> he said where do you usually go? I said well we'll probably start at the hotel where I work and then God knows where</u>
<u n="678" who="S0084">gutter</u>
<u n="679" who="S0041"><trunc>Gu</trunc> gutter and he said oh maybe I'll run into you lol</u>
<u n="680" who="S0084">yeah where are you going to be?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0041">and then I thought <pause dur="short"/> and then I didn't <pause dur="short"/> and then I thought well at this rate I won't have a dress to wear so I don't' think they'll let you in naked <pause dur="short"/> it might be an early night for me <pause dur="short"/> and he said oh no I'm sure you'll find <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm sure you'll find something to wear <pause dur="short"/> girls always say that <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I just  I just  avoided that whole cos can you imagine the first time to meet someone when you're pissed off your face</u>
<u n="682" who="S0084" trans="overlap">horrendous <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0041">there's a big group of people <pause dur="short"/> well that could be the easy actually <pause dur="short"/> by the time you're fucked</u>
<u n="684" who="S0084">but the thing is you will be really fucked</u>
<u n="685" who="S0041">oh yes</u>
<u n="686" who="S0084">so well I mean not just you <pause dur="short"/> I mean both of you will be <pause dur="short"/> even if the <unclear/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> trolleyed yeah yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0084">so even if you were not <pause dur="short"/> I mean you it would be better if you were <pause dur="short"/> but if you're not and he is it's game over</u>
<u n="689" who="S0041">that would be even worse</u>
<u n="690" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Cos he could be dribbling into his shoes</u>
<u n="691" who="S0041">so there could be a lot of dribbling but also an easy way to meet and dump <pause dur="short"/> if you don't like them <pause dur="short"/> easy place to get lost in town <pause dur="short"/> we just vacate</u>
<u n="692" who="S0084">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="693" who="S0041">so that's that <pause dur="short"/> and then the guy that's back from Afghanistan</u>
<u n="694" who="S0084" trans="overlap">the Afghan guy <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="695" who="S0041">is taking me out</u>
<u n="696" who="S0084" trans="overlap">he's not actually Afghan though is he?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0084">he's not actually Afghan though is he?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> he's</u>
<u n="700" who="S0084"><unclear/> keep the photo of him as the Afghan guy</u>
<u n="701" who="S0041">as Afghan <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> no he's not but yes that's fine <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="702" who="S0084">he's taking you out Thursday?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="704" who="S0084">have you decided where yet?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> easy drink <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> or something like that so that I can escape easily</u>
<u n="706" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0041">my only concern is that he's driving from <anon type="place"/> so if I want to vacate I feel a bit bad</u>
<u n="708" who="S0084">it's not that far <pause dur="short"/> no it's only half an hour</u>
<u n="709" who="S0046">mm</u>
<u n="710" who="S0084">it not far</u>
<u n="711" who="S0046">it's not far at all</u>
<u n="712" who="S0041">so yeah but he sent me a picture cos he went to a stag do in  on Saturday</u>
<u n="713" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0041">he sent me a picture from it <pause dur="short"/> cos he asked for a recent photograph and I said I don't have one cos I've had a look through all my Facebook photographs and I can't find one that looks like me cos I keep changing the hair and the fatness</u>
<u n="715" who="S0084">that's true</u>
<u n="716" who="S0041">so</u>
<u n="717" who="S0084">fatness</u>
<u n="718" who="S0041">the ones I do have that I look similar are actually three years old so my face looks younger so it just doesn't look like me</u>
<u n="719" who="S0084">I've got the I have I haven't put the ones up from New Years Eve <pause dur="short"/> you look really nice in those</u>
<u n="720" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> that could be one</u>
<u n="721" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't  I haven't  you haven't got them <pause dur="short"/> I've got them</u>
<u n="722" who="S0041" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I was like I don't have one apart from the one that was taken at the weekend which I was just like just part of my face and my hairs up so I look awful but there we go</u>
<u n="723" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="724" who="S0041">and he sent one from stag do in a suit <pause dur="short"/> and there's three of them stood together and honestly he just looks so young <pause dur="short"/> so so young like wet behind the ears young</u>
<u n="725" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0041">but it's gone too far now <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna have to meet him for a drink even though he's a child</u>
<u n="727" who="S0084">he can't walk</u>
<u n="728" who="S0041">he is actually a child <pause dur="short"/> he looks tiny</u>
<u n="729" who="S0084">how old is he actually?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0041">twenty-three</u>
<u n="731" who="S0084">he's oh he right yeah he is younger than <pause dur="short"/> oh well I know you're twenty-two aren't you but er</u>
<u n="732" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah so he's still a year older than me yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0084">fine <pause dur="short"/> is it not too late to abort? I mean if you feel that this is going to be an awkward situation <pause dur="short"/> you are just going to have to do a runner after ten minutes erm and invent some sort of excuse whereby your leg might have fallen off</u>
<u n="734" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0084">erm and you need to be rushed to hospital immediately <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I ran into <unclear/> yes</u>
<u n="737" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0041">er I did think this and then I thought well if he's been to a war zone he might have some brains <pause dur="short"/> not brains but perhaps he might be able to hold a conversation</u>
<u n="739" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> But is he an officer? Or is he becoming an officer?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0041">I have no idea <pause dur="short"/> I should have probably broached that earlier than now shouldn't I</u>
<u n="741" who="S0084">yeah cos if he's cannon fodder it's a no</u>
<u n="742" who="S0041" trans="overlap">fucked <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> having met an awful lot of squaddies when my friend was at uni in Colchester</u>
<u n="744" who="S0041">it's going to be an abort <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="745" who="S0084">for <trunc>s</trunc> I mean you know are are you just going to meet him from work?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0084">in the granny dress?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0041">I might take  I might  take something else to change in to <pause dur="short"/> just just a guess</u>
<u n="749" who="S0084">as a first opinion</u>
<u n="750" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="751" who="S0084">this is  this is  how I go out</u>
<u n="752" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> loves the granny dress <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> of which I wish they'd ordered me another one already cos that one looks even worse now</u>
<u n="753" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0084">hanging off you</u>
<u n="756" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0084">so you have five dresses that are too big</u>
<u n="758" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they fitted me last month so</u>
<u n="759" who="S0084">briefly <pause dur="short"/> for a short period</u>
<u n="760" who="S0041" trans="overlap">briefly</u>
<u n="761" who="S0084">for about a week</u>
<u n="762" who="S0046">alright ladies and gentleman <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to lay my head</u>
<u n="763" who="S0084">are you alright?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0041">bye</u>
<u n="765" who="S0084">Good night</u>
<u n="766" who="S0046">I shall see you tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow</u>
<u n="767" who="S0041">night night <pause dur="short"/> shall I get Laurie and show the the child?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0084">the baby <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0041">he's child like</u>
<u n="770" who="S0084">what do I need? I think I need a hot chocolate</u>
<u n="771" who="S0041">do you know what I need?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0084">A cake?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0041">cake or phish food <pause dur="short"/> ice cream</u>
<u n="774" who="S0084">where is the phish food ice cream?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0041">like I actually am debating whether I can possibly drive to Tesco's and get the phish food <unclear/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0084">or</u>
<u n="777" who="S0041">phish food <unclear/> in my mouth</u>
<u n="778" who="S0084">you've got to really want to go <pause dur="short"/> it's fricking raining <pause dur="short"/> if they just <trunc>w</trunc> why?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it's really bad <pause dur="short"/> I I just want it <pause dur="short"/> cos I want the chocolate because that's want and I feel bad if I eat real chocolate <pause dur="short"/> look I can even feel my jaw now <pause dur="short"/> don't remember the last time I ever felt that</u>
<u n="780" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0041">like I put my hand on my cheek today and I thought oh my God there's a jaw and it's not covered in rolls of fat</u>
<u n="782" who="S0084">what are you talking about? Well all I can offer you is hot chocolate I'm afraid but that's still better than a poke in the eye</u>
<u n="783" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="784" who="S0084"><unclear/> you don't have to go out in the rain <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0041">and I could drown</u>
<u n="786" who="S0084">you might actually get washed away</u>
<u n="787" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="788" who="S0084"><unclear/> nearly did <pause dur="short"/> if it's doing this tomorrow morning <pause dur="short"/> I'm definitely taking the car</u>
<u n="789" who="S0041">oh fuck this <pause dur="short"/> I hope it's not when I walk to work <pause dur="short"/> so I need to go <pause dur="short"/> I need to Google <trunc>Tri</trunc> on the Triumph website <unclear/> there's some type of something</u>
<u n="790" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> something sexual <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0041" trans="overlap">if you're going to see it at least let's see some sexy underwear</u>
<u n="792" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I need to get something to buy</u>
<u n="793" who="S0041">Cos I did have something which was like a bit like a leotard but in it had bones like around the boobs and straight down</u>
<u n="794" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="795" who="S0041">so but the rest of it was clear mesh</u>
<u n="796" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="797" who="S0041">apart from the bones which were nude <pause dur="short"/> so if you can see it <pause dur="short"/> you can see the you can completely see the underwear but it would be nice underwear</u>
<u n="798" who="S0084" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> so how long ago was that?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0041">that was ages ago <pause dur="short"/> it was Christmas</u>
<u n="800" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="802" who="S0084"><unclear/> Find out what he's doing</u>
<u n="803" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="804" who="S0084">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> oh deary deary dear <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> hot chocolate</u>
<u n="805" who="S0041">uh</u>
<u n="806" who="S0084">there's bugs on the side <pause dur="short"/> there's bugs on the side</u>
<u n="807" who="S0041">actual bugs?</u>
<u n="808" who="S0084">oh I think it's having issues</u>
<u n="809" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="810" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<event desc="sound of filling kettle"/>
<u n="811" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0084">are you alright?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> done it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="814" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> you look a bit lost</u>
<u n="815" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="816" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="818" who="S0084">washing washing washing</u>
<u n="819" who="S0041">oh God <pause dur="short"/> there's dust everywhere <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to have to completely hoover up this flat</u>
<u n="820" who="S0084">urgh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> what have they being doing to you <pause dur="short"/> bloody <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0041">I moved all my bedding up and take that bottom sheet I think and just sleep there</u>
<u n="822" who="S0084">yeah good idea <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0041">and put it all in the wash before I go to work tomorrow</u>
<u n="824" who="S0084">sounds sensible</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="825" who="S0041"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="826" who="S0084"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> briefly <pause dur="short"/> I want to get rid of this one because I know it works but it just pisses me off that I keep having to fanny on with it</u>
<u n="828" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if that one works then <unclear/> Oh it smells smoky in here <unclear/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0041">is he?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0084">must be</u>
<u n="831" who="S0041">I'll tell him off <pause dur="short"/> I thought that when I came in actually</u>
<u n="832" who="S0084"><unclear/> Yeah I suppose you know the weather is pretty grim but still <pause dur="short"/> it does stink</u>
<u n="833" who="S0041">so let's rotate this <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="834" who="S0084">rotate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="835" who="S0041">rotate the picture</u>
<u n="836" who="S0084">oh yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> I need to see the baby</u>
<u n="837" who="S0041">he's so  he's so  young <pause dur="short"/> so so young</u>
<u n="838" who="S0084">what are you doing?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0041">look how young he looks</u>
<u n="840" who="S0084">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>do</trunc> he does look quite young</u>
<u n="841" who="S0041">do you not think he looks about nineteen</u>
<u n="842" who="S0084">he doesn't even look like he's really <trunc>sh</trunc> really shaving does he</u>
<u n="843" who="S0041">no look if you zoom out a little bit</u>
<u n="844" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they all look the same age though <pause dur="short"/> they all look young <pause dur="short"/> so remember that's just what you look like when you're twenty-three <pause dur="short"/> it does look like he's wearing his dad's shirt and tie</u>
<u n="845" who="S0041">yeah he does though he does look tiny</u>
<u n="846" who="S0084">he looks terrified <pause dur="short"/> maybe he's the groom</u>
<u n="847" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="848" who="S0084">he's coming <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Oh God <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> No <pause dur="short"/> hilarious <pause dur="short"/> erm the thing is like you're always going to have that bad erm regret if you don't go <pause dur="short"/> you'll always going to wonder whether you do really get on <pause dur="short"/> you do talk to him a lot don't you</u>
<u n="849" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose I have nothing to lose at the moment</u>
<u n="850" who="S0084">pride <pause dur="short"/> what pride? Oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I knew it wouldn't take you long</u>
<u n="851" who="S0041">ow <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="852" who="S0084">for God sake</u>
<u n="853" who="S0041">I knew it wouldn't take you long <pause dur="short"/> do you know the other day I had it on for like a whole half an hour before it did that</u>
<u n="854" who="S0084">it dies</u>
<u n="855" who="S0041">oh no <pause dur="short"/> you would think so wouldn't you</u>
<u n="856" who="S0084" trans="overlap">die <pause dur="short"/> just trying to believe that <pause dur="short"/> just didn't believe that he'd go to sleep for nothing <pause dur="short"/> he's laughing at you you know</u>
<u n="857" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/> looks like this look <pause dur="short"/> this <pause dur="short"/> could do this</u>
<u n="858" who="S0084">oh that's sexual <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0041">or this</u>
<u n="860" who="S0084">actually cos there was an advert on recently wasn't there and we saw it <pause dur="short"/> and they all look quite nice</u>
<u n="861" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> this <unclear/> doable</u>
<u n="862" who="S0084" trans="overlap">are they a million pounds?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0041">what she's wearing?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0084">yeah that would be really nice</u>
<u n="865" who="S0041">I'd go for the black</u>
<u n="866" who="S0084">A black version of? That doesn't cost a hundred million pounds</u>
<u n="867" who="S0041">yeah it might <unclear/> er if I can find the United Kingdom <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="868" who="S0084">are you alright darling?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0041">Larry <pause dur="short"/> die <pause dur="short"/> shop online <pause dur="short"/> oh Lazzer</u>
<u n="870" who="S0084">is there a sale?</u>
<u n="871" who="S0041">please</u>
<u n="872" who="S0084">but the new stuff won't be in the sales <pause dur="short"/> that's the only problem here <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="873" who="S0041">right so I <unclear/> Do you think it's a shape wear thing?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0084">yeah <trunc>probab</trunc> well it looks like it <pause dur="short"/> they're usually not very attractive those so</u>
<u n="875" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0084">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> that one looks quite nice <pause dur="short"/> who can say?</u>
<u n="877" who="S0041">Cos the other option is to do something like this and actually put proper underwear underneath so that if you see it at least it looks hot</u>
<u n="878" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> that is fifty-one pounds</u>
<u n="879" who="S0041">ah <pause dur="short"/> that's a lot of money <pause dur="short"/> I've got some just like this I go running in <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="880" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah you just want them <pause dur="short"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> that's what you want <pause dur="short"/> you want it to skim over your bum <pause dur="short"/> that's is that twenty pounds each?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0041">sixty pounds it is</u>
<u n="882" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> body stocking <pause dur="short"/> it's really nice though</u>
<u n="883" who="S0041">it is nice <pause dur="short"/> I've got something like this underneath</u>
<u n="884" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> madam</u>
<u n="885" who="S0041">except for it's only black</u>
<u n="886" who="S0084">diamond sensation</u>
<u n="887" who="S0041">could do that</u>
<u n="888" who="S0084">I know but that's just bra and vest <pause dur="short"/> you need the pants as well</u>
<u n="889" who="S0041">you need the whole enchilada <pause dur="short"/> next</u>
<u n="890" who="S0084">all of it please</u>
<u n="891" who="S0041">I wonder if erm <pause dur="short"/> do you know where will do this <pause dur="short"/> marks and Spencers</u>
<u n="892" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's nice <pause dur="short"/> oh they're the hipsters again <pause dur="short"/> that's what you need</u>
<u n="893" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0084">body stocking underwear <pause dur="short"/> oh why's the white one a pound cheaper?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0041" trans="overlap">fifty quid <pause dur="short"/> it's a lot of money isn't it</u>
<u n="896" who="S0084">that one that one's only fifteen <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not very nice</u>
<u n="897" who="S0041">well yeah but it's just on the pants as well <pause dur="short"/> my bum's covered but look at my bazzomers</u>
<u n="898" who="S0084">that's nice</u>
<u n="899" who="S0041">that's pretty <pause dur="short"/> if that was in <trunc>la</trunc> in in skin colour I could rock that</u>
<u n="900" who="S0084">that's really nice</u>
<u n="901" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> so really I've got to come to terms with the fact that if I want something from here it's going to be sixty pounds</u>
<u n="902" who="S0084">basically yeah <pause dur="short"/> or a hundred and eight pounds</u>
<u n="903" who="S0041">wow <pause dur="short"/> wowzers <pause dur="short"/> forty-eight pounds</u>
<u n="904" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0041">not as sexy though <pause dur="short"/> if you <trunc>g</trunc> someone's going to see your underwear you'd prefer it to be sexiest wouldn't you</u>
<u n="906" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="907" who="S0041">the sexiest version</u>
<u n="908" who="S0084">oh look <pause dur="short"/> that's alright though <pause dur="short"/> the erm this one</u>
<u n="909" who="S0041">yeah that's not bad</u>
<u n="910" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="911" who="S0041" trans="overlap">they do this at erm Debenhams for fifteen</u>
<u n="912" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="913" who="S0041">right so let's try er Marks and Spencers</u>
<u n="914" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="915" who="S0041">kinky knickers</u>
<u n="916" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0041">they've written that on Marks and Spencer's website</u>
<u n="918" who="S0084">on M and S?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0041">yes it says kinky knickers on the side <pause dur="short"/> and it's capital K so I think it might be a <unclear/> but still</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="920" who="S0041">go on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="921" who="S0041"><event desc="sound of sneeze"/></u>
<u n="922" who="S0084">bless you</u>
<u n="923" who="S0041">this isn't <pause dur="long"/> It's not as sexy though is it <pause dur="short"/> it's just not as sexy</u>
<u n="924" who="S0084">how much is that one? Twenty-five</u>
<u n="925" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="926" who="S0084">half the price</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="927" who="S0041">I mean this is bridal lingerie but</u>
<u n="928" who="S0084">that will do</u>
<u n="929" who="S0041">like look at this pretty one <pause dur="short"/> it's got a little lace around the bottom <pause dur="short"/> I mean what you would actually want to do is whack something like that out so if someone saw your underwear you would look fricking hot</u>
<u n="930" who="S0084" trans="overlap">oh that's nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah with silk</u>
<u n="931" who="S0041">with <trunc>s</trunc>  <pause dur="short"/> I want to click on it and see</u>
<u n="932" who="S0084">do you get all of that? Everything she's wearing?</u>
<u n="933" who="S0041">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I kind of hope so</u>
<u n="934" who="S0084">that would be worth it really <pause dur="short"/> if you get all the stockings and suspenders out <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> stuff</u>
<u n="935" who="S0041">I think it's just the basque <pause dur="short"/> which is an issue</u>
<u n="936" who="S0084">yeah cos you need it all</u>
<u n="937" who="S0041">yeah you need the whole  the whole  lot</u>
<u n="938" who="S0084">the whole shebang</u>
<u n="939" who="S0041">all of that</u>
<u n="940" who="S0084">that's just mean advertising it all</u>
<u n="941" who="S0041">isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I could get an under slip like this to go underneath it</u>
<u n="942" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you have to be careful about the length though because it's quite short at the front</u>
<u n="943" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0084">and make sure you take the dress with you when you go shopping</u>
<u n="945" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> the suspender belt's only fifteen</u>
<u n="946" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="947" who="S0041">on it's own but still you're gonna rock up to a hundred quid</u>
<u n="948" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="949" who="S0041">although I don't own a suspender belt <pause dur="short"/> I would like to wear one</u>
<u n="950" who="S0084">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> I really want one <pause dur="short"/> what I really want is <unclear/> buy it for me</u>
<u n="951" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="952" who="S0084">in an ideal world</u>
<u n="953" who="S0041">that would be perfect</u>
<u n="954" who="S0084">that's what we need <pause dur="short"/> where are the men that do all the buying of the lingerie? And not the children <pause dur="short"/> not the poor ones <pause dur="short"/> it's only the rich ones that will <pause dur="short"/> the sugar daddy thing never worked out did it</u>
<u n="955" who="S0041">no it didn't <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I pursued it enough</u>
<u n="956" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> I got a bit freaked out</u>
<u n="957" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see this is this this lace</u>
<u n="958" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="959" who="S0041">is quite nice <pause dur="short"/> but then I think if you wear a body that's full body like this then I I don't know if that would look nice or not</u>
<u n="960" who="S0084">it's a tough one</u>
<u n="961" who="S0041">like certainly not that <pause dur="short"/> fricking <unclear/> yourself in <pause dur="short"/> jesus <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit extreme <pause dur="short"/> it's the panty line as well isn't it <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing</u>
<u n="962" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're just going to have to be really careful <pause dur="short"/> that's why you should just take the dress and try everything on with that</u>
<u n="963" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="964" who="S0084"><unclear/> Oh this fridge door doesn't close</u>
<u n="965" who="S0041" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="966" who="S0084">there you go</u>
<u n="967" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="968" who="S0084"><unclear/> open</u>
<u n="969" who="S0041">I think I need to go to Marks and Spencers tomorrow don't I</u>
<u n="970" who="S0084">I think you definitely do</u>
<u n="971" who="S0041">with the dress</u>
<u n="972" who="S0084">try everything on <pause dur="short"/> that blue one <pause dur="short"/> teal one is nice</u>
<u n="973" who="S0041">yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> they do it in a different colour as well</u>
<u n="974" who="S0084">I quite like it in teal it's a bit different</u>
<u n="975" who="S0041">I I I think you might see teal under my dress <pause dur="short"/> I think you might see it</u>
<u n="976" who="S0084">erm <pause dur="short"/> possible yeah <pause dur="short"/> but that's yeah that's the idea isn't it?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0041">there is that</u>
<u n="978" who="S0084">point buying this underwear</u>
<u n="979" who="S0041">well there is that <pause dur="short"/> I suppose as soon as I've put something on I'm gonna know whether it was a good idea to show the underwear or not <pause dur="short"/> I think it will either look really good or it will look horrendous <pause dur="short"/> like horrendous <pause dur="short"/> like it's one thing showing your bra underneath a black top but once you get to kind of nice dress it's a I think it's it would either look sexy or you would look like holy crap <pause dur="short"/> why can we see your underwear when you're wearing a nice dress?</u>
<u n="980" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> tramp</u>
<u n="981" who="S0041">tramp <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="982" who="S0084">yeah that is a bit of a problem <pause dur="short"/> do they let you try on the basques before you buy them?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0084">mm that's alright then</u>
<u n="985" who="S0041">right you have to turn off now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos it's too much <pause dur="short"/> it's just too much in the world <pause dur="short"/> you definitely need a <unclear/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0084">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> all the yummy stuff</u>
</body>
</text>
