<text id="SY5K">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:55:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-12-22</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0651</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At the office of Speaker No 2 in Tunbridge Wells, Kent</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics>What to do for the tape. Consultation process. Business Case. Rationale for location of new project. Organisation of local health services. Relationships with hospices. Patient health. Nursing of people at end of life. Politics and geography. Health budgets. Use of estate agents. What new building might look like.</topics>
		<activity>Discussing a business plan for a new hospice</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0651">
				<exactage>58</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Rotherham S/Yorks</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Maidstone, Kent</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>CEO</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_1</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0282">okay is that recording now? or is it doing something?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0651"><trunc>u</trunc> I wonder if I can do RP now and get rid of my accent</u>
<u n="3" who="S0282">yes <pause dur="short"/> that would fox everybody</u>
<u n="4" who="S0651"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>can't don't know if I can</unclear></u>
<u n="5" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0651"><unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<u n="7" who="S0282">okay so right <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> there are there are <pause dur="short"/> kind of two things really to <unclear>pan</unclear> out today I suppose which is number one these consultation meetings <unclear>you're doing</unclear></u>
<u n="8" who="S0651" trans="overlap">are you gonna do that thing first? do you have to do that first?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0282" trans="overlap">what thing? <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0651">the taping thing</u>
<u n="11" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="12" who="S0651">oh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0282">well no we just tape it</u>
<u n="14" who="S0651">oh right</u>
<u n="15" who="S0282">we just tape yeah just tape the conversation</u>
<u n="16" who="S0651" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> don't? oh right so this is the <trunc>pl</trunc> <trunc>u</trunc> the business plan for this? right okay go on go done</u>
<u n="17" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="18" who="S0651">I'm alright I can do it I can work that one out yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0651"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and then erm no cos er you just have an ordinary conversation that's what they want</u>
<u n="24" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="25" who="S0282" trans="overlap">ordinary conversation <pause dur="short"/> erm so erm <pause dur="short"/> the sessions in January <pause dur="short"/> but also the bit that's troubling me as well is this thing about the location of the new hospice <unclear>in <anon type="place"/></unclear></u>
<u n="26" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0282">and er you said something about a rationale for choosing a particular area</u>
<u n="28" who="S0651">I did so we'll talk about that</u>
<u n="29" who="S0282">and then erm but then I said in my interview <pause dur="short"/> that we should do we could kind of talk to the other local health providers and</u>
<u n="30" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0282">health commissioners to see <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so that it gets positioned in a in a place where</u>
<u n="32" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0282">it kind of fits in logically with <pause dur="short"/> the other services that are available there</u>
<u n="34" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0282">so <pause dur="short"/> I want I need to understand from you what your thinking was about location cos you suggested a specific place</u>
<u n="36" who="S0651">I did <pause dur="short"/> I think erm talking about the business <pause dur="short"/> plan then</u>
<u n="37" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0651">I think we'll always say for the cottage hospice business case</u>
<u n="39" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0651">because not enough people in the organisation <pause dur="short"/> understand the business plan despite trying to consult on it endlessly</u>
<u n="41" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0651">and and the document itself <unclear>as</unclear> the second time we've had a business plan three year business plan</u>
<u n="43" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0651">not enough staff know the business plan well enough <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>r</trunc>really the managers are getting better at it but to see <trunc>w</trunc>what you know the the direction of travel for the next three years which really I think is for the next five in the business plan</u>
<u n="45" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0651" trans="overlap">so if we <unclear>only</unclear> say business case <pause dur="short"/> when we're talking about the cottage hospices</u>
<u n="47" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0651">I think that <unclear>will</unclear> drop into there</u>
<u n="49" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="50" who="S0651">yeah so</u>
<u n="51" who="S0282">okay so</u>
<u n="52" who="S0651" trans="overlap">to avoid them talking about the business plan for the cottage hospices cos they'll get mixed up <unclear>between</unclear></u>
<u n="53" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="54" who="S0651">business plan that right? so in respect of the business case which is what we'd said in that thing about the business case for cottage hospices</u>
<u n="55" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0651">erm in fact my fixation on language cos I wrote a few times didn't I? a full and fully costed kind of business case</u>
<u n="57" who="S0282">yes that was scary</u>
<u n="58" who="S0651" trans="overlap">er it was quite <vocal desc="laugh"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>see what</unclear> the business case yes and one of the big issues will be location without a doubt</u>
<u n="59" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0651">and <pause dur="short"/> also <pause dur="short"/> testing it the first one cos the intention is to open one</u>
<u n="61" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0651">and see how it goes and run it for a while</u>
<u n="63" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0651">and learn the lessons from it before we try to go for a second one but I think there will be a second one</u>
<u n="65" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="66" who="S0651">er but we won't know that until we've had the first one for a while and there may be a third one but we won't know about that until we've had the second one for a while</u>
<u n="67" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="68" who="S0651">so the business case erm a big part of it will be location I don't think there's any doubt about that and my</u>
<u n="69" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0651">rationale in suggesting that it should be</u>
<u n="71" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0651">I think I said <anon type="place"/> but I really meant <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0651">because <pause dur="short"/> I've thought since I got here that the changes in the NHS and the statutory set-up of the NHS <pause dur="short"/> erm puts <pause dur="short"/> the patients' carers and family that live in the <anon type="place"/> part of the patch that we cover it leaves them vulnerable</u>
<u n="75" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0651">to a shift which means that GPs and others might not want to refer to hospice in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0282">oh I see right</u>
<u n="78" who="S0651" trans="overlap">but <trunc>m</trunc> eighty percent of our patients' carers and families come from sorry I should've <unclear>used some</unclear></u>
<u n="79" who="S0282">no that's fine</u>
<u n="80" who="S0651">eighty percent <vocal desc="laugh"/> of our patients' <pause dur="short"/> carers and families come from <anon type="place"/> and twenty percent from <anon type="place"/> and <trunc>s</trunc> and so and that and the funding has always been the same way here traditionally</u>
<u n="81" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="82" who="S0651" trans="overlap"><unclear>of the</unclear> eighty percent of the statutory funding comes for <anon type="place"/> and actually as it happens when I first got here <pause dur="short"/> people <trunc>th</trunc> we didn't know what percentage was but the more the more you cut it <vocal desc="laugh"/> nearly always finds out it's twenty percent of the patients twenty percent of the carers and families for <trunc>s</trunc> for counselling <pause dur="short"/> twenty percent of the funding from the community <vocal desc="laugh"/> about works out too because I worried that</u>
<u n="83" who="S0282" trans="overlap">right gosh</u>
<u n="84" who="S0651">we were kind of cross subsidising if you see what I mean</u>
<u n="85" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0651">we were raising our money in <anon type="place"/> and spending it in <anon type="place"/> but we got everything seems to work to twenty percent</u>
<u n="87" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's quite interesting</u>
<u n="88" who="S0651">and so erm I worry that the maps you know maps in my humble opinion are just lines drawn on a piece of paper</u>
<u n="89" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0651">they're arbitrary</u>
<u n="91" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0651">erm <trunc>s</trunc> but people still see us cos we're based in <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> people see the organisation as being about <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> despite</u>
<u n="93" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0651">the fact that the vast majority of people we see we see in their homes they can see us around this building</u>
<u n="95" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0651">and so that's why I've thought since I got here that we should do something and put a bricks and mortar facility in <anon type="place"/> because the truth of those maps is that you know better than I all of this <pause dur="short"/> where people live is just where people live it's really about work <trunc>u</trunc> er <trunc>u</trunc> home to work routes home to shopping home to facilities home to services and people in <anon type="place"/> and surrounding area see themselves attached to <anon type="place"/> and attached to kind of this part of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0282" trans="overlap">cos they come here</u>
<u n="98" who="S0651">because they come here cos they go shopping to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah and there's an easy road</u>
<u n="100" who="S0651">erm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0282">or an easy route</u>
<u n="102" who="S0651">exactly and and also then the <trunc>n</trunc> if you start fine-graining that</u>
<u n="103" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0651">and you start getting into so this this is er an older erm erm map about and we're not on it if you see what I mean this is</u>
<u n="105" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no I've been looking for you mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah where where where where my little pencil we can we can find these again but if you see my little pencil mark is where we cover in the <anon type="place"/> bit</u>
<u n="107" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0651">and this just happens to be the commissioning groups within <trunc>NAS</trunc>NHS <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> is a complicated area in the sense that as as you know <anon type="place"/> county council is kind of easy and covers all of <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> has two county councils</u>
<u n="109" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0651">west and east</u>
<u n="111" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0651">and so I'm only interested I personally am only interested in in east <pause dur="short"/> and the introduction of the clinical commissioning groups</u>
<u n="113" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0651">and the loss of a strategic health authority and therefore a strategic picture and the government push to localism whatever that means <pause dur="short"/> means that <anon type="place"/> particularly and these clinical commissioning groups within <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0651">I I I I I know I go off at tangents actually that one of the things about the</u>
<u n="117" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0651">about the routes that where people live and where they see themselves belonging to you know the committee development stuff that you know this village or this community ends at that river or that scout hut if you're the other side of the scout hut then you're not part of blah you <trunc>kn</trunc> and so <pause dur="short"/> this part of <anon type="place"/> hasn't got a big <pause dur="short"/> secondary healthcare acute trust hospital and so that's another reason that people from <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and further down to <anon type="place"/> come to <anon type="place"/> cos there's this massive PFI hospital <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> which is</u>
<u n="119" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="120" who="S0651">used to be</u>
<u n="121" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0651">the <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> in the centre of <anon type="place"/> that's been bulldozed and they're building houses <pause dur="short"/> but the PFI hospital is <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> so they see themselves belonging to this as part of the health economy too</u>
<u n="123" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="124" who="S0651">and I just <trunc>w</trunc> er and because there's no <pause dur="short"/> acute <pause dur="short"/> big hospital for the <trunc>s</trunc> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> CCGs</u>
<u n="125" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0651">then some of their political small piece strategy is to run their health economy by limiting the amount of people that are referred to an acute trust cos they've got three hospice hospitals sorry three cottage hospitals and the GPs would like not to send people to hospital</u>
<u n="127" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="128" who="S0651">because it costs them a lot of money so they're trying to run their health economy based on the three cottage hospitals which which will have flaws and problems for the people that live there and so I want to make sure that we as the hospice have some presence there cos I</u>
<u n="129" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0651">worry that one that of the <trunc>unti</trunc>unintended consequences of all of these shifts would mean that people that live there that traditionally have always come to this hospice <trunc>u</trunc> to visit people or supported us with money and feel they belong to <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> will be told by their GP they can't be referred here so that's my logic</u>
<u n="131" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0651">about why in the main I think we should try the first cottage hospice in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0282">yes and</u>
<u n="134" who="S0651">it's interesting that I can't really have that conversation meaningfully</u>
<u n="135" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="136" who="S0651">with the trustees <pause dur="short"/> or or <trunc>th</trunc> even my my fellow hospice leadership team <trunc>m</trunc> erm members really because it <trunc>g</trunc> it gets it it some of is guess work on my part about strategy having seen many times before <vocal desc="laugh"/> these kind of restructurings in statutory services</u>
<u n="137" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0651">end up with unintended consequences</u>
<u n="139" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="140" who="S0651">sorry I stopped you you were gonna say something</u>
<u n="141" who="S0282">no no no no that's fine erm <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>a</trunc> sorry how many CCGs in <anon type="place"/>? one two three four? <event desc="sound of tapping on table"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0651">er in <anon type="place"/> yes yeah there's a yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0651">so this is the whole of <anon type="place"/> and by and large that's the ones for <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="146" who="S0651">and the one that we cover most is this <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="148" who="S0651">and here is the population of of the erm the the CCGs which with <trunc>u</trunc> <trunc>p</trunc><trunc>p</trunc>politics with a big P on I mean there is some argument <trunc>i</trunc> erm bear in mind this only came out <trunc>rec</trunc> the CCGs have only come out in the last four years</u>
<u n="149" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="150" who="S0651">er the health and social care bill</u>
<u n="151" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="152" who="S0651">and there is an argument some people think that they're gonna end up merging cos they think some of these populations are no big enough to get the economies of scale that</u>
<u n="153" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0651">that the CCGs need</u>
<u n="155" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="156" who="S0651">and when I think this this one <anon type="place"/> district <trunc>i</trunc> so it's really these three actually that make up <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="place"/> look at <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/>'s huge</u>
<u n="158" who="S0651">it is but it's a unitary as well so actually</u>
<u n="159" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah so it'll it'll yeah they'll declare <unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> it'll be a <trunc>t</trunc> it'll be private company <unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> <unclear>eventually</unclear></u>
<u n="160" who="S0651" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well it's interesting cos you you like these kind of things I'm not sure and and I <trunc>s</trunc> think I probably do too I'm not sure that the hospice is kinda bit removed in a third sector sense that it floats like an island hospices they're outside the you know they're in the sector but outside the sector</u>
<u n="161" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0651">these three CCGs for <anon type="place"/> yeah? so <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> a rather erm coast <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>c</trunc> is that what it's called? a coastal community healthcare? that's helpful erm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0651">are doing lots of things together so they have one joint newsletter</u>
<u n="165" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="166" who="S0651">and erm and they they and the the economies of the economies of scale for CCGs one of the really main players that's invisible <pause dur="short"/> unless you're immersed in this stuff are the commissioning support units</u>
<u n="167" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="168" who="S0651">and there's a big paper about commissioning support units that's come out of government commissioning support units are supposed to make the economies of scale so these CCGs aren't big enough to commission</u>
<u n="169" who="S0282">no oh</u>
<u n="170" who="S0651" trans="overlap">and so the <trunc>CC</trunc> the commissioning support units are pulling them together <pause dur="short"/> find the economies of scale</u>
<u n="171" who="S0282">er</u>
<u n="172" who="S0651">and so really that's another restructuring by the back door which is putting PCTs and strategic <vocal desc="laugh"/> authorities back in <unclear>and finding</unclear> things but if you read the guidance out of government they are to build the market that's their job is to build the marketplace this is privatisation of the NHS through the back door erm but but also some of the biggest threats around that <pause dur="short"/> are the old the NHS structures themselves</u>
<u n="173" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="174" who="S0651">so erm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0282">so these the faceless bureaucrats will be back</u>
<u n="176" who="S0651">they are still there and they've not really left so the chief exec of the commissioning support unit for what was <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0651">which now covers all of this cos it's now <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="179" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh does it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0651"><anon type="place"/> and something else</u>
<u n="181" who="S0282">promotion</u>
<u n="182" who="S0651">are the same people that went through the revolving door and took their two hundred and fifty thousand pounds redundancy and have popped up again as the chief exec of whatever and as they try separate off commissioning also the deliverers are the same in the sense that if we take the <anon type="place"/> bit here which I haven't isn't in here but it's my pencil line <anon type="place"/> PCT</u>
<u n="183" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0651">the chief exec <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> took her money for redundancy from being the <anon type="place"/> PCT chief exec and became the <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> community health trust chief exec which is a delivery NHS organisation and and they are looking to deliver well beyond <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> so for example</u>
<u n="185" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0651">my choice of cottage hospice again this is all about my choice of cottage hospice being in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> erm CCG has broken ranks with the other two on the issue of community services</u>
<u n="187" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="188" who="S0651">and has pushed out its thirteen million pounds community contract to any bidder so Virgin Healthcare could bid and be delivering that in <anon type="place"/> another <unclear>good result</unclear> my cottage hospice there but also <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> community health trust have bid are bidding to do it</u>
<u n="189" who="S0282">mm mm?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0651">and what was <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh</u>
<u n="192" who="S0651"><anon type="place"/> healthcare community health trust has also bid <unclear>into there</unclear></u>
<u n="193" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0651">so the internal market for the NHS as well as the external market makes a really uncertain time</u>
<u n="195" who="S0282" trans="overlap">wow <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="196" who="S0651">hence me wanting my cottage hospice here for the future for the people that live there</u>
<u n="197" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes yes <pause dur="short"/> yes and also being the one the one identifiable unit <pause dur="short"/> er <unclear/> delivery <vocal desc="laugh"/> that you might actually might give us some money to</u>
<u n="198" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yes and and particularly because that contracts out</u>
<u n="199" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0651" trans="overlap">and people are bidding in and they won't let the contract till next October by which time I'm hoping to have broken ground and say to the new provider by the way chaps we have this new cottage hospice just opening</u>
<u n="201" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah and is it now <trunc>we</trunc> do they not <trunc>ha</trunc>? do they have to have their community involvement section in their business case in their business case for their bid?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0651" trans="overlap">in the <pause dur="short"/> they will have to have their community we er <trunc>n</trunc>now your next the next level of complexity then</u>
<u n="203" who="S0282">mm?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0651">yeah?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0651">so if I was to erm I can draw on this you can have this map if <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>it's interesting that there are possibly if I take this patch here and I said</u>
<u n="206" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0651">they they're putting out <trunc>the</trunc>they're putting out the yellow are putting out their community service thirteen million pounds</u>
<u n="208" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0651">arguably there are six hospices which have a bit of service into that community thing</u>
<u n="210" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="211" who="S0651">so we've tried to talk as hospices</u>
<u n="212" who="S0282" trans="overlap">are you that scribble?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0651">yeah we're that scribble</u>
<u n="214" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="215" who="S0651">erm <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> here</u>
<u n="216" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0651"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> erm <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> they all do a bit they think of</u>
<u n="218" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0651">that kind of service</u>
<u n="220" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0651">and get money six six hospices from that CCG <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> tiny bits of money relatively I think we get about seventy-two thousand pounds</u>
<u n="222" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0651">but they all get <unclear>big <trunc>s</trunc></unclear> and so the hospices then in this brave new world have been talking about pulling together a consortium to speak to the new bidders and providers and to be part of their community planning for their bid</u>
<u n="224" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="225" who="S0651">but the truth is that this is brand new to us as hospices they don't I believe they don't understand what consortium means actually this is back to SRB or or or lottery or you know <trunc>a</trunc> we as hospices don't know what consortium means and they all think that we can be a <trunc>com</trunc> become a consortium</u>
<u n="226" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0651">and we can all have a seat at that big table they don't realise that that consortium will mean subcontracting effectively</u>
<u n="228" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0651">but they have found out that the money that's given to hospices three hundred and eighty-five thousand pounds is not part of the thirteen million pounds so they think everything's okay now but the truth is we have to work with that provider because that is the provider that will refer into hospice services so</u>
<u n="230" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0651" trans="overlap">actually I have had some negotiations with <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> are bidding in we are also on the face of it part of this consortium of six because they don't know what's gonna happen so they're all looking to consult and see what happens but er</u>
<u n="232" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0651">the current provider is called <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> community health trust who has been appalling for ever and so that's why this CCG are getting rid of them</u>
<u n="234" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="235" who="S0651">so all of this means this is the place to go I have no doubt that if we're gonna open a cottage hospice this is the place to go</u>
<u n="236" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="237" who="S0651">it has no acute trust hospital it is fed by cottage hospitals</u>
<u n="238" who="S0282">ah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0651">and actually it is the place this is the most dangerous for us strategically of losing if something happens</u>
<u n="240" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0651">and therefore the patients themselves would struggle and lose out</u>
<u n="242" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0651">er and cos it's just new maps and new <trunc>di</trunc> new lines this <unclear>them on</unclear> the CCG maps didn't exist before so they're new maps and new lines and therefore that's why I think that's where we should go first</u>
<u n="244" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="245" who="S0651">I have floated that idea with the CCG at our meeting who thought it was very interesting and would like to speak more</u>
<u n="246" who="S0282">say that last bit again what? you floated?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0651" trans="overlap">I have floated the idea of our cottage hospice idea with this CCG</u>
<u n="248" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="249" who="S0651">and they're very interested in it and would like to know more the thing is I need to get past the gatekeepers the decision makers</u>
<u n="250" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0651">but it kind of makes sense to them because it makes sense to them cos they're trying to run a health economy with just cottage hospitals</u>
<u n="252" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0651">so the cottage hospice concept fits into their construct of what they see</u>
<u n="254" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0651">as secondary care</u>
<u n="256" who="S0282">right <pause dur="short"/> uhu</u>
<u n="257" who="S0651">there's another level of there about why to have it there cos what I don't want to happen is the cottage hospitals to go for palliative care in a big way cos they would be a major threat to us <pause dur="short"/> because they would be potentially a provider if there's money comes and they get another level of complexity <pause dur="short"/> nationally a couple of years ago there was a palliative care funding review <pause dur="short"/> which was led by Tom Hughes-Hallett who's the chief exec of Marie Curie</u>
<u n="258" who="S0282">mm?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0651">and they what they're trying to do with the palliative care funding review is find a per patient tariff for the government</u>
<u n="260" who="S0282">ah right</u>
<u n="261" who="S0651">to say what should the state do for palliative care patients?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="263" who="S0651">and how do we fund that? so for three or four years they've been trying to pull together this palliative care funding review they had massive consultations they produced various documents they had a final document government were committed to it at the time that's the coalition they did eleven pilot sites to try and work out how the tariff and the currency would work</u>
<u n="264" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0651">they've <trunc>subsequent</trunc> pushed out another report a few weeks ago which is their final version which to me looks like fudge smells like fudge and tastes like fudge there will be no I don't think the well the the final document is clear there will be there's another set of pilots to do but it's clear that there would be no more money and and it will not be a statutory requirement however <pause dur="short"/> if that tariff can be erm an agreement which is voluntary and this CCG decides to follow that agreement and the cottage hospices take that money then that will affect hospices and others and so the palliative care funding review is more of a danger to hospices than it is a benefit <pause dur="short"/> because if acute trusts can get money out of it then they will take money and make money out of it because another level of complexity in getting your head back into the NHS system is <pause dur="short"/> although there is no <pause dur="short"/> secondary healthcare acute trust in this CCG are cos it's at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0651">yeah? <pause dur="short"/> what's happening in the changes in the health economy is foundation status for hospitals</u>
<u n="268" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0651">as they get foundation status it gives</u>
<u n="270" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0651">them far more freedom to behave like a private sector hospital</u>
<u n="272" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0651">which is another reason that this CCG doesn't want them as part of their picture cos they're going to charge more money and do things</u>
<u n="274" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="275" who="S0651">and they could also do by opening palliative care wards if there's money in it they would take that money which'd be another threat to the million pound statutory funding that we do that</u>
<u n="276" who="S0282"><trunc>r</trunc> oh right <pause dur="long"/> so but because there isn't a hospital that would have foundation status here there's less of a risk of that in this <unclear>area</unclear></u>
<u n="277" who="S0651" trans="overlap">it's just over the boundary</u>
<u n="278" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0651">so <trunc>th</trunc>there's still a risk to us</u>
<u n="280" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0651">erm about the foundation status thing but that's in Kent and it's less of a risk I think than here but it is one of the reasons that this CCG is going for a very community based approach</u>
<u n="282" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="283" who="S0651">in what it wants to do that's why it's gonna commission community services thirteen million pounds and part of that contract makes them use the cottage hospitals that are in that patch</u>
<u n="284" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0651">but what I wouldn't want to happen is if those cottage hospitals started effectively becoming mini hospices <pause dur="short"/> and and opening a ward that's that's just for palliative care patients cos lots of cottage hospitals <pause dur="short"/> are under-utilised and looking for a role and I</u>
<u n="286" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0651">don't want them to find the role of our palliative care and de facto hospices</u>
<u n="288" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0651">they're also they're not very good at it usually</u>
<u n="290" who="S0282">well <trunc>prob</trunc> well that's like trying to get a lawyer to be a mediator they don't</u>
<u n="291" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0282">they don't do it</u>
<u n="293" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0282">don't er that's not the skills they have so erm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0651">but that won't stop the CCG trying to get them to do it if the palliative care funding review makes a revenue income string for them</u>
<u n="296" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well they're going to chase the money aren't they?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0651">they're going to chase the money absolutely</u>
<u n="298" who="S0282">like everybody does</u>
<u n="299" who="S0651">and the foundation trust might also chase the money but they're less likely to change the money because they</u>
<u n="300" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0651">chase the money cos they've got such a massive area to cover</u>
<u n="302" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0651">and if you want to go further with some of this if we if I go back to the Kent bit of it</u>
<u n="304" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0651">so this <anon type="place"/> hospital which is really the <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> trust</u>
<u n="306" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0651" trans="overlap">cos it's both actually it's <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> trust</u>
<u n="308" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0651">and so they have two hospital sites one at <anon type="place"/> and one at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0651">which is another reason that I'm okay within that patch really it's another reason I don't need to open the first one here I need the second one to be here I think because we're we get most of eighty percent of our patients eighty percent of our money and we understand <pause dur="short"/> this system this health economic system better <pause dur="short"/> but in the longer term if I wound on ten years it will change maybe five because in <anon type="place"/> there's a brand new hospital called the institute the <anon type="place"/> institute of something something <pause dur="short"/> brand new massive private hospital has been built speculatively for the changes in in health and I know from the <anon type="place"/> CCG chief exec that this institute it's called the <anon type="place"/> and something institute you'll find it on the website is demanding that when they push out the contract which is currently to <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> hospital as it always has been they want the chance to bid into it so it's gonna get competitive about acute trusts and secondary care here</u>
<u n="312" who="S0282">oh god who's building it?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0651">it's been built and I don't know who's built it I think it might be er er er I don't know who the private hospital is but it's brand new <pause dur="short"/> purpose built <pause dur="short"/> and it can't possibly be big enough yet but it is a private sector hospital</u>
<u n="314" who="S0282">mm so somebody's got <pause dur="short"/> billion pounds to</u>
<u n="315" who="S0651">yes throw the money at</u>
<u n="316" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><trunc>spec</trunc>speculate <unclear>on it</unclear></u>
<u n="317" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yes yes <pause dur="short"/> erm <trunc>u</trunc> based around interestingly you know <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so this PFI will need foundation status but it is gonna have to compete with this stuff here so we will come to that later erm that's fine</u>
<u n="318" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0651">if there's those levels of complexity and there's another level of complexity if I talk about the five to ten years thing and if I think beyond ten years I think that <pause dur="short"/> county councils <pause dur="short"/> will become the main stakeholder for hospices not the NHS</u>
<u n="320" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="321" who="S0651">the merging of health and social care will have to happen</u>
<u n="322" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0651">and actually it won't be the health economy and the acute trusts and the cottage hospitals that will be our main worry partner whatever it will be county councils</u>
<u n="324" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0651">because the health and social care and the Dilnot report and everything will have to be addressed by <vocal desc="laugh"/> somebody at some time</u>
<u n="326" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0651">so the demographic is more elderly frail people and so that means they get more cancers and <trunc>s</trunc> and so so there is a <pause dur="short"/> there's another moral imperative</u>
<u n="328" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0651">for elderly frail people and I think that the partner in that will be county councils</u>
<u n="330" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0651">not not the NHS as we know it and therefore health and well-being boards if they continue depending who gets in when the government changes <pause dur="short"/> in in in a in a time horizon of five ten years beyond ten <trunc>y</trunc> it will be them not the NHS</u>
<u n="332" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah well no they've got to it's it does it's ludicrous</u>
<u n="333" who="S0651">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="334" who="S0282">okay so and erm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0651" trans="overlap">mm?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0282">as far as that's concerned this picture you're painting here</u>
<u n="337" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0282">you're you're confident enough enough enough about it to <trunc>s</trunc> to put your shirt on this because your man here</u>
<u n="339" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0282">he backed a <pause dur="short"/> an idea that didn't work and?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0651">the <trunc>me</trunc> the <unclear>markets</unclear> thing back in about care you mean?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so but so but you're confident enough that this is you know your hunch your hunch or your or your strategic thinking about all this is</u>
<u n="343" who="S0651" trans="overlap">hunch yeah yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0282">is right?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0651">I've thought since I got here that cos that was the cusp of the Act the Health And Social Care Act <pause dur="short"/> that <pause dur="short"/> the people at <anon type="place"/> the people in <anon type="place"/> that we serve and it goes further down cos you get you then get into these kind of you know these these <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> it's about where the GPs are in here</u>
<u n="346" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0651">it's this part of this patch</u>
<u n="348" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0651">that this has always been a danger for us because it could <pause dur="short"/> relatively at the stroke of a pen the CCG could say to all their GPs you don't refer to people over the <trunc>bou</trunc> over the border in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="351" who="S0651">and and therefore they could do that at <trunc>an</trunc> at any <unclear>rate</unclear></u>
<u n="352" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah and actually some are already doing that aren't they? so that</u>
<u n="353" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0282">where is it? where they've already said no you can't have choice any more</u>
<u n="355" who="S0651">yes</u>
<u n="356" who="S0282">where you go</u>
<u n="357" who="S0651">and so my worry is <trunc>w</trunc>we'll lose patient choice</u>
<u n="358" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="359" who="S0651">and if you stop the referral routes by GPs then we then people wouldn't get wouldn't get referred into this hospice <trunc>defi</trunc> despite the fact they've supported the hospice for twenty years</u>
<u n="360" who="S0282">I always thought that people self-referrals to hospices</u>
<u n="361" who="S0651">we've we've only just introduced self-referral</u>
<u n="362" who="S0282">really?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0651" trans="overlap">we we</u>
<u n="364" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I thought I thought you elected to</u>
<u n="365" who="S0651">no</u>
<u n="366" who="S0282">I thought you sort you said oh well you know I'd like to go to the hospice please and they said yes fine</u>
<u n="367" who="S0651">well that would</u>
<u n="368" who="S0282">and off you trotted</u>
<u n="369" who="S0651">that would be good if that's the case <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>generally</unclear></u>
<u n="370" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><trunc>doc</trunc>doctors?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0651"><trunc>G</trunc>GPs GPs GPs are the main referrer</u>
<u n="372" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="373" who="S0651">we're trying to break that cycle and we've been trying for a while to break that cycle and we will take self-referrals in fact in the last few months we've put a self-referral button on the website and we'll take phone self-referral but in some respects that's a con because they're not self-referrals because we still then have to go back to the <vocal desc="laugh"/> GP and negotiate and say</u>
<u n="374" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="375" who="S0651">Mrs Smith would like to be referred here can we have a conversation about this please so we have our <unclear/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so the GPs have to consent?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0651">they have to have the consent and mainly main referrals come from GPs cos that conversation should be had with GPs</u>
<u n="378" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0651">there's part of the <trunc>th</trunc> stuff that drives the strategy for us is that <pause dur="short"/> it's a great piece of research which is pretty conclusive and people have bought into that says <pause dur="short"/> cos you can't buck these numbers you see at any one time one percent of a GPs patient population is in the last year of their life</u>
<u n="380" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0651">fact <pause dur="short"/> some of that is sudden deaths and heart attacks and car accidents however there's some good research that says <pause dur="short"/> in western democracies you know developed countries that's <trunc>u</trunc> between sixty-four I think sixty-four and eighty-one percent of those people in the last year of life should be <trunc>s</trunc> should have palliative care needs addressed</u>
<u n="382" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0651">so we know that one percent of our population <pause dur="short"/> three hundred and sixty thousand is in last year of life so we could see three thousand six hundred people a year</u>
<u n="384" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0651" trans="overlap">we know we don't need to see all of them but we do know that actually between sixty odd percent and eighty percent let's say yeah we should be seeing and we're not seeing that so our big quest of of our business plan is to have a forty-five percent increase so at the currently we see about eleven hundred new referrals each and every year and we intend by the end of the business plan period be seeing sixteen hundred new referrals each and every year which is another reason to build some bed capacity in</u>
<u n="386" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0651">which is stepdown bed stuff so it does fit</u>
<u n="388" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0651">together my <unclear>hunch</unclear> and my shirt and my</u>
<u n="390" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0651">my things so</u>
<u n="392" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0651">I'm pretty confident that that would be the first place to go</u>
<u n="394" who="S0282">okay <pause dur="short"/> and then so then</u>
<u n="395" who="S0651" trans="overlap">it's it's a complex picture and argument to make isn't it?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0282">it is <unclear/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0651" trans="overlap">to the uninitiated</u>
<u n="398" who="S0282">it is rather <pause dur="short"/> yes cos you could go if but er</u>
<u n="399" who="S0651">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0282">oh yes mm so so the sort of area you're looking at is sort of <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> that sort of the top half of there</u>
<u n="401" who="S0651">yes</u>
<u n="402" who="S0282">the top half of that</u>
<u n="403" who="S0651">yes <pause dur="short"/> we have a shop in <anon type="place"/> where we've had for many many years we have a shop in <anon type="place"/> which we've had for not that quite that long</u>
<u n="404" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> aha</u>
<u n="405" who="S0651">er and we serve these GP practices up here by and large</u>
<u n="406" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0651">and we will certainly need to get the figures from the GP practices cos it's GP practices which erm <pause dur="short"/> which govern it all but as you can see there are because they're rural communities there are not a lot of GP practices to <trunc>s</trunc> for the population they cover and serve so they're very spread out</u>
<u n="408" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0651">cos erm it we'll get the same thing if this map showed <anon type="place"/> and things you know the <anon type="place"/> GP surgery does a lot of referrals to us which is <trunc>t</trunc> possibly a <unclear>historical appointment</unclear> kind of thing</u>
<u n="410" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh right <anon type="place"/> like yes</u>
<u n="411" who="S0651">and so when you get if you took if that was <anon type="place"/> then if that was that <anon type="place"/> and we're quite you know we get a lot of referrals and good</u>
<u n="412" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0651">relationship with <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> some people that go to <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> live there</u>
<u n="414" who="S0282">yeah I know I was <unclear>thinking</unclear></u>
<u n="415" who="S0651" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so so this becomes you know you could write a business case based around the reality of</u>
<u n="416" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0651" trans="overlap"><unclear>this</unclear> what happens for <pause dur="short"/> home to work routes home to shop routes home to GP routes home to hospice routes blah <trunc>b</trunc> home to hospital routes blah blah blah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0651">etcetera etcetera so I I'm pretty confident that that's the big strategic solution we need to solve</u>
<u n="420" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0651">because of the worries of unintended consequences of changes</u>
<u n="422" who="S0282">yeah well it's already the case in London <pause dur="short"/> I think you know with if you go to a GP surgery <unclear/> but you're over the line</u>
<u n="423" who="S0651">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0282">next door</u>
<u n="425" who="S0651">yeah and <trunc>al</trunc></u>
<u n="426" who="S0282" trans="overlap">we you didn't didn't use to have</u>
<u n="427" who="S0651">ultimately we think we should be about patient choice if they want to come to us and be under our care then that should be their prerogative really</u>
<u n="428" who="S0282">yeah no absolutely</u>
<u n="429" who="S0651" trans="overlap"><unclear>because we can service that care</unclear></u>
<u n="430" who="S0282">no well that's what people expect as well</u>
<u n="431" who="S0651" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0282">okay so and your name is known round there as well already so you've <trunc>alr</trunc> you've already got a presence of</u>
<u n="433" who="S0651">yeah yeah I</u>
<u n="434" who="S0282" trans="overlap">shops and things like that</u>
<u n="435" who="S0651">I think that erm the <trunc>f</trunc> the further you get away from erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0651">the further down you get past <anon type="place"/> although we've got a shop in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> have also got a shop in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> is probably here then</u>
<u n="438" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="439" who="S0651"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0282">oh yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0651">erm actually <anon type="place"/> the <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> has got a shop in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and they're they're they're there</u>
<u n="442" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> naughty thing get back over the boundary</u>
<u n="443" who="S0651">and so this becomes a disputed area of er for</u>
<u n="444" who="S0282">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0651"><unclear>kind of</unclear> where you go</u>
<u n="446" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="447" who="S0651">because arguably you know we're about the same distance <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="449" who="S0651"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0282">yes er er</u>
<u n="451" who="S0651" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0282">and then you said <trunc>w</trunc> you will need figures from the GP practices <pause dur="short"/> figures of</u>
<u n="453" who="S0651">well if we're yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0282" trans="overlap">how many of them how what percentage of them <unclear>there's hints</unclear> you think are going to be</u>
<u n="455" who="S0651" trans="overlap">you see we yeah <unclear>it's hindered you see</unclear> cos cos I know that the that the <pause dur="short"/> that the <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/> practice there and the <anon type="place"/> practice refer to us but I suspect that if the GP practice for <anon type="place"/> is here I wouldn't be surprised if they do refer to there</u>
<u n="456" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0651">because hospices have been <trunc>b</trunc> have grown up around a building and the truth is that we're not about a building we've probably got far more of our nurses in hospice in the home <trunc>g</trunc> active here</u>
<u n="458" who="S0282">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0651" trans="overlap">than they've got anything so buildings are just buildings so you</u>
<u n="460" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0651">you put another layer of complexity <trunc>i</trunc> is that we've got for hospice in the home in a really big way</u>
<u n="462" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="463" who="S0651">compared to other hospices <pause dur="short"/> because the research suggests that that's what people want <pause dur="short"/> so that research we said about Demos you know the number of people that want to die at home</u>
<u n="464" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0651">then we've tried to meet that by putting hospice in the home so effectively our hospice in the home is like I've got a five hundred bed virtual ward</u>
<u n="466" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="467" who="S0651"><vocal desc="laugh"/> all over the place and a significant bit of it is here</u>
<u n="468" who="S0282">but also that it's that that feels like the easier argument to make to people <pause dur="short"/> that actually if a lot of your nurses and a lot of your patients are round here <pause dur="short"/> then there will be quite a big proportion of them who get to the point where they can't be looked at</u>
<u n="469" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and we're therefore having somewhere</u>
<u n="471" who="S0651" trans="overlap">absolutely</u>
<u n="472" who="S0282">number one where you can bring their relatives for training and support</u>
<u n="473" who="S0651" trans="overlap"><trunc>a</trunc>absolutely</u>
<u n="474" who="S0282">and counselling and whatever <pause dur="short"/> and number two that if things get too tough at home you can say well actually just pop up the road</u>
<u n="475" who="S0651">yes</u>
<u n="476" who="S0282">into this unit</u>
<u n="477" who="S0651">I <trunc>s</trunc> I I would have to look at the figures on this when you say about putting my shirt on it I also pretty confident that if you took the population of nursing homes <event desc="sound of tapping on table"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0651">here</u>
<u n="480" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0651">and took them here <event desc="sound of tapping on table"/> this is less so again</u>
<u n="482" who="S0282">oh right okay</u>
<u n="483" who="S0651">there aren't enough of them I I suspect</u>
<u n="484" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0651">er <trunc>c</trunc> because it's about if you want to run a care home do it in a big <trunc>Bir</trunc> urban area <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know run it in Birmingham</u>
<u n="486" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0651"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you know and <trunc>s</trunc>so</u>
<u n="488" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0651">and so they become so it's a scarcity a supply and demand kinda model</u>
<u n="490" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0651">and so although I'm not trying to open a nursing home it is the cottage hospice idea is not the same as a satellite of here I do not want patients with complexity here we've got consultants here we've got very specialist doctors we've got very very <pause dur="short"/> that's not the people I'm thinking I'm putting in a cottage hospice it's stepdown care really <pause dur="short"/> but but the makes sense about the logic that they would rather go <unclear>kind of thing</unclear></u>
<u n="492" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but it <trunc>make</trunc> but it makes senses that the nurses who do go <pause dur="short"/> hospice in the home <pause dur="short"/> are more</u>
<u n="493" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="494" who="S0282">the staff that you want in this one <pause dur="short"/> in in a cottage hospice</u>
<u n="495" who="S0651">I think when we come to the staffing of it I think that it's existing staff that we can utilise who want to do it absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0651">but also the cottage hospice idea is <pause dur="short"/> they can call in <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're still the same patients so if they if they're out and active and they're here <pause dur="short"/> you know the the the the <trunc>s</trunc> clinical nurse specialists and the staff nurses and the healthcare assistants that serve this are <pause dur="short"/> if Mrs Smith and they visit her in her home here <pause dur="short"/> a lot and they know here anyway <pause dur="short"/> and she needs to come in <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>b</trunc>because actually she can't cope at home cos whatever her husband can't cope <trunc>sh</trunc> often a carer failure that means they can't cope</u>
<u n="498" who="S0282">yeah I know I know</u>
<u n="499" who="S0651" trans="overlap">it's not a patient failure it's a carer failure</u>
<u n="500" who="S0282">no well cos they just can't they can't just can't do it</u>
<u n="501" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0282">you can understand why they can't do it and actually the</u>
<u n="503" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0282">the <trunc>n</trunc>not just Demos report but the other reports done by that Help The Hospices thing <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc>you know one of the one of the chief barriers was because the carers just think oh shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0651">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0651"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0282">can't do it</u>
<u n="509" who="S0651">can't do it <pause dur="short"/> don't want to do it</u>
<u n="510" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="511" who="S0651">so</u>
<u n="512" who="S0282">well not don't want to but just think I I I can't how can I? how could I? what can I? I don't want to watch it I don't wanna be there I can't do this I can't do that</u>
<u n="513" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so erm what was I going to say? and sometimes actually it was interesting it's Monday today on Friday one of <trunc>h</trunc> our crisises on Friday was is we were on the run-up to Christmas that <pause dur="short"/> we needed the NHS to put five hospital beds in various places <trunc>w</trunc> been been supposed to have done it all week and their system had fallen down as it often does NHS do not put in <pause dur="short"/> the the <trunc>s</trunc> the things they should put in lifts blah blah blah blah blah beds <pause dur="short"/> erm and so we needed five beds in Arjo beds <pause dur="short"/> and then the contract</u>
<u n="514" who="S0282" trans="overlap">Arjo?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0651">er it's a big <unclear/> manufacturer of beds</u>
<u n="516" who="S0282">oh right okay</u>
<u n="517" who="S0651" trans="overlap">R R A R J O <pause dur="short"/> er but the NHS hadn't got them and they subcontract to Arjo direct and their engineer was off sick so they hadn't put in these five beds</u>
<u n="518" who="S0282">gosh</u>
<u n="519" who="S0651">one of the patients died on the Thursday so it's four beds then cos they need to go in when they need to go in</u>
<u n="520" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0651">erm and at at six o'clock on Friday we <trunc>st</trunc> I still hadn't sorted it out er by getting them in <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and so if that kinda thing happened we gotta <unclear>should actually put</unclear> put them into there</u>
<u n="522" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0651">I could put them in <pause dur="short"/> er I could I could bring them so that there wouldn't be that crisis at home <pause dur="short"/> and sometimes the NHS is just <pause dur="short"/> so poor that it makes people then they're in <trunc>s</trunc> they're in chairs or they go to John Lewis and buy a bed it's not a hospital bed <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't help it doesn't drop down it's not got <unclear>er things</unclear> to put up etcetera etcetera</u>
<u n="524" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="525" who="S0651"><unclear/> mattresses</u>
<u n="526" who="S0282">so it would just be another way that we could even if it wasn't permanent they could be in and in for a while and back out again</u>
<u n="527" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="528" who="S0651">whereas coming here we are</u>
<u n="529" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah and that weekend holiday thing</u>
<u n="530" who="S0651">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0282" trans="overlap">which of course is also the big</u>
<u n="532" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0282">the big thing</u>
<u n="534" who="S0651">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0282">where <pause dur="short"/> erm they the hospitals want you gone before the bank holiday Monday</u>
<u n="536" who="S0651">yes</u>
<u n="537" who="S0282">and the relatives think please don't send them home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0651">so I think it's the logical place to put it's where we're weakest and less known</u>
<u n="539" who="S0282" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="540" who="S0651">it's where the changes are happening er in a big way that's changing the model</u>
<u n="541" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0651">er in the NHS kinda set-up erm healthcare set-up <pause dur="short"/> er there's a new provider coming in to do the community stuff so it's a it's you know that we we'd be there by the time they kinda came in <pause dur="short"/> erm I I er in back to that consortium I really <unclear>did</unclear> jump all over the place the six hospices that serve this area we're serving poorly I think with the six of us and it could be like an end-of-life care facilitator <pause dur="short"/> I could get I could facilitate <unclear>better really</unclear> for <trunc>o</trunc> to the other hospices actually</u>
<u n="543" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0651">as part of that whole process</u>
<u n="545" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="546" who="S0651">although they I suspect they won't like it <pause dur="short"/> that the the hospices will not like me putting a cottage hospices and they'll probably see it as</u>
<u n="547" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no they probably won't</u>
<u n="548" who="S0651" trans="overlap">no they <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm pretty confident they won't</u>
<u n="549" who="S0282">yeah I know that's a tank</u>
<u n="550" who="S0651">they'll see it as competition</u>
<u n="551" who="S0282" trans="overlap">being put on their lawn yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0651">actually but whenever I've had discussions with them <pause dur="short"/> and they <trunc>c</trunc> want to talk about collaboration because <pause dur="short"/> help The Hospices is saying that there should be collaboration <pause dur="short"/> I think in reality there should be mergers and acquisitions actually</u>
<u n="553" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0651">and although they talk collaboration whenever they talk about it they go I don't know what you mean if we can have a shared understanding of this that would be great but if we can't have a shared understanding whenever you say collaboration I'm gonna say and competition because actually <vocal desc="laugh"/> sometimes we're gonna have to compete</u>
<u n="555" who="S0282">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah no nobody wants but no yeah nobody wants to be the one taking over do they?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0651">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear>I mean</unclear></u>
<u n="557" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but but and how much of this goes in the business case? is this all implicit then? <pause dur="short"/> this stuff? <pause dur="short"/> we we take</u>
<u n="558" who="S0651" trans="overlap">I don't mind</u>
<u n="559" who="S0282">we take it as read that that that that decision is kinda made that it's kinda round here?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0651">I haven't I <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>o</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc><trunc>w</trunc>we've just been speaking for what? twenty minutes?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0282">something like that I think</u>
<u n="562" who="S0651">I have articulated this</u>
<u n="563" who="S0282">no thirty-eight</u>
<u n="564" who="S0651">thirty-eight there you go cos I've talked too much and gone off at tangents there</u>
<u n="565" who="S0282">no no no no no no no this isn't</u>
<u n="566" who="S0651" trans="overlap">I <trunc>ha</trunc> I no I do I do no no no I have articulated this I think at board meetings over the last four years I've certainly had quite a lot of discussions <pause dur="short"/> which may now look to be <pause dur="short"/> one of the problems with the chairman <pause dur="short"/> to explain some of the complexities of this</u>
<u n="567" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0651">and although <pause dur="short"/> he's interested because he's the chairman <pause dur="short"/> and he sees parallels cos he's a businessman first and foremost so</u>
<u n="569" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0651">I think he understood what some of this logic was</u>
<u n="571" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0651">not sure that I've told <pause dur="short"/> enough of it to the trustees to paint the picture</u>
<u n="573" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0651">but you also need to have some strategic understanding of the statutory things</u>
<u n="575" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="576" who="S0651">and and how the third sector works to appreciate it so <pause dur="short"/> I I think we can put anything and everything in that business case and I think if we can articulate this in print for people then that would be great</u>
<u n="577" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0651">erm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0282">so it's kind of well there's a sort of future proofing</u>
<u n="580" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0282">section</u>
<u n="582" who="S0651">and I maybe I need to have those conversations more with the hospice leadership team</u>
<u n="583" who="S0282">unless you wanna blame me</u>
<u n="584" who="S0651">no <trunc>w</trunc><trunc>w</trunc> in what way?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0282">well you often ah well you know this is often the case when you buy when you bring people in to do a business case for you a business plan <pause dur="short"/> it's often so <trunc>u</trunc> <trunc>l</trunc> there is a lot of cases where people are punting an idea and they don't know if it's gonna work or not</u>
<u n="586" who="S0651">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0282">so you get your consultant shot down</u>
<u n="588" who="S0651">sure well I'll be alright then <pause dur="short"/> I'm pretty confident</u>
<u n="589" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0651">that this is where we should go but strategy gets complex doesn't it? I mean <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="591" who="S0282">well no I mean the thing is that these things may or they may not come to pass I mean if there's a revolution and we don't have the same government next time</u>
<u n="592" who="S0651" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0282">but then but then that's if there's other reasons why it it it might go there like there were lots of patients there or there were lots of nurses there there is a lack of a great big hospital there <pause dur="short"/> you know the the other reasons which are <trunc>a</trunc> practicalities then come into play as well so</u>
<u n="594" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> see the all the ones that I think that I've just articulated to you are <pause dur="short"/> if were you to have mapped them and used some business tools to map what kind of the reality of them is they're all pretty much a reality <pause dur="short"/> I could go another step about things that <pause dur="short"/> quite possibly as you said if the revolution comes <pause dur="short"/> I don't think ever <pause dur="short"/> erm <unclear>where to start that</unclear> I <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> isn't big enough to be a <trunc>s</trunc> decent county council <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't I don't think it ever has been</u>
<u n="595" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0651">and so <anon type="place"/> is always a problem for them because</u>
<u n="597" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0651">actually some government ought to come in and make sure there's only one county council <pause dur="short"/> having said that that ought to be caught up in the fact of two-tier authorities do not work</u>
<u n="599" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="600" who="S0651">so if I said to you that I think in ten years it will be the county councils that are our main stakeholder relationship person not the NHS</u>
<u n="601" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0651">then they have to be big enough and so some government's got to come in and actually make them big enough and in doing that they've got to address two-tier authorities which nobody ever has so far</u>
<u n="603" who="S0282">no no and then and that's a political hot potato isn't it?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0651" trans="overlap">it's a political hot potato but if they were to merge at some point <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> which is what they ought to do <trunc>r</trunc> in reality is <anon type="place"/> would struggle even more with some of these things so if <trunc>w</trunc>wind on ten years and think <pause dur="short"/> it's the county councils then that's another reason to be down here and make sure that you are there actually</u>
<u n="605" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that's huge though isn't it?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0651">it is it it is huge but you need economies of scale don't you?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh that's massive I mean <pause dur="short"/> how can you? <pause dur="short"/> well yeah but you know that's geographically enormous isn't it? is that that would be bigger than any other local authority? I mean I suppose it's when you say they're too small it's cos of the population</u>
<u n="608" who="S0651">it's the rural population that's diverse and</u>
<u n="609" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0651">and and and scattered as well</u>
<u n="611" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0651">but <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> makes it worse but actually in that revolution kinda thing the more likely the more blue sky thinking kinda stuff is <pause dur="short"/> the county councils have also got to get out of delivery cos too many of them have been delivering about social care</u>
<u n="613" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0651">and they don't do it cost effectively and they don't do it efficiently and they <trunc>d</trunc> so they've gotta get out of that which means being bigger and changing completely because actually they're the commissioners they're contract managers of stuff</u>
<u n="615" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0651">and but that more blue sky and it's more further on it's not something</u>
<u n="617" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah although that no plenty more opportunity for the private sector there</u>
<u n="618" who="S0651">yeah which I think is what's gonna happen the truth is like the <trunc>h</trunc>health is really I wouldn't be surprised to see Virgin Healthcare <trunc>deliv</trunc> look bid for that bid</u>
<u n="619" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0651">they do it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0282" trans="overlap">with a thousand a thousand carers over the whole of <anon type="place"/> of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that but that's probably not it's not easy to write that one in cos then people go but but but but the stuff we've spoken about so far is easy enough to write into the bid to go this is why we're going down into <pause dur="short"/> into this CCG as our first cottage hospice</u>
<u n="623" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0651">with the intention of doing something again on the edges of our patch later <pause dur="short"/> there's also just you know a a a a <unclear>this has become a</unclear> <trunc>bain</trunc>brain dump now really <pause dur="short"/> we've already made the move away from being a building cos I constantly say yeah hospices aren't about a building they're about a philosophy of care</u>
<u n="625" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="626" who="S0651">and we all do that as hospices then we show pictures of buildings to <trunc>reass</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> to reaffirm that we're about buildings <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but we're not and <trunc>a</trunc>also the hospice in the home has moved us away from being about buildings but in public perception we're still about buildings</u>
<u n="627" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0651">and my fellow chief execs of hospices</u>
<u n="629" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><trunc>ex</trunc> ah well then perhaps this is where Macmillan has got the <pause dur="short"/> the rush on the hospices because it's they're about lovely ladies</u>
<u n="630" who="S0651">they are indeed and don't don't have to have a building I agree</u>
<u n="631" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="632" who="S0651">so I think you need both though</u>
<u n="633" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0651">cos you do need to be able to bring people in that's why I said in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="636" who="S0651">Virgin Healthcare deliver everything that we deliver except the inpatient unit and the reason they don't want to do that is cos it's expensive you can't make money out of it <pause dur="short"/> it's not cost effective <pause dur="short"/> so you do always need a building I believe</u>
<u n="637" who="S0282">and who is gonna give money to Virgin? <pause dur="short"/> actually?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0651">well yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0282">I mean</u>
<u n="640" who="S0651">so I think you need a building but it's</u>
<u n="641" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="642" who="S0651">it's <unclear>just a lot about</unclear> building but having said that my fellow it's interesting there are two <anon type="place"/>s there's the <anon type="place"/> there where's <anon type="place"/> on here then? that?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0282">it's a little funny lump</u>
<u n="644" who="S0651">oh it's here sorry that's that's here right down here</u>
<u n="645" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0651">it's interesting that <anon type="place"/>'s got a <anon type="place"/> as well so <anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/> there's a <anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0282" trans="overlap">are they different? <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> different?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yes totally different they're all independent</u>
<u n="649" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but the same <anon type="place"/> originally probably</u>
<u n="650" who="S0651">yes</u>
<u n="651" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="652" who="S0651">but they yeah I'm sure they were this is interesting that they have just outgrown their building which is quite a nice building but they've decided then they're gonna close and sell off that building and building and build a brand new building <pause dur="short"/> so they're all sticking to buildings and we're not doing buildings despite coming to <unclear>a</unclear> cottage hospice we're coming to cottage hospice because we've grown hospice in the home to such an extent <pause dur="short"/> that it's an increase in beds in a stepdown way I think it I'm confident it fits into a bigger model jigsaw model really <pause dur="short"/> er but that's not what most people are doing they're sticking to buildings this <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0651">moved out of a perfectly serviceable but old building to a brand new offsite <pause dur="short"/> architect design winning kind of thing they're still sticking to buildings</u>
<u n="655" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0651">they're they're not going in to hospice in the home kind of territory <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0282">but that's a funding strategy isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> you can always you know in a way</u>
<u n="658" who="S0651">get raise the money for it</u>
<u n="659" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you're doing building works you can always get money for building works</u>
<u n="660" who="S0651">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0282" trans="overlap">as long as you don't go bust doing it but yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0651"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> our nearest neighbour here that covers and would see itself as covering most of this this CCG</u>
<u n="663" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0651">has I don't think any hospice in the home any community care at all</u>
<u n="665" who="S0282"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> what?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0651"><anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0651">and it's called actually <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> hospice and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="670" who="S0651">so it's not even putting itself as a hospice and if you go actually you could go and visit there and should go and visit there actually <pause dur="short"/> is it's here and <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>con</trunc>continuing care's interesting so if you go to visit them</u>
<u n="671" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0651">they've just put a lot of money into a building too <pause dur="short"/> they've got like half of it is a hospice and the other side of it is continuing care <pause dur="short"/> so we need to</u>
<u n="673" who="S0282" trans="overlap">what do they mean <trunc>con</trunc>? what? sorry what is continuing care?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0651">yes well I there's a separate paper if I haven't sent you that paper I need to send you that paper about NHS continuing care</u>
<u n="675" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="676" who="S0651">because one of the income streams to support the revenue <pause dur="short"/> on our cottage hospice will be NHS continuing care</u>
<u n="677" who="S0282">oh <pause dur="short"/> right is this where you have your own budget?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0651">erm</u>
<u n="679" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="680" who="S0651">it's kind of where you have your own budget so it gets</u>
<u n="681" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><unclear>you can you can buy and <trunc>s</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="682" who="S0651">it gets far too complex actually</u>
<u n="683" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm okay</u>
<u n="684" who="S0651">but some hospices have gone for NHS continuing care money in a big way so if you get a <trunc>d</trunc> when you get that diagnosis <pause dur="short"/> about a terminal illness then you can apply for all your social care funding stuff</u>
<u n="685" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0651">with your <trunc>p</trunc> and a personal budget if they give a personal budget</u>
<u n="687" who="S0282" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="688" who="S0651">yeah?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0651">of course it's means tested so lots of people in well in <anon type="place"/> don't get very much around social care</u>
<u n="691" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0651">er but it's <trunc>to</trunc> run totally separate to the NHS which runs NHS continuing care <pause dur="short"/> of with the criteria seems to me to be very complicated and I can't understand erm I can't understand the complexity of it so people don't know why they get it and why they don't get it etcetera etcetera but often people with a terminal illness can get fast tracked and get NHS continuing care money <pause dur="short"/> which can then provide a huge care package for them for at home now often they use the same care <trunc>nurs</trunc><trunc>n</trunc> care and nursing agencies as the social care budgets do</u>
<u n="693" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="694" who="S0651">but it's a pot of money <pause dur="short"/> which you can get on a weekly basis</u>
<u n="695" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0651">as a patient particularly <pause dur="short"/> with a terminal illness in your last year of life</u>
<u n="697" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="698" who="S0651">and we as a hospice have never really tried to get into <trunc>NS</trunc>NHS continuing care</u>
<u n="699" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="700" who="S0651">but with the cottage hospice I want to and I'm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0651">going to have the new nursing director <pause dur="short"/> when he starts in January already get to look at NHS continuing care because we should claim NHS continuing care for our hospice in the home</u>
<u n="703" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but the <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0651">they already have gone for it in a big way really</u>
<u n="705" who="S0282" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> oh <trunc>g</trunc> they're they're gonna be really cross with you then</u>
<u n="706" who="S0651">they're gonna be very cross <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think <pause dur="short"/> but it is part of the income stream I think it's about a hundred and thirty-seven pounds a week I don't know that for sure cos it</u>
<u n="707" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="708" who="S0651">differs different places <unclear>and the</unclear></u>
<u n="709" who="S0282" trans="overlap">hundred and <trunc>th</trunc> whole hundred and thirty-seven pounds a week?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah hundred <trunc>p</trunc> whole thirty-seven pounds</u>
<u n="711" who="S0282" trans="overlap">crikey that must buy you such a lot</u>
<u n="712" who="S0651" trans="overlap">but but I could be wrong about that so I'm kind of erm it might be a day for all I know <pause dur="short"/> but we need to look at it</u>
<u n="713" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0651">in fact it'd probably make more sense if it was a day wouldn't it? <pause dur="short"/> cos actually if you're going into a</u>
<u n="715" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><trunc>w</trunc>well</u>
<u n="716" who="S0651">cos it's supposed to pay for you to go in that care home <pause dur="short"/> and cut through it sorry <pause dur="short"/> the nursing home you'll have to get into that one as well yeah? care home is really about social care and is far less medical intervention a nursing home has nurses has to be registered and <trunc>t</trunc> and takes that money so it's probably hundred and thirty-seven pounds a day</u>
<u n="717" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0651">erm but we don't claim it well enough as a hospice and that knocks onto another issue about hospice in the home so often <pause dur="short"/> we're going to look after people as hospice in the home <pause dur="short"/> and they've got NHS continuing care so the agency goes in then <pause dur="short"/> looks after them and does various things for them and claims the money and we just go in and add value without claiming any money against that and I want to break that cycle</u>
<u n="719" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="720" who="S0651">and I particularly want to break the cycle when they're coming into a cottage hospice <pause dur="short"/> most people coming out of a cottage hospice should be in receipt of NHS continuing care <pause dur="short"/> we do sometimes claim it here in the inpatient unit but very rarely</u>
<u n="721" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="722" who="S0651">because we're not long term it's not like they're gonna be in the nursing home for six weeks they're not supposed to be here for six weeks so we very rarely claim it but sometimes we claim it</u>
<u n="723" who="S0282">oh right but so the reason you don't is because it's a long-winded</u>
<u n="724" who="S0651" trans="overlap">you have to claim it <pause dur="short"/> you have to claim it</u>
<u n="725" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><unclear>route</unclear> and somebody might be here for five days so you think well by the time we've claimed it</u>
<u n="726" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yes <unclear>if you want to</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> you have to absolutely <pause dur="short"/> but the funny thing is I don't think it stops the clock ticking so the agency that's not caring for them at home gets a hundred and thirty-seven pounds a day for nothing cos they're not sending their people in to look after them</u>
<u n="727" who="S0282">oh crikey right</u>
<u n="728" who="S0651" trans="overlap">so it's a bit of a mess that and I will have that unpicked before you start so that we have the position clear about it</u>
<u n="729" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0651">but I do want I don't want to pull people into a cottage hospice and not claim the money that's <pause dur="short"/> available from the statutory services as NHS continuing care</u>
<u n="731" who="S0282">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="732" who="S0651">that enough? <pause dur="short"/> it's more than enough for your <trunc>ta</trunc> <unclear>you having a look at that tape?</unclear></u>
<u n="733" who="S0282" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> well if I ever make any sense of this again it would be a miracle</u>
<u n="734" who="S0651">oh of course yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0282">but <pause dur="short"/> no I can listen to it again though this is the <trunc>advan</trunc> mind you they still</u>
<u n="736" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0282">used to do this for interviews</u>
<u n="738" who="S0651" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="739" who="S0282">in the past okay that's <pause dur="short"/> right okay but erm <pause dur="short"/> okay no let's leave it there for the minute</u>
<u n="740" who="S0651" trans="overlap">that was just about a rationale to go there wasn't it that location?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0651">but it wasn't</u>
<u n="743" who="S0282">well no no no no but it's <trunc>ol</trunc> it's all the</u>
<u n="744" who="S0651" trans="overlap">it was more</u>
<u n="745" who="S0282">the background <trunc>inf</trunc> and I can now sound intelligent when I talk to other people about it</u>
<u n="746" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0282">so erm <pause dur="short"/> but you said that you didn't think it was a new building <pause dur="short"/> is that because <unclear>of the new</unclear> building?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0651" trans="overlap">I think I've changed my mind about that</u>
<u n="749" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="750" who="S0651">yeah yeah I think it's probably a new building</u>
<u n="751" who="S0282">I think it's a new building</u>
<u n="752" who="S0651" trans="overlap">I didn't think it was originally <pause dur="short"/> that's my view's changing</u>
<u n="753" who="S0282" trans="overlap">why did you think it wasn't a new building?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0651">I don't know actually I was wondering where you get your decisions from isn't it about your thought processes?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0282">well no when what's-his-face what was his name? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me</u>
<u n="756" who="S0651">who?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0282">was it <trunc>P</trunc> no it was no no not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who was the other trustee that I met?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0651">you met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0651">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="761" who="S0282">when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said so you've got a picture in your head then</u>
<u n="762" who="S0651" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0282">to me</u>
<u n="764" who="S0651">yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0282">I thought oh good erm so what was the picture in your head?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0651">originally you mean or now?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm no originally</u>
<u n="768" who="S0651">I think I thought we could convert a building</u>
<u n="769" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="770" who="S0651" trans="overlap">and then and that's just I think my <pause dur="short"/> previous experiences of utilising buildings so if I think back to <anon type="place"/> <unclear>or whatever</unclear> and that building I kind of converted that building to make it what we wanted <pause dur="short"/> if I think about that <anon type="place"/> centre which was a shell of the factory from <anon type="place"/> we converted it be I didn't knock it down and build it again and I think it's my construct of buildings and what</u>
<u n="771" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="772" who="S0651">we've done with buildings</u>
<u n="773" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="774" who="S0651">or even seeing bids <unclear/> advisor trust was about conversion so newbuilds are not part of my consciousness and I think it really was as simple as that that you pull your experiences from where your experiences are really</u>
<u n="775" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><unclear>mm yeah</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="776" who="S0651">erm</u>
<u n="777" who="S0282">well I think it's possible if there's the right building</u>
<u n="778" who="S0651">yes</u>
<u n="779" who="S0282">so say if there was a disused school</u>
<u n="780" who="S0651">yes</u>
<u n="781" who="S0282">or an old or a <trunc>ho</trunc> not an old hotel but a hotel</u>
<u n="782" who="S0651">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0282">or erm <pause dur="short"/> or an <trunc>ol</trunc> or a an old <trunc>in</trunc>indeed a cottage hospital that is disused</u>
<u n="784" who="S0651">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="785" who="S0282" trans="overlap">an old NHS building that's disused</u>
<u n="786" who="S0651">if you went</u>
<u n="787" who="S0282" trans="overlap">something like that possibly</u>
<u n="788" who="S0651" trans="overlap">if you went here they're not they're not that disused but er <trunc>b</trunc> I agree we could look and we</u>
<u n="789" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0651">can also envisage that we at the moment we have a kind of erm agreement with <unclear>brackets</unclear> to find us shops that's <unclear>of <trunc>cour</trunc></unclear> we don't pay them for that we only pay them when they find something</u>
<u n="791" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="792" who="S0651" trans="overlap">but they are erm <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a lot of experience of that kind of finding things and knowing things and contact cos we're</u>
<u n="793" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="794" who="S0651" trans="overlap">building furniture warehouses and furniture shops and so when he talks about three hundred square feet he has a great construct about what three hundred square feet looks like and I don't actually</u>
<u n="795" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="796" who="S0651">I really struggle conceptually with it erm <pause dur="short"/> and so we can <trunc>o</trunc> we can cast our once we know where we're going and it this might happen quite soon <trunc>f</trunc> if you <pause dur="short"/> are accepting some of my logic around that and we get HLT to accept the logic then we could be telling people at twenty-ninth and thirtieth this is where we're going guys</u>
<u n="797" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="798" who="S0651">for the first one</u>
<u n="799" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="800" who="S0651">for the first one</u>
<u n="801" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0651">erm then we could start looking and I agree that if we found the right thing we could convert but I also need to look about the costs cos the VAT implications newbuild</u>
<u n="803" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="804" who="S0651">means it's probably better to have a newbuild <pause dur="short"/> I suspect which was another part of that erm set-up really</u>
<u n="805" who="S0282">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> twenty percent</u>
<u n="806" who="S0651">yeah and also we haven't yet decided what's in it cos when you come with your blank piece of paper <pause dur="short"/> there's lots of things like does it need a mortuary? I don't think it does cos I think we need a relationship with a funeral director but that's interesting cos it depends how big it is</u>
<u n="807" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="808" who="S0651"><trunc>b</trunc> so there's so so the the you know so the conversion versus newbuild we haven't yet decided what's in it</u>
<u n="809" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="810" who="S0651" trans="overlap">I in my construct in my head you know I kind of see that there's six rooms or whatever or five or six rooms around it are all open off the centre of a of a you know a <trunc>w</trunc> a nurses station with a kind of kitchen thing so I've got this thing in my head</u>
<u n="811" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="812" who="S0651"><trunc>u</trunc> with <trunc>a</trunc> where I always could see it <pause dur="short"/> so that also probably means newbuild not conversion really but I think if we keep our options open</u>
<u n="813" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> let's find a very large oast house</u>
<u n="814" who="S0651">an oast house that'd be good yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but then also you've got the you've also got <pause dur="short"/> the communal areas</u>
<u n="816" who="S0651">oh I agree yeah I we need I mean we don't know what they look like yet so that's another part of it</u>
<event desc="sound of phone ringing"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
