<text id="SY7T">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:10:39</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-22</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Manchester</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Going outside, times of day, sleeping, lunch/dinner, eating schedule, lounge/ bedroom, families and watching TV, reading, silence and noise, nature sounds, </topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse on the way to visit family</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0421">are we going to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s then? is he in?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">yeah well if you're not happy to go we can leave it</u>
<u n="3" who="S0421">no it's alright</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423">I can drop you home you'd rather</u>
<u n="5" who="S0421">it's alright <pause dur="short"/> I'm out now <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0423">sorry I dragged you out</u>
<u n="7" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I needed</u>
<u n="8" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0421">to change my thing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0423">you should try and get out a little bit every day</u>
<u n="11" who="S0421">why?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423" trans="overlap">instead of just being in the house all day</u>
<u n="13" who="S0421">why?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423">don't you go a bit mad never going out?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="16" who="S0423">oh</u>
<u n="17" who="S0421">I go a bit mad when I go out</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423">I noticed <pause dur="long"/> look at the time it's three o'clock</u>
<u n="19" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="20" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's gonna be dark</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0423"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> it's nearly bedtime</u>
<u n="23" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it seems late it is late though isn't it?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0423">well no it's doesn't feel late for me <pause dur="short"/> I suppose if you it depends how to judge things if you're thinking afternoon wise I suppose it's late afternoon three o'clock isn't it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0423">I suppose it depends what time you get up in the morning and what time you go to bed what time did you get up?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0421">half eight</u>
<u n="28" who="S0423">no well that's late for you isn't it? not much different to what time I got up</u>
<u n="29" who="S0421">I went to bed at like midnight</u>
<u n="30" who="S0423">oh that was late for you <unclear>then</unclear></u>
<u n="31" who="S0421">I know I couldn't sleep so I was like</u>
<u n="32" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="33" who="S0421">I</u>
<u n="34" who="S0423" trans="overlap">probably cos</u>
<u n="35" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you've been in all day</u>
<u n="37" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah no well</u>
<u n="38" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it helps you if you're going out</u>
<u n="39" who="S0421">I I think it's cos my sleeping schedule's been messed up since holiday like I'm going to bed and like I just can't sleep till about midnight every night</u>
<u n="40" who="S0423">oh right are you eating at nine o'clock?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0421">no I eat at a normal time</u>
<u n="42" who="S0423">oh do you not feel a bit hungry by night?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> do I not I have like my main meal at lunch</u>
<u n="44" who="S0423">do you not have supper at night?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0421">well we <trunc>ha</trunc> well cos we have like a big lunch and then at about <pause dur="short"/> five or six I'll have a sandwich <pause dur="short"/> erm at like dinner time</u>
<u n="46" who="S0423">is that all you have for your dinner? a sandwich?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0421">yeah but how like cos in Hungary you have your main meal at lunch</u>
<u n="48" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="49" who="S0421">so that's when I have like the dinner like that's the system we're going on at home</u>
<u n="50" who="S0423">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0421">that's the system we go on at home unless obviously like I'm at school and stuff and then I can't but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I have like my main meal with like <pause dur="short"/> potatoes or whatever for lunch <pause dur="short"/> and then for dinner it would be like a lunch so you have a sandwich</u>
<u n="52" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0421">you have less towards the end of the day</u>
<u n="54" who="S0423">suppose that makes sense that</u>
<u n="55" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that yeah I don't get hungry though like once I've had that</u>
<u n="56" who="S0423">do you not have supper or no?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0421">no <pause dur="long"/> but yeah cos like for a while I was like lying in bed and then I just didn't fall asleep till like midnight so I thought I might as well not go to bed till midnight</u>
<u n="58" who="S0423">so you're the last one in bed now?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I mean I'm in bed but I've not turned the lights off</u>
<u n="60" who="S0423">do you read?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="long"/> yeah I guess you've well you can't really sit in the lounge anyway can you?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0421">yeah but I'd never sit in the lounge ever</u>
<u n="64" who="S0423">you did <unclear/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0421" trans="overlap">when we had a lounge I literally never used it I was always in my room</u>
<u n="66" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="67" who="S0421">like no one ever used the lounge really</u>
<u n="68" who="S0423">do you have a chair in your room?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0423">is it comfortable?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0421">it's okay like it's my desk chair so but <trunc>li</trunc> I usually sit in my chair all day <pause dur="short"/> erm at my desk</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">yeah but do you not</u>
<u n="73" who="S0421" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0423">fancy kind of just spreading out on the couch and</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">lying down on the couch or something?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't know like I never <trunc>u</trunc> the only time we ever used the couch was when we were watching a film</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423">mm and what are you doing at your desk all day? work?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0421">well no but <pause dur="short"/> what am I doing at my desk? it's a good place to sit and do things <pause dur="short"/> work</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423">well yeah it feels like it if you're at a desk you feel like you should it just feels like a bit of a chore to me sitting at a desk</u>
<u n="81" who="S0421">really?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why people have lounges where it's more comfortable that's the place most people spend most of their time although I suppose teenagers now they don't they a lot of time in their bedroom</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421">because what what</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0421" trans="overlap">what do you do in the lounge? watch TV? I never watch TV</u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">well you don't have to have the TV on <unclear/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and <trunc>mam</trunc>mammy doesn't really sit in the lounge I don't think</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423">what she just sits in her bedroom as well?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0421">er although yeah like <trunc>someti</trunc> no she'll sometimes she'll be on the computer</u>
<u n="90" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0421">but she'd only really sit in the lounge when she was watching TV as well</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0421">like what what there's like nothing in the lounge you would just sit there and</u>
<u n="94" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no but it's a more comfortable place to sit isn't it I suppose</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="95" who="S0421">er when did we use the? oh yeah we also used the lounge if mam was on her laptop and I would bring my laptop down and we'd be on our laptops that's what we did in the lounge <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I suppose it's changed since I was your age</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423">that <trunc>wa</trunc> families all used to just sit in the lounge and</u>
<u n="99" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and and do what?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0423">and watch like your favourite programmes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">and things but</u>
<u n="103" who="S0421">we don't watch TV though</u>
<u n="104" who="S0423">well they say that the way people even now that do watch TV programmes it's all changed anyway cos they can watch it online and</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0423">they do their own thing they don't all sit down as a family</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but you'd all wanna watch something different</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0421" trans="overlap">anyway probably</u>
<u n="110" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's it yeah that's what they say now it's really different so</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421">must be it must have been a nightmare to all have to watch the same thing</u>
<u n="112" who="S0423">well no it's good like when you're a family and you all <trunc>wa</trunc> and you're all sat in the same room sometimes you know it's nice to be you I mean but you're not part of a big family anyway are you?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0423">but sometimes you you would have disagreements and arguments over what to watch</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0423">fights over who's got the remote control and things <pause dur="short"/> but that's all part of being part of the big family</u>
<u n="117" who="S0421">but then if you if someone was watching something that you didn't wanna watch would you not just go up and like do something else? cos then you're just sitting there watching something you don't wanna watch it's like wasting your time</u>
<u n="118" who="S0423">well it depends what it was I mean</u>
<u n="119" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0423">if it was watchable then yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0423">I suppose yeah it doesn't matter but</u>
<u n="123" who="S0421">you could do something that really enriches your experience at home</u>
<u n="124" who="S0423">like what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like read a book or you could</u>
<u n="126" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="127" who="S0421">erm I like to go on dictionary dot com</u>
<u n="128" who="S0423">we didn't have never had</u>
<u n="129" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well yeah you could read the dictionary you could</u>
<u n="130" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0421">erm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/> read the dictionary</u>
<u n="133" who="S0421">well you could read a book instead</u>
<u n="134" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't know if anyone <unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0421" trans="overlap">reading books are better reading books are good you see you could do that or you could go up and you could you could draw you could erm play with your animals you could you could do anything</u>
<u n="136" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0421">rather than just sit and watch something that you don't really wanna watch</u>
<u n="138" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0421">and you're just kind of sitting there like nah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0423">but I mean sometimes you can sit down and watch stuff but you're talking as well with other people in your family aren't you?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0421">but then nobody's really watching it cos it the people that maybe who really want to watch it are getting disturbed by the talking and the like I can't fully experience this programme <pause dur="short"/> with that <trunc>noi</trunc> I and I would be annoyed if there was something I really wanted to watch and people were just like ma ma ma ma ma I'd be like</u>
<u n="142" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0421"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0423" trans="overlap">of course although you kind of shut that out don't you? if you're interested in something you have filters in your head</u>
<u n="145" who="S0421">yeah <trunc>somet</trunc></u>
<u n="146" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that filter that out</u>
<u n="147" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but sometimes I can't and I'm just like be quiet because like erm I could never read in like a noisy environment and I just I just can't and I'm just like I need silence please <vocal desc="laugh"/> stop talking</u>
<u n="148" who="S0423">yeah I think I could filter it out cos I used to take books on things like when you're travelling on trains and</u>
<u n="149" who="S0421">I find that</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="151" who="S0421" trans="overlap">quite hard</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423">on the tube and</u>
<u n="153" who="S0421">I just like silence</u>
<u n="154" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you you know if you get immersed in a book it everything just fades into the background</u>
<u n="155" who="S0421" trans="overlap">silence is good <pause dur="short"/> silence is golden</u>
<u n="156" who="S0423">well it's good that you can manage to enjoy silence most people hate it don't they?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> noise in the background</u>
<u n="159" who="S0421" trans="overlap">most people are like I need noise yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0421">and I'm just like mm <pause dur="short"/> although I do like occasionally nature sounds in the background do you like nature sounds? have I told you? I like nature sounds</u>
<u n="162" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what on a CD or something?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0423">oh right I <trunc>d</trunc> I I I like when it's when nature is natural</u>
<u n="165" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0423">I'm not quite sure I could sit and listen to it <unclear/> not part of what it's</u>
<u n="167" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like like you can get on Youtube ten hours of rain noise and it's just ten hours of rain or like ten hours of forest sounds ten hours of like it's usually</u>
<u n="168" who="S0423" trans="overlap">why ten hours?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's usually ten hours so you can just have it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="171" who="S0421">going on like for a long <trunc>ti</trunc></u>
<u n="172" who="S0423" trans="overlap">be a bit odd on a sunny day outside</u>
<u n="173" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0423">and you just listen to like</u>
<u n="175" who="S0421">I know I do I don't know</u>
<u n="176" who="S0423">do you put the rain</u>
<u n="177" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0423" trans="overlap">on do you?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0421">it's good or something like a stream with like birds</u>
<u n="180" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that's good as well <pause dur="long"/> it's a bit of white noise</u>
<u n="182" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="183" who="S0421">it's good it's like</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0421">it's like relaxation or like focus <pause dur="short"/> be either one if you need to focus on something</u>
<u n="186" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I suppose people who who want to they find it relaxing the sound of running water and things</u>
<u n="187" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0423" trans="overlap">don't they? cos it's supposed to be <unclear/> that's fair enough</u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">because sometimes like even classical music it's like you get a bit involved with it so</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like just rain water or something is is good</u>
<u n="192" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
