<text id="SYG9">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:19</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-02-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A pub, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Travelling in the EU </topics>
		<activity>Travelling in the EU </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">sorry</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">think we were talking about uh to get</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">sorry I was just I was saying about <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>im</trunc></u>
<u n="4" who="S0115" trans="overlap">to get we were talking a little bit about politics weren't we? Oh in</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">I was talking about immigration</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">the uh the ID scans um</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">I dunno what it's like in <pause dur="short"/> like in Europe there's not really any problem is there?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">that's a  that's a  hell of statement In Europe there's not really a problem is there?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> What I mean is I think can you still travel like within Europe with just your driving licence?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh well yeah cos Europe's a</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos before you used to be able to travel with just a photo ID</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Europe is a  is a  coast guard you know uh border <trunc>c</trunc> control nightmare isn't it because you've got so many different little countries</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115">with their own cultures and languages and people and there's loads of</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">it's really near to the Middle East it's near to Africa</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">it's near to Russia the the the the there's all potentially dangerous sources of uh illegal immigrants or terrorism or blah blah you know</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">but I'm sure you used to be able to travel just with your</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and so it's a real nightmare like</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037">if you're an EU citizen I'm sure you could travel just with like photo ID like with your driving licence <pause dur="short"/> or your ID card if the country had that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if that's still the case now</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> well uh actually cos me and <pause dur="short"/> when I  when I  was living in uh in Berlin um me and my parents were travelling</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">and my parents were were you know kind enough to drive me to Berlin from England so we had to go</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115">we had to go in the Channel Tunnel you know through uh France but into Holland and presumably into Belgium as well on the way to Holland</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">stopped in Utrecht <pause dur="short"/> that was just like a thing that we developed</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">stayed in Utrecht and then <pause dur="short"/> so we did that now um that journey uh obviously we one two three four five countries there so <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> do you get stopped in <trunc>ev</trunc>? No you certainly don't get <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I think within the EU you don't get stopped</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">uh because Poland's in the EU now <pause dur="short"/> we did get checked quite <pause dur="short"/> when I travelled to Poland on the train there was quite a lot of like kerfuffle</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">and Poland and Germany history are slightly resisting of each other <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> well there was on the night train wasn't they? They took our passports away for a while <pause dur="short"/> remember?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> poland and Germany gives you quite a bit of like <pause dur="short"/> they they they do give you quite a bit of a check</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037" trans="overlap">when we travelled on the night <trunc>pl</trunc> night train they they</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">D'you remember that when they took our passports for like fifty minutes and I was like I hope they bring them back</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">yeah I mean there's there's cos I remember some friends of mine when I was in Berlin some friends of mine travelled down it's not that far to Prague <pause dur="short"/> and uh they travelled on the train and they got like properly like stopped and forced to wait for like two hours or three hours or something and so they missed the</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">they the trip the return trip or something got totally um</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>Cance</trunc> yeah screwed</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115" trans="overlap">totally screwed cos they they were delayed and <pause dur="short"/> they checked the border between Germany and Czech Republic <trunc>appar</trunc> at that time was was a real</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">uh I mean and this post like this isn't the  this isn't the  Cold War any more this was like two thousands you know the noughties</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I remember when I went <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> but I remember when I went to um</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">it I tell you why it's because they were Greek nationals <pause dur="short"/> adding adding complexity you see</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>Poss</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">and I remember when I was in uh going to Szczecin from Berlin with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going on the train <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> like they were like the Germans were like um <foreign lang="ger">Sie fahren nach Hause</foreign> cos they they see that we're English</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">so they assumed that we were going home</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115">to to Britain via</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">from Poland to <trunc>Ger</trunc> to Germany <pause dur="short"/> um which we weren't <pause dur="short"/> uh but</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037" trans="overlap">on a jolly</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they were like <pause dur="short"/> they were thinking where they from? England <pause dur="short"/> why they</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> whey they were</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115" trans="overlap">where where are they going? Why are they going there?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115">they like <pause dur="short"/> it was important you know to them like they're paid to basically try and figure out why people are going places</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's their job <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">and it's certainly much worse out of the EU</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">uh in terms of <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know when I was in <trunc>S</trunc> uh when I was in Switzerland um <pause dur="short"/> we were going to Austria <pause dur="short"/> in the car <pause dur="short"/> and like the people who I was with said to me like Just don't speak and like they take your passport but like <pause dur="short"/> the car will get stopped and they'll look in and they'll speak <pause dur="short"/> but like if you just don't speak to them they'll not know that you aren't Swiss <pause dur="short"/> cos if they know that you aren't Swiss they'll have you out the car they'll wanna know where you're going and what you're doing and what your plans are</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I um <pause dur="short"/> that sort of thing is quite a <trunc>b</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> like feigning ignorance is quite a big uh</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so they said like just stay stay quiet like just say like you know <foreign lang="ger">Ja ja</foreign> whatever</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115">and uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> <foreign lang="ger">Oh ja</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> and um <pause dur="short"/> then it was fine</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I think that <pause dur="short"/> think that my dad got  my dad got  like properly frisked when he was on his own you see</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">he was travelling to to pick me up on the return uh from Paris to take me back home to England for Christmas and um <pause dur="short"/> they they gave it was like he had an estate he was driving a Vauxhall Vauxhall estate car and it was like uh probably quite a lot of random boxes you know and he he got  he got  fully like everything taken out</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> on his own <pause dur="short"/> like I was <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I don't <pause dur="short"/> but I think like I don't mind that it's annoying <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> it's annoying</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he's just got that sort of look</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> it's annoying but</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you can <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037">I think <pause dur="short"/> I don't really mind like oh</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh I think we we it's one of them things where you gotta wait for better technology to come <pause dur="short"/> like better technology you can scan scan the car somehow <pause dur="short"/> sniff it <pause dur="short"/> get a sniffer</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they do do that though <pause dur="short"/> cos you like all those border <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that that that that little weird that uh bee machine that I saw like</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">the what? Oh the sniffing bees <vocal desc="laugh"/>? Oh you were telling me about that</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the bee machine <pause dur="short"/> it was uh one of the strangest most amazing scientific that I'd seen for quite some time</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> d'you want some cream?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">the the bee machine <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> nothing less than than sniffing bees</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ooh sorry <pause dur="short"/> that's crazy</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">uh in a box that looks like a little hand held vacuum</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">but I've <trunc>t</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the <pause dur="short"/> but it's trained trained bees trained to sniff for drugs in little tiny boxes</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> you told me</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115">in uh  in a  in a vacuum cleaner type</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">it is crackers</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">in the little compartments <pause dur="short"/> they put them they sat the bees in like they strapped them up like like like astronauts or something</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0115" trans="overlap">these bees sat in the <pause dur="short"/> put seatbelts on them and like <pause dur="short"/> more or less there's they harness them in little little</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">just imagine a bee that with its head popping out the top <pause dur="short"/> it's it's just surreal it's just amazing but anyway that that little box the highly trained <vocal desc="laugh"/> bees can can scan for like coke and uh uh heroin and stuff like <trunc>the</trunc> these bees had been um</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it is weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">uh so anyway yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">but I think</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">uh better technology will allow to do better checking with minimal uh discomfort to the uh</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115">to the driver</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037">I saw the  I saw the  thing <pause dur="short"/> sorry you finished?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037">I saw a thing with um you know like watching all those like border patrols and um <pause dur="short"/> what they called? Sniffing sniffing dogs and that</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just just waiting room vision</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037" trans="overlap">waiting room telly</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">like <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">but <pause dur="short"/> in that one they have a thing where like you know if they have like stowaways in a  in a  big lorry? They can put like a thing in and see if there's any carbon dioxide in because obviously people breathe out <pause dur="short"/> they've got like a probe and they can like say if it's a lorry full of like bog rolls or something <pause dur="short"/> anything baked beans</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115">oh right to detect if it's full of illegal immigrants?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they've got like a probe and they put it in and if there's any like if there's carbon dioxide in there then they're like oh and then they have to get get all the baked beans off the lorry and then find all the</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0037">immigrants or whatever</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115">well um <pause dur="short"/> of course with every technological advance then there comes uh the the increase in intelligence of the  of the  uh</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">of the criminal to uh <pause dur="short"/> to to counter  to counter  the advance so like uh</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well they were saying about um</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115">so if you you were saying that carbon dioxide well they're gonna have to create a uh put an air conditioner in the  in the  <trunc>f</trunc> in the lorry</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well they do <pause dur="short"/> where they put like they try and like cover themselves in bags and stuff</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115">well they could breathe into like a</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115">like a pipe and that could be connected <pause dur="short"/> that could pipe outside or something <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037" trans="overlap">try and <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think they've <trunc>s</trunc> they've tried all them sort of things but also um</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037">did you hear about the news about those um <pause dur="short"/> like now you're gonna be able to like text someone <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> text someone money?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115">oh yeah I saw uh like Barclays were doing it <pause dur="short"/> was that an advert or on the news or something?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037">it was on the news</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> barclays were doing it so that <pause dur="short"/> but they were saying that actually <trunc>the</trunc> these things are already in place in in countries that we might not have assumed to be more advanced than us but <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah Africa yeah <pause dur="short"/> mobile phones are really popular in Africa</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115">yeah they mentioned Kenya actually <pause dur="short"/> mobile phones are popular across the world <pause dur="short"/> I think it's because they're quite cheap to make and buy</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115">and they're really essential for <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they're now they are <pause dur="short"/> d'you remember Saved By The Bell?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> sounds like it might be more <pause dur="short"/> did that have a guy in it called Cory?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037">ah <pause dur="short"/> saved By The Bell like</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115">did it? Didn't have a guy called Cory in it?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037">zack was the main character</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">was that? It's not Cory or something?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037">zack <pause dur="short"/> he used to go <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> When I wake up in the morning and <unclear/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is that that little like kid with curly black hair?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and then there was like Kelly Kapowsky <vocal desc="laugh"/> who was like the brown-haired sort of one</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115">is it's a school drama right?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037" trans="overlap">then <pause dur="short"/> then and Screech</u>
<u n="148" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is it like a school? Is it like a little kid with dark curly hair?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mr Belding <pause dur="short"/> screech <pause dur="short"/> screech Powers</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what? Sorry?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037">screech</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037">that's what he was called <pause dur="short"/> screech</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115">the little kid with curly</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037">kind of geek one</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115">just uh like he looked like he'd be in like some Stephen Spielberg film or something</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037">I don't know but yes</u>
<u n="158" who="S0115">he's the <unclear/> kid is in the in uh the <trunc>p</trunc> The Princess Bride with</u>
<u n="159" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but then Mr Belding <pause dur="short"/> but thingy-bob from that</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115">yes</u>
<u n="161" who="S0037">um she played like a sort of geeky girl and that went on to be in like Showgirls</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">what's that?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037">is it Showgirls? It's like a  like a  stripping stripper sort of film about strippers?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I dunno what that is <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="165" who="S0037">she got curly hair?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0115">mm I don't really <pause dur="short"/> what are you uh I don't know what you're talking about</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037">aw we're talking cross purposes</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115">oh right I don't I just don't know um <pause dur="short"/> saved By The Bell is like a  like a  school drama is it?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>Sca</trunc> Saved By The Bell was like a <trunc>ear</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> early nineties school American school</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115" trans="overlap">american <pause dur="short"/> bit like Grange Hill maybe? But</u>
<u n="171" who="S0037">I suppose <pause dur="short"/> like an American version</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115">Cos they don't wear uniforms over there do they?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> that's true <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but anyway</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115" trans="overlap">kind of like the uniform cos I so I was always so badly dressed</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037" trans="overlap">this is <trunc>bes</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I'm getting <trunc>s</trunc> really far off the point but um</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037">in Saved By The Bell like Zack had like a mobile phone <pause dur="short"/> but obviously this was like late eighties early nineties and it was like in a suitcase type thing like a massive like</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like a satellite phone?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037">like a massive brick with like a massive antenna</u>
<u n="180" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that that went on his back and had like a receiver that you just had to pick up from the</u>
<u n="181" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was really big and he was like Hello like I remember sort of <pause dur="short"/> thinking it was really <pause dur="short"/> but you're right <trunc>mo</trunc> mobile phones now you can buy them for nothing <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> five quid or something</u>
<u n="182" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah and and I know that they're really popular with um militias</u>
<u n="183" who="S0037">with what?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0115">militias <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>mil</trunc> militia?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> right right</u>
<u n="186" who="S0115"><trunc>Ar</trunc> armed people who take money to carry out military operations</u>
<u n="187" who="S0037">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0115">uh what would you call them? <trunc>In</trunc> insurgents or terrorists or</u>
<u n="189" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah right <pause dur="short"/> but everyone likes mobiles though <pause dur="short"/> like I said</u>
<u n="190" who="S0115">like they use the mobiles to to like obviously coordinate themselves and</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037">but like <pause dur="short"/> they're snooped on aren't they? All like all those sort of phone calls are I'm sure of it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0115">uh they can be but but but not <pause dur="short"/> maybe not fast enough though</u>
<u n="193" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think if they know that you're a target like they follow you don't they?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115">yeah um</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037">they they would <trunc>tra</trunc> they would trace all your calls if they thought you were a threat?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115">yeah the the the monitor will like <pause dur="short"/> all all mobile phone calls are um ultimately able to be monitored aren't they?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I again like I don't think I've got a</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but it would depend on the  on the  politics of like <pause dur="short"/> I mean for example <pause dur="short"/> if you're Osama Bin Laden</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and you're living in Pakistan and uh you're making some texts sending a text <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="201" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Did he really do texting?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0115">got got um <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0037">re plans <pause dur="short"/> lOL <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0115">yeah like uh <pause dur="short"/> See you uh at at the  at the  uh rally</u>
<u n="205" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well he didn't go anywhere</u>
<u n="206" who="S0115">ay?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0037">compound <pause dur="short"/> come round to my compound tonight <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0115">had to burn rubbish again <pause dur="short"/> sad face <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's uh <pause dur="short"/> burn his rubbish <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> we used to do that I mean</u>
<u n="211" who="S0037" trans="overlap">my wives are busy making dinner <pause dur="short"/> lOL <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0037">it's probably really distasteful making sort of Bin Laden text jokes</u>
<u n="214" who="S0115">anyway yeah if you're Ben Bin Laden uh you're in Pakistan so Pakistani you know Pakistan Telecom</u>
<u n="215" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0115">uh is uh it's got your uh your text</u>
<u n="217" who="S0037">your details</u>
<u n="218" who="S0115">obviously <trunc>de</trunc> um</u>
<u n="219" who="S0037">your number</u>
<u n="220" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and if America then wants to scan Pakistani text messages because obviously there are a hell of a lot of uh</u>
<u n="221" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0115">anti-American</u>
<u n="223" who="S0037">feelings</u>
<u n="224" who="S0115">militia in uh Pakistan <vocal desc="laugh"/> Uh so</u>
<u n="225" who="S0037">and elsewhere</u>
<u n="226" who="S0115" trans="overlap">America's then gonna have to try and buy that stuff off the telecom the perhaps and the government might say you can't have our stuff</u>
<u n="227" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0115">Cos we're a sovereign nation <pause dur="short"/> don't want you having telecom details <pause dur="short"/> then America would say okay why don't we just give you a very large amount of money</u>
<u n="229" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> here's some weapons</u>
<u n="230" who="S0115">and then they'll say okay uh we've we've thought about it and uh <pause dur="short"/> so that that's the sort of thing I imagine <trunc>ma</trunc> basically if you've you've got money on you you can get any any <trunc>t</trunc> phone details but uh</u>
<u n="231" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0115">but yeah there was I mean I heard a debate um about ID cards and there was a lot of there was some quite powerful sounding arguments against ID cards and uh</u>
<u n="233" who="S0037">I <trunc>thi</trunc> suppose my thing my worry is like I don't need an ID card and a driving licence and a passport and a European Health Insurance card and a</u>
<u n="234" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean that that's the pro argument isn't it the</u>
<u n="235" who="S0037">like if they can roll all those together into something that be fine</u>
<u n="236" who="S0115">yeah I mean no like</u>
<u n="237" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think you'd probably still have to have your passport cos they need to stamp things on it don't they but?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean <pause dur="short"/> the the essence of it is is that you've got to have</u>
<u n="239" who="S0037" trans="overlap">can your driving licence not be it though?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0115">you've gotta have a massive database but you've gotta be</u>
<u n="241" who="S0037" trans="overlap">because what information is on your driving licence like let me have a look because</u>
<u n="242" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I dunno</u>
<u n="243" who="S0037">the you only really add to need to add a few more things don't you like what have we got? Name um date of birth place of birth address signature picture <pause dur="short"/> I need to get that changed actually don't I?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0115">your your picture which is uh notoriously uh dodgy because it only has one eye visible <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="245" who="S0037">I need to get me  I need to get me  name changed</u>
<u n="246" who="S0115">yep it's it's it's not got your full title there <pause dur="short"/> it's not got your uh</u>
<u n="247" who="S0037" trans="overlap">probably have to pay though don't you? I'm not gonna pay to get it <trunc>ch</trunc></u>
<u n="248" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think we have</u>
<u n="249" who="S0037">when does it expire? It expires in twenty-fourteen <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'll just wait</u>
<u n="250" who="S0115">well yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah so</u>
<u n="251" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's bad that <pause dur="short"/> you have to get it changed every however often</u>
<u n="252" who="S0115">yeah so as we were saying I mean like <pause dur="short"/> if you wanted to drive to Germany from here you'd only get your passport checked in Britain to France</u>
<u n="253" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is that when I passed my test? When did?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you'd only  you'd ony  get your passport in um in Britain and France</u>
<u n="255" who="S0037">but what I mean is</u>
<u n="256" who="S0115">actually Britain</u>
<u n="257" who="S0037">what I was saying before was that I think you can do it with just your driving licence cos it's got your picture of your face on</u>
<u n="258" who="S0115">within the EU uh maybe you can</u>
<u n="259" who="S0037" trans="overlap">two thousand and <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> when did I pass my test?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0115"><trunc>Ma</trunc> but you wouldn't no you can't get uh get to France with just a driving licence</u>
<u n="261" who="S0037">I think you can</u>
<u n="262" who="S0115">you can get to Ireland <pause dur="short"/> it's hard enough getting to Ireland <pause dur="short"/> no you can't get to France with just a driving licence can you? Or can you?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I had a feeling that you could <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'm wrong</u>
<u n="264" who="S0115">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> I doubt <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't  I wouldn't  leave without a passport if the</u>
<u n="265" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="266" who="S0115">I think that would be  that would be  tough but well maybe you probably</u>
<u n="267" who="S0037">maybe I should change my title</u>
<u n="268" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah you can drive all the way to Germany but if if you wanted to go into uh Poland I'm pretty sure they'd they'd stop you there</u>
<u n="269" who="S0037">Cos I've only changed my name on on some things <pause dur="short"/> like I have to be careful <pause dur="short"/> like on so when I was booking my flights on Ryanair they were like Title and I was like oh I'll have to put miss because I haven't changed it on everything like I haven't changed it on my driving licence and I it's not well it doesn't have it on your passport</u>
<u n="270" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so I guess you'll just have to introduce your your new title like at some point and you'll have to</u>
<u n="271" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I need to  I need to  <trunc>ge</trunc></u>
<u n="272" who="S0115">change all your  all your  details</u>
<u n="273" who="S0037">it's not on my bank <trunc>te</trunc> cards or anything</u>
<u n="274" who="S0115">yeah I think it makes a lot of sense to put thing together but the the problem I mean some of the arguments against uh ID cards get tremendously uh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and like your blood group like you should have your blood group on there maybe in case you have an accident or <pause dur="short"/> and whether you wanna give your <trunc>do</trunc> where when you give your organs</u>
<u n="276" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah no no you see like what thing the ID is if it's implemented properly like you know using the eye scanner or a finger print scan right</u>
<u n="277" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0115">um you'd have you would have a massive database but the the the trick of it is that only the relevant information is available to each person like</u>
<u n="279" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0115">the the guy who wants your medical records like a doctor</u>
<u n="281" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0115">he can't see your criminal records</u>
<u n="283" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0115">similarly you know</u>
<u n="285" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0115">the passport guy <pause dur="short"/> customers can't see</u>
<u n="287" who="S0037">how many fillings you've got</u>
<u n="288" who="S0115">your your your medical records your dental records or whatever <pause dur="short"/> like but they can see what they need to see so <pause dur="short"/> if you had an ID database you'd have to have all of that information there linked with your fingerprints and your iris scan</u>
<u n="289" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0115">uh and everybody'd <unclear/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but they do <pause dur="short"/> they do link</u>
<u n="292" who="S0115">but they would have something very <trunc>sh</trunc> uh have to be uh very uh careful to make sure that you can't access information that you're not allowed to have</u>
<u n="293" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they do link your your fingerprints now with your passport <pause dur="short"/> cos mine mine when I went as I say when I went to America they did that there</u>
<u n="294" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0037">they'd put all your fingers on on the screen</u>
<u n="296" who="S0115">yeah I mean no I think it makes sense I mean</u>
<u n="297" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and the picture of your face and that</u>
<u n="298" who="S0115">I think you you just have to embrace that sort of the idea that uh that you're gonna have to show who you are and your birthplace but I mean obviously</u>
<u n="299" who="S0037">I don't think it's a big problem</u>
<u n="300" who="S0115">there's a lot of <pause dur="short"/> there's things associated with um <pause dur="short"/> there is risks associated because uh</u>
<u n="301" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0115">but obviously um you know with <trunc>D</trunc> there's things like DNA evidence at crimes and um</u>
<u n="303" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0115">you know you could appear to be uh present at the scene of a crime that there's some DNA but in reality you weren't and stuff like that and uh so um</u>
<u n="305" who="S0037">I'm sure they must take those things into account</u>
<u n="306" who="S0115">things like like drunken like a lot of police patrol looking for drunkenness don't they in the the town centres or whatever but uh</u>
<u n="307" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0115">of course you you could do something when you were or when you were a teenager or something and like you obviously wouldn't want</u>
<u n="309" who="S0037">everyone to always be on your record</u>
<u n="310" who="S0115">uh you wouldn't wanna  you wouldn't wanna  criminal record you know</u>
<u n="311" who="S0037">maybe that would be a deterrent though like not to do stuff</u>
<u n="312" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="313" who="S0037">to know that it would follow you around for all your life</u>
<u n="314" who="S0115">well yeah uh <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I think there'd be a lot of <pause dur="short"/> I think if you  if you're  if you're drunk then <pause dur="short"/> You know that's one thing but the but uh it's actually a slightly different question because that's a question of whether the State is gonna prosecute you <pause dur="short"/> if you if you've basically</u>
<u n="315" who="S0037">yeah exposed yourself</u>
<u n="316" who="S0115">bared your  bared your  bottom to people on the street</u>
<u n="317" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0115">late at night when you were drunk or something do you then like does the state decide to prosecute for that but they they probably but cos it's a silly thing to prosecute someone for but that sort of incident</u>
<u n="319" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> how many times have you seen that though like when you're out and about people just doing that sort of naughty things</u>
<u n="320" who="S0115">have some sort of <pause dur="short"/> mooning uh yeah a fair amount I mean</u>
<u n="321" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or like having wees up sides of</u>
<u n="322" who="S0115">well that's a <trunc>n</trunc> that's a  that's a  necessity I suppose you know</u>
<u n="323" who="S0037">I know but</u>
<u n="324" who="S0115">things have got to come out somehow uh but <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean that's what the the <trunc>p</trunc> the public and they try to get public urinals and stuff don't they?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0115">uh and then the the the uh portaloos is it the the?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0037" trans="overlap">where was it we saw where they have that?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0115">the the Portaloos the you know</u>
<u n="329" who="S0037">where was it we saw that had like?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0115">um in Soho I think they have like the <trunc>ur</trunc> they had urinals that sort of</u>
<u n="331" who="S0037">popped up that's right yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0115" trans="overlap">pop pop up out of the ground <pause dur="short"/> think it I think that's Soho</u>
<u n="333" who="S0037" trans="overlap">at night</u>
<u n="334" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean <trunc>i</trunc> it's I mean I think everyone's everyone's been there when they when you</u>
<u n="335" who="S0037" trans="overlap">when you need the loo? It's horrible isn't it? It's a horrible feeling</u>
<u n="336" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the toilet and uh <pause dur="short"/> like uh desperately trying to find somewhere <pause dur="short"/> but uh</u>
<u n="337" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah it's not very nice</u>
<u n="338" who="S0115">uh no like well yeah so so I think but it's it's a tough uh <pause dur="short"/> tough thing to do the IDs but I think there's the sentiment overall is against it because of  because of  the sort of sensationalist things that people</u>
<u n="339" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think  I think  the thing that put me off uh the plans that were introduced a while ago was that they were like oh and it's gonna be eighty pounds or whatever <pause dur="short"/> so I'm not paying any more <pause dur="short"/> I paid like <pause dur="short"/> paid eighty quid or whatever it is to get a</u>
<u n="340" who="S0115">for a? Eighty pounds for what? A new passport?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0037" trans="overlap">eighty quid to get a passport <pause dur="short"/> thirty-five quid to get a driving licence like <pause dur="short"/> it's just sort of <pause dur="short"/> I don't see why you should have to have to pay whatever it is to get an ID card if you already paid for this that and the other like <pause dur="short"/> unless you're gonna decommission one of the things and not have driving licence no more or anything</u>
<u n="342" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah well I think if you did it <trunc>n</trunc> you'd have to make it compulsory wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0037">mm</u>
</body>
</text>
