<text id="SYNT">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:27:28</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-15</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0266 S0272 S0273</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>New job with engineering company (education dept.); self-employment v. employed; speakers' children's jobs (engineering apprenticeship, physio, publishing, uni); marriage or not for younger people; styles of parenting and attending parents' evenings at school).</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about Jobs and Styles of Parenting over a glass of wine.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0266">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Almondsbury, Gloucestershire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0272">
				<exactage>56</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Farnborough, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Wooten-under-edge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>education liaison manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0273">
				<exactage>60</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Liverpudlian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0266">so you were telling me what about work your new job or your old job for three years</u>
<u n="2" who="S0272">yeah well it's three years now I've been working at that job yeah so lots of things I prefer erm lots some things I don't so I spent nearly twenty years being self employed so the transition from going from being self employed to being employed was actually mm in some ways difficult and some ways easy erm so that was suddenly having to be at the most difficult was having to be at my desk at eight o'clock every morning I hated that cos that's the latest you can start at <anon type="place"/> so I used to have flexibility on when I started when I was self employed so that wasn't quite so easy but you know like anything you get into a routine and you get used to it erm and we do finish at lunchtime on a Friday because you work four longer days and half a day on a Friday and that's quite nice I don't miss at all erm looking constantly thinking I've got to find new work that was I I didn't realise until I didn't have to do it anymore quite how stressful that was always looking over your shoulder thinking what's the next thing that's coming along and erm <trunc>con</trunc> you know going networking and you know having to be nice all the time</u>
<u n="3" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0272">and you know sort of all of those sort of things actually I don't miss that at all erm but I do miss a little bit of the flexibility of the job you know so you know if I suddenly wanted to have a hence you probably haven't seen me so much because I just can't stop because I can't stop and have a coffee morning or stuff like that that I used to</u>
<u n="5" who="S0273">no cos when when you're self employed you can organise it to suit yourself can't you?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="7" who="S0273">it's just whatever suits you and if you want to take time off that's fine</u>
<u n="8" who="S0272">yeah exactly well I mean I used to just plug out my diary and nobody used to know what I was doing</u>
<u n="9" who="S0273" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="10" who="S0272">really it was up to me and if I said somebody rang up and said oh do you want erm you know can you can I have an appointment then? and if I looked up no I'm having coffee with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I can't it's really inconvenient for me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0273" trans="overlap">I wish I could have persuaded <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to work on that principle</u>
<u n="12" who="S0272">er well erm yeah I'll I'll erm I mean and it's interesting I found I was very I was not very confident about doing doing that to start with when I first started but I gradually got better and better at realising that actually if you said you couldn't do it it doesn't mean to say they're gonna run away to somebody else they've often <trunc>sai</trunc> oh right okay well let's see if we can find another day that suits us</u>
<u n="13" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yeah I can't do it then</u>
<u n="14" who="S0272">exactly</u>
<u n="15" who="S0273" trans="overlap">not that I can't do it at all</u>
<u n="16" who="S0272">I can't do it at all exactly right so in the end I erm I got more confident erm about just saying to people well erm and if it was really really the only time and I was gonna lose out on that then in the end I used to say okay well let me go and speak to the person concerned see if I can move that and come back to you I'd ring you up and say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0273"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0272">can't make that coffee can you make it another time <vocal desc="laugh"/> and we'd change it but erm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0273">see this is something that annoyed me intensely with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> over the years the number of times he knows he <trunc>wan</trunc> he wants to do this or he's got this booked and he'll book something else and he booked himself into ridiculous arrangements of having to be opposite ends of the country on the same day</u>
<u n="20" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0273">consecutive days and not not just saying even if it wasn't true not just saying I can't do that day I'm already booked the number of times I <unclear/> well just tell them you can't do it</u>
<u n="22" who="S0272" trans="overlap">do it mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0273">if you had something else booked you couldn't do it</u>
<u n="24" who="S0272">that's right</u>
<u n="25" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0272">it takes years I was surprised he didn't didn't eventually get to that stage because I got forced into it on a number of occasions because it was things that the children wanted to do I was involved with something at school or something like that and I really really wanted to be there and they were sort of non negotiable really</u>
<u n="27" who="S0273" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0272">in terms of well if I lose that contract I lose it because it's actually more important to me that I'm there for the children but then what I started to realise that actually as you said it isn't wasn't that I didn't want to do it at all it was just that I couldn't do it at that time the more I erm said I can't I'm sorry I that I'm actually doing something that day I'm already booked is it possible how about this and that and the other?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0273">mm yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0272">I was surprised how often you know ninety-five percent of the time people were yeah of course that's fine</u>
<u n="31" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yeah yeah course they're in the same position often themselves so once they <unclear/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="33" who="S0273">got to make a <unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0272" trans="overlap">but he never got to that stage <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0273">oh well he did from time to time he was just so annoying the number of times be couldn't be somewhere because <unclear/> had to backed himself into a ridiculous corner</u>
<u n="36" who="S0272">mm well we all do that on occasions I wonder if he looks back and regrets that now?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0273">I don't think he'd regret it but he certainly doesn't miss it</u>
<u n="38" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0273">erm yeah he went off last week <unclear/> went on Monday evening cos he had to be wherever he was on Tuesday said oh this is just like old times don't miss it then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0272">mm yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says the same thing he doesn't miss it</u>
<u n="41" who="S0273">no it's gone it's over he not not pining for it at all</u>
<u n="42" who="S0272">yeah yeah I know it's interesting but I think that's actually quite an important thing I was talking about that with a I've made one particular friend at <anon type="place"/> and erm we were having lunch last week both of us were talking she's a little bit younger than me but both of us were talking about the fact of erm when we retire and where what we're going to do and who we'd keep up with</u>
<u n="43" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0272">in terms of that in terms of er work erm and it's quite interesting when you start to review that and I really like my job and I really like the people I work with and I really like I cos of the nature of the job I'm involved with a lot of people across the whole group and they're all really nice people</u>
<u n="45" who="S0266">so what what exactly do you do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0272">so I am responsible for all the education liaison that the company does so at the moment there is an enormous erm shortage of engineers in the UK so my role is to work with schools universities put events on and increasingly work with er at government level on this issue around shortage of of erm engineers so it's sort of divided into quarters really erm in those four areas so it's because <anon type="place"/> realise that they had to do something there was always bits that went on but nobody was coordinating it and nobody was actually giving a strategy to it nobody just knows what the other person was doing cos it's a company that works very much in silos you know they've got these fifteen sixteen divisions that all work in silos and don't very often cross fertilise so er all the education stuff that they were doing nobody knew what was happening either so it was a bit ridiculous so you'd be in contact with <anon type="place"/> and have a conversation and somebody'd say oh yes somebody from your company rang last week and we've done this this and this and you think oh well I want you to do this this and this and nobody does repeat so you know so they were all getting irritated and there's no particular <trunc>cu</trunc>cohesion and strategy with erm with schools either so that's sort of really what I do and I've just built I started absolutely nothing completely blank nobody had ever done the job before</u>
<u n="47" who="S0266">that's quite nice though isn't it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0272">so that was one of the reasons that actually decided I decided to take it in the first place because of the fact it was a bit like being your own boss because there was nobody else looking over you you could actually build it from scratch</u>
<u n="49" who="S0273">and nobody saying well so and so always used to do it this way</u>
<u n="50" who="S0272">absolutely</u>
<u n="51" who="S0273">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0272">yeah yeah so starting with that that was actually quite a refreshing thing to have actually that nobody else had done it before but it equally it was quite erm daunting</u>
<u n="53" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0272">because you had to sort of erm prove yourself if you see what I mean</u>
<u n="55" who="S0273">and the other side of that is you didn't have somebody else's experience to draw on or anybody to ask <unclear>for advice</unclear></u>
<u n="56" who="S0272" trans="overlap">exactly exactly I didn't have anybody else's experience to draw on and erm so I had to sort of build it up for myself and and the first two weeks I was there the person I report into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it happened to be a time where there was an enormous erm exhibition he he's head of communications and he's responsible for all UK erm all erm exhibitions across the world and there's a big one that happens biannually erm it was just coming up about a fortnight after I joined erm so I think he saw me for half an hour on the first day erm about erm an hour about five days later and then went away for two and a half weeks so didn't exactly give me a great deal of erm direction of what I should be doing and erm so as a result I really had to start and build it all myself and I think actually looking back if I hadn't of had that experience of being self employed I think it would have been very very difficult to do because if you're employed and a lot of people need some kind of direction because I didn't need any kind of direction cos I'd had to <vocal desc="laugh"/> work on my own for a long time so erm and luckily <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the sort of person he can be quite annoying on occasions because he can be so far the other way but he doesn't micromanage me</u>
<u n="57" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0272">and again I can't cope with <trunc>mic</trunc> being micromanaged yeah I'd go in and tell him the things he needs to know the rest of the time I get on with it so that's fine so that's what I do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0273" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so do you yeah <trunc>that</trunc>that's what you but do you actually do any training?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0272">no I don't do any training anymore the bit that I miss I do a little bit of it but of the bit that I miss is the coaching and at one point I was actually doing some training for erm they <trunc>s</trunc> they always say that they've got <anon type="place"/> always say that they've got a mentoring system for the new graduates coming in but in reality they haven't and they certainly don't give these people any training so I actually did some training for the managers and so which was lovely thank you</u>
<u n="62" who="S0266">do help yourselves</u>
<u n="63" who="S0273" trans="overlap">mm very nice</u>
<u n="64" who="S0272">there's going to be a lot of crunching in this</u>
<u n="65" who="S0273"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0266">that's alright</u>
<u n="67" who="S0272">erm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0266">fairly healthy stuff</u>
<u n="69" who="S0272">erm so</u>
<u n="70" who="S0266" trans="overlap">who doesn't like celery?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0272">no I quite like celery</u>
<u n="72" who="S0273">I'm fine</u>
<u n="73" who="S0266"><unclear>should</unclear> get some</u>
<u n="74" who="S0272">I like celery just had some in a salad actually well it's great celery because it's supposed to</u>
<u n="75" who="S0266" trans="overlap">sorry?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0272">isn't it doesn't it consume more calories to digest it than it does actually have in it all together? I think</u>
<u n="77" who="S0273">that's the theory yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0272">that's the theory yeah but whether it actually works or not</u>
<u n="79" who="S0273">erm so yeah so anyway so that's basically what I do</u>
<u n="80" who="S0266">so are you dealing with all the universities and?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0272">yep</u>
<u n="82" who="S0266">so what do you have to actually do?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0272">oh well I build up the relationships with them so that now we're doing things like <trunc>pro</trunc>projects with them erm obviously the careers fairs which I don't actually have totally responsibility for HR does that thank goodness I just go along to a few I feel like going to erm I helped redo the graduate assessment process did all that recently erm did the apprentice assessment process recently so they <trunc>co</trunc> they <trunc>co</trunc> it's quite interesting they call on me and use my HR and coaching experience quite a lot when they need it but I don't do it as on a day to day basis I suppose but I quite so that's alright I quite like doing that but I haven't really got time I wish I had more time to do the coaching side but that's the bit that's the skill I'm sort of you losing a little bit which I'd like to have the opportunity to carry on with but you can't have everything in life can you so?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0266">but you're happy?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0266">and what who who locally works there there must be a lot of people you know?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0272">mm there's quite a lot yeah but you'd be surprised how far <trunc>pa</trunc>people travel I was always under the feeling that most people just did locally but there's one guy in my office that lives in Ross and one lives in Monmouth <pause dur="short"/> wales is quite popular they people live in sort of Chepstow Newport area erm erm Gloucester</u>
<u n="88" who="S0273" trans="overlap">it's not very much further really than living here and working in Bristol</u>
<u n="89" who="S0272">no it isn't</u>
<u n="90" who="S0273">or a lot of those places it just seems</u>
<u n="91" who="S0272" trans="overlap">a lot of people</u>
<u n="92" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> <unclear>single</unclear></u>
<u n="93" who="S0272" trans="overlap">live in</u>
<u n="94" who="S0273">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0272">a lot of people live in Bristol <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0273" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0272" trans="overlap">lives in Bristol now erm <pause dur="short"/> he works for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0273" whoConfidence="low">does he?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0272">he's done he's the the he's in his third year he's at of his apprenticeship</u>
<u n="100" who="S0273">really?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0273">his third year of his apprenticeship?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0272">he's finally finally found something he loves</u>
<u n="104" who="S0273" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">and how many how many years is it altogether?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0272">four</u>
<u n="106" who="S0266">cos I thought he was working with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bike company or something</u>
<u n="107" who="S0272">no that was ages ago</u>
<u n="108" who="S0266">was it?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0272">mm he went away after that from there he went away to erm Canada and worked for six months er doing a summer season in <anon type="place"/> cos he <trunc>love</trunc> you know his bike how much he loves his biking well that's the the place to be if you're into downhill biking so in the summer working erm basically erm amazed he he didn't concuss himself which I didn't ever find out everybody else knew about it but me</u>
<u n="110" who="S0273" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0272">erm but most of the time he was alright and then he came back and erm as he as he was coming back I <pause dur="short"/> er he came back and I was starting this job and it was just so funny before we came back he said to me <pause dur="short"/> and he didn't know I was applying for this job he said to me I've been giving my future a great deal of thought mum thought my god</u>
<u n="112" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh sounds very mature</u>
<u n="113" who="S0273"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0272">I don't believe this and I'm trying to decide what I want to do and I've decided what I want to do is do an engineering apprenticeship I couldn't believe it <trunc>c</trunc> you know the job I was doing</u>
<u n="115" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0272">and he applied for loads of different ones <pause dur="short"/> and erm and it was very it that was <trunc>th</trunc>the the hardest thing I did actually cos I had to cos I couldn't get involved in it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I had to step away</u>
<u n="119" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0272" trans="overlap">from it completely so I erm I I didn't get involved and when and said to him well I can give you some support for you know interview training I mean I when I think about the kids in <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> that I've helped through getting interview training or help with their CVs and stuff and he said no I don't need you to I'll be fine I don't need it <pause dur="short"/> mm so I didn't get involved and amazingly he got the job so and he loves it absolutely loves it so <pause dur="short"/> he's found his square peg in a round hole square hole</u>
<u n="121" who="S0266" trans="overlap">do you see him every day? do you see?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0272" trans="overlap">no I don't see him at all cos he works in a completely different side <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="124" who="S0272"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't see him <pause dur="short"/> mm so I don't I hardly see him at all now he doesn't live at home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0273">how nice <vocal desc="laugh"/> got the place to yourself</u>
<u n="127" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so where where's he living?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0272"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="130" who="S0272" trans="overlap">got a lovely flat there with <trunc>s</trunc>some old school friends of his so</u>
<u n="131" who="S0266">oh that's nice</u>
<u n="132" who="S0272">and he's very happy</u>
<u n="133" who="S0266">brilliant and what's</u>
<u n="134" who="S0272" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doing?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0272">she started a new job today</u>
<u n="137" who="S0266">did she?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0273">oh</u>
<u n="139" who="S0272" trans="overlap">mm yeah well</u>
<u n="140" who="S0273">so what's she doing?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0272" trans="overlap">that's why I was a bit late cos I was having I was hearing about the first day which is a horrendous start cos she ever she got to to Clapham South tube station to discover both the Northern and the Victoria lines were down and erm she had to run all the way to Wandsworth Common to pick up a train which she just missed the train that was in she got the wrong ticket oh it was just unbelievable the things but she got Victoria she had to get a taxi there was a lot of traffic I mean it was just a nightmare I how she managed to only be five minutes late I still don't know but anyway she a the gym manager and erm she looks so she manages this gym and she also does a lot of erm er sports therapy treatments and it looks like from tonight she's also side it looks like she's gonna be doing er Pilates you know Pilates class as well cos she's a trained Pilates teacher in a company <trunc>calle</trunc> an organisation called erm <anon type="place"/> which is a gym which is on the side of a private club called the <anon type="place"/> which is in <anon type="place"/> it's all terribly posh she's</u>
<u n="142" who="S0273" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm sounds it</u>
<u n="143" who="S0272">she's treating the editor of close <trunc>ma</trunc> Closer magazine or something I don't know I don't really <unclear/> I don't know she's anyway she said it went really well she loves it's gonna be great and so</u>
<u n="144" who="S0266" whoConfidence="low">and and she lives in London?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0272">yep yep that so three weeks ago she moved back to London so yeah she's fine she left London a year ago had six months in <anon type="place"/> working in a rehabilitation clinic came back</u>
<u n="146" who="S0266">where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0272">Austria</u>
<u n="148" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0272">lovely place we went up to see her in February it's really nice I've been talking an awful long time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't been saying anything about <unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0273" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">well we can't talk about your job <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0272">no true well we can talk about you though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0266"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what do your children do?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0273">what do my children do? erm I say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is working in publishing er so I don't know exactly what it's doing but she seems to be enjoying it doing doing quite well erm and she's she's just moved into her house and far more important having moved into her house she's acquired two kittens</u>
<u n="154" who="S0272">oh wow</u>
<u n="155" who="S0273">which was the whole point of getting a house <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the first place</u>
<u n="156" who="S0272">oh was it?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0273">well to hear her talk yes and it's got a cat flap so that's alright <vocal desc="laugh"/> er so yeah I mean she's nicely settled cos she's been with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for six years now</u>
<u n="158" who="S0272">oh a long time isn't it?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0266">where did she meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from school or?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0273">she met him through er <trunc>cha</trunc> tae kwon do in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0266">gosh</u>
<u n="162" who="S0273">but he was he's been a very good friend all the way through school of a lad who's her very best friend from school who also went to tae kwon do and the three of them have been living together for the last two years so they're all <unclear/> going their separate ways which is quite funny cos <unclear/> people kept saying well you can take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with you when you go to your new house</u>
<u n="163" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0273">as though he was a cat or something so erm yeah they're they're very settled so they're like an old married couple she's in charge</u>
<u n="165" who="S0272">well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0273"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does as he's told</u>
<u n="167" who="S0272">do you think they will get married?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0273">I don't know I think I was talking about this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum last week and you know she's oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll get married in a in an instant he he'd be he'd love to erm and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> never shows any <unclear/> desire to you know I would have thought it would be the other way round if anything because his parents have had quite an acrimonious divorce</u>
<u n="169" who="S0272">oh</u>
<u n="170" who="S0273">erm and you know would have thought perhaps he was would be the one who would want to back away whereas she's got us and <unclear/> together forever <vocal desc="laugh"/> so perhaps she wants to go the other way but I they're quite happy and settled and if they never get married they never get married it's it's fine</u>
<u n="171" who="S0272">I think</u>
<u n="172" who="S0273" trans="overlap">had an arrangement with a friend who's going to wear a hat at the wedding for me if they do get married <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0272">I think sometimes as well they they just they don't need to anymore do they?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0273">no</u>
<u n="175" who="S0272">and I think sometimes maybe is she wants children she might start thinking differently about it or she might not</u>
<u n="176" who="S0273">mm I mean even then people very often don't do they? there's just legal implications and complications and <unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yes yes that's the only thing you yeah yeah that's the only thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0273">but erm yeah she seems to be fine settled and if only I could say the same about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0272">did he find some accommodation? cos I</u>
<u n="180" who="S0273" trans="overlap">he did</u>
<u n="181" who="S0272">oh good</u>
<u n="182" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="183" who="S0272">I am pleased on that day?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0273">cos yes well the following day yes he's gone he's gone up back up to London today because there's something he has to do at the university tomorrow but he's not too sure what cos the timetable's all a bit vague but he has to be in tomorrow but he doesn't know why but he's going anyway</u>
<u n="185" who="S0266">so is he studying at the moment?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0266">what's he studying?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0273">he's doing film production at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0266">oh right</u>
<u n="190" who="S0273">and unfortunately</u>
<u n="191" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and what year is he in?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0273">well he's just finished his</u>
<u n="193" who="S0272" trans="overlap">ah there's a story to that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0273">oh well he's just finished his second year he's just starting his second year they they want him to repeat the year er now he says it's purely because back just before Easter he went to a party where somebody accidentally broke a window and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> decided to be very responsible and sensible but in an alcoholic stupor of course and knock the remaining glass out of the window so nobody would get hurt so consequently he had to have surgery on the torn <trunc>ten</trunc> cut tendon in his hand and that he had two pieces of work to come in which he had to get an extension for and couldn't do very well and he says originally he said it was those two pieces of work that they said were a problem and they couldn't decide whether he was capable of doing the third year they didn't have enough to go on but he's been <unclear>told</unclear> to show two pieces of work that they say he hasn't given in and he says has which is a bit but you can never get to the bottom of anything with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0272" trans="overlap">well I know that's the problem when they're responsible and you can't it's not like being at school when you can ring up the teacher is it and ask?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0273">he I mean he swears he he gave it all in and they yeah they have no record of it so so he's repeating his second year and er he's got somewhere to live and it all seems a bit more positive now so he's not snarling at me at the moment <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0272">well maybe in the long run it will be better for him</u>
<u n="198" who="S0273">in some ways it could well be because I think he probably needs a bit of a jolt to to make him realise that it's not just plain sailing and he can't just coast along and he's gonna be with a bunch of people that he perhaps wouldn't have been with <trunc>otherw</trunc>otherwise and mm he might get himself sorted a bit</u>
<u n="199" who="S0272">well I think I think it they need a sort of failure in life don't they sometimes?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0273" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0272">I think erm I think because of the type of parents that we've been all of us have been much more protective of our kids than certainly I experienced as a as a child you can <trunc>co</trunc> you come in and rescue them don't you? and sort of sort things out and I think erm I think as a result they you know I I've been guilt it's just I'm not criticising you cos I'm very guilty of it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0273" trans="overlap">well yeah you do don't you? if if you want to help you want to sort them out that's what we're here for</u>
<u n="203" who="S0272">that's right but the thought of my parents ever I mean I think it was I think it was just a completely different style of parenting I mean my parents didn't I mean they cared very much for me</u>
<u n="204" who="S0273" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0272">and we had a very good relationship but it was just different</u>
<u n="206" who="S0273">well I I mean I don't know how true it is with other people but I was the first person in my family to go to university my parents had no understanding</u>
<u n="207" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0273">of what was involved and so fine you know it was up to me to get on and do the A levels and so on whereas we've done it we've been there we've got the experience that we want to pass on and and help whereas our parents my parents didn't have the expertise or the knowledge</u>
<u n="209" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0273">er so it's just sort of get on and do it which in some ways is probably better because you haven't you didn't then have parental pressure</u>
<u n="211" who="S0272" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="212" who="S0273">encouraging you trying to <unclear/> we see it as encouragement they</u>
<u n="213" who="S0272" trans="overlap">no because my parents didn't know yeah absolutely they didn't know you know I remember them I remember my mother saying is something about parents evening you going? my mum used to say well no I don't think so I don't think I'm a bit tired tonight I don't think I'll bother</u>
<u n="214" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0272">and I'm thinking and I remember this distinctly because I'm thinking I would never have done that always I've turned up at parents evening</u>
<u n="216" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><unclear/> always went to the parents <trunc>even</trunc> well my mum did cos my dad worked nights and I always felt terrible <vocal desc="gasp"/> my mum's going on her own <unclear/> they'll think my dad doesn't care so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0273">but you know one of them my dad went if he could er but certainly somebody always went</u>
<u n="219" who="S0272">but you know when I <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="220" who="S0273" trans="overlap">I can remember one occasion at <anon type="place"/> when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent a note round saying that she was on a course there were two nights of parents evening and she was on a course for one of them so she couldn't see everybody and you know could we let her know if we really needed to see her otherwise <unclear/> and I said oh well don't bother and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was absolutely furious <vocal desc="laugh"/> what you're not going? so we had an exchange</u>
<u n="221" who="S0272" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would have loved it if I hadn't have gone it because <vocal desc="laugh"/> he was <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0273">well we had an exchange over the wall she alright? yeah she's fine</u>
<u n="223" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0272">yeah it's interesting isn't it? how it all how different it is but erm no I mean I just remember well I didn't go to university <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was the first person in our <unclear/> in our our erm family to go to university and erm so we so from that point of view I I started work at eighteen but I just look back and think you know if I'm short of money or anything I just didn't think to ring it's not that I didn't think they wouldn't help I just never I didn't have the mindset to think that I rang them and said oh I'm really a bit short this month could you help out?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0273">well they didn't have it</u>
<u n="226" who="S0272">or they didn't have it that's right they didn't have it whereas my daughter rang yesterday and said oh mum I'm gonna really struggle to pay the rent this month could you pay this month's and then I'll</u>
<u n="227" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0272">as I paid last month's</u>
<u n="229" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0272">as I was had to be a guarantor I did say to her I really do think at twenty-seven that I'm actually fed up with this now I don't think I really wanna do this anymore she sort of looked at me and said mm yes no you're probably right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0273">well if they're renting there's always got to be a guarantor now <unclear/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0272" trans="overlap">well there hasn't if you've got a permanent job</u>
<u n="233" who="S0273" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0272">but she's always messed around doing this that and the other but hopefully she will be so the next one</u>
<u n="235" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><unclear/> do <unclear/> for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this week</u>
<u n="236" who="S0272">not <trunc>dif</trunc> not a problem when they're a student but she's not</u>
<u n="237" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0272">she's done her two degrees and that's <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's it so erm yeah oh well</u>
<u n="239" who="S0273">suppose they'll all get there in the end <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0272">one hopes so</u>
<u n="241" who="S0273">mm</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
