<text id="SYTD">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:08:52</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0084 S0135</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s house, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>The future</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0135">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Haywards Heath, Sussex</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>19 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Admin / Secretarial</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0084">yes my love?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0135">tell me about your panic attacks then</u>
<u n="3" who="S0084">oh it's really weird though <pause dur="short"/> where do like where do they come from?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0135">so when was the first one again? When you were at that party with your friend</u>
<u n="5" who="S0084">the work's do</u>
<u n="6" who="S0135">and you felt like you were in a shadow and you didn't want to say anything</u>
<u n="7" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I suppose that like that often happens <pause dur="short"/> like I feel like like I don't necessarily be the one to make the effort</u>
<u n="8" who="S0135">but then did it subside?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0084">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I just sort of carried on and just didn't give into it <pause dur="short"/> I just thought well look calm yourself down <pause dur="short"/> calm down</u>
<u n="10" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0084">but I really wanted to leave <pause dur="short"/> and I was just really grateful that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>was like oh yeah I wanna go as well</u>
<u n="12" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="14" who="S0135">did you feel sick?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0084">I just felt yeah I couldn't catch my breath <pause dur="short"/> I felt sick <pause dur="short"/> I was shaking <pause dur="short"/> I just thought oh well um I just told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm just going to the loo <pause dur="short"/> I'll be back in a minute</u>
<u n="16" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0084">and just sat on the toilet for a while</u>
<u n="18" who="S0135">sort of composing yourself?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was just like just calm down <pause dur="short"/> it's fine <pause dur="short"/> um stop being an idiot <pause dur="short"/> and er but that makes it worse cos then you sort of put pressure on yourself</u>
<u n="20" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> but it was fine <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I mean I'm just hoping that the more I sort of put myself out of my comfort zone <pause dur="short"/> I think I I think that's what it is <pause dur="short"/> I think because I haven't done anything scary or anything that challenges me for a really long time <pause dur="short"/> like I haven't been travelling <pause dur="short"/> I haven't done anything <pause dur="short"/> I haven't taken a new job <pause dur="short"/> well the last few years has been really</u>
<u n="22" who="S0135">you have taken a new job in your</u>
<u n="23" who="S0084">yeah but it doesn't really count cos it's not <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="24" who="S0135">yeah it does <pause dur="short"/> it's it's a new team <pause dur="short"/> it's new work</u>
<u n="25" who="S0084">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's got its</u>
<u n="26" who="S0135" trans="overlap">it's a new <trunc>buil</trunc> building floor <pause dur="short"/> it's a new desk</u>
<u n="27" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0135">it's a new new thing</u>
<u n="29" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's it has its own challenges I suppose</u>
<u n="30" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0084">I suppose the thing is like you get to <trunc>th</trunc> this year and you start thinking like what have I got to show for myself? I live in a crack den <pause dur="short"/> I'm only earning twenty whatever grand a year</u>
<u n="32" who="S0135">wait <pause dur="short"/> just watch everything that you're saying right now because that will drag me down with you</u>
<u n="33" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No because it's all relative <pause dur="short"/> it's all relative to what you think you should have achieved by the time you're thirty</u>
<u n="34" who="S0135">right</u>
<u n="35" who="S0084">and in my head when I was twenty-one I thought by the time I'm thirty I will have at least have a man if not be married</u>
<u n="36" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0084">and with a potential for children at some time in my thirties <pause dur="short"/> and now that I'm here I think well there's no man on the scene <pause dur="short"/> therefore kinder would be a a number of years later</u>
<u n="38" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">could I be a single mum? Because you've got  you've got  entertain the notion that you're just not datable <pause dur="short"/> which is possible <pause dur="short"/> I might not be <pause dur="short"/> and in which case I er wanna have kids so then I'll just get er some sperm <pause dur="short"/> but I need to be financially stable in order to do that <pause dur="short"/> and I wanna do all the things that I wanna do before I entertain that idea <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="40" who="S0135" trans="overlap">that's just like putting pressure on yourself</u>
<u n="41" who="S0084">I think because there's no it's almost like because there's no limit to the possibilities</u>
<u n="42" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084">it's really difficult to then think okay then what do I want to do <pause dur="short"/> and the more I think about it the more I panic the more I think oh my God well what am I gonna do with myself <pause dur="short"/> I can't  I can't  think of something that I wanna do so much that I'm working towards it</u>
<u n="44" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084">like I don't know whether I should move here or there <pause dur="short"/> or do this job or that job <pause dur="short"/> and then start to <trunc>pan</trunc> really panic myself <pause dur="short"/> and I think just calm down it's fine <pause dur="short"/> but the more times that I get panicked about it the worse it seems to be <pause dur="short"/> so I think I just need to make a plan <pause dur="short"/> just any plan <pause dur="short"/> whatever the plan is <pause dur="short"/> even if it turns out to be shit at least it's a plan</u>
<u n="46" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0084">and at least it means that I'll be working towards something so</u>
<u n="48" who="S0135">I wonder if it's anything to do with the fact that um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> are getting married <pause dur="short"/> and um like we we are both single <pause dur="short"/> we have each other</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084">we have each other</u>
<u n="50" who="S0135">and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is single</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0135">erm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">which is fine <pause dur="short"/> you but you sort of get to this age and think you would have found somebody <pause dur="short"/> and only because it's like four years</u>
<u n="54" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084">single for four years is quite a long time</u>
<u n="56" who="S0135">yeah but you've had blokes in that time though <pause dur="short"/> you've had options and dalliances and</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084">but</u>
<u n="58" who="S0135">it just hasn't been the right one</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">I mean I was only half joking when I said you lose a part of your soul each time</u>
<u n="60" who="S0135">oh right</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084" trans="overlap">Cos people do like <pause dur="short"/> it is quite depressing with each one that you can rule out <pause dur="short"/> cos that's a lot of men that you're ruling out <pause dur="short"/> and a lot of different types of men <pause dur="short"/> my ear keeps um</u>
<u n="62" who="S0135">filling up with fluid and <pause dur="short"/> shall we drain it? Let's lance it <pause dur="short"/> does it go muffley?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I had a bath earlier <pause dur="short"/> maybe that's what</u>
<u n="64" who="S0135">oh no <pause dur="short"/> you're gonna get your ear syringed</u>
<u n="65" who="S0084" trans="overlap">there's water in it really <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh</u>
<u n="66" who="S0135">Don't do that</u>
<u n="67" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Just <unclear/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0135" trans="overlap">Don't get it syringed <pause dur="short"/> don't do that <pause dur="short"/> never let them come at you with a needle</u>
<u n="69" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0135">not towards your ear <pause dur="short"/> it's quite a vital organ</u>
<u n="71" who="S0084">well it's because I was getting what I thought was my wisdom teeth coming through <pause dur="short"/> but the pain is also like here as well</u>
<u n="72" who="S0135" trans="overlap">shit man <pause dur="short"/> just wisdom teeth</u>
<u n="73" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="74" who="S0135">maybe you'll be wise when they come through</u>
<u n="75" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> more wise that'd be nice</u>
<u n="76" who="S0135">wiser <pause dur="short"/> older and wiser</u>
<u n="77" who="S0084">well you'd think something <pause dur="short"/> there must be something good about ageing <pause dur="short"/> there isn't anything good so far <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing that springs immediately to mind</u>
<u n="78" who="S0135">no <pause dur="short"/> I think we should <trunc>may</trunc> maybe your plan should be to invent a time machine</u>
<u n="79" who="S0084">that'd be quite nice <pause dur="short"/> I'll I'll start working on that</u>
<u n="80" who="S0135">but has the pressures come from anywhere else? Or are they all completely self</u>
<u n="81" who="S0084">I think they're self-imposed</u>
<u n="82" who="S0135">right <pause dur="short"/> I think it's part of the western culture that you know you think you should be married and have children</u>
<u n="83" who="S0084">own a house</u>
<u n="84" who="S0135">and have a career and own a house <pause dur="short"/> all that shit</u>
<u n="85" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0135">but if you go into different cultures <pause dur="short"/> and like say for example in Germany no one owns their own house</u>
<u n="87" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0135">no one <pause dur="short"/> I didn't</u>
<u n="89" who="S0084">this is what I keep telling myself</u>
<u n="90" who="S0135">I didn't know a single person in the embassy that owned their own house</u>
<u n="91" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0135">not a single one of them <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="93" who="S0084">it's a different culture</u>
<u n="94" who="S0135">it's just a completely different culture <pause dur="short"/> in Italy the men will live with their mums until their mid-thirties</u>
<u n="95" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0135">um</u>
<u n="97" who="S0084">we're in that we're in the shit generation</u>
<u n="98" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0084">I mean our parents had it quite good</u>
<u n="100" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0084">Cos they were the baby boomers <pause dur="short"/> so they got all the houses so</u>
<u n="102" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0084">mortgages were more readily available <pause dur="short"/> there were more opportunities for work</u>
<u n="104" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0084">but the generation before that <pause dur="short"/> our Grandparent's generation had to live through the war so they were the shit generation</u>
<u n="106" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0084">so I think it's just gonna be that our kids will have a good generation</u>
<u n="108" who="S0135" trans="overlap">reciprocal <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well not</u>
<u n="109" who="S0084">unless we fuck up the world</u>
<u n="110" who="S0135">I'm not having any <pause dur="short"/> but yours maybe</u>
<u n="111" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0135">I'll be their aunty <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0135">maybe I don't know maybe your like biological clock's kicked in or something</u>
<u n="115" who="S0084">something's going on</u>
<u n="116" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0084">I think well what I need is a plan</u>
<u n="118" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="119" who="S0084">and I feel very listless <pause dur="short"/> and I think as soon as I got the job at the press</u>
<u n="120" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0084">I was a bit like right okay so now what?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0135">because that's what</u>
<u n="123" who="S0084">within a matter of moments</u>
<u n="124" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that might be because that's what you'd been always working towards</u>
<u n="125" who="S0084">and you if you lose that</u>
<u n="126" who="S0135">and then you got it and you were like bang <pause dur="short"/> I got it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0084">and and now what?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0135" trans="overlap">now what?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0084">and if you just spend your life working towards something <pause dur="short"/> cos when you were younger your parents were like well you're gonna go to university</u>
<u n="132" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0084">there's never really an option not to</u>
<u n="134" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0084">I mean they say there's not but there isn't</u>
<u n="136" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">so that's what you spend your life working towards <pause dur="short"/> and then you finish uni and you're a bit like oh now what do I do?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">sort of bum around for a while <pause dur="short"/> the you make another plan</u>
<u n="140" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">and that follows through <pause dur="short"/> and you think okay well that's great <pause dur="short"/> got that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0084">well now so now what?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0135">mm mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084">and now I've I've got a job that I really enjoy <pause dur="short"/> I really like my job which is quite fortunate I know</u>
<u n="146" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0084">I know it's like I'm quite lucky to enjoy my job</u>
<u n="148" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0084">but at the same time it is a job I could do anywhere for any publishing house in any business stream</u>
<u n="150" who="S0135" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0084">it's not specific to ELT so again I'm quite fortunate in that regard <pause dur="short"/> but it does mean that I have to find a way of making my skill set unique to an employer in another country <pause dur="short"/> rather than just hire somebody that they have there</u>
<u n="152" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084">so that's that's the problem <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't apply for a job here for a job abroad because they would just hire somebody there</u>
<u n="154" who="S0135" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0084">so I would have to move there <pause dur="short"/> but it it I mean it that's why I would struggle to go somewhere where that I didn't speak the language</u>
<u n="156" who="S0135">what? What is it that makes you think that you wanna move abroad? Change?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0084">it's just yeah just a  just a  new challenge <pause dur="short"/> just to see more of the world <pause dur="short"/> and every time I see somewhere new I get the feeling that I'm not going to see everywhere</u>
<u n="158" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0084">which is just unrealistic <pause dur="short"/> you're not gonna see everywhere</u>
<u n="160" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0084">I'd like to visit every country at least once</u>
<u n="162" who="S0135">mm okay</u>
<u n="163" who="S0084">and I'm thirty now and I've not really seen that much</u>
<u n="164" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="165" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I've seen some <pause dur="short"/> so I mean that's the immediate plan</u>
<u n="166" who="S0135">mm mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0084">Cos there's no point staying at home to save for a mortgage cos I'd never be able to scrape together the deposit</u>
<u n="168" who="S0135" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="169" who="S0084">even though they're saying on er Rightmove I was having a look the other day that there's they've brought something out to help first time buyers <pause dur="short"/> all this sort of gobbins <pause dur="short"/> so like which if you're still interested you should look at</u>
<u n="170" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0084">but I'm still never going to be able to get together half of the deposit for round here</u>
<u n="172" who="S0135">not on your own</u>
<u n="173" who="S0084">not on my own</u>
<u n="174" who="S0135">and that it's not just the deposit <pause dur="short"/> it's about finding a lender</u>
<u n="175" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0135">who will lend your mortgage</u>
<u n="177" who="S0084">exactly</u>
<u n="178" who="S0135">because your mortgage will probably be in the region of you know six hundred to nine hundred pound a month</u>
<u n="179" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0135">could you afford that?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="182" who="S0135">could you find a lender to lend it to you even if you get the deposit?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0135">but I mean do you actually want to own a house? Or do you think you should own one?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0084">I'd like to own a house</u>
<u n="186" who="S0135">right</u>
<u n="187" who="S0084">at the same time it's not on my list of priorities</u>
<u n="188" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0084">versus travelling around the world with a backpack on my back <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0135" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0084">like it would be nice to have the stability that if I owned a house here I could rent it out <pause dur="short"/> I could pay off my mortgage and I could naff off and I would be able to come back to something</u>
<u n="192" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0084">Cos my worry is if I go away I don't know what's gonna happen to the jobs market</u>
<u n="194" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0084">I don't know what's gonna happen to house prices <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="196" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0084">if I go away and come back it's going to be difficult</u>
<u n="198" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0084">and I need to leave myself enough money to come back to and that's why I want to work in the same field that I'm working in now</u>
<u n="200" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0084">because I don't want er to come back and an employer say well why did you go fruit picking for a year when you had a perfectly good career so</u>
<u n="202" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0084">I don't want to go fruit picking but</u>
<u n="204" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084">and at least in that regard I have found a job that I do want to do <pause dur="short"/> so if I were to move abroad that would be the type of job that I was looking for so at least that would be some sort of guide</u>
<u n="206" who="S0135" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">I don't know</u>
<u n="208" who="S0135" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084">I feel like I think about it all the time and I never actually do anything so</u>
<u n="210" who="S0135">I think what you need to do is you need to get either a journal or a massive blank piece of paper and write it all down to try and untangle this web <pause dur="short"/> because I think you've got a lot of uh competing ideas but you're not clear what your priority is <pause dur="short"/> like you don't know</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="212" who="S0135">what is the most important to you <pause dur="short"/> and I think you're being influenced by as one is by I dunno parental expectations friend's expectations the media and</u>
<u n="213" who="S0084">exactly</u>
<u n="214" who="S0135">what everyone thinks everyone should be doing and colleagues and going for promotion and going for a house and doing this and all that <pause dur="short"/> whereas actually if you want to go and fruit pick with a back pack on your back and return to your mum's spare room</u>
<u n="215" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0135">if you are super happy travelling and that's the thing that makes you happy that's what you have to go for</u>
<u n="217" who="S0084" trans="overlap">do that</u>
<u n="218" who="S0135">but I think that you probably need to just sort of take some time you know sort of get it all down on paper maybe <pause dur="short"/> untangle it all and figure out what is it that's actually that what makes you happy</u>
<u n="219" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0135">and what do you want? And there's like a couple of like techniques <pause dur="short"/> um one er you might have heard of it <pause dur="short"/> like the Death Bed test or something <pause dur="short"/> and it's probably quite complicated and you probably shouldn't do it unless there's someone's who's a grown up but like you know if you're on your death bed</u>
<u n="221" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0135">would you look back and think I wish I'd done this or that was a bad idea or I should have done more about that <pause dur="short"/> I wish I hadn't even bothered worrying about that <pause dur="short"/> cos that's like a technique</u>
<u n="223" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0135">of trying to help you figure out what's important</u>
<u n="225" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0135">and all that other kind of stuff</u>
<u n="227" who="S0084">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> well that all makes sense yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0135">um yeah I mean in theory they'll all probably make a lot of sense <pause dur="short"/> but in reality it's quite difficult <pause dur="short"/> um you know just to kind of try and boil it all down because</u>
<u n="229" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0135">there's loads and loads of different causes of panic attacks <pause dur="short"/> I mean with me I think I was bored and so</u>
<u n="231" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="232" who="S0135">my brain</u>
<u n="233" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0135">would start analysing and over-analysing everything <pause dur="short"/> and like being like super um sensitive to what I was feeling</u>
<u n="235" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="236" who="S0135">like oh God I feel a bit sick <pause dur="short"/> oh yes I actually <trunc>d</trunc> I feel really really sick <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna be sick <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta go sort of thing</u>
<u n="237" who="S0084">oh God</u>
<u n="238" who="S0135">so I think it mine was kind of like from boredom</u>
<u n="239" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0135">and also like loneliness</u>
<u n="241" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0135">and like a lack of people to talk to and stuff like that</u>
<u n="243" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0135">um <pause dur="short"/> and so yours are probably going to be quite a different cause <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0084">too much going on in my brain</u>
<u n="246" who="S0135">well maybe <trunc>may</trunc> and it's your body maybe your body's way of saying hold the phone</u>
<u n="247" who="S0084">uh</u>
<u n="248" who="S0135">right <pause dur="short"/> you know? I don't <trunc>kn</trunc> I mean I don't know <pause dur="short"/> we're all just guessing aren't we?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0084">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0135">erm <pause dur="short"/> but you're a hundred percent right when you say and when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and everything says that you have to carry on <pause dur="short"/> it's so true <pause dur="short"/> face your fears</u>
<u n="251" who="S0084">oh man</u>
<u n="252" who="S0135">that is so true</u>
<u n="253" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that's hard isn't it?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0135">it's absolutely terrifying</u>
<u n="255" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0135">like me I haven't been out for a meal in quite a while</u>
<u n="257" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0135">because for whatever reason <unclear/> have got into me <pause dur="short"/> but I know</u>
<u n="259" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0135">the only way to get through it is to go along and do it and everything <pause dur="short"/> and eventually it will get busy erm busy easier</u>
<u n="261" who="S0084" trans="overlap">better</u>
<u n="262" who="S0135">like when I didn't want to go flying anywhere</u>
<u n="263" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0135">and I was absolutely terrified <pause dur="short"/> and the first four sort of three of four flights were absolutely horrendous <pause dur="short"/> I thought I was gonna be sick <pause dur="short"/> I was sweating</u>
<u n="265" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0135">I was horror blah blah <pause dur="short"/> but now the last one I took fine absolutely fine</u>
<u n="267" who="S0084">Good</u>
<u n="268" who="S0135">erm the thing is like even going out for a simple drink <pause dur="short"/> going out for coffee <pause dur="short"/> things like that</u>
<u n="269" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0135">A busy place whatever</u>
<u n="271" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0135">avoid it like the plague</u>
<u n="273" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0135">but you have to put yourself in it <pause dur="short"/> and you have to stick it out so you can prove to your body nothing dangerous happened <pause dur="short"/> it was okay and I survived it <pause dur="short"/> but by  But by  not going into it your body thinks you've got something to be scared of</u>
<u n="275" who="S0084">yeah and that makes it worse</u>
<u n="276" who="S0135" trans="overlap">and if you  And if you  run off before you've experienced it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0135">that's how you build up the fear</u>
<u n="279" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0135">it's the hardest thing in the world <pause dur="short"/> and that's why fear is sort of like self-perpetuating like self-fuelling and everything</u>
<u n="281" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0135">and it's just so terrifying when you're in the minute <pause dur="short"/> logically and rationally you can sit here and go yeah I used to love going out <trunc>t</trunc> moshing it concerts and</u>
<u n="283" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0135">er whatever and meeting new people</u>
<u n="285" who="S0084">being at a festival</u>
<u n="286" who="S0135">and festivals and all that sort of stuff <pause dur="short"/> what's happened now? Why am I a bit? Why am I like querying me? And stuff like that you know <pause dur="short"/> cos it's not like a logical or a rational fear which makes it really frustrating</u>
<u n="287" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think but that's the thing in in the moment that's what you're trying to tell yourself <pause dur="short"/> you're trying to calm yourself down but there's nothing logical or rational about it</u>
<u n="288" who="S0135" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0084">I think you're right <pause dur="short"/> you you know it is just about sort of pulling together more of a plan and and more like more cohesion to my thoughts <pause dur="short"/> because at the moment it is just a massive jumble</u>
<u n="290" who="S0135">it's a jumble</u>
<u n="291" who="S0084">and that's what panics me</u>
<u n="292" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0084">is that there's is that I'm ageing every day <pause dur="short"/> life is getting away from me and I haven't got a plan</u>
<u n="294" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0084">but at least if I was you know I was living in a crack den but it's okay cos I'm saving money and it means that in a year I'm going to be doing something amazing</u>
<u n="296" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0084">but for now I can just take every day as it is and enjoy it</u>
<u n="298" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0084">because I'm working towards something</u>
<u n="300" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0084">so I'm not living in the future <pause dur="short"/> I'm enjoying</u>
<u n="302" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0084">now <pause dur="short"/> but I know that in a year's time or whenever there's gonna be another challenge <pause dur="short"/> there's going to be something interesting and exciting and then something to aim for</u>
<u n="304" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0084">Cos you do sort of inevitably get swept up in the the wheel of the office and you know oh well will I get promoted and will I get a bit more money <pause dur="short"/> and it's worth staying and</u>
<u n="306" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0084">I think if I stayed there I would be living in <anon type="place"/> for the next five years <pause dur="short"/> and I'm never going to meet a man here <pause dur="short"/> not that that's the be all and end all</u>
<u n="308" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0084">but it's just dire for men <pause dur="short"/> and just socially really</u>
<u n="310" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0084">you know there's not an awful lot going on <pause dur="short"/> I think it's just I need to go and meet new people and just go and experience a few things <pause dur="short"/> and I never get the same buzz from anything as I do from when I travel <pause dur="short"/> and the last time I had that was when I was in Australia and as lovely as Croatia was it was very safe <pause dur="short"/> cos it was <pause dur="short"/> you know we were there together and a long time and despite the rain</u>
<u n="312" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah it's quite touristy <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0084">it's quite touristy</u>
<u n="314" who="S0135">it was the monsoon season</u>
<u n="315" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0084">I don't know whether we picked the best dates</u>
<u n="317" who="S0135">it was August I mean what and what else can you do? I mean</u>
<u n="318" who="S0084">we did  We did  get to see some tortoise porn <pause dur="short"/> that was quite offensive</u>
<u n="319" who="S0135" trans="overlap">oh God like</u>
<u n="320" who="S0084">rape of a turtle</u>
<u n="321" who="S0135" trans="overlap">chasing for a rape yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Erm there's not er you know I loved it <pause dur="short"/> it was a really nice break <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't the same as when I was in Australia</u>
<u n="323" who="S0135" trans="overlap">that's not travelling <pause dur="short"/> that was a holiday</u>
<u n="324" who="S0084">that was like you know sort of ten days</u>
<u n="325" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0084">nice couple of days in Berlin <unclear/> A week in Croatia living in our nice little house was you know nice and safe and easy</u>
<u n="327" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0084">whereas when I was in Australia I was on my own <pause dur="short"/> and I was going to see exciting places <pause dur="short"/> and it was different like just having to fly between places and meet new people and <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it's just I get that buzz when I do that</u>
<u n="329" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0084">and I get really excited <pause dur="short"/> and I live for that <pause dur="short"/> and like that's the most important thing</u>
<u n="331" who="S0135" trans="overlap">what's stopping you from booking a flight in two months and going with Nicky over there?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0084">money <pause dur="short"/> financially I couldn't do it</u>
<u n="333" who="S0135">and do you not have the funds?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0084">no cos you have to have five thousand US dollars in your bank account when you enter the country</u>
<u n="335" who="S0135">mm <pause dur="short"/> if you?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and your flights would be like fifteen hundred pounds</u>
<u n="337" who="S0135" trans="overlap">if you had ten thousand pounds would you?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0084">I'd go now <pause dur="short"/> I would get my passport</u>
<u n="339" who="S0135" trans="overlap">you would go</u>
<u n="340" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just a question of funds <pause dur="short"/> I would just get on the first plane <pause dur="short"/> I would er drive to Stanstead now in Olive and I would get on the first flight</u>
<u n="341" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0084">because really it's only money</u>
<u n="343" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0084">and that's what stopping me <pause dur="short"/> like if you know if I came into money now that's it I'd be off</u>
<u n="345" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't take a caravan and go around England with my ex-boyfriend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it seems unlikely <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It seems pretty unlikely <pause dur="short"/> I mean the that's there's er time for that</u>
<u n="347" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0084">when I'm old and decrepit if we haven't destroyed the planet by then <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0135"><unclear/> planet yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0084">er yes so I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm just gonna save like a beast <pause dur="short"/> like with these recordings it's obviously been really great to pay off my overdraft <pause dur="short"/> and I'll get another <pause dur="short"/> I'll get one payment in my next bank in my next pay check which will be</u>
<u n="351" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0084">mid-April <pause dur="short"/> and then the <trunc>ne</trunc> the last one will be mid-May and I'll put that amount into my savings account which will probably be like four or five hundred pounds <pause dur="short"/> put that straight in</u>
<u n="353" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0084">and that'll be the start of it <pause dur="short"/> and my mum's already said like if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does move out in September <pause dur="short"/> cos if she doesn't go to Berlin or</u>
<u n="355" who="S0135">yep</u>
<u n="356" who="S0084">Stockholm she's just gonna move to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> she said but September is the date where she's moving out come hell or high water</u>
<u n="357" who="S0135">okay right</u>
<u n="358" who="S0084">Cos she's finding it really tough</u>
<u n="359" who="S0135">really why?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0084">I think when you finish uni it's horrendous isn't it? Because</u>
<u n="361" who="S0135">I can't remember</u>
<u n="362" who="S0084">reality bites <pause dur="short"/> I think you moved home didn't you and I moved home and</u>
<u n="363" who="S0135">oh I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't know I can't remember</u>
<u n="364" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and you quite enjoyed the temping cos it was always different places</u>
<u n="365" who="S0135">yeah something different</u>
<u n="366" who="S0084">and while you were doing your erm civil service training <pause dur="short"/> you know you did quite a lot of that</u>
<u n="367" who="S0135" trans="overlap">ooh I don't I er generally don't know where I've been</u>
<u n="368" who="S0084">two thousand and one</u>
<u n="369" who="S0135">for the last twenty-eight years</u>
<u n="370" who="S0084">er twenty-nine years <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0135">erm yes yes</u>
<u n="372" who="S0084">but she's er I think she's not in a job she particularly enjoys</u>
<u n="373" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0084">and she's in <anon type="place"/> where none of her friends are <pause dur="short"/> and she's living with my mum and</u>
<u n="375" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0084">it's just I think reality is such it's such a hard fall when you finish uni like <pause dur="short"/> you think</u>
<u n="377" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0084">what it's like when you're at uni <pause dur="short"/> and you go to the student union <pause dur="short"/> and you know everybody and</u>
<u n="379" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0084">every night you're doing something and</u>
<u n="381" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0084">you come down to reality with a quite a hard bang</u>
<u n="383" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah true true true yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0084">so she's finding it quite tough <pause dur="short"/> and I think my mum's finding it hard going cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has never been very good at putting on a brave front <pause dur="short"/> she if she's in a bad mood you'll know about it <pause dur="short"/> it's like living with a stroppy teenager <pause dur="short"/> and I mean I ought to er for all I remember er which I can't remember I was probably exactly the same</u>
<u n="385" who="S0135"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0084">but it was at the time when my mum and dad were together when I was living in the house and</u>
<u n="387" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0084">I think they were quite understanding <pause dur="short"/> I think when I moved back I didn't work for a few months because</u>
<u n="389" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="390" who="S0084">obviously you don't pay rent or anything <pause dur="short"/> I mean you're living with your parents</u>
<u n="391" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0084">but now erm <pause dur="short"/> it's cos she's my mum  my mum  has obviously not got much money so she pays <pause dur="short"/> there's not mortgage on the house so she doesn't pay rent</u>
<u n="393" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0084">but she pays I think she pays a hundred and fifty pounds a month <pause dur="short"/> so that's like board basically <pause dur="short"/> like utilities and food</u>
<u n="395" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0084">so it's pretty cheap <pause dur="short"/> it's cheaper than what she'd be paying in Norwich <pause dur="short"/> so she's managed to save quite a lot of money <pause dur="short"/> and she's quite savvy with money unlike moi</u>
<u n="397" who="S0135">you are so savvy</u>
<u n="398" who="S0084">er I would like to say I am <pause dur="short"/> I think car booting would be good <pause dur="short"/> I've also got my old violins to sell <pause dur="short"/> I weren't take them to car boots though</u>
<u n="399" who="S0135">find a dealer <pause dur="short"/> or a shop of something</u>
<u n="400" who="S0084">I need to get them <unclear/> like I need to get a quote for them</u>
<u n="401" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0084">but they would have been seven hundred pounds new so <pause dur="short"/> but that was you know a good ten years ago so er they would have depreciated</u>
<u n="403" who="S0135">what about doing the lottery?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0084">lottery <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think it's probably a waste of money but yeah maybe <pause dur="short"/> someone's gotta win it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0135" trans="overlap">or maybe taking up gambling</u>
<u n="406" who="S0084">gambling could be the answer</u>
<u n="407" who="S0135">gotta be in it to win it</u>
<u n="408" who="S0084">I mean while while we're there why not prostitution? High class escorting</u>
<u n="409" who="S0135">how much do you wanna go abroad?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0084">A lot</u>
<u n="411" who="S0135">I don't think there's any wrong with it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh well as long as I only have to hold hands</u>
<u n="413" who="S0135">I'm not talking about street walking</u>
<u n="414" who="S0084">no high class  high class  escort</u>
<u n="415" who="S0135" trans="overlap">establishments <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos you can provide conversation</u>
<u n="416" who="S0084">well that's that's the idea <pause dur="short"/> I mean if I had a good body then I'd do pole dancing and erm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0135" trans="overlap">you have got a good body</u>
<u n="418" who="S0084">I've got wobbly bits</u>
<u n="419" who="S0135">where?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0084">everywhere <pause dur="short"/> in all the wrong places <pause dur="short"/> not on my bangers <pause dur="short"/> erm mm yeah there's got  there's got  to be a way of making more money</u>
<u n="421" who="S0135">well it's</u>
<u n="422" who="S0084">because second jobs are not the answer unless they are escorting</u>
<u n="423" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah too exhausting <pause dur="short"/> or <trunc>escor</trunc></u>
<u n="424" who="S0084">too exhausting <pause dur="short"/> and like paying fifty per cent tax is just not viable</u>
<u n="425" who="S0135">no <pause dur="short"/> um so I mean it sounds like if you could say like kind of you said earlier on <pause dur="short"/> next year you wanna be somewhere else no matter where not no matter where it is but overseas somewhere so you can get the new experience and the new challenges and prove that you can</u>
<u n="426" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0135">do all those bits and pieces on yourself <pause dur="short"/> setting the goal you know blah blah but a year's still quite a long time <pause dur="short"/> but is that?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0084">I was just thinking because between now and September I can save money from my salary which would be like a hundred and fifty pounds a month maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe two hundred</u>
<u n="429" who="S0135">is that all you can save?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0084">well I just think <pause dur="short"/> maybe I could save more if I was really savvy <pause dur="short"/> maybe three hundred <pause dur="short"/> cos if I could get say I get fourteen hundred pounds every month <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I could work this out</u>
<u n="431" who="S0135">that's quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> maybe get a pen and paper</u>
<u n="432" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> let's make a plan <pause dur="short"/> I just need to not spend money <pause dur="short"/> and that that's the problem when you get bored is you just wanna go out <pause dur="short"/> and everyone's getting married</u>
<u n="433" who="S0135">that is so expensive</u>
<u n="434" who="S0084">it's just everything <pause dur="short"/> and er if I wanna go and see Tasha <pause dur="short"/> and petrol's so expensive</u>
<u n="435" who="S0135">petrol's so expensive yep</u>
<u n="436" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to go to <anon type="place"/> for her birthday <pause dur="short"/> luckily she's talking about doing that in June so maybe that won't be too bad <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> E pub for ebooks <pause dur="short"/> snooze <pause dur="short"/> oh you're good at maths so that's fine</u>
<u n="437" who="S0135">yep <pause dur="short"/> well used to be</u>
<u n="438" who="S0084" trans="overlap">shall say <pause dur="short"/> uh you are good at maths</u>
<u n="439" who="S0135">that's your income <pause dur="short"/> see that is more than I get</u>
<u n="440" who="S0084">per calendar month yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> after tax</u>
<u n="442" who="S0084">after tax</u>
<u n="443" who="S0135">yep</u>
<u n="444" who="S0084">so coming out of that is three five five for rent</u>
<u n="445" who="S0135">and that includes all bills</u>
<u n="446" who="S0084">that include all bills</u>
<u n="447" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0084">A hundred and fifty which is my careers development loan</u>
<u n="449" who="S0135">yep</u>
<u n="450" who="S0084">twenty-six which is my phone bill</u>
<u n="451" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0084">say sixty quid for a tank of petrol</u>
<u n="453" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0084">but I could er obviously that's a a place to shave money</u>
<u n="455" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah possibly yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0084">erm say what a hundred pounds for food? Would it be more than that? That's like twenty quid a week <pause dur="short"/> that's not that much <pause dur="short"/> Twenty-five quid a week</u>
<u n="457" who="S0135">do you ever buy lunches and stuff like that? And</u>
<u n="458" who="S0084">no I try and make soup every week <pause dur="short"/> but if you say two hundred pounds for food <pause dur="short"/> cos what's that? A hundred and fifty pounds for food <pause dur="short"/> say forty quid a week <pause dur="short"/> four fours are a hundred and sixty</u>
<u n="459" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that includes lunches meals out all that?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that includes lunches <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so if I was to live on a budget of forty quid a week</u>
<u n="461" who="S0135">okay <pause dur="short"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0084">and then spending money <pause dur="short"/> fifty quid a week?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0135">do you have a gym membership or anything like that?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0084">let it go</u>
<u n="465" who="S0135">fifty quid a week <pause dur="short"/> it's quite high that <pause dur="short"/> but that will include clothes</u>
<u n="466" who="S0084">and DVDs and all <trunc>k</trunc> kinds of</u>
<u n="467" who="S0135" trans="overlap">cinema and all that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="468" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what I need to do is then take the money out at the end of the month and if it's not there not spend it <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/>Rescue me<shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> the thing about listening to Kiss is that it is literally the same four songs on repeat</u>
<u n="469" who="S0135">I thought you were gonna say it makes you wanna go out <pause dur="short"/> I was like yeah it does <pause dur="short"/> whoop whoop</u>
<u n="470" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it does make me wanna go out <pause dur="short"/> that too</u>
<u n="471" who="S0135">and be an old hab</u>
<u n="472" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> my salary minus my rent <pause dur="short"/> minus career development loan <pause dur="short"/> minus phone bill <pause dur="short"/> minus petrol <pause dur="short"/> minus spending money <pause dur="short"/> minus food <pause dur="short"/> leaves two hundred pounds</u>
<u n="473" who="S0135">no I don't <trunc>belie</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> give me that <pause dur="short"/> I don't believe that</u>
<u n="474" who="S0084">here you go <pause dur="short"/> I'll just cancel <pause dur="short"/> say I didn't spend money on petrol</u>
<u n="475" who="S0135" trans="overlap">five <pause dur="short"/> six <pause dur="short"/> seven <pause dur="short"/> eight-sixty <pause dur="short"/> nine twenty You can't  You can't  even use a calculator</u>
<u n="476" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0135">for fuck's sake <pause dur="short"/> what are you like? You animal <pause dur="short"/> you've done something really wrong</u>
<u n="478" who="S0084">really retarded</u>
<u n="479" who="S0135">yeah you've got at least four hundred</u>
<u n="480" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0135">what did you do?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm what did I do man? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I am a bit special  as you know</u>
<u n="483" who="S0135">yeah clearly <pause dur="short"/> you've done something very wrong</u>
<u n="484" who="S0084">maths was never my strong point <pause dur="short"/> you know that <pause dur="short"/> I've always been a an artiste</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="485" who="S0084">have you proved me right?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0135">yes <pause dur="short"/> well just while I'm here</u>
<u n="487" who="S0084">oh what's that say? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Four hundred and eighty-nine <pause dur="short"/> what the hell?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0135">right</u>
<u n="489" who="S0084">I must have pressed it er too many times</u>
<u n="490" who="S0135">right <pause dur="short"/> four eight nine <pause dur="short"/> basically</u>
<u n="491" who="S0084">so we could say four hundred</u>
<u n="492" who="S0135" trans="overlap">to take that up to <pause dur="short"/> to take <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> to round that up to five hundred pound shave off your</u>
<u n="493" who="S0084">petrol</u>
<u n="494" who="S0135">petrol to be forty</u>
<u n="495" who="S0084">forty pounds</u>
<u n="496" who="S0135">forty-nine I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah forty-nine</u>
<u n="497" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah but just in case you can just say forty <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> forty-five pounds <pause dur="short"/> but that's fine because that means I'd ask my dad to put in fifteen pounds worth of petrol a month <pause dur="short"/> which is fine because that's all he actually uses</u>
<u n="498" who="S0135">now what the issue is here <pause dur="short"/> that's food <pause dur="short"/> is that this bit here the two hundred pounds is literally that's going out</u>
<u n="499" who="S0084">that's pretty meagre that is</u>
<u n="500" who="S0135">that's clothes <pause dur="short"/> it's cinema <pause dur="short"/> it's trips</u>
<u n="501" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0135">travel <pause dur="short"/> it's er hotels <pause dur="short"/> it's gifts</u>
<u n="503" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0135">and that is only fifty pounds a week <pause dur="short"/> I mean that is <pause dur="short"/> is that quite? Yeah that is <pause dur="short"/> maybe that's quite a lot</u>
<u n="505" who="S0084">I mean it sounds pretty generous when you say it like that but in reality as we know like if you go to the cinema <pause dur="short"/> or if you go and like get a bit of food <pause dur="short"/> it's because I never check <pause dur="short"/> because I just find it so incredibly boring to be the person to be like I can't you know I'm only gonna give you two pounds <pause dur="short"/> like with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's not good at thinking oh you paid so I'll do this</u>
<u n="506" who="S0135" trans="overlap">you got that so I'll get this or I'll <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0084">you know like if we're at the bar she's like sort of cos she's on cloud cuckoo land</u>
<u n="508" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="509" who="S0084">she'll just be faffing around <unclear/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0135">oh like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0084">yeah it's sort of like</u>
<u n="512" who="S0135">not cos she's not got the money just cos she's a bitch</u>
<u n="513" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> she's just not there <pause dur="short"/> so I'm like well I'll get these <pause dur="short"/> because otherwise you could be standing there for hours</u>
<u n="514" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0084">and it's not like she's tight</u>
<u n="516" who="S0135" trans="overlap">you need to be</u>
<u n="517" who="S0084">she's not a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> she's not like I'm not gonna pay</u>
<u n="518" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah she's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0084">I just think right I'm I'm gonna I'm just gonna sort it because otherwise we'll be here forever</u>
<u n="520" who="S0135">right well you need to</u>
<u n="521" who="S0084">but I need to not do that</u>
<u n="522" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0084">and just let her</u>
<u n="524" who="S0135">and that <pause dur="short"/> I mean I was like that with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've known <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and lived with her so it's probably different a slightly different relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> like I can</u>
<u n="525" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="526" who="S0135">scream and say why have you gotta be so fucking tight <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0135">but erm but but in the end like I'd be like that <pause dur="short"/> for fuck's sake <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta buy all this shopping because I bought you that pizza <pause dur="short"/> I bought you that glass of wine and the bus fare</u>
<u n="529" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0135">oh yeah of course <pause dur="short"/> no worries</u>
<u n="531" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0135">Cos she's generous</u>
<u n="533" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0135">she's generous but she'll just never</u>
<u n="535" who="S0084">she's just a bit scatty</u>
<u n="536" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0084">which is the same as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know money isn't an an issue <pause dur="short"/> she's not tight <pause dur="short"/> she just isn't engaged on the <trunc>p</trunc> on the same planet</u>
<u n="538" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how much money would you wanna have if for example you did wanna go travelling?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0084">say it's Australia I would need to have so on entry into the country you need to have five thousand dollars</u>
<u n="540" who="S0135">which is?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0084" trans="overlap">which is three thousand five hundred pounds</u>
<u n="542" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0084">but you also wanna pay for your flights</u>
<u n="544" who="S0135">which are what?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0084">about fifteen hundred pounds <pause dur="short"/> when I flew out my flights were one thousand pounds</u>
<u n="546" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="547" who="S0084">and that was Christmas <pause dur="short"/> and I won't be flying at Christmas so it'll be cheaper</u>
<u n="548" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="549" who="S0084">and I won't be flying to mental places <pause dur="short"/> but if I wanna fly if I wanna stop over somewhere then basically I need to have five thousand pounds saved</u>
<u n="550" who="S0135">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0084" trans="overlap">so if you think  So if you think  in May <pause dur="short"/> with my May which is the eighteenth of May I'll put five hundred pounds in then</u>
<u n="552" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0084">because that'll be the recordings</u>
<u n="554" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="555" who="S0084">I suppose I could put more in because it'll be the recordings plus the start of my <pause dur="short"/> I just don't know what my overdraft will be like then <pause dur="short"/> cos I've had my mum's birthday and all kinds of stuff going out recently so</u>
<u n="556" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0084">say say in May we that's the point where we start <pause dur="short"/> may June July August September October November December <pause dur="short"/> by December that's eight months of five hundred pounds <pause dur="short"/> eight fives are forty</u>
<u n="558" who="S0135">yeah in only ten months</u>
<u n="559" who="S0084">so I need to be <trunc>t</trunc> so in March <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I could book things in March next year</u>
<u n="560" who="S0135">er let me just double check your maths <pause dur="short"/> no offence</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">February maybe</u>
<u n="562" who="S0135">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> In March <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say March April <pause dur="short"/> no May June July August September October November December January Feb</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0135">so you can technically</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I'd book in March probably</u>
<u n="566" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084">that would give me five thousand pounds</u>
<u n="568" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084">and I'd want to have at least that really <pause dur="short"/> so this is the point</u>
<u n="570" who="S0135" trans="overlap">it's a lot sooner than we thought actually</u>
<u n="571" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and plus if I do move home in September <pause dur="short"/> I mean this is based on me not having to move home which the is the is what what we're aiming for <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to move home</u>
<u n="572" who="S0135">do you not?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="574" who="S0135">how much would you save by moving home though? Not that much</u>
<u n="575" who="S0084">not that much because I'd have to give my mum</u>
<u n="576" who="S0135">how much does she want? A hundred and eighty</u>
<u n="577" who="S0084">A hundred and fifty <pause dur="short"/> so I'd get</u>
<u n="578" who="S0135">hundred</u>
<u n="579" who="S0084">I'd save two hundred pounds more every month for</u>
<u n="580" who="S0135">um but actually if that if that was just for September October November Jan Feb and you knew you were off in March for example</u>
<u n="581" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it would literally be six months <pause dur="short"/> and two sixes are twelve so that'd be an extra grand</u>
<u n="582" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0084">it's worth doing isn't it?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0135">so then technically you could almost leave earlier then <pause dur="short"/> you could almost leave in January</u>
<u n="585" who="S0084">but then my plan was always to leave in March next year</u>
<u n="586" who="S0135" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh was it?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0084">Cos I decided in March right that's it I've gotta get out <pause dur="short"/> this time next year I've gotta be off</u>
<u n="588" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="589" who="S0084">so March is fine <pause dur="short"/> any later than March I would feel like I'm not sticking to the plan</u>
<u n="590" who="S0135">okay <pause dur="short"/> done</u>
<u n="591" who="S0084">okay well that's er that's actually made me feel quite calm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0135" trans="overlap">the really hard thing though is</u>
<u n="593" who="S0084">not spending any money</u>
<u n="594" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you're better than me cos I'm like that <pause dur="short"/> it's really it's completely different though because I have got a lot of money in the bank</u>
<u n="595" who="S0084">yeah you have</u>
<u n="596" who="S0135">that is why I'm just like that <pause dur="short"/> bah bah bah bah bah bah <pause dur="short"/> even if I knew that I had to save up for something <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I could be like that <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to make a sandwich and take in into work in cling film <pause dur="short"/> I'm not going to go to Pret</u>
<u n="597" who="S0084">but you've done really well like in Berlin you could've just sacked it off <pause dur="short"/> you could have booked flights to Thailand <pause dur="short"/> you could've done <pause dur="short"/> cos you've found it quite hard going you know being quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0084">you could have come home every weekend <pause dur="short"/> you were quite savvy with money to be able to save the money you've got <pause dur="short"/> because you thought well you <unclear/> had the sense to do it</u>
<u n="600" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but do you know what though? I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other day some days I I could go three days without spending a single cent because I say say like someone has like got food in the house and I would walk to work and I wouldn't go out <pause dur="short"/> I could literally go there days without spending money <pause dur="short"/> here day in day out I've got my train fare</u>
<u n="601" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0135">I give money to my mum</u>
<u n="603" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0135">and I'm in Pret for at least breakfast at least lunch possibly breakfast as well</u>
<u n="605" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0135">erm I might use my Oyster to go on the tube <pause dur="short"/> might meet <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> for a drink <pause dur="short"/> go out to the cinema with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> maybe <pause dur="short"/> something Blah blah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0135">clothes</u>
<u n="609" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0135">do you like my jeans?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0084"><unclear/> I love them <pause dur="short"/> they're really nice</u>
<u n="612" who="S0135" trans="overlap">I've got them in like a really nice coral colour as well from Dorothy Perkins</u>
<u n="613" who="S0084" trans="overlap">ah lush</u>
<u n="614" who="S0135">Cos once I found they fitted I trawled all the Dorothy Perkins cos on line they only had a six <pause dur="short"/> I was like who's a size six?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="616" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> maybe</u>
<u n="618" who="S0135">yeah so I went round all the Dorothy Perkins shops <pause dur="short"/> so I found these ones in like beige or whatever <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="619" who="S0084">no they're really nice</u>
<u n="620" who="S0135">cos they're a really nice fit aren't they? They're really nice</u>
<u n="621" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no but you also have been trawling the charity shops so it's not like you've been</u>
<u n="622" who="S0135">yes</u>
<u n="623" who="S0084">you know totally splashing the cash</u>
<u n="624" who="S0135">yeah no no <pause dur="short"/> that really nice Kate Moss dress is from the charity shop and hopefully I'll make a profit on it <pause dur="short"/> fingers crossed</u>
<u n="625" who="S0084" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> plus you know at this point you don't know what you're doing in terms of your abode <pause dur="short"/> like it's suiting you right now to be in a  room</u>
<u n="626" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0084">erm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0135">but at least I'm in a I'm in a sort of similarish position as you <pause dur="short"/> like I don't really know what's going on <pause dur="short"/> like I don't even know erm what job I'm gonna do after my Olympics job</u>
<u n="629" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0135">but it's different because my when I was in Berlin my next step was right come home</u>
<u n="631" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0135">and I'm home now and I'm just like yeah it's all just sort of ticking along <pause dur="short"/> and what shall be shall be</u>
<u n="633" who="S0084" trans="overlap">but then so is this job just temporary then?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0084">you can't stay in the Counter Terrorism Unit once the Olympics is over?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0135" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> it's an Olympics Desk Officer</u>
<u n="637" who="S0084">right I see <pause dur="short"/> but maybe <pause dur="short"/> would that lead on to a permanent position do you think?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0135">no at that grade unless I pass my FAB in May</u>
<u n="639" who="S0084">oh no <pause dur="short"/> are you actually gonna do that?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0135" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> I gotta do it <pause dur="short"/> I gotta do it</u>
<u n="641" who="S0084">oh man</u>
<u n="642" who="S0135">it's a two and a half hour exam</u>
<u n="643" who="S0084">that's not the scary one where you were telling me where they have like the people coming in and the actors and they're playing like</u>
<u n="644" who="S0135">oh no <pause dur="short"/> that's for the next level</u>
<u n="645" who="S0084">oh fine</u>
<u n="646" who="S0135">this one is just a written exam</u>
<u n="647" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> good cos that one sounded intense <pause dur="short"/> I remember you saying you weren't going to go to that</u>
<u n="648" who="S0135"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah right that's a no</u>
<u n="649" who="S0084">that's a no from me</u>
<u n="650" who="S0135">yeah so erm that's my plan but <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0135">you should talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0084">she is the best person to speak to about not spending any money</u>
<u n="654" who="S0135" trans="overlap">she's the ultimate <pause dur="short"/> ultimate <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sh</trunc> yeah but she's not tight with it <pause dur="short"/> it's really funny <pause dur="short"/> but then she will she's also got a lot more strict with herself so so a lot of her friends wanna go for er <trunc>m</trunc> <trunc>m</trunc> er meals and dinners like <pause dur="short"/> two of them are one step away from being a partner in their law firm <pause dur="short"/> so they've got</u>
<u n="655" who="S0084">fuck</u>
<u n="656" who="S0135">a lot of money</u>
<u n="657" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0135">whereas she'll be like that <pause dur="short"/> let's go for coffee <pause dur="short"/> she will sip that coffee till it is stone cold</u>
<u n="659" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="660" who="S0135">erm and she'll be like that <pause dur="short"/> no I can't come and do that because I haven't got any money</u>
<u n="661" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="662" who="S0135">I've seen her bank statements <pause dur="short"/> she's literally got no money <pause dur="short"/> cos I opened it by accident <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was sent to me <pause dur="short"/> erm but she's like I really wanna go travelling <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta get out <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta get away <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna hammer it over the summer doing</u>
<u n="663" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="664" who="S0135">whatever <pause dur="short"/> I do not know <pause dur="short"/> get the money <pause dur="short"/> bank it and then go</u>
<u n="665" who="S0084">and she is determined though isn't she</u>
<u n="666" who="S0135">she'll do it <pause dur="short"/> she'll go</u>
<u n="667" who="S0084">what about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0135"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0084">do you think it's on the cards?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0135"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0084">off off the cards? On the rocks</u>
<u n="672" who="S0135" trans="overlap">no I I don't know <pause dur="short"/> they're very much in love but his well his music is his first love <pause dur="short"/> like it really is so</u>
<u n="673" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah she'll always be second</u>
<u n="674" who="S0135">yeah she will be <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know</u>
<u n="675" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I suppose then he's a bit funny isn't he <pause dur="short"/> like when he was like yeah I'm moving to London</u>
<u n="676" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0084">and you enjoy whatever it is that you're doing <pause dur="short"/> to see her</u>
<u n="678" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="679" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0084">ha</u>
<u n="681" who="S0135">and then <trunc>sh</trunc> that was when she came to Berlin <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="682" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0135">I was like alright? And <unclear/> like actually no I'm gonna move into <pause dur="short"/> but at that point when she came to Berlin it was like that <pause dur="short"/> no I'm not moving into <anon type="place"/> cos he needs his own space and whatever blah blah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0135">and then erm</u>
<u n="686" who="S0084">she moved into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0135">she moved to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0135">but <anon type="place"/>'s pretty cool I've gotta say</u>
<u n="690" who="S0084">it's good isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes living in the prison <pause dur="short"/> I find it quite intriguing that she's in the prison</u>
<u n="691" who="S0135">have you visited her yet?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0084">yeah I've been a couple of times</u>
<u n="693" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0084">and the doors do slam like she lives in a prison <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty funny <pause dur="short"/> like she lives in the houses around the prison itself</u>
<u n="695" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0084">on a hill <pause dur="short"/> and erm they're old warden's quarters so the doors</u>
<u n="697" who="S0135">oh God</u>
<u n="698" who="S0084">are made of lead and they do slam <pause dur="short"/> like lights out</u>
<u n="699" who="S0135">oh God</u>
<u n="700" who="S0084">it's really funny <pause dur="short"/> but the flats are lovely <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>th</trunc> whoever owns her flat they've done it up really well</u>
<u n="701" who="S0135" trans="overlap">really nice yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0084">I mean she was living in a  in a  room <pause dur="short"/> I I really would say it's probably not bigger than the Toblerone room when she first moved in and it was probably like four hundred pounds a month all in <pause dur="short"/> it was so cheap</u>
<u n="703" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0084">and then one girl moved out and she got bumped up the list of good rooms <pause dur="short"/> and then they got somebody else in</u>
<u n="705" who="S0135" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> and they'd start off in a shit room and then?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah and then work your way up depending on how long you've been there <pause dur="short"/> like a pecking order</u>
<u n="707" who="S0135">do you know what's so funny though Liz? Take for example <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who got married at twenty-two <pause dur="short"/> Twenty-three was it? Twenty-four?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I'll have a look <pause dur="short"/> mm I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't feel like that long ago but it probably was <pause dur="short"/> I think I was living in Haywards Heath so</u>
<u n="709" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="710" who="S0084">it must have been</u>
<u n="711" who="S0135">I mean her husband Steve has now just quit his teacher training</u>
<u n="712" who="S0084">cheats on her every left right and centre</u>
<u n="713" who="S0135">yeah but it it and he's quit his teacher training now <pause dur="short"/> so that's out the window <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't know what he's gonna do next <pause dur="short"/> but he inherited eighty grand from his grandparents evidently so he doesn't have to know what he's gonna do next</u>
<u n="714" who="S0084" trans="overlap">fuck <pause dur="short"/> that's be the point when you do quit your job I suppose <pause dur="short"/> but that'd be <trunc>f</trunc> pretty foolhardy if you don't know what you're gonna do though</u>
<u n="715" who="S0135">I mean it's not  it's not  a huge amount but oh</u>
<u n="716" who="S0084">it's enough to buy a house</u>
<u n="717" who="S0135" trans="overlap">it yeah it depends <pause dur="short"/> well only if you've got an income <pause dur="short"/> you need</u>
<u n="718" who="S0084">only if you've got an income yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah cos you need a mortgage</u>
<u n="720" who="S0084">no one's gonna lend to you without</u>
<u n="721" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0084">a fixed income</u>
<u n="723" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and income yeah <pause dur="short"/> or your partner who's got a fixed income or something <pause dur="short"/> but I tell you say for example this happens <pause dur="short"/> you book all your flights <pause dur="short"/> I bet you bottom dollar six weeks before you go you will meet the man of your dreams and you probably won't end up going or something</u>
<u n="724" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> I would definitely go</u>
<u n="725" who="S0135" trans="overlap">Cos that is absolutely sod's law <pause dur="short"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="726" who="S0084">well absolutely <pause dur="short"/> well they can come with me <pause dur="short"/> if er if it's the man of my dreams he can come in my handbag</u>
<u n="727" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="728" who="S0084">but erm I meet I might meet the man of my dreams out there <pause dur="short"/> you never know <pause dur="short"/> I think what I need to do now that I've got this plan is now work out where I am going <pause dur="short"/> cos if if Aus is the plan that's fine cos that's perfect cos that's when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes back <pause dur="short"/> so my plan my my theory</u>
<u n="729" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="730" who="S0084">is my thinking that I couldn't actually go with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos one of us might die <pause dur="short"/> like I genuinely think I might</u>
<u n="731" who="S0135">oh how?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0084">kill her</u>
<u n="733" who="S0135">oh right</u>
<u n="734" who="S0084">she's lovely <pause dur="short"/> she's a really nice girl but we would get on each other's nerves</u>
<u n="735" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="736" who="S0084"><unclear/> you know we we we'd really fall out</u>
<u n="737" who="S0135" trans="overlap">what cos she's a bit of a space cadet or?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0084">yeah we're just <pause dur="short"/> we are really really different <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="739" who="S0135">right</u>
<u n="740" who="S0084">over a long period of time we would really grate on each other <pause dur="short"/> I think even after like the first day like being on a plane with each other for twelve hours I think would be a bit taxing <pause dur="short"/> whereas with some people you know you can just rub along with quite nicely</u>
<u n="741" who="S0135" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="742" who="S0084">erm but that might tie in cos her flight's booked her return flight's booked for February <pause dur="short"/> but she's gonna extend it if she needs to</u>
<u n="743" who="S0135">mm mm</u>
<u n="744" who="S0084">Cos she can extend it up to three times <pause dur="short"/> so maybe she'll still be out there if I booked it <pause dur="short"/> if like if I book it in March to fly out in you know whenever</u>
<u n="745" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0084">A couple of months after that <pause dur="short"/> erm then yeah <pause dur="short"/> or I could book it at the beginning of the year couldn't I I suppose <pause dur="short"/> cos I'd have money and I I I'd leave in April</u>
<u n="747" who="S0135" trans="overlap">so you you'd need you need a <trunc>hund</trunc> a thousand five hundred to book the flight? Did you say?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0084">well I I'm only going on what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> recently paid for June flights</u>
<u n="749" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0084">but when I flew at Christmas</u>
<u n="751" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0084">on Boxing day they were one thousand pound return</u>
<u n="753" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="754" who="S0084">so I'm figuring it would be less than that</u>
<u n="755" who="S0135">Cos what I'd be inclined to do would be whenever you hit enough money for the flight</u>
<u n="756" who="S0084">book the flights</u>
<u n="757" who="S0135">is to book the flights</u>
<u n="758" who="S0084">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="759" who="S0135">because then that way</u>
<u n="760" who="S0084">I've gotta go</u>
<u n="761" who="S0135">you're going</u>
<u n="762" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0135">because I know oh at one point you were talking about going this January</u>
<u n="764" who="S0084">yeah but then I got the new job</u>
<u n="765" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0084">which is why I didn't go</u>
<u n="767" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0084">I was gonna go at the end of the year <pause dur="short"/> that was my original plan <pause dur="short"/> but in September when the job came up I was like well I'm gonna  I'm gonna  stay and take that</u>
<u n="769" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="770" who="S0084">because actually it makes more sense go with that skill set</u>
<u n="771" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0084">behind me because then it it would open up more doors than the job that I was doing before for Chloe <pause dur="short"/> and I wanted to kill myself</u>
<u n="773" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0084">erm and er really my plan was when we got back from Croatia to stay at and to stay at my mum's and work my arse off</u>
<u n="775" who="S0135">hammer it</u>
<u n="776" who="S0084">and not spend any money <pause dur="short"/> but obviously I had to move out and all those costs that I incurred</u>
<u n="777" who="S0135">oh yeah</u>
<u n="778" who="S0084" trans="overlap">like I had to pay my deposit and</u>
<u n="779" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0084">we'd been on holiday so there was</u>
<u n="781" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="782" who="S0084">you know you're already</u>
<u n="783" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="784" who="S0084">you know having spent money there and it just wasn't very feasible</u>
<u n="785" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0084">but I think yeah you're right <pause dur="short"/> I'll probably book the flight for like yeah maybe start of the year</u>
<u n="787" who="S0135">when at what  at what  point of of the year are they cheap? Cos you know like if you book them really far in advance you get an early bird deal or</u>
<u n="788" who="S0084" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well the winter would be cheap <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="789" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="790" who="S0084">this sort of time really</u>
<u n="791" who="S0135"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0135">booking for a winter flight do you mean?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0135">is that the cheapest way?</u>
<u n="796" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I suppose from this point on</u>
<u n="797" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0084">between April and September are the cheapest flights cos that's when it's winter <pause dur="short"/> sort of September round to March is peak season</u>
<u n="799" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="800" who="S0084">and obviously that hits a head at Christmas cos it's the hottest part and it's Christmas so</u>
<u n="801" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0084">if my flights on boxing day were a thousand pounds</u>
<u n="803" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="804" who="S0084">but that was with erm budget China bucket airlines</u>
<u n="805" who="S0135"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="806" who="S0084">which only had one <trunc>s</trunc> TV set in each headrest</u>
<u n="807" who="S0135" trans="overlap">nice <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="808" who="S0084">but the thing is if you're  if you're  not that fussed when you go surely you can find a flight</u>
<u n="809" who="S0135">A flexible one</u>
<u n="810" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and you know like if you  if you  there're like eight changeovers you can get really cheap flights <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="811" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0084">you can go on standby</u>
<u n="813" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0084">and live at the airport for a week</u>
<u n="815" who="S0135" trans="overlap">what about working for an airline quickly?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0084">very very quickly</u>
<u n="817" who="S0135">qantas</u>
<u n="818" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0135">very quickly</u>
<u n="820" who="S0084">very</u>
<u n="821" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0084">there might be some sort of law about not getting like perks for the first three months</u>
<u n="823" who="S0135" trans="overlap">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="824" who="S0084">you might have to pass your probation and then you're fucked</u>
<u n="825" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I think also like I'm sure you've got all the guide books and that that kind of gumph and that already</u>
<u n="826" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="827" who="S0135">but like figuring out what is it you fancy doing when you get there <pause dur="short"/> or do you just literally wanna just touch down and take it from there <pause dur="short"/> did you wanna go across to Asia? And the start of you know putting some meat on the bones of the plan</u>
<u n="828" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0135">sort of make it a reality</u>
<u n="830" who="S0084">I think when I started thinking about it I thought well I'd fly into Melbourne because that's where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lives and because that's the place that I like the most</u>
<u n="831" who="S0135">ah <pause dur="short"/> so you can go</u>
<u n="832" who="S0084" trans="overlap">if it's it's quite I could stay with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0135">ah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0084">very temporarily</u>
<u n="835" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0084">and just say to her look can I just sleep on your floor for a couple of weeks? I'll take a sleeping bag <pause dur="short"/> and I will actively look for jobs straight away</u>
<u n="837" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="838" who="S0084">I mean like have a nice time settling in and you know be with her <pause dur="short"/> but your money gets used up so quickly when you're there that I'd wanna work straight away <pause dur="short"/> get a job straight away like in the first couple of weeks</u>
<u n="839" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0084">erm but it would take time so I'd like do a bit of sight-seeing in that time <pause dur="short"/> and maybe fly over to Sydney and see Tasha and get a job started straight away and then I could move out</u>
<u n="841" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0084">or it depends on her situation <pause dur="short"/> cos she's had a spare room for a while and it depends what she's doing <pause dur="short"/> cos we could move out together and then at least you know you've got somebody <pause dur="short"/> and then use that as my base and then save money</u>
<u n="843" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="844" who="S0084">and then work there for maybe six months <pause dur="short"/> and then go travelling <pause dur="short"/> I think because I'd wanna get my money coming in straight away <pause dur="short"/> and then I can use that as a base and have long weekends and</u>
<u n="845" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="846" who="S0084">and then keep money and then come home through Asia <pause dur="short"/> and then maybe do a few tours in places that I didn't feel that safe</u>
<u n="847" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0084">I'd like to go over to New Zealand as well <pause dur="short"/> you know go and see some places that I <trunc>w</trunc> like that I <trunc>rea</trunc> <unclear/> Either that I missed on the first time or</u>
<u n="849" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="850" who="S0084">like one of my colleagues <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she  she is erm from New Zealand <pause dur="short"/> she's a Kiwi <pause dur="short"/> and we worked together for about nine months <pause dur="short"/> and she's just moved back there <pause dur="short"/> down the</u>
<u n="851" who="S0135">nice</u>
<u n="852" who="S0084">the South island <pause dur="short"/> in Dunedin <pause dur="short"/> and er she's always like yeah come up come up cos last year obviously my plan was to be in Australia for Christmas <pause dur="short"/>  you've gotta come and spend Christmas with us and</u>
<u n="853" who="S0135">ah how sweet</u>
<u n="854" who="S0084">and she's really cute <pause dur="short"/> she's got two little kids and her husband Matt who's a professor who teaches at the university</u>
<u n="855" who="S0135" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0084">so they're both really clever <pause dur="short"/> she's got a PhD <pause dur="short"/> and she was working as like like an office <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> basically while to support him doing his PhD <pause dur="short"/> it's like love</u>
<u n="857" who="S0135">that is love man</u>
<u n="858" who="S0084">it took her ten years to do her PhD because she decided to have kids in between</u>
<u n="859" who="S0135">fool</u>
<u n="860" who="S0084">hilarious</u>
<u n="861" who="S0135">I pity the fool</u>
<u n="862" who="S0084">she's really smart <pause dur="short"/> um so yeah there's definitely that would be the main plan I think because I'd want to work as quickly as possible</u>
<u n="863" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0084">so that I don't use up all my funds</u>
<u n="865" who="S0135">is there any way of? Does your company have a branch in Australia?</u>
<u n="866" who="S0084">yeah it does <pause dur="short"/> but I think you have to  you have to  wait for them to have a job to apply</u>
<u n="867" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="868" who="S0084">and I've just I've never ever seen a job advertised for the Melbourne office <pause dur="short"/> but I'm gonna speak to my group director <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know I used to do <unclear/> for?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="870" who="S0084">and erm see if a job ever comes up <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a different business stream <pause dur="short"/> it's education as opposed to English language teaching <pause dur="short"/> it's slightly different <pause dur="short"/> erm but my job would be the same <pause dur="short"/> erm I might talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she works in education <pause dur="short"/> she does my job at the senior level</u>
<u n="871" who="S0135">yeah and you don't know also like even if they don't have a job maybe they know someone that looks for temporary people to do marking of er some sort of thing like you do at IELTS marking or something like that</u>
<u n="872" who="S0084">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="873" who="S0135">I mean you just don't really know</u>
<u n="874" who="S0084">well I think I would definitely get in contact with people in the office there and just say well I'm planning to move over and I just wondered if you've got jobs or how you go about recruiting people through the office and</u>
<u n="875" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0084">just sort of branch out really <pause dur="short"/> cos you never really get you never really meet them <pause dur="short"/> you never really work with them</u>
<u n="877" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="878" who="S0084">even though we've spoken <pause dur="short"/> we're working globally now <pause dur="short"/> we never really do so <pause dur="short"/> they're just so far away</u>
<u n="879" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0084">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> oh <pause dur="short"/> so it's certainly um the <trunc>f</trunc> the basis of a plan</u>
<u n="881" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah 'tis a plan</u>
<u n="882" who="S0084">'Tis a plan <pause dur="short"/> thanks Mary</u>
<u n="883" who="S0135">yes I'm glad I came cos otherwise you probably would have figured out you could save eight thousand pounds an hour</u>
<u n="884" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="885" who="S0135">or it would take you twenty years to save up five grand or something</u>
<u n="886" who="S0084">yeah you you've erm you've certainly helped me with the maths there</u>
<u n="887" who="S0135">whoa <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0084">God what the hell's the matter with me?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0135">ha</u>
<u n="890" who="S0084">I think from this point on I need to just start being more savvy with money</u>
<u n="891" who="S0135">have you paid for all of your <trunc>t</trunc> trip so far? Like the hotels and flights and everything?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0084">yeah basically <pause dur="short"/> I haven't obviously it's things like petrol that I have to just</u>
<u n="893" who="S0135">keep an eye on</u>
<u n="894" who="S0084">budget for before</u>
<u n="895" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="896" who="S0084">so Brighton I'm gonna drive down just just for the sake of convenience but I think I need to think is it actually worth driving when I could get National Express and stuff <pause dur="short"/> like for the wedding</u>
<u n="897" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0084">it's first thing on Saturday morning <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna drive down and</u>
<u n="899" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="900" who="S0084">it's much easier to do that <pause dur="short"/> and I don't have to worry <pause dur="short"/> and I can take whatever I need for the wedding and that</u>
<u n="901" who="S0135">where are you staying on the Saturday night then?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0084">in the hotel</u>
<u n="903" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="904" who="S0084">in Kemptown <pause dur="short"/> in the B and B</u>
<u n="905" who="S0135">oh right you are</u>
<u n="906" who="S0084">and then I'll just pop in and see her on Sunday or something but erm</u>
<u n="907" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0084">for for <anon type="place"/> I'll probably be cos it's not far from here I'll probably just get the train</u>
<u n="909" who="S0135">yep</u>
<u n="910" who="S0084">I wonder if you could get quite a cheap train ticket versus spending like twenty-five quid on petrol</u>
<u n="911" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="912" who="S0084">or thirty quid on petrol <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't really make much sense</u>
<u n="913" who="S0135">God you're gonna have to be really dedicated</u>
<u n="914" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0135">like you're gonna <trunc>ha</trunc> you need to prove how much you want it because</u>
<u n="916" who="S0084">it's gonna be a real test</u>
<u n="917" who="S0135">if it all boils down  if it all boils down  to money basically</u>
<u n="918" who="S0084">which it does</u>
<u n="919" who="S0135">then you have to make those sacrifices</u>
<u n="920" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="921" who="S0135">those short term sacrifices</u>
<u n="922" who="S0084">well that's why I've said no to all the hen parties <pause dur="short"/> well I think I might just do that from now on anyway</u>
<u n="923" who="S0135" trans="overlap">oh no but that is just so hard</u>
<u n="924" who="S0084">it's really hard because I was so looking forward to Barcelona and I hadn't seen <unclear/> for ages and I knew I just know they're gonna have a lovely lovely time</u>
<u n="925" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="926" who="S0084">and Barcelona's beautiful</u>
<u n="927" who="S0135">yeah and you really like Barcelona</u>
<u n="928" who="S0084">and I mean it might even get to the point where I cancel Belfast <pause dur="short"/> but we'll see cos that's July and I haven't got anything planned <pause dur="short"/> like May is gonna be expensive</u>
<u n="929" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0084">April and May <pause dur="short"/> if I'm not careful <pause dur="short"/> erm and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to go to <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> for her birthday in June <pause dur="short"/> like the Jubilee weekend so that's the beginning of June</u>
<u n="931" who="S0135" trans="overlap">I mean technically these things could all be done on the <trunc>ch</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> they don't necessarily have to be</u>
<u n="932" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0135">costly</u>
<u n="934" who="S0084">but like if it was in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday like if we drive there'll be four of us in the car so we'll just all chip in for petrol</u>
<u n="935" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0084">so that's going to be cheaper than getting the train to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> then we'll stay at her dad's free <pause dur="short"/> and then so it'll just be drinking money</u>
<u n="937" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="938" who="S0084">and It's <anon type="place"/> so presumably it's north therefore it's cheap</u>
<u n="939" who="S0135">yeah should be about fifty P a pint</u>
<u n="940" who="S0084">er at least <pause dur="short"/> if not I'm gonna be very annoyed</u>
<u n="941" who="S0135">otherwise you're on tap water</u>
<u n="942" who="S0084">yes <pause dur="short"/> and plus I think I really can sort of drum up some crap in here and sell Ebay all my life because</u>
<u n="943" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you ever sell anything on Ebay?</u>
<u n="944" who="S0084">I tried once and got really bored with it</u>
<u n="945" who="S0135">I'm addicted now</u>
<u n="946" who="S0084">are you?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think you just have to do your research though <pause dur="short"/> before you list anything</u>
<u n="948" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="949" who="S0135">have a look online <pause dur="short"/> see if there's anything else similar and then see if it shifts</u>
<u n="950" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="951" who="S0135">Cos sometimes people you know try and sell something <pause dur="short"/> there's no market if it doesn't go anywhere</u>
<u n="952" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="953" who="S0135">so like keep an eye on stuff that's actually selling and see see if you've got any like labelled clothes for example</u>
<u n="954" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="955" who="S0135">you know <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0084">yeah well not with my Primani wardrobe but certainly <pause dur="short"/> I mean and I've got things like a digital camera that I don't use now because I've got my Smart phone that</u>
<u n="957" who="S0135">but you will wanna take that with you if you went travelling though wouldn't you? Or <trunc>d</trunc> you'd want a digital camera</u>
<u n="958" who="S0084">well it's an eight mega-pixel camera which is what my phone is</u>
<u n="959" who="S0135">oh really?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0084">but I suppose I wouldn't be able to use my phone so that's actually quite a good point</u>
<u n="961" who="S0135">I mean it I mean those sorts of things though <pause dur="short"/> you could probably make all that money at the last stage of the plan</u>
<u n="962" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="963" who="S0135">like when you need to hike it up <pause dur="short"/> like you don't need to sell everything now</u>
<u n="964" who="S0084">yeah true</u>
<u n="965" who="S0135">I mean I suppose when you do move away you would <trunc>f</trunc> try and sell the bed</u>
<u n="966" who="S0084">sell the bed yeah</u>
<u n="967" who="S0135">if even if you ended up having to free-cycle it <pause dur="short"/> it's I don't know if you could sell the TV or give it to your mum or whatever</u>
<u n="968" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0135">or put it into storage <pause dur="short"/> you know sell whatever bits you know <pause dur="short"/> but that was all that's all stuff you'd do at the very end maybe</u>
<u n="970" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="971" who="S0135">erm</u>
<u n="972" who="S0084">just see how you go</u>
<u n="973" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> see how you go</u>
<u n="974" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah cos basically all this stuff <pause dur="short"/> I mean you might find that you never come back</u>
<u n="975" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="976" who="S0084">or you might just be <trunc>y</trunc> a constant hermit</u>
<u n="977" who="S0135">A hobo</u>
<u n="978" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="979" who="S0135">A nomad</u>
<u n="980" who="S0084">A hobo <pause dur="short"/> actually <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>' friend is called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for just this very reason <pause dur="short"/> it's just</u>
<u n="981" who="S0135" trans="overlap">wait <trunc>w</trunc> oh as what a nickname or a real name?</u>
<u n="982" who="S0084" trans="overlap">as a nickname yeah</u>
<u n="983" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="984" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm I dunno I can't remember what her real name is but she's emigrating to Canada I think this weekend <pause dur="short"/> she's going to erm <pause dur="short"/> she's going to <pause dur="short"/> where is she going? <anon type="place"/> for some sort of leaving emigrating party or something <pause dur="short"/> well that was her excuse</u>
<u n="985" who="S0135">is she emigrating with work?</u>
<u n="986" who="S0084">erm <pause dur="short"/> no she doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how she's emigrating <pause dur="short"/> I really don't</u>
<u n="987" who="S0135">family?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0084">I think she's got a girlfriend out there or something I don't</u>
<u n="989" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="990" who="S0084">no I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> but but I think she tried to emigrate there once before but then got bored so came back <pause dur="short"/> and now maybe had a change of heart <pause dur="short"/> I think this is  I think this is  at least the second emigrating party they've had for her</u>
<u n="991" who="S0135" trans="overlap">attempt <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="992" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="993" who="S0084">like seriously will you just leave now</u>
<u n="994" who="S0135" trans="overlap">bye <pause dur="short"/> bye <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0084">stop coming back</u>
<u n="996" who="S0135">what does your mum make to everything?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0084">I think she knows that restless</u>
<u n="998" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="999" who="S0084">she knows that I've got itchy feet and I think she worries that I think she probably it's a double edged sword <pause dur="short"/> she wants me to go but she doesn't want me to go <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0135">really?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0084">I think she wants me to go because otherwise I'll always wonder why</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0084">and like feel like I've missed out <pause dur="short"/> but at the same time she doesn't want me to go because she knows if I do go I'll be really far away and it'd be for quite a long time so</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0084">I think she feels a bit sad about that</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0084">and she likes the fact that now that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s moving has moved back that we're all in the same city and it's all really easy and I could just <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>f</trunc> last week I just popped round for lunch</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0084">and we had to go and sit in the garden because it was so warm</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0135">oh and your mum has got a gorgeous garden as well</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and mum's got a really nice garden <pause dur="short"/> and so she really likes that that we can just see each other for a cup of tea or you know it's really easy</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah without making sort of plans six months in advance to meet up or something</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0084">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos how long have you been in <anon type="place"/> now?</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0084">too long</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0135">I've</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well if I finished my degree in September O nine</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0135">okay so</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0084">two and a half years <pause dur="short"/> cos I've been at the press just over two years now</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0135">where did you do your degree?</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0084"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1022" who="S0135">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I forgot about <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0135">two and a half years <pause dur="short"/> I think my limit anywhere is two years <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0135">limit for like doing something or being somewhere or something like that</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0084">that's the point when you're like well what's next then</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0135" trans="overlap">what's next? Yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0084">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0084">Cos it might take you you know that's the problem where you think right I've got to change <pause dur="short"/> and it might take you another year or half a year to get yourself together</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0084">but it's that point where you think right well I've gotta do something about this</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but your mum could come and visit you</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0084">erm <trunc>sh</trunc> I'd never be able to afford a flight for her and she'd never be able to afford it</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0135">ah</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0084">I'd love her to <pause dur="short"/> I'd love them both to come out</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0135">ah</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0084">because you know they've never really travelled themselves and like that's quite upsetting that thought but they don't notice</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0135" trans="overlap">but <trunc>do</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc> not everyone wants to <pause dur="short"/> like I met a guy <pause dur="short"/> not met a guy obviously I don't meet guys any more</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0135">but I was talking to a guy someone's flatmate on Saturday night and um he didn't use his passport until five years ago <pause dur="short"/> and he went to like Tunisia or something for a holiday</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0135">and he's been to Egypt and something else since <pause dur="short"/> but he can take it or leave it <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't want to go to Asia <pause dur="short"/> he's not interested in seeing Machu Picchu or whatever</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0135">in Peru <pause dur="short"/> or you know he's genuinely perfectly happy thank you very much in England</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> how old was he?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0135">our age</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0135">yeah so I mean it's not for everyone</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0084" trans="overlap">it's interesting to know <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> not everyone wants to go backpacking with lamas <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0084">yeah I think both of them would love to see more of the world</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0135" trans="overlap">do you think?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0084">but yeah and I know my dad would</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0135">would <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0084">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> I mean she's scared of flying so that's a bit of an issue <pause dur="short"/> but with my dad definitely he'd love there's certain parts of America I know he'd love <pause dur="short"/> and he'd love Canada and New Zealand cos he's so like</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0084">he'd love it <pause dur="short"/> he'd go absolutely wild erm</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0135">is he? Can he not afford it then? Or?</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0084">no no he'd never be able to afford it</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0135">that he erm I would find that really frustrating if I worked my whole life</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's so depressing to watch it</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0135">and I couldn't afford to do what I wanted to do <pause dur="short"/> iE go and</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0135">go to New Zealand Australia whatever blah blah</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0084">and it <trunc>make</trunc> it's what makes you think well well in that case I've just got to do it <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't want to get into that position so</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0135">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> you don't  You don't  want life to well get in the way or whatever they say <pause dur="short"/> you know and erm get swept up in all that</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0084" trans="overlap">but that's not <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think you know they they had they did the norm <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0084">they met <pause dur="short"/> they got married <pause dur="short"/> they bought a house <pause dur="short"/> they had kids <pause dur="short"/> you know they had the two point four family life <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0084">I think you know it still kills me that it's just not what how my dad thought it was gonna be</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0084">but that's life <pause dur="short"/> you know you you pick yourself up and you carry on <pause dur="short"/> that's what he's done and</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0084">it's the best of a bad situation <pause dur="short"/> like they're civil to each other and I think really that's all you can sort of hope for now but I think every so often he says something and I think I dunno how or where he is that that's not a possibility <pause dur="short"/> like he's like oh <unclear/> on <pause dur="short"/> you know fingers crossed we win the pools and then we can all have a lovely holiday <pause dur="short"/> and the five of us can have some money <pause dur="short"/> and er <trunc>d</trunc> I think he's never really detached himself from that idea like it it's always going to be five of us <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is slightly different <pause dur="short"/> did I tell you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s pregnant? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna have a baby <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna be an aunty <pause dur="short"/> I just realised I probably haven't told you</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0135"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> your brother?</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0135">he's pregnant?</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0084">well he's not pregnant <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s pregnant</u>
<u n="1082" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1083" who="S0135">I was like a pregnant man? Like that pregnant man thing</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No no no no no no</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0135" trans="overlap">fucking hell <pause dur="short"/> hasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> already got two kids?</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0084">well no <pause dur="short"/> he hasn't got any kids <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got two girls from a previous relationship</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0135"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s pregnant <pause dur="short"/> dweeb <pause dur="short"/> yeah fine</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1089" who="S0135">his wife is pregnant</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0084">his wife is pregnant and then</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0135">you're not allowed to be an aunty cos you don't talk to your brother</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0084">I don't talk to him no <pause dur="short"/> erm my dad called me a few weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> and he was like I've just spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> it was like Thursday afternoon</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0084">I've spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> you'll never guess <pause dur="short"/> they're pregnant <pause dur="short"/> it's so exciting <pause dur="short"/> and he was so pleased and so chuffed <pause dur="short"/> he sounded so excited <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0135">Cos the oldest one must be what eight ten years old?</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0084">ah no <pause dur="short"/> she's sixteen <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0135">why did they decide to have a kid now then?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0084">I don't think they did <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's the most planned of pregnancies</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0084">well er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s forty-one <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be forty-two in September</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0135">she's forty-one? I mean in the grand scheme of things that's probably quite old for kids</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0084" trans="overlap">well she'll be forty-one when the baby's born <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they'll be sixties when the baby's eighteen <pause dur="short"/> so it's pretty old <pause dur="short"/> if they have had their three month scan <pause dur="short"/> everything's fine and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cried and blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> but I just thought this is the point where we are not gonna be able to part ways because I'm gonna have to see that kid <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna have to be involved er because my dad is so excited about it</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0135">when's it being born?</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0084">September <pause dur="short"/> which I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday his birthday is the first of September and it's due about the same sort of time</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0135">but you're gonna have to reconcile with <trunc>m</trunc> with erm</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0084">well I sent him a text message the next day I think just saying oh erm congratulations <pause dur="short"/> dad told me your really exciting news <pause dur="short"/> I'm really happy for you both <pause dur="short"/> I hope you're both okay <pause dur="short"/> and I'm sorry we haven't spoken for ages <pause dur="short"/> blah</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0135" trans="overlap">that's good of you yeah</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0084">well I just thought er you know now is the time <pause dur="short"/> and I thought about doing it at Christmas</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0084">but I didn't and erm he didn't</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0135">he didn't? Oh he didn't yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0084" trans="overlap">he didn't get in contact <pause dur="short"/> and then he replied almost straight away and said oh er you know we're really excited <pause dur="short"/> thanks for your you know your kind words and yeah I'm sorry too <pause dur="short"/> um I'll definitely get in touch with dad and we should organise a a meet soon which was like a month ago <pause dur="short"/> so that hasn't happened</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0084">er never mind the fact that he's only like an hour down the road <pause dur="short"/> and er he said he went for the scan and he was really emotional and it was you know they're really excited about it</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0135">it's his first baby?</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0084">yeah his first baby</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0135">yeah okay yeah</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0084">so my dad's proper first grandchild <pause dur="short"/> so the girls were quite shocked when they found out</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0135"><event desc="sound of fast intake of breath"/></u>
<u n="1120" who="S0084">but they're <trunc>g</trunc> coming around to the idea now <pause dur="short"/> cos they're sixteen and fourteen so they were a bit like mum what are you doing? You're like an old woman now <pause dur="short"/> you can't have a baby</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0135" trans="overlap">ah ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> does does she actually want one though because <trunc>sh</trunc> she was quite career orientated isn't she?</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0084" trans="overlap">she was <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah she is <pause dur="short"/> erm I don't know if it's morally they would have never considered a an abortion or whether they just want to have a baby</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0135">right</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0084">I don't know but um I mean financially they can afford it <pause dur="short"/> I think it's just like health reasons <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos that's the other thing that it's risky</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0084">it's really risky erm I think it's more risky if you haven't had a child</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0135">right <pause dur="short"/> if it's your first one</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0084">which she has</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0084">so it lowers the risk <pause dur="short"/> but obviously you know you're in your forties so it does runs a risk</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0084">um but everything is healthy <pause dur="short"/> anna's healthy <pause dur="short"/> the baby's healthy <pause dur="short"/> so unfortunately as much as I would like not to ever have to see them again erm that isn't an option</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0135" trans="overlap">what was it? I know I always ask you this <pause dur="short"/> but what was the last thing and why did it end so on bad terms?</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0084">erm he it was the Christmas before last and it had been er just over a year <pause dur="short"/> and I was messaging him to find out what his plans were and to see if he wanted to see dad and when and what</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0084">and I think the year before dad had seen him on Christmas day because they hadn't had the girls <pause dur="short"/> and we'd seen mum <pause dur="short"/> because of course dad can go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> mum doesn't have anybody to spend Christmas with if we're not with her</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0084">so that's what they done <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>following</trunc> that year that I'd emailed him I was thinking would they have the girls or not <pause dur="short"/> and so I emailed them and said are you having the girls? Are you gonna invite dad over? It might make more sense for you to invite dad for Christmas day if you want to</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0084">um but just let me know and I'll try and organise stuff as well</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0084">and he wrote back just saying well if you know we've not got the girls <pause dur="short"/> and of course we will invite dad because we love dad <pause dur="short"/> subtext you don't love dad <pause dur="short"/> um I'm just wondering why you always seem to put your own mother first <pause dur="short"/> and I'm just really confused because we don't you know it seems very strange that dad's feelings always come second <pause dur="short"/> blah de blah blah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0135">he needn't have written that</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0084" trans="overlap">so it was really cutting <pause dur="short"/> it it er came back straight like that in an email <pause dur="short"/> he must have just fired it off <pause dur="short"/> and I don't I just thought even if you now feel really guilty he never followed it up with anything <pause dur="short"/> he never <trunc>f</trunc> he never wrote back and was like sorry that was off the cuff <pause dur="short"/> I didn't mean it</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I didn't even think it through or anything</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0084">I didn't reply and</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0084">I thought am I being really selfish <pause dur="short"/> I spoke to mum about it <pause dur="short"/> and I was obviously I was really upset and I just and fucked off because I think</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0135">it's not true</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0084">I'm the eldest <pause dur="short"/> it always falls to me to organise it</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0084">and it's not fucking true</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0135">yeah it's not true <pause dur="short"/> that's the most annoying thing <pause dur="short"/> it's unjustified</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0084">yeah and where has it come from? It's come let out of left centre</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0135">left field yeah</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0084">left field because all I ever do is try and make sure that his feelings are taken into consideration so you can fuck off <pause dur="short"/> and in fact how often do you see dad?</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0084">so even like last Christmas my dad didn't see him for like two or three weeks after Christmas <pause dur="short"/> he had the presents for the girls <pause dur="short"/> er it wasn't till the end of January that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually got his fucking act together and came to see my dad <pause dur="short"/> he bought him a massive state-of-the-art TV <pause dur="short"/> talk about guilt</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0135" trans="overlap">guilty <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0084">erm</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0135">but nice nice</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0084">my dad was like my dad called me and was like I've got a new TV</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0135"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1164" who="S0084">he was so excited <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0084">talk about buying your love</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0084">he lives just down the road <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> in Chelmsford still is he?</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0084" trans="overlap">there's absolutely no excuse <pause dur="short"/> yeah Chelmsford</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0084">and he had the the balls to say to me that I don't love my dad <pause dur="short"/> so he can just fuck off</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0135">that's so weird</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and this just came after a long list of you know the wedding saga</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0084">and and meeting him in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> everyone crying but then <pause dur="short"/> you know when we went to that meal where everyone cried</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0084">and er me thinking like that was us turning a corner</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0135">yeah turning the corner yeah</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0084">but never then never hearing from him and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s obviously was twenty-one last year</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0084">and he didn't call her <pause dur="short"/> didn't text her <pause dur="short"/> didn't send a card <pause dur="short"/> for Richard's twenty-first whenever that was he gave him two hundred and fifty pounds worth of HMV vouchers <pause dur="short"/> or like a hundred pounds or like a really decent amount</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0135" trans="overlap">something substantial yeah</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0135">why do you think that?</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0084" trans="overlap">and came for a party and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but we had a do <pause dur="short"/> um we had a do and he just um</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0135">ooh someone <unclear/> Yep</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0084">he just did nothing and I just though you know what</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0135">it's really weird</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0084">it's rude <pause dur="short"/> it's really fucking rude</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah it's rude</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1192" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> you know it's getting on a bit <pause dur="short"/> do you wanna just stay?</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0135">problem is it is getting quite late I've got um I'm seeing this lady in</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0084">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> what is that?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0135"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and um she cancelled my appointment today that I had in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1196" who="S0084">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0135">it's tomorrow now</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0084">what time is it?</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0135">well it's at two</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0135">but the problem is that because I can never rely on the damn traffic</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0135">I just don't know <pause dur="short"/> you can't go</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0084" trans="overlap">you're not confident</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0135">you can't guarantee how long you'll be on the M25 for</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0135">and I don't wanna miss it <pause dur="short"/> so I probably will go back tonight <pause dur="short"/> but thanks anyway my love <pause dur="short"/> what are you up to tomorrow anyway? Have you got plans or just chilling or?</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0084">erm no real plans for the day <pause dur="short"/> I've got to go and do a few bits in town <pause dur="short"/> take some stuff back which is nice <pause dur="short"/> rather than spend money</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0135" trans="overlap">oh clothes?</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0084">and stuff that I got for Moulin Rouge <pause dur="short"/> not Moulin Rouge <pause dur="short"/> salon Rouge <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0135">oh for the dressing up party?</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0084">yeah the burlesque thing <pause dur="short"/> so take all that back</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0135" trans="overlap">Good girl <pause dur="short"/> money money money</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0084">take that back <pause dur="short"/> take some stuff to the charity shop that's just rank that you could never sell</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0135">are you sure you can't sell it?</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0084">it's something that I got from a charity shop <pause dur="short"/> it was like a red satin robe that I thought you could wear as like a sort of thing for the burlesque night <pause dur="short"/> but I was never planning on wearing it <pause dur="short"/> and I only bought it for ninety-nine P so</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0135">A good find <unclear/></u>
<u n="1220" who="S0084">and then I found some stains on it so rank</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0135">nice</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0084">nice is nice</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0084">and I've got a few things to get from Boots</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> and then I'm seeing Claire and Matt tomorrow night</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0135">who's Claire and Matt?</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0084">Claire is my work buddy</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0135">ah</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0084">erm we started on the same day</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0135">oh right</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0084">erm she's a really nice girl actually <pause dur="short"/> really fun and this is who I'm doing the recording for cos she's the manager of the corpus</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0084">erm so she's in charge of that <pause dur="short"/> she's just finished her PhD <pause dur="short"/> she's like a linguist as well</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0084">erm really really clever but really sort of down to earth with it which is nice <pause dur="short"/> and her boyfriend Matt is just finishing off his PhD and he is scarily clever <pause dur="short"/> like he's really nice and doesn't make you feel stupid or anything</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0135">yeah oh that's good</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0084">but he's he's just up there <pause dur="short"/> he's on another level</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0135">okay</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0084">with his cleverness <pause dur="short"/> erm but they've invited me round for a bottle of wine <pause dur="short"/> so I might go round there <pause dur="short"/> and then they said oh we might go into town <pause dur="short"/> but I might say like let's just like keep it in the house</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0084"><unclear/> a bottle of wine or something</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0084">it's always a bit safer</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0084">or maybe we should just go for a pint</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0135">otherwise you'll get absolutely wasted</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0084">absolutely wasted <pause dur="short"/> but then that's that's the danger because then you're like yeah yeah have my card</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0135">oh God <pause dur="short"/> keep it behind the bar</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0084" trans="overlap">yeah fifty quid on the card <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Well no cos then they're like yeah that'll be a hundred pounds</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh shit <pause dur="short"/> it's not my card</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0084">it's not me</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0135" trans="overlap">just run off yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then what are you doing on Saturday</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0084">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think probably seeing the fam at some point<unclear/></u>
<u n="1255" who="S0135" trans="overlap">which one? Which bit?</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0084">which bit? I think pop in and see mum briefly on Saturday</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0135">what's she doing with herself then? Sort of keeping herself busy a and that <pause dur="short"/> is she just sort of like campaigning <pause dur="short"/> keeping abreast of all the  and all that sort of stuff and</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0084">current affairs yeah</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0135">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0084">yeah just all of the usual really</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0084">she's um</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0135">gardening and</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0084">she's got a friend who's got cancer and it's really yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty um pretty serious <pause dur="short"/> got some sort of rare cancer</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0135">oh God</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0084">um and she's been helping her out <pause dur="short"/> she's an author</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0084">she's been helping her out with a bit of like sorting her life out basically</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0084" trans="overlap">but I think it obviously it's massively draining on my mum <pause dur="short"/> my mum's already like</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0084">obviously she's a <trunc>depressi</trunc> a depressive so it's obviously quite um she's really quite volatile about stuff like that so</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0135" trans="overlap">it's difficult yeah</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0084">er I think she's alright</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0135">Good</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0084">the thing is she doesn't ever talk to me <pause dur="short"/> it's the complete opposite of you with your mum when she's you know she's not sort of like you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="1277" who="S0135" trans="overlap">I had that third hand though</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0084">you had that yeah</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0135">third hand though <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't to me <pause dur="short"/> that was to someone else who told someone else who told me within the <unclear/> So that was third hand</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to me or something so</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0084">Good</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0084">yeah um</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0135">but who do <trunc>you</trunc> I I assume thought <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that she will talk to her friends about it though <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0084">I hope so</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0135">someone else</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0084">yeah and and in fact I'm pretty sure she does</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0084">and I think it's just that she feels like she doesn't want to burden me with it</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0084">yeah which is <trunc>f</trunc> fine <pause dur="short"/> but I</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0084">also want her to to know that she can if she wants to but</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0084">also selfishly I sort of don't want her to</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> good and also don't forget she you know mother daughter relationship she should technically go to her friends or partner or somebody else</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0135">and it should be all upward <pause dur="short"/> it should be you going to her with all your problems</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0084">it should be all upward <pause dur="short"/> escalate up <pause dur="short"/> don't cascade down</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0135">that's it <pause dur="short"/> that's it that's it <pause dur="short"/> well we've already had it cascading down</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0084">we have</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0135" trans="overlap">and now it's our turn to send it upwards and let them</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0084">yeah keep the crazy up there <unclear/></u>
<u n="1307" who="S0135">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0084" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah well I don't I really I think she's fine actually <pause dur="short"/> she likes her little house <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0084">she likes her garden and she's <pause dur="short"/> when I went round last weekend she'd been out in the garden digging which for her is a really good sign <pause dur="short"/> like last year she wasn't <pause dur="short"/> she didn't really feel motivated to get out <unclear/></u>
<u n="1311" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0084">I think she had quite a difficult time of it <pause dur="short"/> whereas this year she feels like</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0084">right let's get on it and that's why I try to go round like at least once a week</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0084">I mean obviously I don't want to worry about her that in extent</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0135">no</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0084">but it's nice to sort of check in and</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1321" who="S0135">but isn't <pause dur="short"/> is this something that came about relatively recently? Or do you think she's always been prone to being a bit?</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0084" trans="overlap">she's always been like that <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah she was really bad when we were growing up <pause dur="short"/> really bad <pause dur="short"/> I think because with Richard's <pause dur="short"/> you know imagine if you knew something was wrong with your kid but no one believed you <pause dur="short"/> and everyone thought it was you being a bad mum</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0135" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0084">like even if you won't a depressive</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0084">that'd be fucking hard and</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0135">it wasn't sort of diagnosed and it wasn't?</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0084">it wasn't diagnosed until he was a teenager and and also having your husband doubt you <pause dur="short"/> like that was the beginning of the end I think</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0084">it's to not feel support from her her husband <pause dur="short"/> and because my dad just was he would want to</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0084">I think he was just incapable of doing it because he didn't really want to believe that his son had this condition</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0084">and because it's so intangible</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0084">and it was quite unknown at the time and</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0135" trans="overlap">it's subjective as well <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0084">he</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0135">you <trunc>proba</trunc> really you probably still find people today who would question</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0135">that it that such a condition exists and wouldn't just put it down to</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0135">badly behaved</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0135">or unruly or blah blah blah</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0084" trans="overlap">that's certainly what people were telling her <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0135" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0084">so I think for those reasons you know that was obviously a massive part of why she moved out of  so</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0084">um and ultimately what led to the end of their marriage <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0084">I think because she had a really crappy upbringing</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0084">A really really rubbish time and um it's amazing like you know  told you about that book <pause dur="short"/> they fuck you up <pause dur="short"/> like it's true <pause dur="short"/> like your parents play as you as we all know you know</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0084">it just starts from such a young age <pause dur="short"/> and it's so scary that you know if you have a bad experience it could ruin you for the rest of your life <pause dur="short"/> if if you allow it to</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0084">like with her she's worked really hard not to</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0084">like she could have been one of those parents on Jeremy Kyle that's horrible to their kids and you know</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0084">she's deliberately gone the other way and always makes an effort <pause dur="short"/> and says</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0084">you know I love you and I care about you and I'm proud of you <pause dur="short"/> and all that sort of like you know all that stuff that mums are supposed to say</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0084">but I mean actions speak louder than words as well</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0135">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0084">and um you know with  you know with your family you do get a lot of support from your family even if there there's not like the vocal</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0084">follow up there</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0084">so yeah I think you know this is sort of the way it is now</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0084">um <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps texting me</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0135">huh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1377" who="S0135"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1378" who="S0084">shall I meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0135">what is?</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0084">shall we meet him for a coffee now?</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0135">yes <pause dur="short"/> you we shall <pause dur="short"/> not me</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no you've gotta meet him</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0135">I'll drive you there</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0084">well I'll go and pick him up was what I was thinking <pause dur="short"/> but I wasn't chasing you out but um</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0135">coffee?</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0084">everyone knows what coffee at half past eight everyone knows what coffee means</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0135">oh do they? I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I would be like that <pause dur="short"/> I'll have a latte thank you</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0084">I'll have a <trunc>latt</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well I mean I just don't know because obviously this is the first time we we'll see each other</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0135" trans="overlap">I didn't know that coffee meant something else <pause dur="short"/> that's where I'm going wrong <pause dur="short"/> I always be like right okay great let's go to Starbucks <pause dur="short"/> and they mean let's roll around in the hay</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0084">well</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0135">I better do a wee <pause dur="short"/> oh how exciting <pause dur="short"/> but wait I thought he'd said end of the honeymoon <pause dur="short"/> or the honeymoon's over <pause dur="short"/> or there was no honeymoon</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0084" trans="overlap">we we both agreed the honeymoon's over <pause dur="short"/> but then there was the oh I'll come round for coffee and show you the ab movements</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0135">huh</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0084"><unclear/> maybe that's what everyone's going on about</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0135"><vocal desc="gasp"/> That's like maybe that's like text speak for something else</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0084">I think we're too</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0135">maybe that's what the kids</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0084">we're too old for all that carry on <pause dur="short"/> like we're not  we're not  down with the kids enough to know that that actually means <unclear/></u>
<u n="1399" who="S0135" trans="overlap">I don't know I would  I would  have genuinely thought coffee meant coffee and abs meant abs</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0084">you'd be forgiven for thinking it though</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0135">I didn't know it meant slap and tickle and slap and tickle mark two</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0084">all of the above</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0135">no I should make a move anyway</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0084">well I don't want to chase you out but I would</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0135">no no yeah I've gotta make a move anyway</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0084">I would rather you stayed here if it got late</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0135">yeah no no I'll go</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1409" who="S0135">I've gotta get back anyway</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0135">I've gotta get back but it was so nice seeing you</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0135">I've haven't seen you in well not it's not ages</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0084">it's been about two months</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0135">yeah I haven't seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in like years</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1417" who="S0135">I was supposed to go round on Sunday for tea and cake</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0084">yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> well why was she not er</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0135">and then at the last minute</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0135">literally that morning she just text me then goes oh I've got to take my car to my parent's house <pause dur="short"/> can we postpone? Or something</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0135">and I was like fine not a problem at all</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0084">curious though</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0135">and then we arranged to talk on the phone and then I rang her and she's like oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hasn't gone out after all <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s still here</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0135">with and that means we cannot talk now <pause dur="short"/> and I'm like</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> nice but dim <pause dur="short"/> is he still on the scene?</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0135">why can we not talk because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is here like? What's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gotta do with anything?</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0084">why is he even there?</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0135">well we know you're together but that's just what does that mean? I mean um but why couldn't we talk anyway? Just cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0135">it was really weird</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0084">is it because she wants to talk about him?</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0135">yeah it must have been</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0084">but why was she not in <anon type="place"/> for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday?</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0135">well surely <unclear/> I don't</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0084">have they fallen out?</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0135">I don't think they ever lived together cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> took <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s room</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0084">oh did she?</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0135">yeah so they don't actually</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0135">sort of know each other like that</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0084">oh God I'd forgotten all the ins and outs of it <pause dur="short"/> cos there was quite a few erm changes of cast in the er</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0135">mm</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0084">in the  house <pause dur="short"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still living in your room?</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0135">who?</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1449" who="S0135"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1450" who="S0084">is she still living in your room?</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0135">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the house is being sold</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0084">oh yeah you said</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0135">so they've all got to move out by May the something</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0084">is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then two other girls?</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0135">yeah but the other girl has bought a house <pause dur="short"/> a flat somewhere <pause dur="short"/> ester's getting married and also gonna move in with her B F</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0135">and then erm</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0084">staying in London?</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0135">yep</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0135">Cos her <trunc>hus</trunc> er her fiancé works as an architect or something</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0084">oh nice</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0135">I've gotta pee man</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0084">you've gotta pee <pause dur="short"/> well that's totally fine</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0135">are you going straight round now?</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0084">er</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0135">wait are you going for <trunc>coff</trunc> what's what's the what do you ring the bell?</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0084" trans="overlap">no I just pick him up</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0135">and then where do you go then?</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0084">er well back here <pause dur="short"/> and what er and I don't intend to spend any money then I'll kick him out <pause dur="short"/> that's my master plan at the moment <pause dur="short"/> that's what I'm working on</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0135">that is brilliant <pause dur="short"/> so you just go and pick up? That's do you know what we call that in the trade? Bootai</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0084">bootie call yeah</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0135">I mean</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0084">but that's what  that's what  he's always been</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0135">well let me pee then</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0084">well this is the first time it'll have happened <pause dur="short"/> if it happens which I'm still not sure about since the we've all broken up <pause dur="short"/> actually no we did try and break up once before <pause dur="short"/> not that we were ever together <pause dur="short"/> that was what was so hilarious <pause dur="short"/> we had a conversation where he texted me saying I'm like crying right now <pause dur="short"/> erm you're so nice <pause dur="short"/> you seem more into this than I am <pause dur="short"/> because he'd been round to here and we'd like cooked dinner together</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0135">oh really</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0084">and it'd been quite a couply thing</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0084">and the next day I think he kind of freaked out</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0135">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> freaked out</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0084">and we had a conversation and er I was like I don't wanna see you as as a boyfriend <pause dur="short"/> I don't want anything like that</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0135">yeah don't worry</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0084">I'm just having a good time <pause dur="short"/> he was like oh</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0135">yeah</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0084">well okay then <pause dur="short"/> so we tried not seeing each other <pause dur="short"/> that didn't work so we just carried on seeing each other so I dunno</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0135">what does he look like? Have you got a photo of him? Are you friends with him on Facebook?</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0084">he's not on Facebook</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0135">do what I do with Ed and just go like that</u>
<u n="1490" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1491" who="S0135">right okay</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0084">I hear they really appreciate that</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0135">I think when everyone's drunk you can get away with that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0084">this is true <pause dur="short"/> this is very true</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0135">be in the morning and everything so</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0135">ya <pause dur="short"/> no cos I spoke to her yesterday but she's er she cancelled on me <pause dur="short"/> what time is it anyway? Quarter to <pause dur="short"/> do you know they're put the erm Dartford</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0084">quarter to bedtime</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0135">erm bedtime <vocal desc="laugh"/> The Dartford crossing bit up to one pound fifty</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0084">Jesus <pause dur="short"/> I thought it they supposed to get rid of the toll as soon as they paid off the bridge <pause dur="short"/> and they must have paid of the bridge about ten years ago</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0135">they're bastards <pause dur="short"/> I thought I did a return journey <pause dur="short"/> lOL <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah start at Union lane <pause dur="short"/> oh you're right it is Arbury road <pause dur="short"/> interesting</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Funny funny that <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1503" who="S0135">as you said</u>
</body>
</text>
