<text id="SYX3">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:31:22</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-11-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0646</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At the home of ANON in Wimbledon, South London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Having and being treated for cancer. Knowledge and terminology. Attitudes of younger women to sex. Talking to and being examined by doctors. Symptoms. Screening and testing. Personal experiences. Types of cancer. Assisted fertility treatments. Process of investigation at hospital. Being given the news. Men’s experience. Being a woman after surgery. Marital relations afterwards. 1970s feminist messages. Need for radical surgery.</topics>
		<activity>Members of a cancer support group talking about their illness</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0646">
				<exactage>57</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kingston on Thames</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>35 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Communications Consultant</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0282">button start recording okay that's started recording <pause dur="short"/> and that one I think has started recording if I <trunc>mi</trunc> yes it has okay so erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I are going to talk about erm er er something that we've both been going through erm over the last few months and years which is our experiences of having cancer and being treated for cancer specifically gynaecological cancers and we're doing this recording with two objects erm number one is towards the Cambridge University Press erm research but secondly we're hoping that the tape will be used as well by a charity which is called The Eve Appeal erm which erm is campaigning on erm a greater awareness of <trunc>gynaec</trunc><trunc>gyn</trunc> I can't even say it gynaecological cancers <vocal desc="laugh"/> amongst obviously amongst women er in erm in this country and erm are interested in the views of some of their members and supporters er in the awareness of cancer and the symptoms of cancer et cetera amongst young people er in particular so we're gonna talk about that and the other thing we're gonna talk about is about the cancers that we've had and our experiences of of having cancer so we're gonna talk about body parts and stuff like that as well because <vocal desc="laugh"/> part of what The Eve Appeal has discovered is that younger women are less likely to know the parts of their body involved be able to locate them on a map of the body and actually be able to use the terminology so although there's an assumption in our society that younger people are freer and easier about sex and and er health et cetera this turns out from a recent piece of research to be not at all the case so I don't know what you felt when you read that press release that they put out?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0646">well I was so shocked actually er and baffled because erm the point is that many people die because they feel too embarrassed to go to their doctor and use words like vagina or vulva and er and obviously the earlier you can get get cancers the better and this thing to tie in with this project cos it's also a language issue so it just seems a rather nice tie-up to do</u>
<u n="3" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0646">erm so interestingly thinking about language erm you know er it's I suppose to use words the ones er where the synonyms for them are are kind of off-putting and rather horrible and and their clinical terms sound clinical so er so just isn't a kind of nice word is there? erm so vagina or vulva that's it you you might feel comfortable with erm the kind of the slang would be possibly derogatory <unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no and then when you go and see the doctor and they say I'm afraid I'm gonna have to stick my finger up your back passage</u>
<u n="6" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0282">and you sort of think oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0646"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0282">that's a bit weird as well and the the doctor using kind of baby language or something</u>
<u n="10" who="S0646">yeah yeah exactly I mean the language that doctors use I have actually interestingly found erm that the language they use to you is quite subtly different to the language that they write to your GP</u>
<u n="11" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0646">so sometimes erm I have the consultation with the oncologist and I think I I've got it what she said and then when I get the copy of the letter to the doctor I find that the language is slightly different and actually the meaning is slightly different as well which is quite interesting</u>
<u n="13" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0646">and so perhaps they also recoil at using words like that</u>
<u n="15" who="S0282">and a lot of them are young women as well</u>
<u n="16" who="S0646">they are yes exactly I mean my oncologist is <unclear>a woman</unclear></u>
<u n="17" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0646">erm and er yeah that that's kind of odd isn't it? and so how does one get people <trunc>t</trunc>to realise that it's a lot less daunting to go to your doctor and say the word vagina or the word vulva than it is to get cancer?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0646">which</u>
<u n="21" who="S0282">well perhaps actually if these young women don't know can't point to a picture of what is what when they're shown a diagram then perhaps the doctors aren't using the proper language because they <trunc>d</trunc> they think the hearer's not gonna</u>
<u n="22" who="S0646">yeah true</u>
<u n="23" who="S0282" trans="overlap">understand it</u>
<u n="24" who="S0646">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and er but they I mean if I was a doctor I would probably assume that it was the ladies of sixty-seventy-eighty that that didn't use those words or didn't like those words or didn't understand what those words referred to and that it would actually conversely be the younger women who <trunc>ha</trunc> erm had done personal and social health education at school or biology O level or GCSE more recently who would be able to say oh yes and pin the tail on the donkey <trunc>th</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> easily</u>
<u n="26" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0282">given a diagram</u>
<u n="28" who="S0646">exactly</u>
<u n="29" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but actually it seems to be the younger women who are having the difficulty and is that because biology is optional at school these days? I mean what what is that about?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0646">I really don't know it's <trunc>w</trunc> it I I really really don't know why that is whether they are thinking of examining that at all or studying it at all wonder if it's just</u>
<u n="31" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm it's just a huge gap</u>
<u n="32" who="S0646" trans="overlap">that we're more squeamish or whether people of an older age were just more down-to-earth about their bodies or</u>
<u n="33" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I don't know but that cos at first I thought okay they said women in erm a particular age group which was er what age group was it? erm <pause dur="short"/> women aged sixty-six to seventy-five and I thought well okay erm <pause dur="short"/> perhaps it's because older women have had babies but then you and I haven't had babies</u>
<u n="34" who="S0646">no</u>
<u n="35" who="S0282">so erm but we <trunc>st</trunc><trunc>st</trunc> thought you know perhaps I think well perhaps they you picked up the language about the body parts during obstetric <trunc>con</trunc>consultations erm but it's not necessarily that</u>
<u n="36" who="S0646">yeah and also I mean the the other surprising thing anyway is that you know it was meant to be like cancer was the sort of big unmentionable subject in</u>
<u n="37" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0646">those days</u>
<u n="39" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0646">and actually it's mentioned all the time now</u>
<u n="41" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0646">and so it's not the big unmentionable subject but perhaps conversely because it is mentioned so much people are maybe more frightened of it than they were before I don't know because you you just read so much stuff about it</u>
<u n="43" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0646" trans="overlap">erm it's it's just a very strange</u>
<u n="45" who="S0282">I mean the other thing that strikes me in that that really depresses me is that when you hear stories about young people and sex and pregnancy it still seems to be the case that girls aren't enjoying sex particularly they're doing sex cos boys want it <pause dur="short"/> boys and girls are learning about sex through the internet and through watching pornography which gives them a completely unrealistic picture of what it's all about and what it can be like and in particular girls that that sort of portrayal is not particularly helpful for girls and for girls having a healthy sex life and then you also then hear that girls are doing it under duress and they're not really enjoying it they're doing it cos boys want them to do it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0282">and you just think after all these years of effort about sex education and liberation of women and you've still got a situation in which young women are missing out in this <vocal desc="laugh"/> really really major way on something that's really important in life and perhaps those two things are going together then perhaps that sort of ignorance about having a healthy joyous sex life and not knowing about what your bits are called and what they do <trunc>perha</trunc> you know perhaps it's all of a piece so and that actually sex the whole sex education thing has just gone to pot</u>
<u n="48" who="S0646">I don't know but I mean I suppose aligned with that is all the other pressure on women to look perfect and</u>
<u n="49" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0646">looking up the sort of airbrushed models of perfection all the time and maybe there's something about body image in that erm that perhaps we didn't used to have you know</u>
<u n="51" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well people are having plastic surgery now in their</u>
<u n="52" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah well exactly so that sort of erm I mean it and it's sort of ironic isn't it? that kind of the likes of you who have been mauled over by major surgery but we're glad to be here on the planet really <vocal desc="laugh"/> never mind what we look like you know we're glad to exist erm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0646">so it's a it's a strange er you know it's a very long journey you go on from er from being too worried to say the word to to I mean <unclear/> that you've got cancer you know you just can't be squeamish cos there's lots of stuff that's gonna happen to you and erm you know <trunc>n</trunc> it's none of it's pleasant and er you know you've gotta deal with the fact that nurses are gonna have to clear up after you and you know <trunc>n</trunc> embarrassing and horrible but that's life</u>
<u n="55" who="S0282">yeah well I mean</u>
<u n="56" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and that's</u>
<u n="57" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I was at the hospital yesterday for a check-up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was with me erm erm and so er they sort of they feel all your glands and then they stick a speculum in your vagina and they look look to see what's there and then they feel and then they stick their fingers up your bum as well and then erm so and my husband's just sitting there on the other side of a curtain and the first time this happens he said <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>pre</trunc> but you you just lay there and they did that to you and like this is really extraordinary I said yeah <trunc>th</trunc> I mean that's been done thousands of times hundreds of times you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he found it really strange that you could meet somebody and the next minute they're poking <vocal desc="laugh"/> you around like that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0646"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0282">and he he couldn't believe it and he said is that what women have to put up with? and I said yeah yeah yeah yeah you know have it from the age of whenever from teenage years upwards from the time when you have your first smear or erm you know you first have a er any kind of gynae problem erm you just get used to sort of hopping on the couch and putting your legs in stirrups and stuff like that and he was horrified erm and he will hardly go to the doctor about anything let alone the prospect of somebody sticking their fingers up his bum when he goes</u>
<u n="60" who="S0646"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so that <vocal desc="laugh"/> too bad so so I I <trunc>d</trunc> well perhaps as women you do get used to stuff <trunc>p</trunc>people kind of poking around in your nether regions and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0646" trans="overlap">well I mean I think I mean I think that an equivalent with men and prostate cancer and <trunc>m</trunc> bowel cancer as well that you know</u>
<u n="63" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0646">they don't go for those things either and er</u>
<u n="65" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="66" who="S0646">erm and those sort of all also embarrassing things maybe there's a need for a kind of common cause across the cancers to erm to just get you know to say look don't be squeamish cos <trunc>y</trunc>your life is on the line here and it's</u>
<u n="67" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0646" trans="overlap">better to go and talk to someone and these doctors and nurses they've seen it all before that's what they do day in day out you know and our bits don't know any different to anybody else's <vocal desc="laugh"/> bits and</u>
<u n="69" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="70" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you know that's what they're trained to do and</u>
<u n="71" who="S0282" trans="overlap">er although actually I remember once having a cyst erm on my vulva erm which which got infected in the end and having to go to the doctor because it <trunc>th</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> this sort of giant lump which <vocal desc="laugh"/> was really quite painful and sore and everything and went to see a doctor but just booked in to see the doctor the <trunc>n</trunc>next nearest doctor who turned out to be a young Asian woman and when I said I had a cyst erm <trunc>sh</trunc> and the look of absolute distaste that went across her face was really and then so she said oh <trunc>y</trunc> I'd better have a look and I got on the couch and her face was just she was just really repulsed and I'd and I was and I was mortified at the time and then afterwards I thought you know what? <trunc>y</trunc>you know that would be enough to make you not go back quite</u>
<u n="72" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0282">clearly</u>
<u n="74" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and it was only it was er only a second or two until she caught herself and sort of thought right you know I'd better get on with this you know I've gotta do it and but but I saw the look go across her face very very plainly so I think <trunc>peo</trunc> that is exactly what people are scared of exactly what they're scared of there's somebody thinking oh that's disgusting ah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0646">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0282">and I suppose if I had been bolshier I might have kind of picked her up on it and but I didn't I just went away and erm and then when I did have cancer erm it took me <pause dur="short"/> quite a while to feel that my symptoms were severe enough to justify bothering the doctor because I went and I was going and I was saying look I've got these symptoms <pause dur="short"/> and the doctor was saying oh that's very <unclear/> I wonder what that is? and and I kept sort of thinking to myself should I go back? should I shall I say something? shall I say that the you know that that what she's done so far hasn't sorted this out? and and so every few months I would go back and I'd say okay well I'm still I'm still bleeding and and she would say oh that's a bit strange erm er to the point where I sort of though well perhaps it's not of interest at all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0646">well I mean I do think one of the most important things is to educate women</u>
<u n="79" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0646">about what's normal and what isn't normal</u>
<u n="81" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0646">and and what to ask for</u>
<u n="83" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and maybe it's quite a good thing on this tape to say something about what your symptoms were and if you were doing it again and you were going to advise a young woman sort of in your position you know what what what would you have done differently do you think?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0282">oh well I <trunc>d</trunc> well it's like and haven't even asked you what your cancer was</u>
<u n="86" who="S0646">oh well mine was ovarian</u>
<u n="87" who="S0282">it was ovarian okay alright so mine was endometrial cancer which is erm a cancer of the lining of the womb <pause dur="short"/> and erm it is most prevalent in women post-menopause so the way usually what happens is that I think or I gather is a women will have her menopause and her periods will stop and then after menopause she'll have an unexpected bleed which is either a one-off thing erm which my mother actually had when she was in her seventies just all of a sudden a cascade of blood out of nowhere after years and years of having been you know post-menopause or else persistent bleeding so erm so I think that's <trunc>probab</trunc> the reason cos I was er gosh how old was I? fifty-three or something and I hadn't finished my periods I think that's the reason why the doctor didn't think that there was anything sinister about me just having this persistent bleeding but in retrospect I hit fifty and when I hit fifty I didn't I <trunc>wa</trunc> I <trunc>wa</trunc> just wasn't well in this really weird kind of unaccountable kind of way and I couldn't work out what was wrong with me but I was just distinctly out of sorts and then erm I started to get erm my periods having sort of tailed off and got lighter and lighter and lighter started to get slightly heavier periods and a bit of pain and erm and then they sort of tailed off again and then I started spotting and then the spotting became permanent erm so it was happening all the time erm and then later on it got more persistent so there was more blood and</u>
<u n="88" who="S0646" trans="overlap">how long a period was that? I mean</u>
<u n="89" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well this is probably this is probably over eighteen months to two years</u>
<u n="90" who="S0646">okay</u>
<u n="91" who="S0282">during which time I I went to the doctor and I said look I've got this persistent spotting and erm and she <trunc>s</trunc> and she sort of said oh I think it's probably going to be your thyroid that's out of whack cos I also said well I've put on a lot of weight over the last year or two and erm I don't think I'm doing anything particularly different but I just keep on seem to get fatter and fatter all the time so she said oh I think it's probably your thyroid because the bleeding will be consistent with thyroid problem so she sent me for tests and indeed I did have underactive thyroid so she put me on Levothyroxine and then erm and then I sort of on a hunch sort of said to her oh and I haven't had my blood pressure taken for ages and it turned out I had absolutely sky high blood pressure as well so they put me on drugs for that and then as I went back to the doctor for checkups cos when they put you on Levothyroxine they have to keep doing blood tests to work out if you're on the right level of of drugs and to control your and bring your body up to the right level of kind of <trunc>m</trunc><trunc>m</trunc>metabolism and then also erm with my blood pressure I was going cos I didn't get on with the drugs so I was being tested for different drugs to <trunc>contr</trunc> try and control my blood pressure and every time I went back I said to her you know I'm still bleeding? and she would say oh that's really really strange that that should have been sorted out by now so she was really definitely pinning my bleeding onto my thyroid problem and it was only after about eighteen months that she said I think you'd better see a gynaecologist and then I I got and sent up to <anon type="place"/> and they did er er a scrape so just erm stuck a a oh a <trunc>d</trunc> a a kind of swab I suppose through my cervix and into my womb and just took a swab of the lining of my womb and then erm about a week later I got a call saying you'd better come to the hospital this afternoon please so <trunc>th</trunc> it was it was a very very simple test for endometriosis and actually it can't cost that much because it's just as long as they can get their little <unclear>dibber</unclear> through your cervix</u>
<u n="92" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0282">which they can't always</u>
<u n="94" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and and do we know why they don't do that when they are doing cervical screening tests? why do they not do that at the same time?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0282">I don't know well it's just it's like breast cancer isn't it? like if you say as a women and you've got cancer people go oh is it breast cancer? because there's so much awareness of breast cancer and there's also a lot of awareness of cervical cancer I mean I know</u>
<u n="96" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0282">you know</u>
<u n="98" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and they have all these checks all the time</u>
<u n="99" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah and I <trunc>kn</trunc> but you know you've got anomalies like people like Jade Goody who managed to not ever have a well I don't know I think she was possibly too young to have smears but you know that you still get people who are not going for their smear tests</u>
<u n="100" who="S0646">no</u>
<u n="101" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but but the awareness</u>
<u n="102" who="S0646" trans="overlap">but I mean while you're doing that here</u>
<u n="103" who="S0282" trans="overlap">is so much higher</u>
<u n="104" who="S0646">you're not actually testing for the endometrial</u>
<u n="105" who="S0282">no because you</u>
<u n="106" who="S0646" trans="overlap">cancer are you? you're</u>
<u n="107" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="108" who="S0646" trans="overlap">the so that and it wouldn't require a great deal more cos you are putting the whatever they call that this thing up and taking a swab</u>
<u n="109" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0646">so actually why not take a swab of the endometrial <unclear>why</unclear> I don't know</u>
<u n="111" who="S0282">I don't know I mean I think it is a bit it er some people can't take it some people have got such a tight cervix that they can't get their little tube up there</u>
<u n="112" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0282">erm and other people erm and it does actually hurt it feels like</u>
<u n="114" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you're being stabbed</u>
<u n="116" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0282">in the cervix so erm and I er probably a lot of women would just say oh no you've got to stop it's just too painful so</u>
<u n="118" who="S0646" trans="overlap">oh well maybe they don't want to do it because they think that would put women off having the</u>
<u n="119" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0646" trans="overlap">cervical test</u>
<u n="121" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0646" trans="overlap">I mean</u>
<u n="123" who="S0282">but then also</u>
<u n="124" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I <trunc>s</trunc> I don't know what the prevalence of the different cancers is whether <trunc>m</trunc>my I don't know this might be completely uninformed but my hunch is that there's more women around with cervical cancer</u>
<u n="126" who="S0646">sure yeah I'm sure that's right</u>
<u n="127" who="S0282" trans="overlap">than there are with endometrial cancer</u>
<u n="128" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and and also my hunch and and also this <trunc>gynae</trunc>gynaecological support group that I'm in the older women seem to have ovarian cancer and the younger women seem to have cervical cancer</u>
<u n="130" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0282">so I don't know whether there's a kind of shift in the patterns of cancer or oh I don't know whether it's about awareness campaigns and there just being more awareness of cervical cancer now which means that it looks like there are more people suffering but it's really that more people and</u>
<u n="132" who="S0646" trans="overlap">who are coming forward</u>
<u n="133" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no er</u>
<u n="134" who="S0646">I mean</u>
<u n="135" who="S0282" trans="overlap">coming forward</u>
<u n="136" who="S0646"><trunc>ye</trunc> and to follow your story right through but you know just to pause on the screening bit cos that's something I think is really important and I've worked in screening so I have some understanding of how it works but erm but screening programmes are decided on or not according to whether as a population whether they do more good than harm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0646">and the harm can be getting false erm readings that look positive</u>
<u n="139" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0646">or sending people off for treatments they don't need</u>
<u n="141" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0646">and so</u>
<u n="143" who="S0282" trans="overlap">as with prostate</u>
<u n="144" who="S0646" trans="overlap">there is a little risk thing so I do respect that er and I know there is a study er going on at the moment about looking at erm more screening for gynae cancers erm but what I kind of feel is that if if ovarian cancer and and these other cancers gynae cancers don't meet that threshold you still do have an opportunity where women come regularly hopefully most of them to do the cervical smear test</u>
<u n="145" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0646">and at the very least it seems to me one could be providing those women with information about the other cancers and saying to them</u>
<u n="147" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="148" who="S0646">this is what the symptoms would look like if</u>
<u n="149" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you have those symptoms do not be afraid to to go to your erm you know to ask your GP erm don't be put off by the language thing and ask for these particular tests so</u>
<u n="151" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0646">you know erm in the case of ovarian cancer erm the first test would be a blood test called CA125</u>
<u n="153" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0646" trans="overlap">now that's not an expensive thing to do</u>
<u n="155" who="S0282">oh isn't it?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0646" trans="overlap">GPs are doing all GPs do blood tests all the time it's just</u>
<u n="157" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0646">one more</u>
<u n="159" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0646">you know parameter that you can ask for</u>
<u n="161" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and that's the <trunc>tha</trunc> and that's the test for</u>
<u n="162" who="S0646">and so that</u>
<u n="163" who="S0282" trans="overlap">for endometrial as well</u>
<u n="164" who="S0646">right so</u>
<u n="165" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0646" trans="overlap">I mean those tests are not you know difficult</u>
<u n="167" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="168" who="S0646" trans="overlap">for GPs to organise in any way and then obviously if that comes back it's it's indicative but not diagnostic so that</u>
<u n="169" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0646" trans="overlap">we have to send people off for other tests but you know what I'm trying to say is I think that you know you have a captive audience</u>
<u n="171" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0646" trans="overlap">of people and you were talking about gynae cancers at that point and yet no conversation is had about these other tests and er just because there isn't a full-on national screening programme erm does that mean we can't even mention them or raise awareness or give people a leaflet or at least make them aware?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0646" trans="overlap">er and you know it seems to be that's an absolutely ideal opportunity to do that with</u>
<u n="175" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it would</u>
<u n="176" who="S0646">along with other er ad hoc interventions that they might have with their GP which might be around HRT treatment erm in the case of ovarian cos it tends to be more older people but could be around family planning</u>
<u n="177" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you know just so it's people should know what the symptoms are</u>
<u n="179" who="S0282">well no absolutely</u>
<u n="180" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and and we should follow your story and then I'll say a bit about kind of <trunc>sym</trunc> the normal symptoms of having ovarian cancer</u>
<u n="181" who="S0282">well I mean I was gonna comment on that because erm when I was in my <pause dur="short"/> er when I was about thirty my next door neighbour died of ovarian cancer and she was a erm she was quite a challenging woman cos she was really highly strung and really nervous and she she did panic she had a sort of quite a lot of OCD and and she was always on edge about stuff and really sort of erm a bit kind of I <trunc>d</trunc> be to use a very non-PC word really neurotic about stuff <pause dur="short"/> and she had had symptoms for years and years and years and it turned out to be ovarian cancer and she had been dismissed by her doctors as just being a hysterical woman</u>
<u n="182" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0282">with these sort of er these symptoms which were were said by them or interpreted by them to be a sign of her neuroticism and <trunc>h</trunc> and her borderline sort of hysteria but when <vocal desc="laugh"/> the fact that her getting to stage four <pause dur="short"/> ovarian cancer without being diagnosed so by the time she was diagnosed she was she'd had it she was done for erm and you know so this is actually this is actually bloody scary stuff because everybody knows with breast cancer you look for a lump <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>ev</trunc> and everybody is sort of they ask you have you been looking for lumps? you know when was the last time you examined your breast? you you go and have a smear for cervical cancer I had no idea to until recently that there was such a thing as cancer of the vulva <pause dur="short"/> or cancer of the vagina and actually that makes my blood run cold because I you know to this day I don't even know what the symptoms of those are erm you know although I do know what the symptoms of ovarian cancer are but coming back to my previous theme about going to your doctor it's one of the kind of things that you go to a doctor about and they think oh well that could be anything and it's probably IBS it's probably</u>
<u n="184" who="S0646">irritable bowel syndrome</u>
<u n="185" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0282">erm or it's you know some some woman at her time of life just being you know like god knows what they think but erm but the symptoms were not definitive enough that a doctor has alarm bells going oh my god must get a blood test must send them off to a doctor must send them for an ultrasound</u>
<u n="188" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0282">et cetera so it I mean it seems to be the doctors are very are scientists and they're very practical people and so I think my the doctor I went to see that I went to see because she said I've got a</u>
<u n="190" who="S0646" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0282">specialism in gynae stuff erm I think she looked and thought fifty-two the odds are that it's X and Y but you know the chance of it being cancer are you know one in twenty or something so therefore I'm not even gonna go down that avenue I'm gonna follow the most logical explanation of these symptoms</u>
<u n="192" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0282">so</u>
<u n="194" who="S0646" trans="overlap">it's actually funnily enough mine actually to their credit did the absolute opposite</u>
<u n="195" who="S0282">oh really?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0646" trans="overlap">she said to me cos I went in and said with bleeding persistent bleeding and and she said well let's get the nasty scary things out of the picture first and then we'll</u>
<u n="197" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><trunc>g</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="198" who="S0646" trans="overlap">see if it's something simple</u>
<u n="199" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so she did actually on my first visit erm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0282">wow</u>
<u n="202" who="S0646" trans="overlap">send me off to the hospital <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0282">and how did</u>
<u n="204" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and got <trunc>lo</trunc></u>
<u n="205" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and what what's the what's diagnostic tool for ovarian cancer?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0646" trans="overlap">well I mean mine was not usual er the the normal erm symptoms of ovarian cancer are feelings of being intolerably bloated</u>
<u n="207" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0646">because what happens is the the erm er the the body creates a lot of fluids in the</u>
<u n="209" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0646" trans="overlap">abdominal area so people do get very very bloated sometimes they can have like litres and litres and litres of this fluid which has to be drained off and</u>
<u n="211" who="S0282" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="212" who="S0646">cos that's the normal symptoms but my symptom actually was like yours was bleeding which again was confusing for everybody cos I had erm I had just come off HRT treatment</u>
<u n="213" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0646">and so I thought oh well maybe it's just erm you know residual normal menopausal</u>
<u n="215" who="S0282">ah yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0646">erm so you know I wasn't that concerned about it and I I had a cervical cancer <trunc>ch</trunc> screening test spoke to the nurse and said you know should I be worried about this? she said oh well you know if it doesn't go away in a few weeks go back to the doctor</u>
<u n="217" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and you know and it eventually you know you know I thought well it hasn't gone away so I will erm and to her credit she did yeah start with the kind of nuclear option first <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="220" who="S0646" trans="overlap">but she might well not have done</u>
<u n="221" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and and and it and then coming back to the thing about what oncologists say to your a GP it was only much later on kind of right almost at the end of the cancer treatment that she she put something in the letter to the GP which suggested that it had actually gone into the fallopian tubes and it was because it was in the fallopian tubes that I got bleeding</u>
<u n="223" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="224" who="S0646" trans="overlap">but that was sort of lucky for me that it was</u>
<u n="225" who="S0282">oh my word</u>
<u n="226" who="S0646" trans="overlap">cos otherwise cos I hadn't got any of this bloating</u>
<u n="227" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="228" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and I felt perfectly well you know I was I was tried to be very fit I went running every day swimming you know I was one of these kind of not a fitness fanatic but I did do exercise every day and I felt</u>
<u n="229" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0646">perfectly fine so you know <vocal desc="sigh"/> it these cancers can be the result of <unclear/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0646" trans="overlap">but I think one other thing is you know if if a woman knows that one of the key indicators is just this blood test I mean often the doctor will be doing blood tests for other stuff I mean you know when you first went there and they did your thyroid test</u>
<u n="233" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0646">they could actually have just ticked another box which</u>
<u n="235" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0646" trans="overlap">would have been</u>
<u n="237" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0646" trans="overlap">CA125</u>
<u n="239" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0646">and you might as well find this out</u>
<u n="241" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0646">you know eighteen months earlier</u>
<u n="243" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0646">so if if women know that that is <trunc>t</trunc> that test exists they could just say well look you know while we're about it why don't we just test that as well?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you know and that could just be the thing that saves their lives because I know that that thing like seventy-five percent of all women with ovarian cancer get diagnosed at stage 3C</u>
<u n="247" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0646" trans="overlap">now what that means is that you know cancer is usually graded into four stages?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0646">one two three and four erm four is when it's really you know a a pretty tough call and it's gone</u>
<u n="251" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0646">everywhere in your body</u>
<u n="253" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0646">three is when it's spread somewhere else</u>
<u n="255" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0646">erm so 3C is not fantastic but</u>
<u n="257" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="258" who="S0646" trans="overlap">the one of the one of the reasons why the cancer outcome statistics are not great for ovarian cancer is that everyone is found so late</u>
<u n="259" who="S0282">I know</u>
<u n="260" who="S0646">erm so you know it has spread by that by the time you get that bloating you know it it's spread</u>
<u n="261" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0646">so there is no lump to feel so it's all so I think you know the message is <pause dur="short"/> you know rather that your doctor might be a bit irritated and you just ask for the CA125 blood test which after all is not that as expensive for the NHS but</u>
<u n="263" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well I don't know you but is</u>
<u n="264" who="S0646">not that that's a totally diagnostic device</u>
<u n="265" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="266" who="S0646" trans="overlap">I should say that you know not every ovarian cancer will be shown by that test and I think that's one of the reasons why a lot of these screening decisions are complicated</u>
<u n="267" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0646">erm like you know if you just did that test it wouldn't necessarily pick up everything so that you know I think it's a very complicated area all this where</u>
<u n="269" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0646" trans="overlap"><unclear/> have to be very finely calibrated and</u>
<u n="271" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but I think they're not</u>
<u n="272" who="S0646" trans="overlap">indeed they are in breast I mean and breast cancer has been very controversial because you know an awful lot of women end up getting er breast surgery for things that might never had turned into cancer but you can't know one way or the other so it's</u>
<u n="273" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0646" trans="overlap">it you know it's always that balance and so I do respect the sort of academic process that that they use but sometimes I think you also have to be pragmatic and say well look the more women understand what kinds of cancer there are and what kind of cancers do not have obviously lumps that you can feel</u>
<u n="275" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0646">and what kind of test it might be reasonable for them to ask for at least have the discussion with your doctor you know and you don't want to raise panic amongst people but at the same time you know there's a real issue of late diagnosis</u>
<u n="277" who="S0282">yeah <trunc>abs</trunc> well absolutely I mean I I when I was twenty-five I think I found a lump in my breast and it was quite a hard one and it wasn't it <trunc>ob</trunc> it wasn't a cyst it was erm turned out to be a fibroadenoma but I was in hospital having it removed within within the month and it was only recently that I thought oh my god they thought it was a cancer didn't they? because otherwise I wouldn't have been whipped into hospital and had this lump removed</u>
<u n="278" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0282">you know then er then and there erm but erm so erm I er the I at the time I suppose I was a bit bemused about why they'd want to take it why they'd want to take it out I don't think I ever stopped to think about why did they want to take it out but I'm quite relieved they did</u>
<u n="280" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0282">and and that I got that attention</u>
<u n="282" who="S0646" trans="overlap">do you think you were in denial at the time? that <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no it just never crossed my mind no because actually what was <vocal desc="laugh"/> really strange is that I think that there's probably a genetic component in my cancer because I think my grandmother had endometrial cancer</u>
<u n="284" who="S0646">right</u>
<u n="285" who="S0282">erm or possibly ovarian cancer erm years and years and years ago erm and but I had never it had never crossed my mind that I might get cancer because my mother goes around saying there isn't cancer in our family nobody in our family has got cancer erm never heard of anybody having cancer erm and so therefore I er I had kind of on some real subliminal level thought I'm not I'm not going to get cancer I'm not gonna be prone to cancer I don't know why I would have swallowed that message whole it seemed to me that I suppose that there is some logic in that that if nobody in the family had ever had cancer then obviously there isn't a a kind of genetic component in our family like the BRA gene or what</u>
<u n="286" who="S0646" trans="overlap">BRCA yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0282" trans="overlap">gene the BRCA gene whatever so erm I suppose I just had this sort of whole sense of security about it but</u>
<u n="288" who="S0646" trans="overlap">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0282" trans="overlap">actually an even falser because actually my grandmother almost certainly had erm a gynaecological cancer and I don't think she was ever even told that she did because and and when <trunc>wen</trunc> I said to my mother and my my <trunc>fa</trunc> it's my father's mother and I said to my father and my mother oh well of course nan had a hysterectomy and they said no she didn't and I said <pause dur="short"/> she did and they said no she didn't and I said you know what I'm pretty sure she did and they said no no we can't remember that spoke to my uncles who also said no I can't remember her having a a a hysterectomy and then and I said said not only did she have a hysterectomy but they treated her with with radium rods which were put into her vagina and she had to lie in bed for five days with radium rods in her vagina without moving and they said you've made that up that's a load of old twaddle that never happened and I thought to myself do you know what I'm so convinced it happened but they were convinced equally that it hadn't and the only way <vocal desc="laugh"/> that it turned out that I was right in the end is because I've got a diary of hers just happened to have a diary of hers for that year which talks about the whole process</u>
<u n="290" who="S0646">wow</u>
<u n="291" who="S0282">and until they saw their diary somehow it had gone right over their heads</u>
<u n="292" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so had they had they not been told? or had they been told but just were in denial?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0282">I don't</u>
<u n="294" who="S0646" trans="overlap">or</u>
<u n="295" who="S0282">absolutely don't know but I I</u>
<u n="296" who="S0646" trans="overlap">how <unclear/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0282" trans="overlap">really don't think they told her because</u>
<u n="298" who="S0646" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I think she she was kind of quite a nervy high-strung person who was always a bit hypochondriac and she never sort of went round in her later life say oh well I wonder if it's cancer erm or I'm really scared of having cancer again or something like when through all the symptoms she had when she was a ninety she did live till ninety-three so obviously they caught it in time and they put it right but erm so there is hope at least <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0646">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but erm erm but erm I don't I don't think that they could ever have told her what what</u>
<u n="302" who="S0646" trans="overlap">what yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0282" trans="overlap">what it was</u>
<u n="304" who="S0646">strange well I mean guess that's another whole issue isn't it? about how people are told and</u>
<u n="305" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0646" trans="overlap">how much they're told and er you know how much one chooses to ask erm and the first thing I realised was that they said here's your Macmillan nurse and I thought ah okay it's cancer then before they said the word cancer</u>
<u n="307" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0646">erm that's how I knew it was <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="309" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh gosh and then so what happened? you went you had you went for a scan?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0646">I well I had so yes I had er first of all I had an ultrasound scan</u>
<u n="311" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0646">and then erm they did that CO125 test to corroborate it and at that point it was pretty the two of them so a lump and this raised level of CO125 so that was pretty certain that it was and erm I mean it was I think that it was at that point that they introduced the Macmillan nurse I'm kind of trying to remember now exactly but erm and this was all it was a bit of a <trunc>h</trunc>horrendous thing because I was due to have go off with my choir on a tour which I had spent the year</u>
<u n="313" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0646" trans="overlap">organising so</u>
<u n="315" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0646">I got this on a Thursday and we were meant to be setting off with my choir on Saturday er to my house in in France for a tour that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I had organised er and we had all the kind of venues booked and the tickets and you know everybody else it complicated holidays and booked around it so I said ah you know I I I need to go away next week and they said well look okay go away but you know it was meant to be a three-week holiday erm but you know do your choir tour then and you must come back erm and so <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it was a very strange choir tour I was sort of doing all this singing and thinking oh my goodness I'm going back to so what I went back to then was a erm they do a CT biopsy a CT</u>
<u n="317" who="S0282" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="318" who="S0646" trans="overlap">guided biopsy so they put you under a CT scanner</u>
<u n="319" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0646">and they extract a tiny bit erm yeah of the tumour erm sort of guided by the CT scan so they can see where they're</u>
<u n="321" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0646" trans="overlap">getting it from erm and so that that came back erm and and another thing perhaps it's helpful to say is that when I got that er they said oh yes it's a very aggressive form of cancer and I think that can be a scary thing to hear but what</u>
<u n="323" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0646" trans="overlap">they said was that actually paradoxically erm aggressive cancers can be the ones that react best to chemotherapy because what a chemotherapy is doing is addressing rapidly dividing cells</u>
<u n="325" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so if you have a cancer that has rapidly dividing cells IE it's aggressive erm chemotherapy sometimes works better with those ones</u>
<u n="327" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="328" who="S0646" trans="overlap">than the ones that are slower burners and and I would see if I would be able able to tell that to another friend of mine who was just told it's an aggressive form of cancer without having that extra bit</u>
<u n="329" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so I mean to me that extra bit was really kind of <vocal desc="laugh"/> the difference between it being awful news and it being</u>
<u n="331" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0646" trans="overlap">sort of here's the good news and here's the bad news sort of thing</u>
<u n="333" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so erm so that was kind of it's kind of a helpful thing for people to know I think</u>
<u n="335" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0646">so erm yeah so that's how I got diagnosed and I I was very lucky that you know although it was still stage 3C you know if because I wasn't having any pain or symptoms you know if I had waited until I had got that I might well have been stage four and</u>
<u n="337" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0646" trans="overlap">incurable and erm er so mine had gone and rather unusually to my lymph nodes and when they first said it to me before the choir and told me that oh well it might be lymphoma or it might be ovarian cancer or it could be both</u>
<u n="339" who="S0282">oh that's a</u>
<u n="340" who="S0646" trans="overlap">come back in a week <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="342" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so erm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0282">scary</u>
<u n="344" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and so yeah erm but it it's nice to know that actually on the twenty-ninth of November erm that that's the actual anniversary of me having the seven hours of surgery and being like in hospital for six weeks</u>
<u n="345" who="S0282">oh what</u>
<u n="346" who="S0646" trans="overlap">with post <trunc>comp</trunc> you know post-<trunc>op</trunc> er complications on that day this year one year on I shall be singing Bach and Handel and Purcell in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> so that's just been</u>
<u n="347" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="348" who="S0646" trans="overlap">like the most brilliant</u>
<u n="349" who="S0282">cos that is brilliant</u>
<u n="350" who="S0646" trans="overlap">kind of</u>
<u n="351" who="S0282">that is brilliant</u>
<u n="352" who="S0646" trans="overlap">life-affirming omen really</u>
<u n="353" who="S0282">yeah no I guess I'm about yes er they operated on me in about mid-November as well</u>
<u n="354" who="S0646">so I mean going back to your your</u>
<u n="355" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but a couple of years further back</u>
<u n="356" who="S0646" trans="overlap">diagnosis and everything</u>
<u n="357" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so is it you know do you wanna just say a little bit more about what endometrial <trunc>c</trunc>cancer is? and</u>
<u n="359" who="S0282">well erm I I suppose it's erm it's cancer of the lining of the womb so it's not necessarily in the wall of your womb it's in the lining so the first time I talked to the consultant about it I said well <trunc>perha</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc>you know perhaps it's like having woodworm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0646"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you know and you've got but you know you've just got woodworm in the floorboards it hasn't got into the joists yet and it hasn't got into <vocal desc="laugh"/> the walls and it hasn't got into the roof and he sort of said yes I suppose that you know I suppose that's a definition of stage one but you know actually it's just still contained in that</u>
<u n="362" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0282">in that area and hasn't got out and spread and in fact mine had erm and that is a function of the fact that it wasn't diagnosed for eighteen months because erm in fact a friend of mine who had a hysterectomy because she'd had a bad childbirth experience they sort of said oh you've got stage one <pause dur="short"/> er you know or you've got precancerous cells inside your uterus erm <pause dur="short"/> so but they didn't give her any treatment because it was still really really</u>
<u n="364" who="S0646" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="365" who="S0282" trans="overlap">localised erm so erm but mine I think that I had probably or things had probably made my life slightly more complicated because erm we had been trying for a baby and we were going to this clinic where we weren't having <trunc>I</trunc> we weren't actually having IVF but we were having kind of assisted conception and as part of that they injected some coloured fluid into my womb to see if there was a free flow of this and then they had <trunc>m</trunc> they <trunc>g</trunc> <trunc>d</trunc>did an ultrasound to see if the fluid kind of flowed up through my uterus and into my fallopian tubes and came out of the end of my fallopian tube</u>
<u n="366" who="S0646">okay</u>
<u n="367" who="S0282" trans="overlap">to see if the reason I wasn't conceiving was because I had a blockage</u>
<u n="368" who="S0646">right</u>
<u n="369" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and the eggs weren't travelling down my fallopian tube now in retrospect I think the reason why they then found little drifts of cancer cells up my fallopian tubes in one of my ovaries and down around the outside of the exterior of my uterus was because that process had sent cells</u>
<u n="370" who="S0646">oh my god so they sort of flushed them round?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0282">I think they <trunc>s</trunc> I think that possibly they <trunc>star</trunc> yeah sort of endometrial cells had been flushed out of my or through my fallopian tubes and outside into my abdominal cavity</u>
<u n="372" who="S0646" trans="overlap">oh how terribly ironic</u>
<u n="373" who="S0282">and then either they were cancerous at the time and it was a very very slow cancer and they just sat there quietly without giving me any symptoms for a couple of years or on the other hand they were ordinary cells and they were perfectly fine and then when something in my genes kind of clicked over and they decided that they were going to be cancerous they all started <pause dur="short"/> playing <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="374" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0282" trans="overlap">cancerous little games all at once in their various little locations I'm not sure which way round it was but erm <pause dur="short"/> but you know I suppose it is I had had an ultrasound <pause dur="short"/> erm when my periods started getting bad and when I started having pain and the the radiologist had said said oh don't worry you've got fibroids <pause dur="short"/> but there's nothing more sinister there well erm endometrial cancer doesn't show up as a tumour or a lump and so you don't have a tell-tale lump as you would in breast cancer</u>
<u n="376" who="S0646">no</u>
<u n="377" who="S0282">erm and</u>
<u n="378" who="S0646" trans="overlap">or even in ovarian cancer actually</u>
<u n="379" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="380" who="S0646">with ovarian cancer</u>
<u n="381" who="S0282">yes I suppose you could have a localised lump</u>
<u n="382" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you you probably if you think of it</u>
<u n="383" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0646" trans="overlap">if you see see the lump</u>
<u n="385" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="386" who="S0646">in erm when you have</u>
<u n="387" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0646" trans="overlap">have an ultrasound and you do feel the lump yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so now I find it a bit weird when I go back for checkups and they're sort of looking they sort of get down and look at assess my tummy to see if there's any sort of lumps and bumps on it and I think well there was never a lump in the first place <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know would there be a lump now? I'm not sure whether there would be a lump now to this day</u>
<u n="390" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but but anyway but so there's no lumps to look at and there's no lumps to feel and actually if they send you for an ultrasound that doesn't tell you whether you've got endometrial cancer because</u>
<u n="392" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0282">actually if they can be just sitting there looking perfectly innocent when you scan them but <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="394" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0282">they're not innocent at all</u>
<u n="396" who="S0646">no so just to cut through that again so if if somebody had persistent bleeding</u>
<u n="397" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0646">er and they had some reason you know they might have some reason to check out <trunc>endomet</trunc>endometrial I can almost say it cancer the only way they would actually know that would be to scrape</u>
<u n="399" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0646">the wall</u>
<u n="401" who="S0282">yeah which is a kind of basic erm it's kind of like a D and C or the start of it <trunc>th</trunc> if you have a D and C they</u>
<u n="402" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0282" trans="overlap">kind of put a a hollow tube up your cervix well actually you probably have a they probably inject your cervix to dilate your cervix if you if you go for day surgery <pause dur="short"/> and if you and actually have a miscarriage and they're trying to deal with the aftermath of a <trunc>mis</trunc> a miscarriage they'll put this tube up with a with a kind of implement into it into your womb and then just sort of go round and sort of scrape the lining so</u>
<u n="404" who="S0646" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="405" who="S0282">if they're doing that to see if you've got cancer cells up there it's just it's the work of what? thirty seconds or something?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0646">oh really? right</u>
<u n="407" who="S0282" trans="overlap">to get a to get a scrape as long as as long as</u>
<u n="408" who="S0646" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0282">you can cope with the the <pause dur="short"/> I I wouldn't say it was pain I don't know it's <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't say it was pain so much as a kind of <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I suppose there's somebody sort of <pause dur="short"/> stuck their thumb in you really hard <pause dur="short"/> you know it's that kind of pain it's a kind of <vocal desc="misc"/> sort of pain</u>
<u n="410" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0282">but not a sharp kind of cutting of a knife sort of pain</u>
<u n="412" who="S0646">okay</u>
<u n="413" who="S0282">so but I think erm <pause dur="short"/> they er a lot of a lot of women find that too <trunc>discom</trunc> too uncomfortable</u>
<u n="414" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0282">I mean actually if you</u>
<u n="416" who="S0646" trans="overlap">well it's a very difficult one to diagnose though</u>
<u n="417" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0646" trans="overlap">endometrial</u>
<u n="419" who="S0282">well if you've had erm if you've had a coil</u>
<u n="420" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it's easier cos you've had that before so you'd know exactly what you're in for in terms of discomfort cos</u>
<u n="422" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0282" trans="overlap">they have to in the same way that they put a <trunc>coi</trunc> they put a hollow tube through your cervix and then they pop the coil through the tube</u>
<u n="424" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and then it pops out and opens up like an umbrella inside you so <pause dur="short"/> if you've had that you wouldn't you wouldn't have the problem with</u>
<u n="426" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0282">having a scrape really</u>
<u n="428" who="S0646" trans="overlap">okay but it's it's a more tricky one to find then cos there's not even a lump if you're having an ultrasound?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0646">like you would still have this CO125</u>
<u n="431" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0646">which would indicate</u>
<u n="435" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0646">but if you had raised CO125 but no lump through an ultrasound then you should be saying could it be this</u>
<u n="437" who="S0282">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0646">to your doctor?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0646">and asking for that scrape?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0646">okay</u>
<u n="443" who="S0282">and you can have a local and you can have a <pause dur="short"/> and you can have a general I mean and</u>
<u n="444" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you know if they in fact actually</u>
<u n="446" who="S0646">did you just have a local anaesthetic?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0282">no no just</u>
<u n="448" who="S0646" trans="overlap">just doing it</u>
<u n="449" who="S0282" trans="overlap">did it then and there and went from there was the the registrar</u>
<u n="450" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you didn't have any <unclear/> at all?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0282">no no they just said</u>
<u n="452" who="S0646" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0282" trans="overlap">hop up here and this might hurt and <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then you know within five minutes it was all done and dusted and got sent away and then you know a week later as I said they called me back to hospital I have to say the way he told me was absolutely appalling</u>
<u n="454" who="S0646">oh really?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0282">there was this this consultant I'd never seen before who got wheeled into the room and there was a student who was obviously there to hear how to tell a patient they've got cancer there was a registrar who obviously was just they were just the gynae the gynae guy so mostly they were dealing with pregnancies and miscarriages and stuff and not with cancer so they were all beside themselves and didn't know what to do about it and didn't know what to say so they just told me and then we all just stared at each other <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then I had to go away for a month and wait for them to tell me how bad it was</u>
<u n="456" who="S0646">a month? why?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0282" trans="overlap">er because it took a month for the results to come back</u>
<u n="458" who="S0646">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="459" who="S0282">cos the I had to go for a CT scan and then an MRI scan and whatever before before they erm you know sort of decided they <trunc>s</trunc> as I said they you know it could have been just the equivalent of woodworm in the floorboards</u>
<u n="460" who="S0646">gosh that must must have been agonisingly worrying having that long wait I mean I as for me I mean the first <pause dur="short"/> the the equivalent I had I suppose of er erm when I first saw the oncologist cos erm they kind of had a whole team of people saying would I like to be involved in research? but it was like there there seemed to be a room full of people there must have been some were</u>
<u n="461" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0646">shadowing the oncologist and there was lots of people from the research project and there was the Macmillan nurse and I can't even remember there were quite a lot of people and me and the oncologist who I've never met before and she started off with</u>
<u n="463" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and were you on your own?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0646">I was that day actually I don't know</u>
<u n="465" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="466" who="S0646" trans="overlap">quite why</u>
<u n="467" who="S0282">oh god</u>
<u n="468" who="S0646" trans="overlap">anyway erm erm she said well look erm one third of people die straightaway er one third of people erm die kind sort of in the treatment somehow and a third of people get well five years running and it it was like my god you know it was like really desperately awful</u>
<u n="469" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that is brutal</u>
<u n="470" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and it and she just came out with that in front of all these people that I didn't know at all</u>
<u n="471" who="S0282">god that's brutal</u>
<u n="472" who="S0646">and and <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I thought oh great you know thanks you know erm so if one <trunc>thir</trunc> I think the the correct statistic is one third of people die straightaway</u>
<u n="473" who="S0282" trans="overlap">does that sort of that echo in your brain?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0646">oh god yeah you know one third of people erm <pause dur="short"/> die within five years and one third of people last beyond or something like that so it's it's er you know it's kind of two thirds of them die before the you know</u>
<u n="475" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="476" who="S0646" trans="overlap">five years but it's you know awful statistics and and erm and of course you have to you know when you when you will have that you do have to do a bit of reality check that actually all this data doesn't relate to you know the past and how things were and it probably is improving all the time erm and you know the sort of there are other factors in that</u>
<u n="477" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0646">like the age of the person</u>
<u n="479" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0646" trans="overlap">how fit they were and what <unclear/> but anyway</u>
<u n="481" who="S0282">and my husband <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="482" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so so being told that</u>
<u n="483" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0646" trans="overlap">was the like in <trunc>whe</trunc>when I then had to keep it together because that was the meeting in which they were gonna explain whether or not I should do this research and</u>
<u n="485" who="S0282"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and erm and</u>
<u n="487" who="S0282"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0646"><trunc>ye</trunc> and I was trying to take in all the details of the research project and the treatment options and you know once I'd heard that I didn't really get much further than oh my god I'm gonna be dead</u>
<u n="489" who="S0282"><vocal desc="misc"/> no well quite what else did you hear? I mean</u>
<u n="490" who="S0646"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0282">I can't er I can't understand what else you would hear even after that had been said to you I mean I just I <trunc>p</trunc> I put my head very very firmly in the sand <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me the statistics are irrelevant actually cos you are not a statistic and the statistics no matter what the statistics say that doesn't necessarily affect you</u>
<u n="492" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0282">so erm</u>
<u n="494" who="S0646" trans="overlap">but of course everyone will say that</u>
<u n="495" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and you you kind of</u>
<u n="497" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0646" trans="overlap">erm the I mean I think I think there's a kind of pragmatic middle way between</u>
<u n="499" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0646" trans="overlap">sort of erm of being aware of the statistics but at the same time you know not getting completely bogged down in them cos you know</u>
<u n="501" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0646">er every person is unique and everybody but every journey is unique and some people who have stage four go on to live and some people who are stage one go on to die and you know so you can't</u>
<u n="503" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0646">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0646">you know once you've heard then you can't un-hear</u>
<u n="507" who="S0282">no no I mean it makes a lot of difference that where if you know there are staging significant and the aggressiveness is is significant obviously I mean mine because mine had left my erm womb and had got out it was stage three and I realised it was stage three when I saw the consultant <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the surgeon I saw him write stage three upside down on his notes</u>
<u n="508" who="S0646">right</u>
<u n="509" who="S0282">so erm so and I just thought oh <pause dur="short"/> I oh erm you know because I had been hoping and hoping that up to that point that they would say look you know it's just confined it's fine but it had got out and got round a bit but not into my lymph glands so</u>
<u n="510" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0282">but you know er <vocal desc="sigh"/> I didn't know what to do about my doctor afterwards because I just thought you know what? a few months more and it would have been in my lymph glands and it would have been you know proportionately hugely more serious erm and so it took me a long time to get over being angry with her I was just so livid with her for such a long period of time</u>
<u n="512" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0282">erm and I just thought you careless bloody woman <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0646">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0282" trans="overlap">erm and you know especially when she had kept you know I was just on the verge of just not talking about it anymore and also the other thing I think that's quite important is that my mother had really bad really bad periods before she had her menopause the process of her menopause was was appalling I mean she had appalling bleeding she had terrible pain she had flooding you know it was you know she had a terrible time and other women I know have had a really bad time through menopause so when I felt I was having a bad time I just thought you know what? that's what women go through and it's menopause and you read stuff about menopause and you hear erm you know stories about people you're not you know you can't go anywhere and you can't do anything cos you're just bleeding all the time all over the place and and I just sort of thought well I'm in the bound of a normality and you know other women have had have had just this sort of thing and it's just been kind of normal</u>
<u n="516" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0282" trans="overlap">for their age and and so erm and so I I kept thinking to myself you know do I complain about it? perhaps I shouldn't complain about it perhaps you know the doctor's sort of thing oh yeah yeah you and a thousand others yeah yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0282" trans="overlap">get over it sort of thing erm <pause dur="short"/> so I I don't know whether you know you I I mean once when I had a miscarriage and I we went to erm A and E and I overheard one young doctor saying to another young doctor well you know they always exaggerate how much they've been bleeding and it's not you know ever as bad as they say it is you know and you'd sort of think oh well you know okay blood makes a mess doesn't it? so you know a a tablespoon of blood is actually quite a lot of blood</u>
<u n="520" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0282" trans="overlap">to clear up you know and it makes quite a big splash as it were erm but you know so I kept thinking to myself perhaps I'm perhaps I'm overreacting perhaps you know</u>
<u n="522" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0282">this really is within the bounds of normality and I shouldn't be whinging so much about it</u>
<u n="524" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I think I think a lot of people are put off</u>
<u n="525" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0646">going to their GP for that especially as we know how busy GPs are and</u>
<u n="527" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="528" who="S0646">you know you can see they're under great pressure and</u>
<u n="529" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0646">and erm you know er and we're all er unsure and so on I mean I suppose I all I can say is I think that educating people about symptoms</u>
<u n="531" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and just being aware that you can just try to sort of you know get some reality checks for yourself as to</u>
<u n="533" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0646">whether things you know if things go on and on being being wrong</u>
<u n="535" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="536" who="S0646">erm and if they follow you know a pattern that you've read about you know then you shouldn't feel it's unreasonable to take their time I mean it's a perfectly reasonable thing to to say you know</u>
<u n="537" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0646" trans="overlap">it it it isn't a and to persist if you don't feel well like I said there's the like the thyroid thing which you know was a perfectly reasonable <trunc>in</trunc> you know intervention because of the fact that you did have a thyroid problem</u>
<u n="539" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0646" trans="overlap">so it wasn't an unreasonable</u>
<u n="541" who="S0282">no no no</u>
<u n="542" who="S0646">intervention</u>
<u n="543" who="S0282">no no that you got but you know to just have that confidence that that you know just cos you've got one thing that's been diagnosed correctly doesn't mean you might not have another parallel set of</u>
<u n="544" who="S0282" trans="overlap">absolutely</u>
<u n="545" who="S0646" trans="overlap">that has been missed</u>
<u n="546" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0646">you know so just to have that confidence to to pursue it with your with your GP</u>
<u n="548" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but to this day I couldn't tell you what the symptoms of vulvas of cancer of the vulva were or cancer of the vagina I have I have and I <trunc>d</trunc> almost don't dare dare to look them up really I mean the</u>
<u n="549" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0282">you know erm cervical cancer erm well we have smears so we don't have to worry so we have smears so that's fine breast cancer we know about erm you are supposed to examine your breasts but the other ones they are just they really are hidden aren't they? they're</u>
<u n="551" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so hidden</u>
<u n="553" who="S0646">they are absolutely hidden yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and actually I mean the other thing as well that erm there was another survey which was done by the Ovarian Cancer Action about outcomes for women after having gynaecological cancers in terms of the continuation of their sex lives and erm there was something on Woman's Hour about it erm last year and erm and and actually when blokes have prostate cancer a lot of attention is paid to their continuance of their erectile function and whether they you know are incontinent and stuff like this erm but you know there's people talk about their libido and you know their sex lives and and it's actively part of their treatment to talk about this and to counsel men about this but there isn't</u>
<u n="555" who="S0646">no</u>
<u n="556" who="S0282">in parallel er conversations with women about the more <trunc>gen</trunc> the general issue about how a do you are you are are you a real woman if you haven't got your bits anymore? do you still feel attractive as a woman of a certain age and you're kind of you know you're not attracting attention from men anymore perhaps your looks are going off or whatever you've certainly got physical problems of various kinds erm and now actually you've had surgery so you feel kind of maimed in</u>
<u n="557" who="S0646" trans="overlap">well you are maimed</u>
<u n="558" who="S0282" trans="overlap">a way you are maimed by the surgery</u>
<u n="559" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0282">erm and so you are you know in one in one respect of being a woman redundant erm and then actually because you haven't got the hormones anymore there are all kinds of difficult consequences of not having oestrogen in your body erm and then what's more your sex life goes up the spout because <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know erm because of all those previous factors including the fact that you haven't got oestrogen and progesterone anymore erm and so you know <trunc>y</trunc> just do people talk to us about this? no they bloody don't actually</u>
<u n="561" who="S0646">no they don't they don't erm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0282">is that a boy coming in for <unclear>for his tea</unclear>?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0646" trans="overlap">it's isn't a boy</u>
<u n="564" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="565" who="S0646" trans="overlap">erm erm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh we've</u>
<u n="567" who="S0646">well how many <unclear/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0282" trans="overlap">we've got six five minutes to go before we before we've done the hour so if we could just do</u>
<u n="569" who="S0646" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="570" who="S0282" trans="overlap">five minutes more and then</u>
<u n="571" who="S0646" trans="overlap">okay erm yeah I mean I think that is a huge issue and I suppose I think a lot of people feel they've just got to be so grateful that they're here on the planet</u>
<u n="572" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0646" trans="overlap">at all</u>
<u n="574" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0646">that all those other things just kind of you know they can't whine about those things because they're just quite glad that they're here at all</u>
<u n="576" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0646">on the planet and so unless but I kind of do somewhat feel that erm</u>
<u n="578" who="S0282">but then on the other hand you see</u>
<u n="579" who="S0646" trans="overlap">but but but</u>
<u n="580" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I my husband's younger than me he's only in his forties and even if for myself I thought well you know well you know <vocal desc="sigh"/> you know I can cope I mean I can't I can't say to my husband that's that's the end of the line for him and he's not even hit fifty yet</u>
<u n="581" who="S0646">no no no but that I I think that I I I think the point of raising the point about it not being talked about is an important point and I think it's a</u>
<u n="582" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0646" trans="overlap">really hard point erm the er I mean there must be that kind of yeah it's something I totally struggled with I mean I've basically struggled with it because I also did IVF before unsuccessfully and so for myself from that point wasn't really a real woman</u>
<u n="584" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0646">before I even got this erm and now I've got this and I've got a fucking great scar right through my pubic area right up to my breast bone you know and it it's not attractive it just is not <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know and erm and I think that is very hard yeah er er so I don't have any sort of easy thing to say about it other than to say yes I think it's probably is something we probably should give women the opportunity to talk about</u>
<u n="586" who="S0282">perhaps we need <trunc>th</trunc> but did you have when you were young cos I think we're kind of more or less the same age did you ever have a copy of Our Bodies Ourselves?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0646">er no</u>
<u n="588" who="S0282">didn't you? it was the most amazing American publication I think by a <trunc>f</trunc> an American feminist and in fact actually <vocal desc="laugh"/> in a way it was really bad news to me because they had a real thing about women <trunc>giv</trunc> being given hysterectomies for no good reason and how it's men wanting to kind of cut of women's bits because they were jealous of them et cetera so they were like really hysterically against people having erm hysterectomies and so on the basis of this I turned down the opportunity of explore having a hysterectomy <vocal desc="laugh"/> for quite for a while during all of this process but but the one thing it did do it had diagrams of your body names for all the bits an analysis of the kind of the things that women get plus the symptoms plus kind of conversations with women about how they felt about these things plus you know kind of quite intimate things about sex and bodies and stuff like that and it was a great big tome and they did and it was sort of published in the seventies and it was kind of quite a radical piece of pro really erm possibly reading back on it not as medically informed or sensible as it as it might have been but on the other hand you know a real good medical handbook for women's problems</u>
<u n="589" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0282">which I did get an updated version of many years later but I wonder if there's you know might even be a role for kind of republishing it or</u>
<u n="591" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0282" trans="overlap">reimagining it with with this kind of information in it for women so not just about</u>
<u n="593" who="S0646" trans="overlap">interesting cos your age there must be all kinds of interesting ways that you could do that actually</u>
<u n="594" who="S0282">yeah and I mean I read when I was having when I started getting well when my periods started getting peculiar I bought a book called Is it the Perimenopause? which is a book all about what symptoms you would get you know in the years leading up to menopause erm which was actually very useful but then described as being normal symptoms of menopause some of some of the symptoms I was having they're cos I've got cancer you know so therefore</u>
<u n="595" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0282" trans="overlap">again you know erm I wasn't getting the full picture and I probably wasn't as alarmed as I should have been and I wasn't as aeriated as I should have been and I wasn't as insistent with my doctor as I should have been cos I thought oh this is still par for the course</u>
<u n="597" who="S0646">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it's what you get when you're fifty you know and you know what what again coming back to your point what is normal? what is abnormal? if you've got a symptom how long should you leave it</u>
<u n="599" who="S0646">yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0282" trans="overlap">before you go to and say to somebody this is not right?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0646">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0282">so oh god it does make you right I mean it makes me frightened in</u>
<u n="603" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you can probably</u>
<u n="604" who="S0282" trans="overlap">retrospect actually</u>
<u n="605" who="S0646" trans="overlap">end this conversation by</u>
<u n="606" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0646" trans="overlap">just saying that kind of on a more upbeat note</u>
<u n="608" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0646" trans="overlap">at the moment both of us are in remission</u>
<u n="610" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and erm you know and I suppose the other kind of big message I have erm for the NHS is that or one of the most important things is radical surgery and having erm the opportunity to have that</u>
<u n="612" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0646">and one of the most poignant stories that I have heard is that a person I know who who was given erm an operative <trunc>sur</trunc> an operative slot of two and a half hours and she was taken down to surgery and they had they had only had two and a half hours and there was still cancer left inside her and they were obliged to sew her back up again leaving it there and</u>
<u n="614" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="615" who="S0646" trans="overlap">er whereas as I and this you know er and I am just appalled that that was done to her</u>
<u n="616" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0646">er whereas I had seven hours of exploratory surgery and they just went at it just as long as it</u>
<u n="618" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0646" trans="overlap">took them to take everything out and</u>
<u n="620" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0646" trans="overlap"><unclear>to empty the</unclear> lymph nodes and you know that that is the single most important bit of treatment</u>
<u n="622" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0646" trans="overlap">all the chemotherapy is is really precautionary to</u>
<u n="624" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0646" trans="overlap">wash up any other cells that might be hanging around but</u>
<u n="626" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0646">the treatment is the surgery</u>
<u n="628" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="629" who="S0646">and and and you</u>
<u n="630" who="S0282" trans="overlap">if it offends me pluck it out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="631" who="S0646">you yeah exactly and and I think that you know er how ridiculously short-sighted of the NHS to <trunc>tr</trunc> to to compromise on that because all that happened to that woman is she then obviously came back</u>
<u n="632" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0646">you know cos it then recurred and now she's you know having this I think this er the drug Avastin which is considered <unclear/></u>
<u n="634" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="635" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and you know and if if they'd actually done the surgery properly in the first place</u>
<u n="636" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0646">you know that would have been more effective it would have saved her life and it would have saved</u>
<u n="638" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0646" trans="overlap">them a great deal of time and energy and money and</u>
<u n="640" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0646">you know so I mean I'm a very passionate believer that you know erm women have a you know a a right to have this and it <trunc>rad</trunc> more radical surgery</u>
<u n="642" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="643" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and one of the reasons why these figures have actually improved somewhat on ovarian cancer is that they've you know they do now try this much more radical approach to</u>
<u n="644" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0646" trans="overlap">to the surgery to get everything out whereas before they did routinely leave little bits in and it only one cell</u>
<u n="646" who="S0282">oh yeah no</u>
<u n="647" who="S0646" trans="overlap">it it will go back again and you think well why on earth</u>
<u n="648" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="649" who="S0646" trans="overlap">did they ever leave a little bit in there? it was seems mad really</u>
<u n="650" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well perhaps yeah perhaps there's a part</u>
<u n="651" who="S0646" trans="overlap">perhaps they were very difficult to get hold of and maybe they just didn't have the surgical skills I'm not sure but I mean that's a really important message that you know</u>
<u n="652" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0646" trans="overlap">to to know that actually you you know you er it's really important that the NHS does give that investment</u>
<u n="654" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0646" trans="overlap">to women</u>
<u n="656" who="S0282">and perhaps <unclear/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0646" trans="overlap">in the surgery in the first round and then maybe you've cleared it</u>
<u n="658" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you know if you're lucky maybe you have you know</u>
<u n="660" who="S0282">and perhaps women need to face up to the fact that perhaps they will need a hysterectomy and that it might be the norm to have a hysterectomy in the end and actually in a lot of ways I'm really glad it's all gone really am glad</u>
<u n="661" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0282">I mean I never got on with it for the whole of my life anyway particularly</u>
<u n="663" who="S0646" trans="overlap">mm so am I</u>
<u n="664" who="S0282">it was always on a different page to me so actually the fact that it's gone and it's all been whipped away is like wahey you know</u>
<u n="665" who="S0646" trans="overlap">yeah well I mean it's funny how</u>
<u n="666" who="S0282" trans="overlap">relief</u>
<u n="667" who="S0646" trans="overlap">your attitude changes cos er erm my sister's been delightfully put that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you <unclear/> in the pelvic area</u>
<u n="668" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0646"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and erm</u>
<u n="670" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and I've thought you know I thought kind of that er when I got the menopause it would be some awful rite of passage cos I'd had IVF unsuccessfully you know and blah blah blah but I actually when I did get to that point I thought well you know I I've got beyond all that I'm not going to you know I did adopt a <trunc>ba</trunc> a baby so I was lucky and that has been hugely fulfilling and so you know that's what I did instead and</u>
<u n="672" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0646" trans="overlap">there are other ways of getting a child and erm erm so then you know I've built it up in my mind as being you know it would be this enormous like you know psychological thing but actually do you know it wasn't</u>
<u n="674" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="675" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and and similarly to you I think you know actually erm because I wasn't going to have a baby at this point anyhow</u>
<u n="676" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0646">you know I I don't feel especially you sort of sentimental about all these bits I feel god if well if that's my ticket to life get on with it and take it out</u>
<u n="678" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0646" trans="overlap">just get rid it</u>
<u n="680" who="S0282" trans="overlap">get it put it in the bin</u>
<u n="681" who="S0646" trans="overlap">you know and er put it in the bin</u>
<u n="682" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0646" trans="overlap">and so erm you know I think I didn't feel sentimental about these bits I think you know er when it comes to life or death you know there's no <unclear/> you've just gotta go for life</u>
<u n="684" who="S0282">oh yeah absolutely gosh that</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
