<text id="SYZX">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:30</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0519 S0520</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Hunsonby, Cumbria</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>traffic, family, brother, social services, take away</topics>
		<activity>chatting in the car on the M6</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0519">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Dublin, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith, `</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Recently retired maths teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0520">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead, UK`</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>India/Thailand/UK (Hunsoney</hab_city>
				<hab_country></hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Transcriber, Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0519">god has taught him how how to pray and how to be erm okay in his soul</u>
<u n="2" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0519">erm and er it's erm it's very very beautiful but really quite erm it's quite challenging to feel <trunc>u</trunc> feel that uplift it's quite er quite you know what you mostly feel is sad even though you're saying it is well you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it's interesting <pause dur="long"/> busy busy busy</u>
<u n="4" who="S0520"><vocal desc="yawn"/> what are all these people doing here?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0519">erm oh this is not it</u>
<u n="6" who="S0520">I hope there's not a queue on the er roundabout</u>
<u n="7" who="S0519">ah <unclear/> I I think it should be okay going the other way it's erm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0520">I don't know bit er it's a bit of a bottleneck it's one of those I suppose yeah it's not a busy time of day isn't it? are they supposed to tell you on this thing when there's traffic as well</u>
<u n="9" who="S0519">they do yes erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't always trust it really we need to get it updated cos cos we've had the car six years erm they bring to updates but I think they charge a hundred pounds or something so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mind went are you having a laugh</u>
<u n="10" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what a wally</u>
<u n="11" who="S0519">not having an update so we end up we go to things that are roundabouts and it says turn left at the junction you know? and things like that so places are not are not you know as they were</u>
<u n="12" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0519">it doesn't have them <pause dur="long"/> wally erm so first thing I do when we get home is take the key from dad</u>
<u n="14" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah you have to set reminders this is the key apparently not that I've ever done it but according <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's all about reminder setting</u>
<u n="16" who="S0519">so I've got a like a reminder thing but I've never known how it works really</u>
<u n="17" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah well it's quite easy just erm select the time of day and the day that you want to be reminded and you write something in the box like key from dad and then it makes it makes a little song at that time but you have to be kind of one of those peeps that has their phone with them</u>
<u n="18" who="S0519">all the time</u>
<u n="19" who="S0520">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s phone is constantly going off with these things and er it's quite a good thing to do because the those type of things that you forget and it's just a massive pain in the backside</u>
<u n="20" who="S0519">I can't believe I didn't take it from him or that nothing twigged but like that yesterday when I couldn't find my glasses my mind used to be</u>
<u n="21" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0519">that it would know that I didn't have them with me and I couldn't see the paper and there were so many clues and I didn't remember them</u>
<u n="23" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0519">that is unusual and and it's happened a couple of times and I it erm I just starting to realise that my mind isn't as good as it was cos I never used to make lists or do anything cos I had a pretty good</u>
<u n="25" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you just remembered yeah know I can imagine</u>
<u n="26" who="S0519">erm but now I I really need to</u>
<u n="27" who="S0520">need some assistance yeah well the thing is with looking for things I mean the wallet for instance is that dad could have moved it with no recollection of having done so and he often does</u>
<u n="28" who="S0519">no that's right</u>
<u n="29" who="S0520">so you know and then</u>
<u n="30" who="S0519">so you then are</u>
<u n="31" who="S0520">he's so surprised that you're asking him what he's done with it</u>
<u n="32" who="S0519">I know I know</u>
<u n="33" who="S0520">and it's like really dad? you know it's not really a time to be taking offence its just that's the way you are</u>
<u n="34" who="S0519" trans="overlap">this is normally what you do yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0519">but this time it wasn't him which is hilarious</u>
<u n="37" who="S0520">well why did you why did you put it in the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0519" trans="overlap">well I didn't I didn't so whatever they were all piled up weren't they and erm?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0520" trans="overlap">well it does quite often prove to be him being a wally doesn't it?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0519" trans="overlap">of course yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0520">oh yeah now I remember vaguely <pause dur="long"/> yeah this is what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s trying to teach me lists and reminders he says that's the way forward you make lists of what you need to do and in his case lists upon lists upon lists I think he spends more time</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="42" who="S0519">I forgot to text him back er I wanted to wait till dad had got the reply from the removers the remover guy thinks it's going to take two days which it isn't but we'll have to just let him have his two days so I told dad not to change anything else</u>
<u n="43" who="S0520">so the <trunc>wa</trunc> when are they coming eventually?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0519">Friday Saturday</u>
<u n="45" who="S0520">oh</u>
<u n="46" who="S0519">but I personally think he'll get it all done on the Friday cos we've got much less of a normal packing stuff that most people have cos we're gonna move you know pictures and some things here that we've already taken</u>
<u n="47" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah it's none of that fiddly stuff</u>
<u n="48" who="S0519">lots of stuff the kitchen there's hardly anything left in the kitchen</u>
<u n="49" who="S0520">yeah I dunno maybe they need to time to suss it out before the start as well like figure out what goes in where</u>
<u n="50" who="S0519" trans="overlap">he did say the travelling erm so that's fine I don't mind</u>
<u n="51" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0519">but if if they're coming back for a second day then it'll be pretty quick the second day cos it'll just be load the van and go</u>
<u n="53" who="S0520" trans="overlap">so then you could drive back on the Saturday yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0519">so we'd drive back on the Saturday yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0520">have you been <unclear/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this morning er <unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0519">good <pause dur="short"/> gosh I'd give a lot for that to work out for him</u>
<u n="57" who="S0520">yeah I mean even if it's just on a stable</u>
<u n="58" who="S0519" trans="overlap">even if it stays as a voluntary job and he's he's happy</u>
<u n="59" who="S0520">keeps doing it yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0519">that's right but erm <pause dur="short"/> he <pause dur="short"/> one of the other people just as it happened one of the other people started out like him did some voluntary work and then was taken on to do a few hours you know</u>
<u n="61" who="S0520">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0519">a few hours' paid work</u>
<u n="63" who="S0520">do you think he'll stay up there?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0519">erm I don't know I don't know er he certainly seems so we were saying he you know he wasn't quite the same the last few times but er still quite good</u>
<u n="65" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0519">erm but there was some some er sort of thing with the friendship with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that that's really quite important cos he he's not really got a lot going on if he hasn't got this friendship erm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0520">and where's he from?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0519">erm so he's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0520">no but is he part of like where did they meet is he?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0519">they met through the schizophrenia</u>
<u n="71" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0519">er fellowship see the these are this is the misery lane</u>
<u n="73" who="S0520">the misery lane</u>
<u n="74" who="S0519">we're going hopefully the other way</u>
<u n="75" who="S0520">oh good bye misery</u>
<u n="76" who="S0519">one two three four</u>
<u n="77" who="S0520">oh yeah yeah this is where we were queuing with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I</u>
<u n="78" who="S0519">that way?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0519">oh god</u>
<u n="81" who="S0520"><anon type="place"/> that's where I'm from <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm but okay I mean yeah it just seems that it's quite er seems to be the cycle doesn't it? you know that he has these friendships with people</u>
<u n="82" who="S0519">that's right</u>
<u n="83" who="S0520">but they're not very stable</u>
<u n="84" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no it's very intense</u>
<u n="85" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you can understand why</u>
<u n="86" who="S0519">mm sort of trying to help him to realise that you know? they have their off days and they have their low moments</u>
<u n="87" who="S0520">of course</u>
<u n="88" who="S0519">and they have their time that they need quiet</u>
<u n="89" who="S0520" trans="overlap">time off yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0519">and it doesn't mean they don't want to be with you</u>
<u n="91" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0519">but anyway erm we'll see</u>
<u n="93" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0520">but you don't think that he'll decide I mean he could decide to move further south</u>
<u n="96" who="S0519" trans="overlap">south</u>
<u n="97" who="S0520">I mean I know it's a huge upheaval in terms of his life and also all of the erm social services that he's</u>
<u n="98" who="S0519" trans="overlap">the support that's right</u>
<u n="99" who="S0520">connected to</u>
<u n="100" who="S0519">that's right erm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0520">I mean it's good that you'll see him you know</u>
<u n="102" who="S0519">we've got this regular thing going</u>
<u n="103" who="S0520" trans="overlap">regularly yeah so as long as that and but I just wonder if he'll feel you know once you're gone</u>
<u n="104" who="S0519">it's just too</u>
<u n="105" who="S0520">that he's too kind of er</u>
<u n="106" who="S0519">too isolated</u>
<u n="107" who="S0520">isolated I don't know if he would</u>
<u n="108" who="S0519">if something came of the job or any job I think that could make a big difference</u>
<u n="109" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0519">but er <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0520">and the people at erm <pause dur="long"/> that he used to be connected to at the house where do they still keep in touch at all</u>
<u n="112" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no they don't know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no that's a shame</u>
<u n="114" who="S0519">yeah it you know I I suppose it's not part of it yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0520">I guess they've just got to focus on yeah I suppose it's not part of it yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0519" trans="overlap">he's <trunc>ha</trunc> he's sort of passed over to the next so he's got some other erm support system erm and eh sees two people erm that's a big change you know just two people a week instead of somebody every day</u>
<u n="117" who="S0520" trans="overlap">every day yeah it is a big change <pause dur="long"/> but yeah they've been really good in general up there haven't they? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0519">yes really good</u>
<u n="119" who="S0520">mm mm <pause dur="long"/> traffic jam innit?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0519">oh oh</u>
<u n="121" who="S0520">we're still ducking in a twelve O the ETA</u>
<u n="122" who="S0519">come on little peeps</u>
<u n="123" who="S0520">come on little peeps</u>
<u n="124" who="S0519">we have a little person to pick up</u>
<u n="125" who="S0520">no erm we've overcome the er main one already up here there's that turning that's really</u>
<u n="126" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="127" who="S0520">trafficky <pause dur="short"/> so what are we going to do with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are we just going to drive with him</u>
<u n="128" who="S0519">we just strap him in at the back</u>
<u n="129" who="S0520">strap him in in the back</u>
<u n="130" who="S0519">and hope he's okay</u>
<u n="131" who="S0520">he can sit on my lap as well in the back</u>
<u n="132" who="S0519" trans="overlap">on a little cushion no I think you you he's be better just in the strap cos he'll wriggle and fiddle erm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0520">illegal manoeuvre as long as the er when the parents aren't looking</u>
<u n="134" who="S0519">oh heck what's going on? come on</u>
<u n="135" who="S0520">dunno a queue <pause dur="long"/> sometimes there are just those big lorries that need to turn around or that kind of thing <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0519">look this fits in here and everything</u>
<u n="137" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0519">mm yeah it did look like a good little one that</u>
<u n="139" who="S0520">good little travelling thing yeah it's really good</u>
<u n="140" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0520">and it's got special detangling</u>
<u n="142" who="S0519">and nice little</u>
<u n="143" who="S0520" trans="overlap">technology</u>
<u n="144" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and nice little shape to it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0520">yeah little comfortable shape yeah I've read about it before and it's supposed to be good and er good like holiday</u>
<u n="146" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0520">thing</u>
<u n="148" who="S0519">it's nice not to have a handle</u>
<u n="149" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> do do doo <shift new="normal"/> have you had Chinese Delight yet?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0519">no I haven't</u>
<u n="151" who="S0520">it's good</u>
<u n="152" who="S0519">have you?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0520">yeah we've had takeaway from there</u>
<u n="154" who="S0519">oh</u>
<u n="155" who="S0520">it's alright you know erm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0519">I wouldn't thank you for a Chinese delightful or otherwise</u>
<u n="157" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you've just got to get your dish that you like you know? that's the thing</u>
<u n="158" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I think I might like</u>
<u n="159" who="S0520">sweet and sour or</u>
<u n="160" who="S0519">I don't like sweet and sour</u>
<u n="161" who="S0520">do you not? no I don't either erm there are some things</u>
<u n="162" who="S0519" trans="overlap">who wants to put a pineapple in their food?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0520">don't put pineapple in my in my chicken yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0519">or raisins</u>
<u n="165" who="S0520">sometimes the Chinese do some really nice vegetables like green you know those those green vegetables with a nice sauce or something I like that</u>
<u n="166" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0520">it's all a bit nondescript</u>
<u n="168" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I like rice</u>
<u n="169" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0519">you know with stuff</u>
<u n="171" who="S0520">with stuff in it yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0519">erm and I so I don't like that any of that sort of extremely chewy bits of meat</u>
<u n="173" who="S0520">very elasticy bit nondescript bits</u>
<u n="174" who="S0519">nondescript chewy and grim</u>
<u n="175" who="S0520">no I agree with you with the fish normally they put all kind of sea creatures in it which you're not sure what they are but Thailand is like that as well they do there's a lot of seafood which is basically squid and like some some weird sort of thing with knobbly bits I think it also</u>
<u n="176" who="S0519">ooh squid little squid</u>
<u n="177" who="S0520" trans="overlap">type of squid with knobbly bits</u>
<u n="178" who="S0519">with legs</u>
<u n="179" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm not tasty never been tasty</u>
<u n="180" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="181" who="S0520">don't get it</u>
<u n="182" who="S0519">rather strange textures</u>
<u n="183" who="S0520">mm I like erm prawns but that's kind of the end of that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm they're right on the border or what I like</u>
<u n="185" who="S0520">they have to be good I find</u>
<u n="186" who="S0519" trans="overlap">really good I love them</u>
<u n="187" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah I agree</u>
<u n="188" who="S0519">and sometimes they're a bit dense</u>
<u n="189" who="S0520" trans="overlap">sometimes they have a weird texture yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah oh we're right there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0520">I know not liking it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0520">we went to this place a couple of times in Thailand which we didn't we don't like very much but they do with some friends and they erm it's like a buffet it's kind of a traditional way to eat</u>
<u n="194" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0520">erm they come with a boiling hot sort of well in the middle of the table with water at the bottom and a kind of a a raised bit with a blob of fat basically and you go to this massive buffet and you choose all this raw food and they have like meat seafood vegetables and different stuff and then you cook it yourself in this kind of</u>
<u n="196" who="S0519">vat</u>
<u n="197" who="S0520">vat of everyone else's food as well and erm it's just basically really grim but what reminds me is that you get prawns but they're like not cooked yet so they're that grey colour</u>
<u n="198" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0520">which is really off putting erm but if you do buy them fresh like that and then cook them yourself they have that really nice texture instead of the kind of</u>
<u n="200" who="S0519">okay</u>
<u n="201" who="S0520">massively over heated dense</u>
<u n="202" who="S0519">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0520">thing but yeah gosh they have a lot of weird looking creature that you can put in your bowl you know it's not that nice and nothing tastes of anything cos</u>
<u n="204" who="S0519">well you've just boiled it in water</u>
<u n="205" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you've just boiled it in water yeah and the fat as some flavouring in it I don't know I'd rather have a someone</u>
<u n="206" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah well it's a kind of a bit like erm what's it called that's not fondue that's</u>
<u n="207" who="S0520">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="208" who="S0519">cooking your meat in the middle of the table</u>
<u n="209" who="S0520">yeah you yeah we have it as well don't we? erm it has a special name</u>
<u n="210" who="S0519">I can't remember</u>
<u n="211" who="S0520">raclette you have as well</u>
<u n="212" who="S0519">oh that's right</u>
<u n="213" who="S0520">raclette is nice though raclette is when you</u>
<u n="214" who="S0519">that's frying it on like a little frying pan</u>
<u n="215" who="S0520" trans="overlap">fry the <trunc>li</trunc> we yeah we did that no this is but I mean the thing is is you pay a fixed amount and then you can have as much as you want</u>
<u n="216" who="S0519" trans="overlap">have as much as you like</u>
<u n="217" who="S0520">it's really popular er amongst the Thai people and they have a chain which is built around the same concept and in fact I did it before in China with that family that was like the special meal that they did for me</u>
<u n="218" who="S0519">oh gosh</u>
<u n="219" who="S0520">of was this</u>
<u n="220" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0520">I don't know what it's called I'm afraid buffet of raw food <vocal desc="laugh"/> and erm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0519">DIY dinner</u>
<u n="223" who="S0520" trans="overlap">kind of sort of yeah like a vat of soupy water in front of you no idea</u>
<u n="224" who="S0519">sounds horrid so</u>
<u n="225" who="S0520">er yeah I'd rather eat other things but it's nice kind of experience</u>
<u n="226" who="S0519">I suppose that's it isn't it? it's the same as us with a</u>
<u n="227" who="S0520" trans="overlap">fun mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0519">it's the sort of sharing idea</u>
<u n="229" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="long"/> we're early <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0519">why are there no other cars here? only two minutes to go</u>
<u n="231" who="S0520">I know that's what I was thinking as well</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
