<text id="SZ94">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:03</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0653 S0654 S0655</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home kitchen, Comberton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Eddie Izzard’s marathon challenge, Sport Relief, sponsoring, running, Insane Terrain challenge, obstacle courses, amazing cinema recliner seats, seeing The Chipmunks film, annoying neighbours playing loud music, Bikeability, cycling without stabilisers, coin collection of the children’s Granddad, reverse charge calls</topics>
		<activity>Talking about Sport Relief, sports and the cinema</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0653">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dartford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0654">
				<exactage>7</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0655">
				<exactage>9</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury St Edmunds</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0653">okay so I wanted to tell you about Eddie Izzard because</u>
<u n="2" who="S0654">who who?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0653">who who? sit down</u>
<u n="4" who="S0655"><unclear>ha ha</unclear></u>
<u n="5" who="S0653">he's a comedian</u>
<u n="6" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0653">and he is running seven no twenty-seven marathons over twenty-seven days</u>
<u n="8" who="S0654">oh my goodness that's a lot</u>
<u n="9" who="S0653">that is a lot</u>
<u n="10" who="S0655">and so a <trunc>marath</trunc>a marathon a day?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0653">a marathon a day</u>
<u n="12" who="S0655">woah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0653">so the few years</u>
<u n="14" who="S0654">can I pour it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0653">no I'll pour it a few years ago he did forty-seven marathons in fifty-one days I think</u>
<u n="16" who="S0654" trans="overlap">OMG</u>
<u n="17" who="S0653" trans="overlap">something something like that but yeah really an incredible thing to do and he is doing that for Sport Relief so I was wondering if we wanted to well we can either sponsor him er and or we could try and do something ourselves for Sport Relief couldn't we? could try and raise some money what do you think?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0653">what would you like <trunc>t</trunc> any ideas of what we could do?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0654">er we could <unclear/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0655" trans="overlap">win the lottery and give all the money to charity</u>
<u n="22" who="S0653">hang on er don't talk at the same time</u>
<u n="23" who="S0654">we could give some erm we could do a little children's thingy</u>
<u n="24" who="S0653">children's thingy?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0654">you know a little children's sport's day in the summertime and erm it costs one pound</u>
<u n="26" who="S0653">but that that would take a lot of organisation and planning and that would I'm just wondering if there's anything that we could do now really you could do a sponsored silence <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that'd be interesting</u>
<u n="27" who="S0654">yeah I think I might do a sponsored silence how would people know you're doing it?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0653">because you would tell people we could put it on Facebook and Twitter and things couldn't we?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0654">I want I really want to do it today</u>
<u n="30" who="S0655" trans="overlap">or you could have a sign saying sponsored silence</u>
<u n="31" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I think you could but I'm just wondering if it could be a sporty challenge that we do</u>
<u n="32" who="S0655">I could try and run a huge amount</u>
<u n="33" who="S0653">well we could all</u>
<u n="34" who="S0654">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're <trunc>l</trunc></u>
<u n="35" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0654">you're <unclear/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0653" trans="overlap">try and go to er the <anon type="place"/> race erm you know they have a every Sunday what's it what's it called? a junior park run where people run around <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0655">how long er how <trunc>w</trunc> long is that?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0653">er do you mean the distance that people run?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0655" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="41" who="S0653">I'm not sure actually I think I don't know because the erm grown-up one is five K so I think it might be half of that two and a half K</u>
<u n="42" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0653">but we could get in training for it couldn't we? and I was thinking that that might be a fun thing to do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos you don't really like running at the moment do you?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0655">but mum</u>
<u n="45" who="S0653">that could be a long challenge that we do erm from now until the summer perhaps <unclear/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0654">okay</u>
<u n="47" who="S0653">yeah?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0655">maybe I could run the six miles</u>
<u n="49" who="S0653">yeah but yeah this is what I'm saying you can't just go and run six miles we'd have to train for it wouldn't we?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0655">yeah I'll train and <trunc>tr</trunc> I'll train for a lot or I'll train for a while and then I'll be quick</u>
<u n="51" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I've mama erm now we're gonna start doing races</u>
<u n="52" who="S0655">erm and I'll be quite a bit faster once I've completed my goal</u>
<u n="53" who="S0654">mama <trunc>ev</trunc> I've got er something to do every time I come back from school here I'm gonna get erm I'm gonna go outside and run <trunc>ar</trunc> a lap around the garden not the one which is erm our backyard the one which is erm the people's</u>
<u n="54" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0653">the one <unclear>out</unclear> the front?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0655">we could all do that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0653">well I wonder if I could <trunc>c</trunc> find on the internet a a running plan for for little people</u>
<u n="59" who="S0654">and then I would run it five <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="60" who="S0653" trans="overlap">and then we could all do it together couldn't we?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0654">and I would run this er</u>
<u n="62" who="S0655">it's not just running though it's exercising</u>
<u n="63" who="S0654" trans="overlap">eight times eight laps so</u>
<u n="64" who="S0653">that would be a start <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0654">and I would see how fast I had gotten</u>
<u n="66" who="S0653">well it is exercise anyway running but yeah there's it's there's lot of things about running and how I started this nought to five K thing a couple of years ago was when you you know you run for a minute then you walk for a minute and a half so that's I think how we would have to start it with you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> nice and slowly to keep you</u>
<u n="67" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">happy</u>
<u n="68" who="S0653">feeling that you're achieving and everything but that that could be a really good thing to aim towards and there is the <anon type="place"/> race isn't there? there's a fun run in <anon type="place"/> in September and that's a really nice time of year to run cos it's not too hot and it's not too cold and I bet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if we start training perhaps in Easter when it's a little bit nicer and less muddy I reckon you could totally do that race in <anon type="place"/> in September what do you think? do you wanna give it a go? and we could raise money we could sponsor ourselves</u>
<u n="69" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0653">the trouble with erm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0655">or people could sponsor us</u>
<u n="72" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0655">or people could sponsor us</u>
<u n="74" who="S0653">that's what I mean the trouble with the erm running at <anon type="place"/> is that it's it's outdoors running I mean <trunc>i</trunc> like on the grass which is very muddy and it's a little bit more difficult than running kind of on the roads and things erm but it's <trunc>actua</trunc> it's lovely cos you get to have a a beautiful view so I think we'd need different shoes you can get a different type of running shoes for kind of muddy terrain there's also something called Insane Terrain on er September which is what I was gonna do in September last year but then you were poorly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm which is a running race but lots of fun so they have <trunc>s</trunc> er mud and <trunc>sl</trunc> water slides and just like fun obstacles to do to make it</u>
<u n="75" who="S0655">messy</u>
<u n="76" who="S0653">entertaining</u>
<u n="77" who="S0655">and messy</u>
<u n="78" who="S0653" trans="overlap">and messy</u>
<u n="79" who="S0654">but people will get messy I don't want to get messy</u>
<u n="80" who="S0653">oh baby girl it's fun</u>
<u n="81" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="82" who="S0653">you don't like that idea</u>
<u n="83" who="S0654">I don't want to get messy because in the car then I don't like it</u>
<u n="84" who="S0653">well they've got showers they've got showers</u>
<u n="85" who="S0654">I don't want to be naked in the shower with people</u>
<u n="86" who="S0653">you won't be <trunc>nak</trunc> oh yes because you hate being naked normally alright well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> maybe you and I could do that cos they've got a special junior one for kids in September so parents and kids can can do it together</u>
<u n="87" who="S0655">I think I just won't care because I walked around quite muddy in the house like in granny's house don't worry I didn't spill any mud erm er a while ago and I was like and I had jumped in the muddy ditch</u>
<u n="88" who="S0653">what? on purpose?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0655">yes a load of times <pause dur="short"/> is there like a rope swing?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0654"><vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0653">bless you</u>
<u n="92" who="S0655">is there like a rope swing to one <trunc>s</trunc>side</u>
<u n="93" who="S0653">erm they have different erm obstacle and activities every year so I don't know but they definitely have shoots to slide down erm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0655">what? like in like those things that go <vocal desc="misc"/>?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0653">a big big big shoot that goes into water</u>
<u n="96" who="S0655">so like that?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0653">so you get so actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you do get pretty clean by the end of it cos they've got a bit of a muddy thing that you've got to go through probably crawl under some stuff and go over some stuff but then</u>
<u n="98" who="S0654">there's like</u>
<u n="99" who="S0653">then they have a massive er massive slide where you go into the water and actually that cleans you up pretty well</u>
<u n="100" who="S0654">but <trunc>da</trunc> but mama is that er quite deep I can</u>
<u n="101" who="S0653">is it quite deep? it's not well no because this one will be for children so it's not going to be</u>
<u n="102" who="S0654">I can only swim with er goggles on</u>
<u n="103" who="S0653">yeah but this is for children so they're going to tailor it aren't they? to to people your age so they're not gonna drown you that wouldn't be very popular would it? if they did that so no it's not gonna</u>
<u n="104" who="S0654">how can I see? I can't see <unclear/> water</u>
<u n="105" who="S0655">only one pound</u>
<u n="106" who="S0653">cos you're only gonna be under there for like a couple of seconds</u>
<u n="107" who="S0655">only one pound to go</u>
<u n="108" who="S0654" trans="overlap">so would we have to hold our breath?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0653">no course not you're just sliding down into the water</u>
<u n="110" who="S0654">does it have is it like swimming pool water?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0653">er well I don't know I think it's just probably normal water but it will be in September it'll be warm still it's always really nice in September</u>
<u n="112" who="S0654">I know but <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="113" who="S0653">and you'll be really hot from having run around the track</u>
<u n="114" who="S0654">I think I might do that</u>
<u n="115" who="S0653">yeah? you're having a think about it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0655" trans="overlap">but mum is the shoot going to be like this? or like this?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0653">it's gonna be a big wide shoot I think but as I say</u>
<u n="118" who="S0655">but will it like have the top <unclear/> will it have <unclear>a</unclear> top?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0653" trans="overlap">it's different every well listen I'm gonna probably do an Insane Terrain in the summer beforehand so I can take photographs and show you what it's like but because it's for children <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's gonna be a lot of fun <pause dur="short"/> I really do think that you will enjoy it</u>
<u n="120" who="S0654">shall I wear a bikini?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0653">no you're gonna have to wear <vocal desc="laugh"/> shorts and a T-shirt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos you'll be running in a race first <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I think you could run in a bikini but you might look a little bit silly</u>
<u n="122" who="S0654"><unclear>why</unclear>?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah you'd get a muddy bikini</u>
<u n="124" who="S0653">huh?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0655">you'd get a muddy bikini <unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0654">I've got an idea I could wear a bikini erm underneath my clothes</u>
<u n="127" who="S0655">and then er just er</u>
<u n="128" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah but you you don't wanna wear too much cos you'll get hot</u>
<u n="129" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0653">and you know what you'll be like then</u>
<u n="131" who="S0655">so then at the very last slide you'll take your clothes off</u>
<u n="132" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0655">and then your shorts and T-shirt</u>
<u n="134" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0655">and then er you'll be in your bikini</u>
<u n="136" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0655">slide down the slide <unclear/> going <vocal desc="misc"/> I love this slide <vocal desc="nonsense"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0655"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0653">what do you think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? are you coming around to the idea?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0653">yeah?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0655" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0653">I'll try and find some photographs but I I think this is the first year that they've ever done it specifically for children</u>
<u n="146" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0653">so I don't think there's any photographs to show you of children doing it but I can</u>
<u n="148" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">then we might get photographed</u>
<u n="149" who="S0653">oh yeah you er all get photographs they that's the big thing there they always make sure everybody is photographed so then you can see yourself doing it</u>
<u n="150" who="S0654">and you get a trophy in the mud? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0653">mm I think you do get a trophy or a medal or something</u>
<u n="152" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I had er mum I had a erm <trunc>d</trunc>dream about that drink</u>
<u n="153" who="S0654">mama?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0653">about this drink? the vitamin drink?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0653">what was the dream? hang on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0655">you don't want <trunc>n</trunc> to know exactly</u>
<u n="158" who="S0653" trans="overlap">right okay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0655">yet</u>
<u n="160" who="S0654">erm mama you know what? I had a dream which was er like I was at school and</u>
<u n="161" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I had a dream</u>
<u n="162" who="S0653">just for a change</u>
<u n="163" who="S0654">I was in my PE kit</u>
<u n="164" who="S0653">uhu?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0654">and there was like this arena which had loads of mud and water and the water <trunc>w</trunc> and er some bits you can't fall off because the water is yellow and if you do then you lose and you have to get up</u>
<u n="166" who="S0653">uhu?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0654">and if you fall into that one it cleans you so</u>
<u n="168" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0654">you don't have to be all muddy so the first one is a race</u>
<u n="170" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0654">erm you need to run <trunc>arou</trunc>run around</u>
<u n="172" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0654">a track which is really muddy me and some other people won the race and got a medal</u>
<u n="174" who="S0653">ah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0654">and they take it away if you lose</u>
<u n="176" who="S0653">ah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0655">what? like Ninja Warrior?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0654">no well we only got medals to remember it cos the weakest people erm just fall over just get like a chocolate coin or something so the person <unclear>falled</unclear> over and they got a chocolate coin then it was the next bit we</u>
<u n="179" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0654">had to cross some bridges</u>
<u n="181" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0654">which were like there were two poles to each side</u>
<u n="183" who="S0653">two what?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0654">two poles</u>
<u n="185" who="S0653">two poles</u>
<u n="186" who="S0654">so there was like poles</u>
<u n="187" who="S0653">I'm saying poles</u>
<u n="188" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0654">it was like there was a bit there and poles then a bit there a bit and then some poles it was like a zigzag thing</u>
<u n="190" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0654">but some were so this one was the first height that one was the second height and that one was the second <trunc>h</trunc> third height there were two things and they had a bit of gaps you had to jump and they were quite narrow <unclear/> and erm two people fell off called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0655">you're making this up</u>
<u n="193" who="S0654">I'm not it was in my dream and they and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was watching me and so were you and they</u>
<u n="194" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0653">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was what?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0654">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was watch</u>
<u n="197" who="S0653">watching you do talk very fast sometimes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and so were you and then after those people fell off they got <pause dur="short"/> a bubble blower like a bubble blower a bubble blower kit a bubble blower machine that thing which you have to dip and blow</u>
<u n="199" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0654">yeah and then</u>
<u n="201" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0654"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> me <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were left</u>
<u n="203" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0654">and when and then there was this like slide which went up and down and up and down and it went into water and we had to swim across the water as fast as we could</u>
<u n="205" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0654">so we all did that</u>
<u n="207" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0654">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he erm he didn't want to do that again so he just went up the side again and he cheated because he erm he didn't go up he just walked around the side and was going to touch the bell when he got alluminated</u>
<u n="209" who="S0653">eliminated or illuminated?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0654">illuminated</u>
<u n="211" who="S0653">lit up that means</u>
<u n="212" who="S0654">yes he like there was like torches around him which lit up</u>
<u n="213" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="214" who="S0655">why?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0654">because if if that happens and points someone's <unclear>they</unclear> if that <trunc>ha</trunc> if he if they cheat that means the lights</u>
<u n="216" who="S0655" trans="overlap">how did he cheat?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0654">go up <unclear>the other way</unclear></u>
<u n="218" who="S0655">how did he cheat?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0654">erm he walked across the side when we had to swim</u>
<u n="220" who="S0653">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dream has been affected by Ninja Warrior</u>
<u n="221" who="S0654">yeah it was</u>
<u n="222" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0655" trans="overlap">my dream has been affected</u>
<u n="224" who="S0654">and then</u>
<u n="225" who="S0655">infected by your drink don't worry no one gets infected by it</u>
<u n="226" who="S0653">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0654"><unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0653">was that it? was that when you woke up?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="230" who="S0653">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0654">then there was erm <pause dur="short"/> this slide which had a swing you were like needed to go down and <trunc>th</trunc> only three seats</u>
<u n="232" who="S0653">uhu?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0654">and <pause dur="short"/> ten of us so we knew it was five so we let three go down <unclear>and</unclear> three go down and the first <trunc>th</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0654">they all went and couldn't grab onto the swing and they fell down they had water though and they got like a fake medal and then</u>
<u n="236" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sit down</u>
<u n="237" who="S0654">and then the other people <trunc>f</trunc> went down and landed on the swings erm it was including me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="239" who="S0654">they had <unclear/> for four seats</u>
<u n="240" who="S0655">wait which <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? there are</u>
<u n="241" who="S0653">well the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s class</u>
<u n="242" who="S0654" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in my class</u>
<u n="243" who="S0655">well there are three <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in the school that I know of</u>
<u n="244" who="S0653">there are no only one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0654">and <trunc>o</trunc></u>
<u n="246" who="S0653">there's only one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s still in there isn't she?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0654">there's two <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>s me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0653">so there's three?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0653">right let me put how long is this story gonna take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and <trunc>th</trunc> and then er one minute</u>
<u n="252" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="253" who="S0654">and then</u>
<u n="254" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> another minute</u>
<u n="255" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0654">we're on this machine which was like really fast and they fell off and I won</u>
<u n="257" who="S0653">great</u>
<u n="258" who="S0654">they got like <unclear>little</unclear> fake trophies but I got the real trophy</u>
<u n="259" who="S0653">excellent</u>
<u n="260" who="S0654">it was it said complete this challenge we are going to give you a free and it says you completed this challenge and then I got a free shower</u>
<u n="261" who="S0653">you got a free shower <vocal desc="laugh"/> I would hope so too</u>
<u n="262" who="S0654">yeah and er <trunc>w</trunc> erm and er erm because of the trophy I got six hundred erm million pounds <unclear>and we built</unclear> a swimming pool</u>
<u n="263" who="S0653">and you got a swimming pool as well? wow so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0654">and I got a recliner seat I got a recliner seat</u>
<u n="265" who="S0653" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you got a recliner seat? I can't believe we're still talking about the recliner seat</u>
<u n="266" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and that was the <trunc>d</trunc>and that was the day before we went to Alvin and the Chipmunks</u>
<u n="267" who="S0653">right so do you know what? I posted on Facebook <trunc>ab</trunc>about the the new seats in the Vue cinema saying look at these amazing seats it made seeing Alvin and the Chipmunks a load of fun and since then so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum saw that and then she took <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to see the chipmunks</u>
<u n="268" who="S0655" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0653">and then my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saw that and she took her son to see the chipmunks at the Vue so about and about four people in total and of course the reason why I took you there was because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> took her girls there a couple of days before we did and she said oh my goodness the seats are amazing and I was like what? what? what do you mean? she said just take them and you'll see so <vocal desc="laugh"/> like everybody has seen the chipmunks <vocal desc="laugh"/> in that particular cinema now</u>
<u n="270" who="S0655" trans="overlap">that's six</u>
<u n="271" who="S0653">mm loads and it yeah but they are amazing seats though aren't they?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0655">yes</u>
<u n="273" who="S0654">I wanna buy a recliner</u>
<u n="274" who="S0653">I know you want your own recliner</u>
<u n="275" who="S0655">you should've done <trunc>w</trunc> you should've <unclear/> said you should've said my quote</u>
<u n="276" who="S0653">what was your quote?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0655">I'm not sure what I preferred the seats or the film</u>
<u n="278" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well yeah it kind of it doesn't really matter what the film is any more does it? cos the seats are so much fun although I think it's silly with the two the two trays</u>
<u n="279" who="S0655">yeah cos a kid kept</u>
<u n="280" who="S0653" trans="overlap">cos they're sort of erm on either side aren't they? why are they not?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0655">yeah the kid</u>
<u n="282" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0655">kept pushing my tray out of like towards me</u>
<u n="284" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh onto you? yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0655">or like</u>
<u n="286" who="S0653">I don't think he realised though darling cos he was very little</u>
<u n="287" who="S0655">well I hadn't realised</u>
<u n="288" who="S0653">but that but that well did you say anything to him?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="290" who="S0653">no</u>
<u n="291" who="S0655">cos I knew he had started</u>
<u n="292" who="S0653">mm that's the problem though rather than say always be on the left-hand side then one is on the left and one is on the right so they touch each other don't they? so that's a bit</u>
<u n="293" who="S0655"><unclear>so they</unclear> <unclear/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0653">so they are gonna knock each other <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stop scraping your bowl but they are amazing seats but they look fine er but they're massive <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean if we had one in our house it would take up half the living room <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't it? did you mention them to dad?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0654">I er yeah <trunc>w</trunc> I</u>
<u n="296" who="S0653">did you suggest that he should get one?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0654">well kind of and we kind of didn't</u>
<u n="298" who="S0655">we didn't</u>
<u n="299" who="S0654">I really want to bulldoze the house next to us</u>
<u n="300" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0655">why?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0653">to have more room</u>
<u n="303" who="S0654">cos yeah cos last night I heard erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er next door</u>
<u n="304" who="S0653">he was shouting at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> last night wasn't he? a lot did you hear that?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0655">and usually I just hear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> banging on the wall</u>
<u n="307" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah and I heard a thump and it was like</u>
<u n="308" who="S0655">hammering something down</u>
<u n="309" who="S0654">it was like that <unclear/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0653">he just keeps going <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like that I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s being more and more naughty as she gets older cos I think she was sitting on the sofa like however when we first moved here</u>
<u n="311" who="S0655"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bit me on the ankle</u>
<u n="312" who="S0653">no well yes but that wasn't when we first moved here but we've been here five years and three months and so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you were only two well not even two nearly two very nearly two</u>
<u n="313" who="S0654">very nearly two</u>
<u n="314" who="S0653">and <pause dur="short"/> erm there were moments when I'm sure I've I've shouted at you guys or was like go to sleep go to sleep and I still do that from <trunc>t</trunc>time to time</u>
<u n="315" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0653">or of course you would've might've been crying in the night and things so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s had to put up with all of that and now of course you guys are older so you don't I don't really that never really happens and now he's doing it with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but then who knows what happens when you become a teenager</u>
<u n="317" who="S0655">I should I think I'm going to be a lovely teenager</u>
<u n="318" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yeah she really wants to run away she doesn't really like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does she?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0653">sorry?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0654">she doesn't really like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does she? she wants to run away</u>
<u n="321" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? she does she's just a she's just remember she's an abused dog so she wasn't cared for very well beforehand so she's a bit sensitive but I meant to say when you were away this weekend the teenager <trunc>l</trunc> that lives at the end of the of our garden that house</u>
<u n="322" who="S0655">mm?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0653">that backs onto it you know that always play their music quite loudly in the summer?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0655">yes</u>
<u n="325" who="S0653">well he had a party on Friday night</u>
<u n="326" who="S0655">and got sent to court</u>
<u n="327" who="S0653">and well no but he so most people wouldn't even have music that loud anyway around here but the general the law is is that you've got</u>
<u n="328" who="S0654" trans="overlap">or even have music</u>
<u n="329" who="S0653">I know the general law is is that you've got to turn the music down at eleven o'clock at night which is quite late anyway but he didn't so he was still playing his music at midnight and I was so grateful that you guys weren't here cos it would've really you would've had to sleep in my room I think</u>
<u n="330" who="S0655">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0653">but he's so kind of selfish but it's a typical kind of teenager thing to do is to have</u>
<u n="332" who="S0655">but he broke the law</u>
<u n="333" who="S0653">he did well I did ring the police but there's not a lot they can do about it it's not a police matter it's an environmental issue so</u>
<u n="334" who="S0655">why is it an environmental issue?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0653">well partly it's because police have got lots and lots of things to deal with and that's sort of the last er you know they should be doing other things that are more criminal if you see what I mean but I will I will complain I didn't ring yesterday but I will complain because actually we've never complained have we about that?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="337" who="S0653">and they there have been a lot of times when they've played really loud music</u>
<u n="338" who="S0655">yeah like when the time we had to watch Star Wars six that is the only thing I'm gonna thank them for and I'm not gonna thank them for it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0655">cos I was really tired in the morning</u>
<u n="341" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0655">even if I did get to see Star Wars six <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I mean even when it's in the summer holidays it's still rude isn't it? to do that because obviously everyone's windows were open but I mean even over the weekend when everyone's I mean all the windows were shut I could still hear the music from my bed even with my er my door shut as well so it was very loud I just felt really sorry for the <trunc>n</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the neighbour you know? the the man that we always say hello to?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0653">the <trunc>ne</trunc> that he's the next-door neighbour and he would've been kept awake wouldn't he? but it was a big teenage party</u>
<u n="346" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">well I'm surprised you didn't go round and shout at them yourself</u>
<u n="347" who="S0653">well the problem is is that if you do that then they kind of get all cross with you don't they?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0655" whoConfidence="low">yeah and then they turn the music up even louder</u>
<u n="349" who="S0653">and some people most people I would say I would go and complain but I <trunc>n</trunc> if if I knew that they were going to be kind of reasonable about it but I know that they er they were I would know that they weren't going to be reasonable about it so and it's difficult for me cos I work at the school</u>
<u n="350" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0653"><unclear>the</unclear> all of the children that were there the teenagers were there also go to the school so I kind of don't really want to attract attention in that way erm now what was our decision about World Book day? are we?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0654">see what the books were</u>
<u n="353" who="S0653">so we're gonna just get the tokens from school and then we'll go into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0654"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0655">when is World Book day?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0653">it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0654">today's Bikeability</u>
<u n="358" who="S0653">that's Balanceability today isn't it?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0655">balance?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and I can't wait to do it yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0653">yeah so <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is gonna do some balance at I didn't sign you up for any Bikeability stuff cos there wasn't anything relevant but the</u>
<u n="363" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0653">but it could actually help <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to learn to ride a bike</u>
<u n="365" who="S0654">yeah so erm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0655">without stabilisers</u>
<u n="367" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0654">yeah so that so mum <trunc>si</trunc> so I told erm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0654">this is gonna be the <trunc>la</trunc> that I can't go on erm <trunc>stabli</trunc> that I have to go on stabilisers and it <trunc>ca</trunc> and I can't go erm very fast on it and it doesn't help me cos if I go cos if I see a <unclear/> then I can't they have to lift my bike up</u>
<u n="371" who="S0653">you told Mrs <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0654">yep</u>
<u n="373" who="S0653">and what did she say?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0654">erm erm she'll she put me down for the balance</u>
<u n="375" who="S0653">yeah no it should be good that's today isn't it?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0654"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0653">World Book day is on the third of March so that's not next week that's the week after so will you all you'll all get some vouchers and then we'll go to <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> we could go to <anon type="place"/> on Mother's day</u>
<u n="378" who="S0654"><vocal desc="gasp"/> yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0653">cos that'll be</u>
<u n="380" who="S0654">get you a book</u>
<u n="381" who="S0653">or we could go on the Friday after school</u>
<u n="382" who="S0654">cos mama <unclear/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0653">or we can in fact go on the World Book day straight afterwards if you want</u>
<u n="384" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0654" trans="overlap">cos do you remember the book called erm I Love Santa Claus? there's a book called I Love My Mummy</u>
<u n="386" who="S0653">is there?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0654">yeah and there's a book called I Love My Dad</u>
<u n="388" who="S0653">yeah but er ah yeah but er these World er Book day thingies there are specific books aren't there? that you can get with them so that'll be good</u>
<u n="389" who="S0654"><unclear/> <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="390" who="S0653">so <trunc>Mo</trunc>Mother's day secrets will be announced soon won't they? at school</u>
<u n="391" who="S0654">I wish I could <unclear/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I'll buy you something and I'll also make something</u>
<u n="393" who="S0653" trans="overlap">could ask daddy for the money don't bash the table yes well you know anything would be lovely cos I know you guys love me loads and loads and loads</u>
<u n="394" who="S0654">I really want to buy two Mother's day presents from school</u>
<u n="395" who="S0655">yeah well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0653">well one one is fine</u>
<u n="397" who="S0655">you don't need to</u>
<u n="398" who="S0653">it's a good thing <unclear>to support</unclear></u>
<u n="399" who="S0655" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> <unclear>buying</unclear> one is fine okay?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0654" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="401" who="S0653">one is fine</u>
<u n="402" who="S0654">but you said one one is fine</u>
<u n="403" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0654">one one is fine</u>
<u n="405" who="S0653">you just one is perfectly fine my love and a big cuddle</u>
<u n="406" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and okay</u>
<u n="407" who="S0655"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <unclear/> <unclear> money collection remember</unclear></u>
<u n="408" who="S0653">and then maybe</u>
<u n="409" who="S0654">oh yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0654">erm erm er since</u>
<u n="412" who="S0655"><unclear/> granny's erm er last time we were at granny's which wasn't long ago</u>
<u n="413" who="S0653">mm?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0654" trans="overlap">it was this Saturday and Sunday</u>
<u n="415" who="S0655">we found out that grandad liked collecting pennies</u>
<u n="416" who="S0654">she already we already know he liked it</u>
<u n="417" who="S0655">yeah he was kind of a magpie</u>
<u n="418" who="S0654" trans="overlap">but erm and er erm he knew he was gonna die so he gave us his coin collection</u>
<u n="419" who="S0653">what? the two of you? or all of the children?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0654">erm all of his <trunc>chil</trunc> all of the children</u>
<u n="421" who="S0655">yeah a starter coin collection <unclear/> Victorian coin</u>
<u n="422" who="S0654" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0653">hang on you're both talking together</u>
<u n="424" who="S0654">not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though</u>
<u n="425" who="S0653">well no cos she didn't really know them did he? I don't think</u>
<u n="426" who="S0654">yeah he <trunc>w</trunc> gave</u>
<u n="427" who="S0653" trans="overlap">I don't think he ever met them</u>
<u n="428" who="S0654" trans="overlap">it to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and me</u>
<u n="429" who="S0653"><unclear/> sorry carry on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0655">and he had a he even had a Victoria coin</u>
<u n="431" who="S0653">oh er so where are these coins?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0654"><unclear/> at dad's</u>
<u n="433" who="S0653">dad's got them has he got so were they like divided up? into four piles five piles?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0654">no no no</u>
<u n="435" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0654">they were in a book</u>
<u n="437" who="S0653">oh they're in a book?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0654">some of them</u>
<u n="439" who="S0653">right</u>
<u n="440" who="S0654">yeah and they were like for the oldest erm to the newest and he didn't collect any coins now</u>
<u n="441" who="S0653">I didn't know he had collected coins</u>
<u n="442" who="S0654">and then we need to get a new we get we need to get a pound cos the pounds are gonna change</u>
<u n="443" who="S0653">are they?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0654">yeah they're gonna</u>
<u n="445" who="S0655">yeah they're gonna become hex-a-tagonal or something</u>
<u n="446" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="447" who="S0654">yeah and there were some coins that there was one which was golden which was I think was a pound</u>
<u n="448" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0654">I've finished my breakfast now</u>
<u n="450" who="S0653">good</u>
<u n="451" who="S0654">it's still got a bit of the thingies in</u>
<u n="452" who="S0655" trans="overlap">and I'm going to check</u>
<u n="453" who="S0653">well at least you've eaten it</u>
<u n="454" who="S0655">so all I need is a one P</u>
<u n="455" who="S0653">stay sitting down a minute</u>
<u n="456" who="S0655">a two P a five P a ten P</u>
<u n="457" who="S0653">stay sitting down</u>
<u n="458" who="S0655">a twenty P a thirty P</u>
<u n="459" who="S0653">so have you seen this collection then?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0655">oh yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0653">so</u>
<u n="463" who="S0654">we've seen it</u>
<u n="464" who="S0655"><unclear/> a twenty P a fifty P one pound and two pounds</u>
<u n="465" who="S0654"><unclear/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0653">but these that's current money but you see older coins are much harder to come by</u>
<u n="467" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and do you know what?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0653" trans="overlap">sit down</u>
<u n="469" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I want to get it</u>
<u n="470" who="S0654" trans="overlap">his dad was in erm him a long time ago his dad was in a shop</u>
<u n="471" who="S0653">oh cos his dad used to run a shop</u>
<u n="472" who="S0654">yes and it was called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0653">I think it was the post office wasn't it?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0654">and erm you can still see erm red post box post box today</u>
<u n="477" who="S0653">well we still used red post boxes darling</u>
<u n="478" who="S0654">yeah but in those days you had to put some money in</u>
<u n="479" who="S0655">it's a telephone box</u>
<u n="480" who="S0654">and if and if nobody called</u>
<u n="481" who="S0653">oh you mean a telephone box? yes</u>
<u n="482" who="S0655">not a red post box <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0653">yes you did have to put some money in isn't it funny?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0654">and then if you if you <trunc>pr</trunc> and if nobody answered you press B and you <trunc>m</trunc> get your money back</u>
<u n="485" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><unclear/> A and B</u>
<u n="486" who="S0653">that's right</u>
<u n="487" who="S0654">if you've pressed A then your money wouldn't come back</u>
<u n="488" who="S0653" trans="overlap">don't do that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's right you could do a reverse charge call do you know what that is?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="490" who="S0653">so there used to be operators people in a special place so you'd ring and you'd say operator I'd like to reverse the charges please so then they would ring whoever you wanted to speak to and they would say erm hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er would <trunc>l</trunc> is ringing you from <anon type="place"/> she would like to reverse charges is that okay? are you prepared to accept the charges? so and I would say yes or no so if you had suddenly run out of money for example and you needed to make a call to me then you could</u>
<u n="491" who="S0655">like say she'd just won the war</u>
<u n="492" who="S0653">what?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0655">like say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had just won the war and</u>
<u n="494" who="S0653">won what war?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0655" trans="overlap">she was <trunc>ama</trunc> world war five</u>
<u n="496" who="S0653" trans="overlap">no we don't oh for goodness sake but isn't that funny?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> World War Two</u>
<u n="498" who="S0653">but imagine <trunc>w</trunc> those phone <trunc>bo</trunc> don't do that to the chair those phone boxes that's all people had to communicate if you obviously you got your phone at home but you people didn't have mobile phones so you could you'd have to arrange to meet your friends like in the shops you'd say right I'm gonna meet you in <anon type="place"/> outside the cinema at twelve o'clock and that was it so you couldn't then change your mind and say oh no the cinema's full I'm gonna go somewhere else so you had to really plan whereas now <trunc>w</trunc> people with mobile phones are like yeah I'll meet you in town at some point just let me know where you are don't they?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0654">and mum?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0654">erm erm <vocal desc="cough"/> when you went to er er only very very rich people got telephones <unclear/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0653">hang on</u>
<u n="505" who="S0654">so</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
