<text id="SZAP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:03:42</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-30</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In a park in Australia</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>ideas for a small online business, social media technologies, higher education and university students, friends’ involvement in the business. </topics>
		<activity>A couple discussing ideas to set up a small online business. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, inviting, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0261">there we go okay?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0262">alright</u>
<u n="3" who="S0261">so er now it's on</u>
<u n="4" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="5" who="S0261">we are on <pause dur="long"/> this is</u>
<u n="6" who="S0262">so let's just pretend okay</u>
<u n="7" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="8" who="S0262">the</u>
<u n="9" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so we're starting with three shapes which represent</u>
<u n="10" who="S0262" trans="overlap">the three three core competences of the business</u>
<u n="11" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="12" who="S0262">okay? not in any particularly <trunc>ord</trunc> well yes no it will be in a particular order</u>
<u n="13" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0262">this represents technology</u>
<u n="15" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="16" who="S0262">social media technologies</u>
<u n="17" who="S0261">right so this is er about communication</u>
<u n="18" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0261">yes?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0262">so it's about using technology to good effect</u>
<u n="21" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="22" who="S0262">off the back of that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0261" trans="overlap">making the most of being able to spread the word</u>
<u n="24" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="26" who="S0262">exactly erm off the back of that because I've already made a start and there's other people who I can draw in erm to come into the academic world so this represents a an academic world and academic world is important because if you really got the end game being on the erm the er publishing companies erm most of the way I think you actually get to do this sort of work is when you've been hanging around here and getting to know people in the right places</u>
<u n="27" who="S0261">er publishing in academia?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0262"><trunc>ye</trunc> er publishing in in people buying books like your study skills books</u>
<u n="29" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="30" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah okay yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0262">study skills that's what I'm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="34" who="S0262">well known for</u>
<u n="35" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="36" who="S0262">so <pause dur="short"/> this actually funnily enough is erm really what I wanna do er <trunc>pub</trunc> to publishing I I want to do more work in this area of how to argue</u>
<u n="37" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0262">okay?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="42" who="S0262">there's a lot more that can be done in this area and I known that cos I've been working in this study skills learning skills area for three and a half years</u>
<u n="43" who="S0261">right yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay so I know that business quite well</u>
<u n="45" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="46" who="S0262">so this is <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="48" who="S0262">and this how we get the students to tell us what they want <pause dur="short"/> so we do our market research by getting students involved in telling us what they want</u>
<u n="49" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="50" who="S0262">we get we get that information and we kind of cherry-pick the bits that we think are useful for us and</u>
<u n="51" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0262">in terms of moving into the academic realm and hobnobbing with the right people that means going to conferences and shit</u>
<u n="53" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0262">and then when erm you rub up again with erm academics who know people who are already in with the with the publishing companies erm you make the sort of erm you know business step into you know a fully and what I would call a digital a digitalised you know <trunc>p</trunc> publication you know it's a it's <trunc>i</trunc> it's going to the next realm of what we were looking at in terms of China and and and Vietnam not necessarily on language proficiency though I do think language and arguments do go together</u>
<u n="55" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="56" who="S0262">so I can see that I can teach people language but I can also teach people how to argue</u>
<u n="57" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0262">more effectively</u>
<u n="59" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0262">in academic world</u>
<u n="61" who="S0261">okay</u>
<u n="62" who="S0262">and we could even go to <trunc>Sainsbur</trunc> secondary school with this as well so cos it's poorly done so that's what I think is how it could work</u>
<u n="63" who="S0261">yes okay so <pause dur="short"/> you're interested in delivering a message to the masses about how to learn <pause dur="short"/> or <trunc>lear</trunc> the the context of learning within er university</u>
<u n="64" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0261">er and other institutions or or university university?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0262">we'll keep it to universities for now</u>
<u n="67" who="S0261">so you'd start there</u>
<u n="68" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0261">so it's kind of like how Facebook started</u>
<u n="70" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0261">that started at college basically</u>
<u n="72" who="S0262">mm okay</u>
<u n="73" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and and everybody so that they tested an idea within one crowd and and within moments it had spread to all these other unis that wanted the same system <pause dur="short"/> so and of course there are others who like to be involved and think that they were there first erm so yes testing it within er a university crowd is probably a reasonable context <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> what what is it that you're seeking to try and share the message of and take out of? what do you get out of it?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0262">okay well</u>
<u n="75" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so if you're if you say that</u>
<u n="76" who="S0262" trans="overlap">in social yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you've got people who er you would choose to interview</u>
<u n="78" who="S0262">okay wait so social media <pause dur="short"/> erm typically where what we've been looking at erm is is like say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's got a message <pause dur="short"/> er he responds to people</u>
<u n="79" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0262">he does respond but he's basically the person delivering the message yeah?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0262">I I don't see any other people around right now what I like about the interview technique is that it puts people normally if you're really good at it it puts people on an equal level of contribution</u>
<u n="83" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262">and erm what you'd call collaboration knowledge co-construction of knowledge right?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">so yes I do want students to deliver me messages more importantly I want them to come to that site and <trunc>s</trunc> and and basically put in er you know an email request for me to interview them about something that they think passionately about in terms of the higher education you know realm of studying and learning and erm and I ask them questions on it and then I'm getting the message loud and clear that oh shit things aren't really that great <pause dur="short"/> and if anybody else is watching they can have benefit from that too <pause dur="short"/> primarily I'm meant to be benefitting from it because basically I'm the one who's running that work that erm that website</u>
<u n="87" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0262">okay? so I don't know how all the IPR stuff works I have no idea but yes essentially I'm creating a platform where people can come deliver their message to me <pause dur="short"/> and I'm not delivering any messages there is a <trunc>cer</trunc> another side to it though and I think outsourcing could be useful here <pause dur="short"/> is that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0261">can I just be clear about what message are people trying to</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right so in this book in this article</u>
<u n="91" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0262">it talks about and you need to read it but it talks about student engagement and disengagement so I deliver a message at the beginning of my website which explains the mission of the website the mission of the website is to get students to deliver messages or ideas on how to engage at university and to stop disengagement from occurring at university cos at the moment we're experiencing high levels of attrition in the first year <pause dur="short"/> because students are not engaged with what's going on when they're learning they're not given options to actually engage it's a fundamental problem for all Australian universities at the moment</u>
<u n="93" who="S0261">so <pause dur="long"/> really that that sounds like a <pause dur="long"/> er a mothers' meeting <pause dur="short"/> it sounds a <trunc>pl</trunc> a place where people share their problems on that er</u>
<u n="94" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no no it's not cos there's gonna be a dogma yeah? the dogma's gonna say <pause dur="short"/> you're allowed to <trunc>y</trunc> you're allowed to mention the name of your university but that's it you're not allowed to mention any names <pause dur="short"/> okay? you're <trunc>all</trunc></u>
<u n="95" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you mean persons?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262">yeah you're allowed to talk about the success <pause dur="short"/> of what your university is doing to engage you in your study so this one is geared up for success story it's not bitchy and moany and whining</u>
<u n="97" who="S0261">right okay</u>
<u n="98" who="S0262">yeah?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0261">yeah and that okay and that's fine <pause dur="short"/> and so in that context you can get others involved who aren't students who help teach the students about the the bigger picture?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262">well also success breeds success so if you see that erm Perth a Western Australia university is doing a student erm film festival and then the other students see that over on the other side er east side of of the coast and go well why don't we do that?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0262">we should go and ask the people who were meant to be engaging us to allow us to do shit like this and give us money so that we can run our own student film festival</u>
<u n="103" who="S0261">mm uh-mm mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="long"/> and so if you look at where you start from yeah there you've gotta create some kind of database of information to start with <pause dur="short"/> and that <pause dur="long"/> you need to find a mechanism to spread your message before you start</u>
<u n="104" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0261">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so there are certain lead elements before you actually go live with the stuff that you're doing</u>
<u n="106" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="107" who="S0261">and have you got a picture in your mind of when you would like to make that happen?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah I want this to happen in I want it to go live in <pause dur="long"/> yeah I'm flexible by about a week but essentially erm <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="short"/> yeah no oh yeah okay no I <trunc>n</trunc> I need it to go live I need it I need it to be launched in that week <pause dur="short"/> that</u>
<u n="109" who="S0261" trans="overlap">well frankly you're dreaming <pause dur="short"/> you're talking about the six-week period that we have available <pause dur="short"/> before we go to August <pause dur="short"/> yeah? what is it that you want to launch rather</u>
<u n="110" who="S0262">erm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0261" trans="overlap">I'm not saying I want you</u>
<u n="112" who="S0262" trans="overlap">some videos a few videos <pause dur="short"/> a few interview videos of students' work</u>
<u n="113" who="S0261">right so <pause dur="short"/> strategically <pause dur="short"/> don't you wanna hit the ground like massively running?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0262">what size are you thinking of?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0261">well <pause dur="short"/> you need time to to allow the message to get out there to build an audience right?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0261">and what you want is an audience to turn up on day one</u>
<u n="118" who="S0262">I know that's why it's</u>
<u n="119" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0262">semester one <pause dur="short"/> the week one semester</u>
<u n="121" who="S0261">that's this year</u>
<u n="122" who="S0262">yeah week one semester</u>
<u n="123" who="S0261">well if you consider the amount of work that actually needs to be done in the context of what else you've got to to do <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0262">well yeah but let's just say that we can get some hands on you know resources of people backing us to get that bit going</u>
<u n="125" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm not afraid of hard work <trunc>bu</trunc></u>
<u n="126" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I thought we were gonna outsource some of this</u>
<u n="127" who="S0261">yeah just hear me out right?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm okay</u>
<u n="129" who="S0261">going away in June</u>
<u n="130" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah? come back midst June</u>
<u n="132" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0261">you're talking about the six five to six week period er it's a six week period to get to there</u>
<u n="134" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0261">right? so in that six weeks you've still got to deliver certain things</u>
<u n="136" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0261">and <pause dur="short"/> what we talked about was having say ten interviews available</u>
<u n="138" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="139" who="S0261" trans="overlap">right?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0262">I didn't say ten er you said ten I never said ten</u>
<u n="141" who="S0261">er okay so when you start erm what kind of frequency do you want to publish information on <pause dur="short"/> to keep up the momentum?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0262">I dunno well you tell me what do you think's beneficial?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0261">well <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you could start with weekly <pause dur="short"/> you know so you're doing one per week</u>
<u n="144" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="145" who="S0261">and erm <pause dur="short"/> it it's not usual to do a higher frequency than that people who do a higher frequency than that are working particularly hard right?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0261">or they have that particular focus so if you start somewhere start with one per week</u>
<u n="148" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0261">and er and you need to maintain a connection with your audience right?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0261">so you you get your your pre-message out there you create a launch platform</u>
<u n="152" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0261">you have a a a landing page for a website</u>
<u n="154" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0261">which people you get people to sign up to that to start with</u>
<u n="156" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0261">before you get to the video stage</u>
<u n="158" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0261">right? and you might try and erm promote that there's there's a product that they might be interested in yeah? so they get access to that by signing up <pause dur="short"/> create a mini product which gives a benefit to people right for free yeah? they sign up they get the product they they see what's going on and they get an interest and then you can put out a couple of YouTube videos which er which tag in at your website yeah? so then you've got a visual message out there that you can steer people to straight up without going to your website but it takes it back through a loop to your website so the curious go and have a look at that and sign up</u>
<u n="160" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah? erm and you can and you and you wanna try and create some kind of message that goes through your Facebook er and Twitter et cetera so the it can get shared</u>
<u n="162" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0261" trans="overlap">amongst the social stuff</u>
<u n="164" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0261">so you have to get all those things in place upfront and then you want erm a a a series of videos that you've got pre-prepared that you can launch to take the pressure off having to create those at those times</u>
<u n="166" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0261">so you launch one you're going to be dealing with trying to capture that market and capture the people</u>
<u n="168" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0261">and that's where your time's gonna be spent rather than making videos</u>
<u n="170" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0261">so if you've got a few made in advance you've bought yourself time to get used to that process</u>
<u n="172" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0261">and then <trunc>cre</trunc> and then you start creating them ongoing basis</u>
<u n="174" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0261">so you might say oh well I've got a couple of weeks left I need to start creating some more videos so then I've got a buffer</u>
<u n="176" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0261">of more right? erm and you'll find that information will come in that you'll want to try and adapt with</u>
<u n="178" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0261">to try and help streamline a few things and what have you all sorts of systems you need to make sure are set up</u>
<u n="180" who="S0262">yeah you say you</u>
<u n="181" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and so on</u>
<u n="182" who="S0262">meaning I er is that meaning like you?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0261">well that's us yeah?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0262">oh oh okay</u>
<u n="185" who="S0261">that's us</u>
<u n="186" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0261">erm er and and sure outsourcing and getting people onboard erm some of the stuff I have an awareness of but I've never done</u>
<u n="188" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0261">so I need in that June period I would be looking to be using something to to to learn and create and I'd prefer to know how to do that first before I do it in real for this</u>
<u n="190" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0261">right? so erm part of it is what I I would have put that kind of platform together with <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0261">but they weren't receptive to that but I have a quite a big big picture of</u>
<u n="194" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0261">it's quite a large platform of</u>
<u n="196" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0261">how you bash it out yeah?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0261">and and you're <trunc>tryi</trunc> the real thing is about trying to create a strong launch</u>
<u n="200" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0261">and getting people's email addresses so you're getting messages out to them as soon as you've got that you can create email campaigns</u>
<u n="202" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0261">to keep people onboard they're quite that is quite straightforward</u>
<u n="204" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0261">you keep them engaged that way</u>
<u n="206" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0261">and you can do that on a on a however many day basis</u>
<u n="208" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0261">but it's really you bash out a message side of A4 boom</u>
<u n="210" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0261">out there</u>
<u n="212" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="213" who="S0261">you know?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0261">and that gets them interested and connected upfront and you can use other carrots to get them involved like free products et cetera and then you go boom on that day this is what's gonna happen come and have a look at us you might flash out some kind of certainly a social media message if not a media message you try and get something published in er connecting forums or pages or media</u>
<u n="216" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0261">that leads to your site</u>
<u n="218" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0261">so you say you go to Education Supplement dot com or whatever it is you write a little article you get them to publish it you put stuff into their forums</u>
<u n="220" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0261">and you say this is who I am come and have a look at my stuff boom you're getting people from all these different corners who go boom land on your on your site at the same time</u>
<u n="222" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0261">yeah? so erm and you you kind of want to you know there are technical things you need to be aware of that <trunc>cou</trunc> you know could fall down because too many people come along for the size of server that you've got available you know</u>
<u n="224" who="S0262">yeah that's kind of cool though</u>
<u n="225" who="S0261">and that's kind of cool but it fucks up your launch and that</u>
<u n="226" who="S0262" trans="overlap">sure</u>
<u n="227" who="S0261">so you wanna you wanna get through that and keep that going so there's a <pause dur="short"/> there's grounds for having a test first you <trunc>nee</trunc> you wanna try and test it first</u>
<u n="228" who="S0262">yeah this is the test</u>
<u n="229" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you want you want to you want to take some guinea pigs</u>
<u n="230" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0261">and you wanna have them be the guinea pig run</u>
<u n="232" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0261" trans="overlap">for it first</u>
<u n="234" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay this is the test</u>
<u n="235" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so <trunc>p</trunc> pick a few pick a few students</u>
<u n="236" who="S0262">oh I will</u>
<u n="237" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0262">yeah thanks and er the test is semester two two thousand and thirteen the real launch will be semester one two thousand and fourteen because the semester one launch is fucking massive</u>
<u n="239" who="S0261">right okay</u>
<u n="240" who="S0262">it's huge orientation is when students are switched on they're at their most engaged and that's when we know we've got a captive audience</u>
<u n="241" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0262">I know it</u>
<u n="243" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0262">okay I've seen it been there and I've seen five hundred people in a lecture theatre</u>
<u n="245" who="S0261">okay so this test that you do here</u>
<u n="246" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0261">what are you gonna do with the other six or eight months <pause dur="short"/> in between those two times?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0262">well interview people grow a repository</u>
<u n="249" who="S0261">right erm and if you are one of those people somebody came along and said do you mind if I interview you blah-blah-blah-blah-blah erm we wanna use this we're gonna use it on this basis oh but we're not gonna use it for six months</u>
<u n="250" who="S0262">no no we'll would we'll we'll figure out a frequency that will be enough to keep it ticking along</u>
<u n="251" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0262">but you can have a</u>
<u n="253" who="S0261" trans="overlap">plan</u>
<u n="254" who="S0262">you can have a mini launch</u>
<u n="255" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0262">and you can have a major launch</u>
<u n="257" who="S0261">yeah yeah you're right erm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so the ones who are the early adopters are all cool with it</u>
<u n="259" who="S0261">yeah yeah for sure and you've got the early adopters who who who who are by <trunc>def</trunc></u>
<u n="260" who="S0262" trans="overlap">are spreading the word for us</u>
<u n="261" who="S0261" trans="overlap">who are by definition people outside the normal box of</u>
<u n="262" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0261" trans="overlap">the bell curve anyway</u>
<u n="264" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0261">so erm <pause dur="short"/> and that's good because that allows six months to actually build quite a significant</u>
<u n="266" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0261" trans="overlap">erm product</u>
<u n="268" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0261">yeah? and</u>
<u n="270" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and the universities will never compete on that level as quickly as we can move because marketing is so full of bureaucracy that no one will be able to make decisions on anything</u>
<u n="271" who="S0261"><trunc>y</trunc> yeah the erm part of part of my concern would be with the exposure to others who could do the er the same thing in</u>
<u n="272" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well they can't <pause dur="short"/> the universities can't do it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0261">no I'm talking about other individuals</u>
<u n="274" who="S0262">oh yes of course</u>
<u n="275" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you know?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0262" trans="overlap">they can always do it yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah? anywhere yeah?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so could <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s one</u>
<u n="279" who="S0261">so if you're looking at trying to get <pause dur="short"/> erm a strength in in in the market <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0262">I think you're right and a a product or a service attached to the interviews would be useful</u>
<u n="281" who="S0261">yeah and you and you build a series of those things as you go</u>
<u n="282" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0261">so you can say in that six months that allows you to build one side of it and the other</u>
<u n="284" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0261">the interview side of it and the core business side</u>
<u n="286" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0261">yeah? and you're linking those things together you're getting messages out there et cetera</u>
<u n="288" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well <trunc>bu</trunc> business is comes later the business is gonna be down here</u>
<u n="289" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0262">this is just a platform to get credibility in order to move into these areas</u>
<u n="291" who="S0261" trans="overlap">well you still want to find mechanisms to get your money in the door</u>
<u n="292" who="S0262">yes well the mechanism <trunc>ye</trunc> well the money will come here I don't know how to make money on this</u>
<u n="293" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Arnold come here</u>
<u n="294" who="S0262">I don't even know how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s making money</u>
<u n="295" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Arnold</u>
<u n="296" who="S0261">hey fella</u>
<u n="297" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="298" who="S0261">you know <trunc>y</trunc> yay get out of it</u>
<u n="299" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">sorry</u>
<u n="300" who="S0262">oi that's alright</u>
<u n="301" who="S0261">that's alright <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0261"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0262">erm yeah <trunc>potent</trunc></u>
<u n="305" who="S0261" trans="overlap">he's not allowed our beer or our crisps</u>
<u n="306" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> come on</u>
<u n="307" who="S0261"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0262">but</u>
<u n="309" who="S0261" trans="overlap">cheers mate</u>
<u n="310" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's alright</u>
<u n="311" who="S0261">have a nice day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah alright</u>
<u n="313" who="S0262">potentially sponsors <pause dur="short"/> hanging advertising off it that's all I can think of</u>
<u n="314" who="S0261">well yeah yeah well</u>
<u n="315" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but we need to <trunc>sh</trunc> pick <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brain</u>
<u n="316" who="S0261">well look look in in terms of of websites right</u>
<u n="317" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0261"><trunc>a</trunc> they do typically what's called affiliate marketing</u>
<u n="319" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0261">so like what that other guy was doing he was hanging different products off his site</u>
<u n="321" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0261">but it's such that if somebody clicks through your site to go and purchase that product he would have got a commission from the software company</u>
<u n="323" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0261">so it's a kickback yeah for sending people in in in their direction</u>
<u n="325" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0261">so what you would do</u>
<u n="327" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0261">is you would identify key parts that er <pause dur="short"/> erm key erm <pause dur="short"/> key companies or key outfits that you would want to connect to</u>
<u n="329" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0261">and what you're trying to do is you're getting exposure because you are actually <trunc>usi</trunc> you wanna use their email list their contacts you wanna draw them in as well</u>
<u n="331" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="332" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0262">okay I I'll need to <trunc>g</trunc> check with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about how to do that cos I don't I don't know how to do that but I will ask him how to do that but I've got a couple of ideas in mind</u>
<u n="334" who="S0261">well I know how to do in an internet marketing way</u>
<u n="335" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="336" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0262">but we can also get some free <pause dur="short"/> advice from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about</u>
<u n="338" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0262" trans="overlap">how to do it cos I think he does that day in day out so it would be good to touch base with him and</u>
<u n="340" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah for sure</u>
<u n="341" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and I think getting a a sound erm independent outlook</u>
<u n="343" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0261">is good</u>
<u n="345" who="S0262">get some measurements in thrown in there cos that's what companies want to see</u>
<u n="346" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0262" trans="overlap">how do you measure this?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's what you don't know but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does yeah?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="351" who="S0262">okay so let's have him</u>
<u n="352" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and then</u>
<u n="353" who="S0262" trans="overlap">more as a sort of you know cursory kind of advisor</u>
<u n="354" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm and we want to be able to capture some metrics as we go</u>
<u n="355" who="S0262">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="356" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0262">so I have got a couple of ideas of how to do that erm <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> of cool port is er makes you think of you know water but <trunc>simi</trunc> similarly erm if you take the idea of port being an airport right?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0261">or a portal</u>
<u n="359" who="S0262">a portal yeah I'm thinking port meaning something like you know <pause dur="short"/> port it's a place where you arrive it's a place where you kind of get off at a destination that's why we got the idea airport <pause dur="short"/> harbour port you know?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0261">you're saying well you pitch this to an international student saying you're arriving from outside of this place</u>
<u n="361" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so one of my dogma questions in the interview is <pause dur="short"/> so Sarah tell me what's so cool about studying in where you are?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="363" who="S0262">and she gets hey Montreal is like blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0262">and oh Sydney's fantastic because blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm and so people</u>
<u n="367" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and if you go to</u>
<u n="368" who="S0261" trans="overlap">get this international feel for it</u>
<u n="369" who="S0262">so <vocal desc="whistle"/> planes</u>
<u n="370" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0262">that's what kids get on these days buy er plane tickets and they go somewhere</u>
<u n="372" who="S0261">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0262">so I'm thinking airline carrier</u>
<u n="374" who="S0261">oh as an affiliate?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0261">well could be <pause dur="long"/> that's one one option yeah <pause dur="short"/> of the myriad sector you could choose</u>
<u n="377" who="S0262">well I mean it would only happen if it was a majorly successful site</u>
<u n="378" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0262">it's may as well aim big there</u>
<u n="380" who="S0261">well you wanna be aiming high</u>
<u n="381" who="S0262">I'm aiming very high</u>
<u n="382" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0262">I'm thinking New <trunc>Zeal</trunc> Air New Zealand or Qantas <pause dur="short"/> or someone else air er if we go Asia Pacific</u>
<u n="384" who="S0261">Virgin</u>
<u n="385" who="S0262">who? Virgin yeah alright</u>
<u n="386" who="S0261">er if wanna kind of think flamboyant and think entrepreneurial and think the kind of people who like the spirit of entrepreneurs Virgin's a good outfit to run</u>
<u n="387" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0261">if you get somebody like Branson saying hello</u>
<u n="389" who="S0262">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0261">you just have to get him to say hello</u>
<u n="391" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0261">because he would like the idea that you're sending business his way er <trunc>thr</trunc> through some educational means <pause dur="short"/> or maybe he wouldn't he hates the education</u>
<u n="393" who="S0262">does he?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0261">yeah he doesn't believe in the <trunc>con</trunc> well it's not that he hates the education he doesn't believe in the <trunc>contex</trunc> the concept of of business schools et cetera</u>
<u n="395" who="S0262">but this is about students telling us</u>
<u n="396" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0262">what they want he likes that he likes having</u>
<u n="398" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0262" trans="overlap">customers telling you</u>
<u n="400" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0262" trans="overlap">what you want</u>
<u n="402" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0262" trans="overlap">what they want</u>
<u n="404" who="S0261">yeah no I'm I'm let's not suppose that one but yeah that in the rounds that sounds quite strategically interesting <pause dur="short"/> erm so you're saying <pause dur="short"/> er a small launch that is focussed on a bunch of people so like we talked about having a list of a bunch of people that have a strong network contact so then you can start building</u>
<u n="405" who="S0262">I think it should be thematic as well</u>
<u n="406" who="S0261" trans="overlap">through their</u>
<u n="407" who="S0262">I I actually do think month in month out you should we should be picking themes <pause dur="short"/> so one theme could be you know tell us about something recent that you've done that you've engaged with outside of your curriculum you know something like that but much catchier</u>
<u n="408" who="S0261">yeah mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and then another theme might be you know tell us about something cool that your lecturer did the other day you know or tell us about some educational technology that you didn't know about and how you you know so the themes are always about engagement but I know <trunc>h</trunc> I know so much about engagement that I can pick off probably twelve themes that I could cover throughout the year</u>
<u n="410" who="S0261">yeah okay erm <pause dur="short"/> I I think starting with themes seems reasonable <pause dur="short"/> and then as you kind of get through it you you probably wanna mix things up so it's it's less kind of chunk chunk chunk</u>
<u n="411" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I want a box where people can write in to me and suggest themes like so frank so people write in say you know</u>
<u n="412" who="S0261">well that's what you use your test crowd for upfront</u>
<u n="413" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0261">you'll ask them their opinions you'll get their feeling you see what they like and try them on products and see <trunc>wh</trunc> how they react to it get their feedback all of that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="415" who="S0262">don't want too much cos students have got a completely minimal attention span</u>
<u n="416" who="S0261">yeah well you're probably trying to draw in those who will react like that say if it's strength on</u>
<u n="417" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah I don't want it too hard <unclear>basket</unclear> straight away though we need to make it as fucking easy to participate as possible and I know that basically</u>
<u n="418" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah well that that's what you're trying to to test</u>
<u n="419" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0261">you're trying to test whether your your ideas are are <trunc>a</trunc> aligned with what they think</u>
<u n="421" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0261">as as much as you think you know you will find surprises</u>
<u n="423" who="S0262">well I know a <trunc>sh</trunc> short amount of time to fill out erm an an email thing where they give me my their email address is good</u>
<u n="424" who="S0261">yeah and and I mean just what I you know I obviously said that to <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> I said well engage some of your erm customers to start with before you launch this stuff get the feeling of what they like and dislike and then build that into the system before you</u>
<u n="425" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0261">before you do the major launch and that's what I'm saying with the six month period you look to try and optimise that so when you do go bang you go bang with a big bang</u>
<u n="427" who="S0262">yeah alright</u>
<u n="428" who="S0261">and <trunc>a</trunc> amongst all of that time you've got to test that you've damn well</u>
<u n="429" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0261">got some some money</u>
<u n="431" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that dog's making a freeking beeline for us again</u>
<u n="432" who="S0261">he is</u>
<u n="433" who="S0262">get your hand out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="435" who="S0262">he's coming straight at you</u>
<u n="436" who="S0261">yeah he's gonna he's gonna hey dog</u>
<u n="437" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0261">something about cricket you like isn't it? yeah? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="439" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">sorry guys he can smell the chips a mile off</u>
<u n="440" who="S0261"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> does he like eating them?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0261">bribery</u>
<u n="443" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">he loves potato chips</u>
<u n="444" who="S0262">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0261" trans="overlap">here we go <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="446" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">go on move it</u>
<u n="447" who="S0261"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0262">that's pretty funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0261"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">go on move it</u>
<u n="451" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0261"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0262">now there isn't gonna be just me by the way interviewing students I'm going to do erm er I'm gonna close the learning loop okay so <pause dur="long"/> for me the learning <trunc>l</trunc> loop is about getting the dialogue going which is what I'm good at doing and I'm getting getting to the really good questions and the students are pumping out some really good answers about what's going on with them and then we need another person an off-sider who's cool <pause dur="short"/> who's not a woman but a man</u>
<u n="454" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0262">yeah double act always works perfectly</u>
<u n="456" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="457" who="S0262">erm who actually is a lecturer and lends credibility to the whole thing okay?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0261">right okay</u>
<u n="459" who="S0262">so I'm a learning advisor and we need a lecturer</u>
<u n="460" who="S0261">academic lecturer somebody who's</u>
<u n="461" who="S0262" trans="overlap">academic lecturer it's somebody who's really working in the environment and knows what you know students are up against</u>
<u n="462" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0262">but can also give a little bit of themselves and say you know yeah but I'm <trunc>tr</trunc> I am I'm trying to do stuff like this but it's not so easy because and they give some reasons why</u>
<u n="464" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0262">so mainly to do with universities but you don't slag off the universities you just let so this person is going to be called is going to be faceless is not gonna have a face I'm gonna be the face yeah?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="467" who="S0262">not two two competing faces but he's gonna have a voice and he's gonna be a podcast voice okay?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0261">oh so he's gonna be like the stick?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> fantastic I'm so glad you've got that but do you know what his name's gonna be? Sage</u>
<u n="470" who="S0261">Spod</u>
<u n="471" who="S0262">Sage</u>
<u n="472" who="S0261">Sage</u>
<u n="473" who="S0262">Sage on a stage</u>
<u n="474" who="S0261">right okay</u>
<u n="475" who="S0262">wise one whatever</u>
<u n="476" who="S0261">yeah okay</u>
<u n="477" who="S0262">and Sage is gonna be the word of reason and reflection <pause dur="short"/> so what happens is that I interview the person the student and we have that nice dialogue going and then Sage will listen at a later date and he will he will er <trunc>re</trunc> review sorry he will</u>
<u n="478" who="S0261" trans="overlap">the footage</u>
<u n="479" who="S0262">he will listen</u>
<u n="480" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0262">will make some notes and then he will record his erm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0261">response to that</u>
<u n="483" who="S0262">response to that</u>
<u n="484" who="S0261">and what do you do with that response?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0262">and then I post it up so that's another little side bit so interview and then maybe a day or two later I don't know how the trickledown effect will happen</u>
<u n="486" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0262">but you've always got a follow up</u>
<u n="488" who="S0261">yeah okay</u>
<u n="489" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you've got another reason for going back and having a and and listening</u>
<u n="490" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I I I I like that</u>
<u n="491" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you've got that</u>
<u n="492" who="S0261">you can say</u>
<u n="493" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0261">like in a couple of days it <trunc>w</trunc> and and never make it a consistent number so people don't get used to</u>
<u n="495" who="S0262">exactly</u>
<u n="496" who="S0261">it being there</u>
<u n="497" who="S0262">it's just</u>
<u n="498" who="S0261" trans="overlap">but within a week</u>
<u n="499" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0261">you say at some time during that week it becomes quite random</u>
<u n="501" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0261">that you you <trunc>al</trunc> you you post this thing in response to the the item of the week</u>
<u n="503" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0261">and when you post it that that is done through an email and distribution as well as it going up on that website</u>
<u n="505" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0261">so people go well this week we had this you've got the link to the web</u>
<u n="507" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0261" trans="overlap">the the video so people can come and watch the video</u>
<u n="509" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0261">and then you've also got the link that goes to the response</u>
<u n="511" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0261">to that</u>
<u n="513" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0261">yeah? so then you've got a story to tell we had an interview with X Y Z</u>
<u n="515" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0261">these were the points</u>
<u n="517" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0261">and then this is the feedback or that this is some reflection from guest lecturer blah-blah-blah-blah-blah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0261">that that that</u>
<u n="521" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I mean don't tell them too much cos you really do want to</u>
<u n="522" who="S0261" trans="overlap">the Sage from the the Sage</u>
<u n="523" who="S0262">yeah you just give them a log line of about three words and then they've got to go and listen to the podcast on the website</u>
<u n="524" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah yeah but what it however it's formatted</u>
<u n="525" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="526" who="S0261">and how whatever it looks like but you can I can get the gist</u>
<u n="527" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="528" who="S0261">that's quite cool</u>
<u n="529" who="S0262">so the thing</u>
<u n="530" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0262">about it is then is that</u>
<u n="532" who="S0261">what's in it for the lecturer?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0262">oh well we'll come to that in a minute erm Sage <pause dur="short"/> sage has got to have a personality because he hasn't got a face <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0262">so Sage has to have a narrative working around him</u>
<u n="536" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="537" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay otherwise he's just gonna be fucking boring</u>
<u n="538" who="S0261">well you can make it sound like a podcast</u>
<u n="539" who="S0262">yeah well it will be a podcast but what I'm trying to say is I'm creating a persona for Sage here</u>
<u n="540" who="S0261">yes yeah that's right</u>
<u n="541" who="S0262" trans="overlap">cos he hasn't got a face he's like an avatar in a way</u>
<u n="542" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0262">but not cos I don't hate avatars okay</u>
<u n="544" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0262">so he won't have a cartoon face he will not have a face he will just have a voice okay? so that's something that students are gonna feel a bit wary about but what are we gonna tell them about Sage? hang on let me have a go cos I'm I haven't had a chance</u>
<u n="546" who="S0261" trans="overlap">I haven't said anything</u>
<u n="547" who="S0262">well you were about to Sage is gonna have two things going for him okay? to appeal to the male student audience he's gonna love test-driving cars <pause dur="short"/> and the other one <pause dur="short"/> for the female audience who are gonna have a really kind of like you know over sort of imagination about who this fella is yeah there's gonna be a question about I haven't really kind of got it right yet but it's something like along the lines erm you know who do you think Sage most resembles in your role in a role er not a role model but erm you know it'll be better than that but it's about basically you've got to put up photographs of who you think Sage might be okay? so we're gonna have things called wiki surveys and then you always click between two choices and you're getting this interaction going on where students come in they'll listen to the interview and then they get to be interactive and then get to click which car they want test-driven next time or which car they think would most be coolest to test drive okay? so when Sage starts his little piece about the reflection piece he's always starts with it's formatted yeah? so I was driving along the other day in my or in a you know test-driving whatever car yeah? blah-blah-blah-blah-blah and I was thinking about Sarah's interview with you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or whatever and this is my response so it always starts with driving along in a car <pause dur="short"/> or a motorbike</u>
<u n="548" who="S0261">yeah okay cool</u>
<u n="549" who="S0262">yeah?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0261">yeah yeah alright</u>
<u n="551" who="S0262">so the reason why I want that to happen is because I want students to engage with the personalities that I've presented to them</u>
<u n="552" who="S0261">well Sage could be Richard Hammond</u>
<u n="553" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0261">cos he loves science and education</u>
<u n="555" who="S0262">Sage could be anyone it's just a voice but Sage actually has to be quite clever</u>
<u n="556" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0262">he can't be somebody who's a bit of a nonce <pause dur="short"/> cos he's got to be able to articulate between what the students are telling him and what he fucking knows about how universities actually work</u>
<u n="558" who="S0261">yeah okay mm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0262">so he's got to be an inside job</u>
<u n="560" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0262">but he can't be too inside on the outside</u>
<u n="562" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="563" who="S0262">cos people start getting a bit wary about it</u>
<u n="564" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0262">even though I clearly work from <anon type="place"/> university</u>
<u n="566" who="S0261">people don't need to know that</u>
<u n="567" who="S0262">ah well this is then this is gonna be the interesting thing isn't it? credibility <pause dur="short"/> anyone say they're a learning advisor but credibility is about you're a learning advisor at which university</u>
<u n="568" who="S0261">at a university</u>
<u n="569" who="S0262">no but think about it you your English fella <anon type="place"/> university he could spread that all around</u>
<u n="570" who="S0261">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0262">well what did he get out of that? well what did they get out of that? so that somebody wants to go to <anon type="place"/> university because they've seen his website</u>
<u n="572" who="S0261">maybe <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's interesting <pause dur="long"/> so <pause dur="short"/> well it sounds like there's quite a lot to do before this end of July</u>
<u n="573" who="S0262">and that's just the beginning</u>
<u n="574" who="S0261">yeah I know</u>
<u n="575" who="S0262">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="576" who="S0261">so</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="577" who="S0262">does that frighten you?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0261">oh I <trunc>don</trunc> I don't know that it frightens me I'm just trying to think realistically that's all</u>
<u n="579" who="S0262">well we <trunc>don</trunc> this is an ideal version you know</u>
<u n="580" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah I know I know I know I know I know know know <trunc>th</trunc> and and there's no reason why it <trunc>ha</trunc> <trunc>wh</trunc>what is the <trunc>wh</trunc> rather what is the reason why it has to be before er that end of July? that's the start of a new semester is it?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0261">okay</u>
<u n="583" who="S0262">it also means I maximise my erm time at <anon type="place"/> university</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="584" who="S0261">yes erm <pause dur="short"/> I I kind of think before you get to that semester you <trunc>y</trunc>you wanna have a few things in place that are already kind of there</u>
<u n="585" who="S0262">like?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0261">well it's like when you're trying to say to somebody you want to steer them to a certain place that they want to see that others have already been there</u>
<u n="587" who="S0262">that's how no I've got really good</u>
<u n="588" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that kind of thing</u>
<u n="589" who="S0262">student contacts <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="591" who="S0262">trust me</u>
<u n="592" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0262">we've got people who I know would turn up tomorrow and do an interview with me and they'll be fascinating</u>
<u n="594" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I'm not I'm not worried about that</u>
<u n="595" who="S0262">well that's the content that's the bit I do</u>
<u n="596" who="S0261"><trunc>ye</trunc>yeah what I'm saying though is you get to semester one and you want to be trying to launch something</u>
<u n="597" who="S0262">mini launch</u>
<u n="598" who="S0261">mini</u>
<u n="599" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0261">launch yeah and so this mean you you you're actually trying to constrain anything or are you</u>
<u n="601" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="602" who="S0261">no? you're just doing a mini launch and see where it goes?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0261" trans="overlap">right so you take that where where where does it go and before you launch you wanna have already engagement with things like your social sites yeah?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0261">on a small level but so at least at least that it looks like it's being used</u>
<u n="607" who="S0262">of course</u>
<u n="608" who="S0261" trans="overlap">it's not brand new</u>
<u n="609" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0261">yeah? so erm</u>
<u n="611" who="S0262">so we need er seeders</u>
<u n="612" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and you need outsourcers</u>
<u n="614" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's where you come in</u>
<u n="616" who="S0261">yeah <trunc>ye</trunc> yeah that's right <pause dur="short"/> but I I just need to get a context of of er how how much work you expect that you'll be doing and how much you think I'll be doing</u>
<u n="617" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I'll I'll do everything I can in the hours that I've got to make this happen</u>
<u n="618" who="S0261">right okay</u>
<u n="619" who="S0262">and I will really really rely on fucking massive favours from people to get it to happen for that for that launch</u>
<u n="620" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0262">and we will be away in the UK for the launch so that will be very advantageous</u>
<u n="622" who="S0261"><trunc>ye</trunc> <trunc>ye</trunc> in which context that that you you're er already putting in place a system which is which is others will be dealing with it</u>
<u n="623" who="S0262">no you and I will be dealing it you you're testing this rebel location right? that's what I thought we were doing</u>
<u n="624" who="S0261">yeah yeah no no no that's fine so you wanna test it from afar</u>
<u n="625" who="S0262">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="626" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah that's okay</u>
<u n="627" who="S0262" trans="overlap">remote that's what we're talking about</u>
<u n="628" who="S0261" trans="overlap">absolutely that's fine</u>
<u n="629" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0261">that's absolutely fine so you get to you get to get a a kind of a full dog hog kind of understanding of</u>
<u n="631" who="S0262" trans="overlap">plus</u>
<u n="632" who="S0261" trans="overlap">where the</u>
<u n="633" who="S0262">we'll have three weeks</u>
<u n="634" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s studio</u>
<u n="635" who="S0262" trans="overlap">hanging out with my dad who'll be loving it my brother will come up have a look</u>
<u n="636" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="637" who="S0262">and he will totally engage with it</u>
<u n="638" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="639" who="S0262">and he will just start pumping ideas in</u>
<u n="640" who="S0261">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he might even give us people</u>
<u n="642" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="643" who="S0262">to connect with and make it even better</u>
<u n="644" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0262">so we've gotta be on the UK ground so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can be readily available to help with it</u>
<u n="646" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so that's what you're interested in trying to get a a a a right buy in from?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0261">yeah okay alright I can <trunc>un</trunc> now I can understand actually why the deadline's</u>
<u n="649" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that deadline so erm <pause dur="short"/> I mean my first focus obviously is to finish the stuff or <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> and that's gonna be shove anyway but I've set a date a few days before I go away and we need to <pause dur="short"/> pre-plan and have other things in place for when I go away as well</u>
<u n="651" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0261">yeah we made a big list so I think it's kind of a case of having to crack on but do a bit of each every day</u>
<u n="653" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="654" who="S0261">rather than do that chunk and then do that chunk and then that chunk</u>
<u n="655" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0261" trans="overlap">I mean there is priorities but <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="657" who="S0262">we'll we'll give them</u>
<u n="658" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you need to do a little bit each day so you don't kind of find that it's a struggle</u>
<u n="659" who="S0262">given the given the new er impetus <pause dur="short"/> we can now revise what we talked about last last yesterday and we can reprioritise okay? so erm you know we'll we can have that as conversation another day what I wanna understand is if you think you've got the skill set to deliver this</u>
<u n="660" who="S0261">er explain what what you expect to be delivered</u>
<u n="661" who="S0262">a website</u>
<u n="662" who="S0261">and?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0262">erm <pause dur="short"/> a fucking cool website</u>
<u n="664" who="S0261">carry on</u>
<u n="665" who="S0262">erm and all of the directional traffic around it going straight leading into the website</u>
<u n="666" who="S0261">er okay so you're talking about any peripheral stuff that helps feed traffic into the site</u>
<u n="667" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0261">okay so I mean the it</u>
<u n="669" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I hate those fucking balls cos they could just come</u>
<u n="670" who="S0261" trans="overlap">oh they it's not gonna come over near us</u>
<u n="671" who="S0262" trans="overlap">are you sure?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0261" trans="overlap">it's alright they're way over there one's wearing an English rugby jersey</u>
<u n="673" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0261">and the other is South African yeah and they've got an Aussie football ball</u>
<u n="675" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> bit confused</u>
<u n="676" who="S0261">yeah it's a bit of shitty oh no it's er yeah it is it's a <pause dur="short"/> anyway that that aside erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so there's actually you know if you wanna make it work properly there's quite a lot of work in all of that and and can I make it happen? of course I can make it happen I'm gonna be learning a lot along the way and that's great cos I've always wanted to do that I've wanted to know how it works as a whole system</u>
<u n="677" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0261">and I can actually start getting a better credit and credos by doing you know this is where I sit outside the box with a lot of these <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> people they just do that <pause dur="short"/> I go away and I do that</u>
<u n="679" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and it's gonna be the same in this case I do that to start with</u>
<u n="681" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0261">not this</u>
<u n="683" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0261">and that's where the project management awareness and skill comes in</u>
<u n="685" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0261">and really it comes down to you look at it and you go well I haven't got time to do this so I I have to outsource it</u>
<u n="687" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0261">yeah and it's better probably to start with and you say well we'd if we set a budget of X that that money is some of it is set aside for getting others to get certain things done for us</u>
<u n="689" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0261">and in some context I would prefer to use some of the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> people that I know can do it <pause dur="short"/> but if there's a price</u>
<u n="691" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's up to you</u>
<u n="692" who="S0261">then</u>
<u n="693" who="S0262" trans="overlap">if if that's it's</u>
<u n="694" who="S0261" trans="overlap">I'd go somewhere else and try the outsourcing thing</u>
<u n="695" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but I see there's clearly defined roles that's your role that's</u>
<u n="696" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="697" who="S0262">for to decide</u>
<u n="698" who="S0261">absolutely fine but you understand that we need we might need some money to be able to</u>
<u n="699" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0261">facilitate that to make that easy</u>
<u n="701" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0261">and probably it's easier to do it that way and get good product</u>
<u n="703" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0261">straight up</u>
<u n="705" who="S0262">okay so who wants to be in control of that money budget thing?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0261">well I think er just need to schedule a a bunch of things and say well which bits am I gonna do and which bits are we gonna outsource? and then look at relatively how much of my cost</u>
<u n="707" who="S0262">who wants to be control of costing?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0261">I'm happy to cost everything</u>
<u n="709" who="S0262">okay <pause dur="short"/> cool <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="710" who="S0261">er we obviously <pause dur="short"/> can I have a beer?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="712" who="S0261">erm we obviously erm <pause dur="short"/> talk about and share all that before anything gets spent but erm <pause dur="short"/> I think if if you said for er that period of time if you said you had five hundred dollars you'd do well with it yeah? and and the aim is obviously to spinning it down as best you can and get the best quality out of somebody so erm</u>
<u n="713" who="S0262">I might need some flyers done just for when you're going around to different parts of Asia or when you're in cities and things and you maybe you know just have a postcard or something that kind of has you know the actual <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> and then maybe you know a very succinct kind of mission statement of what</u>
<u n="714" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and a website</u>
<u n="715" who="S0262">website</u>
<u n="716" who="S0261">like an oversized business card</u>
<u n="717" who="S0262">yeah so you can hand it out to students</u>
<u n="718" who="S0261">yeah yeah for sure</u>
<u n="719" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="721" who="S0262">that would be really useful</u>
<u n="722" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="723" who="S0262">cos we need that trajectory over into erm er Asia Pacific</u>
<u n="724" who="S0261">yeah and exactly and so</u>
<u n="725" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and in New Zealand I can do the same</u>
<u n="726" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0262">when I'm in <anon type="place"/> hopefully I will go and find some students in <anon type="place"/> university and they will just hand out flyers</u>
<u n="728" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="729" who="S0262">so we get them coming in straight away</u>
<u n="730" who="S0261">mm so that kind of stuff needs to be designed what's the content what's gonna go on it</u>
<u n="731" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="732" who="S0261">erm you know and and you you hit at things with you know we're gonna have a launch date and that's er so before you get that hand that stuff out you wanna you wanna landing page up</u>
<u n="733" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="734" who="S0261">on your website</u>
<u n="735" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0261">you know</u>
<u n="737" who="S0262">well well we really want what you did with <unclear>Ula</unclear> you just want people to know to go to the landing page and put in their email address</u>
<u n="738" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="739" who="S0262">that's really what you want</u>
<u n="740" who="S0261">yeah that's right and I can use that same template if that's what you like and I can make it look better than it did for them</u>
<u n="741" who="S0262">well if it speeds the whole process up then yeah use the same template</u>
<u n="742" who="S0261">well it's it's it's a template called Launch Effect</u>
<u n="743" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="744" who="S0261">yeah and part of the thing that <unclear>Ula</unclear> don't use but is in the system is that each person who signs up gets a code and if they then pass that code on to their friends and their friends sign up then the system records that they're they're the the creating affiliates</u>
<u n="745" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="746" who="S0261">so then you say well you look at the top five of them and you go well we're going to do something for these people</u>
<u n="747" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="748" who="S0261">and you could say the carrot could be you could be one of our first interviewees</u>
<u n="749" who="S0262">yeah yeah absolutely now</u>
<u n="750" who="S0261" trans="overlap">something like that</u>
<u n="751" who="S0262">there's another part to this <pause dur="short"/> which does need someone a little bit more long-term outsourcer <pause dur="short"/> okay?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0261" trans="overlap">carry on</u>
<u n="753" who="S0262">so you know when we were talking about how erm that fella erm keeps finding all these tools on the internet and we reckoned he didn't do that himself that he just got someone to do it for him close up on Facebook?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="755" who="S0262">I need to have <pause dur="short"/> a learning advice forum <pause dur="short"/> I need it where students will come in post something up go</u>
<u n="756" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0262">I don't know how to <trunc>arg</trunc> I don't know how to do referencing</u>
<u n="758" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and then and and others and they'll interact yeah? so you want there's a part of your website a forum that that punters can sign up register and interact on</u>
<u n="759" who="S0262">alright but I</u>
<u n="760" who="S0261" trans="overlap">like a wiki</u>
<u n="761" who="S0262">I need to be there every now and then like you</u>
<u n="762" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah but you can drop and drop out</u>
<u n="763" who="S0262">sure</u>
<u n="764" who="S0261">so that's exactly what happens on</u>
<u n="765" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but I don't want that person to really think that</u>
<u n="766" who="S0261" trans="overlap">Location Rebel</u>
<u n="767" who="S0262">exactly but I don't really want that person to be me I want it to be somebody else</u>
<u n="768" who="S0261">yeah that's fine well many people on Location Rebel for instance get paid to do that stuff</u>
<u n="769" who="S0262">excellent</u>
<u n="770" who="S0261" trans="overlap">right? so but you want somebody who's in education basis</u>
<u n="771" who="S0262">I could get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to do it for a little while</u>
<u n="772" who="S0261"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0261">great</u>
<u n="775" who="S0262" trans="overlap">she's smart</u>
<u n="776" who="S0261">yeah and and <trunc>sh</trunc> she'd be interested probably</u>
<u n="777" who="S0262" trans="overlap">she was always a good student</u>
<u n="778" who="S0261">yeah she can write</u>
<u n="779" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could do it</u>
<u n="780" who="S0261">yes exactly so you want <pause dur="short"/> yeah and and er the idea is to try and get people to do it on a friends voluntary basis</u>
<u n="781" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="782" who="S0261">don't have to pay them anything</u>
<u n="783" who="S0262" trans="overlap">just to start now exactly</u>
<u n="784" who="S0261">yes erm</u>
<u n="785" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but with a view that eventually when it really kicks off <pause dur="short"/> it could be a steady little income a little side thing</u>
<u n="786" who="S0261">well it it could it could be yeah exactly erm and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hires one of the location people to be his person who does all that</u>
<u n="787" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> his bitch <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="788" who="S0261">yeah well she no she she sounds quite nice she's just kinda she's really helpful</u>
<u n="789" who="S0262">but we could also use <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as seeders so they can run around and write up stuff in various places and Facebooks and</u>
<u n="790" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><trunc>a</trunc> absolutely of course and</u>
<u n="791" who="S0262" trans="overlap">you know you give them a list of things to do</u>
<u n="792" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0262">they just do it in a day</u>
<u n="794" who="S0261"><trunc>ex</trunc> exactly we need you to feed into this forum we want a a little article that we can post on this over here</u>
<u n="795" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0261">and all of that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="797" who="S0262">both of them can write really well</u>
<u n="798" who="S0261">yeah yeah so anybody that you feel happy with trying to get involved and that fine absolutely and I'm happy to be the go-between to make sure that the the organisational message goes out to say this week we need to try and do this are you available to do this?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0261">let me know what you can do</u>
<u n="801" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0261">or you can't do</u>
<u n="803" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0261">and if you have two or three people then you just share the wealth</u>
<u n="805" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0261">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> and that's good for us because then we're managing people</u>
<u n="807" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0261">and that's all a part of what a company's about</u>
<u n="809" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0261">and it's better to do it with people that you can rely on that you don't have to pay much for</u>
<u n="811" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0261">and</u>
<u n="813" who="S0262" trans="overlap">pay them in kind anyway there's always a way to negotiate these things</u>
<u n="814" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah well the the kind for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could be well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will teach you how to do a website</u>
<u n="815" who="S0262">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="816" who="S0261" trans="overlap">or whatever</u>
<u n="817" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0261">you know and that's fine by me</u>
<u n="819" who="S0262">I mean I could also erm you know proofread <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s er thesis <pause dur="short"/> you know in kind I can always do stuff for her</u>
<u n="820" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><trunc>yea</trunc> yes <trunc>e</trunc> <trunc>e</trunc> exactly</u>
<u n="821" who="S0262">okay now so that's that bit</u>
<u n="822" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="823" who="S0262">oh okay by the way I'm thinking of asking <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be Sage</u>
<u n="824" who="S0261">I don't yeah okay whoever <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is yeah</u>
<u n="825" who="S0262">well you have to meet him</u>
<u n="826" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="827" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0261">okay mm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0262">but at the moment he's the only one I can think of who might actually possibly do it</u>
<u n="830" who="S0261" trans="overlap">can you trust him?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0262">yes</u>
<u n="832" who="S0261">and what's he lecture?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0262">er well he's er lectured in quite a number of things but erm he's in the marketing and management department of <anon type="place"/> university erm first level he does human resource management he can lecture business law he's setting up a new unit called negotiating <pause dur="short"/> erm he's <pause dur="short"/> done other shit that I can't remember what the units are called but I know they're third year level units and <trunc>gl</trunc> and something or other I can't remember but he's he's he's he's in that area of marketing and management which is quite cool which</u>
<u n="834" who="S0261" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="835" who="S0262"><unclear/> like</u>
<u n="836" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="837" who="S0262">could be <pause dur="short"/> er career-wise he's quite interesting</u>
<u n="838" who="S0261">yeah so is he</u>
<u n="839" who="S0262" trans="overlap">he's er he's also double he's so he got a double degree in law and social science and economics</u>
<u n="840" who="S0261">okay so you can handle erm</u>
<u n="841" who="S0262" trans="overlap">and he's a doctor</u>
<u n="842" who="S0261" trans="overlap">having him involved and trust him to be involved</u>
<u n="843" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0261">without screwing us or anything like that?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0262">no he wouldn't screw us over</u>
<u n="846" who="S0261">alright <pause dur="short"/> okay yeah of I'll meet him</u>
<u n="847" who="S0262">he's either in or he's out that's</u>
<u n="848" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0262" trans="overlap">the way it would be</u>
<u n="850" who="S0261">okay</u>
<u n="851" who="S0262">okay and then <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are meant to be <trunc>worki</trunc> working together to finish off well to finish off to do a fucking research project which was meant to go in for this crappy fucking thing that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants me to do but I'm gonna switch angles on her and she's not gonna see it coming so basically yes I'll do what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told me to do but at the same time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I will try and get for this time next year we're gonna try and get both well both our names will be on the general article for <unclear>her so again</unclear> yeah? we'll go if we get the paper accepted which we will cos fucking hell I've been I've been reading this shit man and they're not that it's not that fucking brilliant</u>
<u n="852" who="S0261">it's not that hard yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no erm and er then we go to the conference and we start rubbing up against people <pause dur="short"/> connected to these people <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s and other people</u>
<u n="854" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="855" who="S0262">so that's the lead time</u>
<u n="856" who="S0261">okay so what is it that you hope to get out of <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>? er an opportunity to publish stuff?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0261">digitally?</u>
<u n="859" who="S0262">yeah and I'll tell you who's gonna come in on this</u>
<u n="860" who="S0261">do you think you'll make any money out of <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="861" who="S0262">fuck yeah <pause dur="short"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> I don't care who they are I'm just telling you this is the this is the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is just a publishing company I don't care who they are I don't need any publishing company <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s massive</u>
<u n="862" who="S0261">yes I know that</u>
<u n="863" who="S0262">so I don't care if it's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> or Macmillan or whoever it is right</u>
<u n="864" who="S0261" trans="overlap">do you make any money out of publishing through</u>
<u n="865" who="S0262" trans="overlap">we make</u>
<u n="866" who="S0261" trans="overlap">another company?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0262">yes we make <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="868" who="S0261" trans="overlap">well can't you self-publish?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0262">ah now then you're talking right but that's really really long-term and the people who could potentially <pause dur="short"/> not get us in this area but leapfrog over into the self-publishing area yeah is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0261"><trunc>ye</trunc> in yeah well look you know the reality is is a lot of people are self-publishing now and</u>
<u n="871" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I need</u>
<u n="872" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and and and</u>
<u n="873" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I need names I need big names I need two three doctorates <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is a doctorate <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a doctorate and so is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="874" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="875" who="S0262">I would have to be catching up with them then</u>
<u n="876" who="S0261">er you're talking about publishing academic articles?</u>
<u n="877" who="S0262">publishing study skills books on how to argue <pause dur="short"/> and by the way that I've I'm thinking a little bit different here I'm not just thinking a digital version of this</u>
<u n="878" who="S0261">so you're talking about those being distributed amongst educational institutions?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0261">rather than something that's a self-help book for students that they buy off a bookshop shelf?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah this is selling back to it's</u>
<u n="882" who="S0261" trans="overlap">or through Amazon</u>
<u n="883" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>ba</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> do <trunc>whatev</trunc> do what you want but selling to mainly the ones who've got cash which is the institutions <pause dur="short"/> cos they've</u>
<u n="884" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so that's based on volume?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="886" who="S0261">and so why wouldn't you just steer the students to buy straight off a web website and self-publish?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0262">alright do both <pause dur="short"/> students always have to buy their own textbooks</u>
<u n="888" who="S0261"><trunc>ye</trunc> yeah mm</u>
<u n="889" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but do you know what something else happens?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="891" who="S0262">is a lot of the time the institutions yeah don't fucking know how to teach so what they do is they buy the licence to the textbook so they actually put that into the syllabus of their unit</u>
<u n="892" who="S0261">yeah okay because that tells the appropriate story</u>
<u n="893" who="S0262">and they get the student to buy a subscription so they get to practise it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0261">right <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> so if we were to write down some some first-hand core actions that need to happen before I go away</u>
<u n="895" who="S0262">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0261">we talked about <pause dur="short"/> what we might do while I'm away but we'll come back and reassess that yeah? erm <pause dur="long"/> so we need logo design <pause dur="short"/> we need this er hand-out a <trunc>leaf</trunc> a leaflet</u>
<u n="897" who="S0262">a flyer yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0261">a flyer <pause dur="long"/> you want a landing page for the website</u>
<u n="899" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="900" who="S0261">erm we want <pause dur="long"/> we want FB and Twitter feeds sorted out</u>
<u n="901" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="902" who="S0261">and Google Plus</u>
<u n="903" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="904" who="S0261">do you use Google Plus?</u>
<u n="905" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="906" who="S0261">mm okay that's good I haven't got my head into yet but I need to the idea is to connect all this stuff together so the messages are much the same they're just spread amongst it</u>
<u n="907" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="908" who="S0261">yeah erm</u>
<u n="909" who="S0262">so I need to come up with the message <pause dur="short"/> er okay my stuff can you write down what I need to do as well? so I need to have the introduction to the landing page</u>
<u n="910" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="911" who="S0262">I need to have a erm self intro video that explains the dogma</u>
<u n="912" who="S0261">so is that something you put up on YouTube or Vimeo or something?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0262">I don't know I don't get it I don't know do you have to be on YouTube? does it have to be can you not have it on your website?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0261">well there look that <trunc>Y</trunc> YouTube's owned by Google right?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="916" who="S0261">so if you put it up on YouTube it's like marketing you you're putting it out there into the masses</u>
<u n="917" who="S0262">alright then</u>
<u n="918" who="S0261">and then what you're doing is you're providing a message in your video to go back to your website</u>
<u n="919" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="920" who="S0261">so that's how you would get messages that go through that and come back to get people to sign up their emails</u>
<u n="921" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="922" who="S0261">yeah? erm so self intro video and you could put that on YouTube or Vimeo or whatever</u>
<u n="923" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0261">and then you can say to people go and have a look at this that's quite you know <pause dur="short"/> and then they go round the circuit <pause dur="short"/> and if they like what they see they'll sign up erm <pause dur="short"/> what else do you have to do?</u>
<u n="925" who="S0262">interview some people</u>
<u n="926" who="S0261">so how many?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0262">erm <pause dur="short"/> okay so I've got on the list</u>
<u n="928" who="S0261">five?</u>
<u n="929" who="S0262">hang on a minute <pause dur="short"/> wait a sec <pause dur="long"/> alright well we'll aim for five yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="930" who="S0261">well we're talking about one a week yeah?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0262">yeah so that will get me if it's if week one is erm twenty-ninth of that will get me to mid-semester break <pause dur="short"/> so I think there's six weeks in the first half of the semester yeah four five <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> six yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0261" trans="overlap">do you want more?</u>
<u n="933" who="S0262">so we've got ninth of September is mid-semester break so basically</u>
<u n="934" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so you want six?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0261">six</u>
<u n="937" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so so yeah shall I give you the week numbers? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0261">no erm that's yeah but you'd be doing them June through July yeah?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0261">yeah okay carry on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="941" who="S0262">but the whole point is that I can do them remotely</u>
<u n="942" who="S0261">yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="943" who="S0262">yeah I can do them in the the Sunday night and then post them up on a Monday morning <pause dur="short"/> just like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does</u>
<u n="944" who="S0261">yeah but you need to edit them</u>
<u n="945" who="S0262">no he said you don't he doesn't</u>
<u n="946" who="S0261">erm what you do edit is not edit out the content but when when you film it right you've got two you've got two things you've got the the other person and you've got you</u>
<u n="947" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0261">so it records both of those pictures</u>
<u n="949" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0261">and what you edit is you cut them together so it's like you're speaking they're speaking you're speaking they're speaking</u>
<u n="951" who="S0262">oh right</u>
<u n="952" who="S0261">yeah? which isn't hard to do because you just go through the tape and it's like you're talking so then you show a picture of you</u>
<u n="953" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="954" who="S0261">and then they're talking</u>
<u n="955" who="S0262">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>d</trunc> he's actually when he's not talking he's still in the frame and he's drinking from his white mug</u>
<u n="956" who="S0261">let me go back and have a look at it</u>
<u n="957" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="958" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="959" who="S0262">look at it</u>
<u n="960" who="S0261">I mean you wanna cut down that crap as much as you can but <pause dur="short"/> let's just imagine six we've got six weeks so one a week okay? just think of it like that</u>
<u n="961" who="S0262">well let's do it exactly like how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does it <pause dur="short"/> I wanna do it exactly like how he does it</u>
<u n="962" who="S0261">are you happy with what you see there?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah it works for him</u>
<u n="964" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="965" who="S0262">it'll work for us</u>
<u n="966" who="S0261">mm okay yes so what we're saying is is study <pause dur="short"/> er the <unclear/> output <pause dur="short"/> now he uses software which is either ScreenFlow for Mac or or Vodburner for for Windows</u>
<u n="967" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="968" who="S0261">Vodburner costs a hundred dollars</u>
<u n="969" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="970" who="S0261">you can use it as a trial</u>
<u n="971" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="972" who="S0261">so you can try it as a trial</u>
<u n="973" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="974" who="S0261">and you can probably outsource it</u>
<u n="975" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="976" who="S0261">so you just get somebody for a fiver to to to edit it together for you</u>
<u n="977" who="S0262">alright</u>
<u n="978" who="S0261">if you can and provide easy instructions which is when I'm talking I wanna see a picture of me and when I and he's talking I wanna see a picture of him</u>
<u n="979" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I actually quite I think if you find they're actually both</u>
<u n="980" who="S0261" trans="overlap">if it's both of them</u>
<u n="981" who="S0262" trans="overlap">simultaneous</u>
<u n="982" who="S0261" trans="overlap">then that's fine you know</u>
<u n="983" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's like a</u>
<u n="984" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and that works</u>
<u n="985" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's like a conversation</u>
<u n="986" who="S0261">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> erm so when you say interviews that's X number over six weeks</u>
<u n="987" who="S0262">by the way they're never gonna they are meant to be no more than ten minutes long</u>
<u n="988" who="S0261">er that's what you want</u>
<u n="989" who="S0262">it's dogma <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="990" who="S0261">er er yeah okay erm <pause dur="short"/> I mean he he puts the stuff out er on podcasts as well so he does his video interview it goes up on his website</u>
<u n="991" who="S0262">what software does he use for the podcast?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="short"/> I I think it's probably Itunes so erm</u>
<u n="993" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that means you have to have Apple</u>
<u n="994" who="S0261">well we've got Apple</u>
<u n="995" who="S0262">no but do students have Apple?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0261">no but it gets distributed through RSS and stuff so I've got it on my phone through <trunc>bl</trunc> beyond <trunc>bl</trunc> be BeyondPod yeah?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="998" who="S0261">right? so <pause dur="short"/> the I looked at erm the blog that got sent out from <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> <pause dur="short"/>  you've got all the stats on who collected what where and how many people opened it and all that kind of stuff and what devices they used right? so of the hundred odd <trunc>peo</trunc> it was about a hundred people went to seventy-one percent opened opened it and read it yeah? of that seventy-one percent something like ninety percent were using Apple <trunc>s</trunc> Apple systems <pause dur="short"/> yeah? so that's in New Zealand but predominantly that's what you'd expect to see in western countries and Asian countries you'd probably see er the <unclear>Samsung</unclear> stuff yeah? so it's America versus North Korea China er South Korea China or whatever yeah? <pause dur="short"/> but you try and get it out on all platforms <pause dur="short"/> that's what it's about</u>
<u n="999" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so everybody gets to see it</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so then the thing</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0261" trans="overlap">however they see it</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's gonna take a lot of time I think is actually me coming up with a dogma and a sort of format and you just format these interviews yeah? it's it there is a little bit of er kind of wavering a bit around with creativity</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0261">but you want systems that are straightforward</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0261">bam bam bam bam bam</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0261">that's it you don't wanna be fucking around with oh I want it to look good I wanna change it</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0261">the reality is is that it's only the graphic designers that really want to try and put that kind of shit together</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0262">so yeah so we need something that will appeal to the young audience</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0261">yes exactly</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay? and I'm defining for you who the <trunc>mai</trunc> primary audience is</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0262">erm so they are erm eighteen <pause dur="short"/> to twenty-six <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0261">okay now <trunc>y</trunc> I wanna go back you mentioned about avatars and er whatever yeah? one of the guys who the <trunc>Austra</trunc> one of the Australian guys he uses cartoons and avatars as part of</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0261" trans="overlap">his thing</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0262">not having that no</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0261">that's fine</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0262">don't want it it's looks babyish and it gives the wrong signal I'm not interested in Second Life fucking you know war of war of world of no <pause dur="short"/> it's not about that it's about the fact that they've got me and I'm I'm enough yeah? I'm already putting my face out there on all frigging internet <pause dur="short"/> that is it</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah and I'm probably gonna get some shit for it from from trolls and stuff yeah okay but <pause dur="short"/> there's no need for another face to be attached to this</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0261">no that's fine absolutely that's that's that absolutely right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0262">so it's just the play on words of Stig Sage</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0262">everyone's fucking seen erm what's it called?</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0261">Top Gear</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0261">erm</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0262">and if it's not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it'll be somebody else <pause dur="short"/> it has to be that way it has to work that way</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
