<text id="SZAZ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:40</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-11-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0404 S0405</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Footpath, Slough-Windsor</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Movie reviews, feminism, Islam, religion, morality, ethics</topics>
		<activity>Talking about modern issues whilst walking to rugby training</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0404">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Taifi</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Saudi Arabia</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>British</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Slough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>student, full time</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Filippino -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0405">
				<exactage>17</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Slough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Slough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years and 6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0404">I I have a I have a theory that I just came up with right now</u>
<u n="2" who="S0405">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0404">perhaps the only way to get the perfect review <pause dur="short"/> is to have no expectations of the movie at all</u>
<u n="4" who="S0405">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="5" who="S0404" trans="overlap">or</u>
<u n="6" who="S0405">even even to the extent of not watching the trailers</u>
<u n="7" who="S0404">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0405">I try sometimes</u>
<u n="9" who="S0404">to you you have no no in-depth knowledge of the movie</u>
<u n="10" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0404">you have no no predestined concept ideas</u>
<u n="12" who="S0405" trans="overlap">concept</u>
<u n="13" who="S0404">you I don't know maybe even go as far as to put them in the cinema and have them watch the movie don't even tell them the title</u>
<u n="14" who="S0405" trans="overlap">that that would be the fairest review</u>
<u n="15" who="S0404">that would be the fairest review I believe</u>
<u n="16" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah that's why I don't like yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0404" trans="overlap">cos <pause dur="short"/> watching trailers hearing</u>
<u n="18" who="S0405">what your friends say</u>
<u n="19" who="S0404"><trunc>hear</trunc> yeah hearing from what your friends say hearing from what the actors themselves say</u>
<u n="20" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0404">maybe though eh it sort of creates a a pre <pause dur="short"/> predestined ideal or expectation of the movie</u>
<u n="22" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah pre <pause dur="short"/> exactly it's true</u>
<u n="23" who="S0404" trans="overlap">I mean <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> you know who you know who Jennifer Lawrence is?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0404"><trunc>sw</trunc> of course you know who Jennifer Lawrence is</u>
<u n="26" who="S0405">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> social culture</u>
<u n="27" who="S0404" trans="overlap">you're a guy you would know yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0404">so <unclear/> loves Jennifer Lawrence and I told her that her films are <pause dur="short"/> alright</u>
<u n="30" who="S0405" trans="overlap">eh god they're alright</u>
<u n="31" who="S0404" trans="overlap">they're alright</u>
<u n="32" who="S0405">just alright</u>
<u n="33" who="S0404">just alright</u>
<u n="34" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what do you think of her acting?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0404">her acting? ah I haven't seen any of her films</u>
<u n="36" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's funny</u>
<u n="37" who="S0404">yeah I know</u>
<u n="38" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah erm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0404">she called me an idiot for that</u>
<u n="40" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think erm I know I like her personality I've I got really into Emma Watson because she was</u>
<u n="41" who="S0404">Emma Watson?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0405">cos of her yeah cos of her feminist views and what not erm did you <trunc>s</trunc> did you I watched her speech to the UN and everything I mean there are issues towards that as well</u>
<u n="43" who="S0404">how old is she now?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0405" trans="overlap">she's addressing eh</u>
<u n="45" who="S0404">because I can never</u>
<u n="46" who="S0405">approaching <trunc>thi</trunc> no not thirty twenty-five</u>
<u n="47" who="S0404" trans="overlap">in my <pause dur="short"/> in my mind she's always going to be that sixteen-year-old Hermione</u>
<u n="48" who="S0405"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I know</u>
<u n="49" who="S0404" trans="overlap">sixteen-year-old Hermione Granger</u>
<u n="50" who="S0405">erm yeah she she she's just finished her Oxford thing</u>
<u n="51" who="S0404">oh she went to Oxford?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0405">yeah she's smart</u>
<u n="53" who="S0404">really?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0405"><unclear/> erm and and that's something else you see from a lot of actors they'll drop out the moment they get a sign of fame she she continued her course <vocal desc="laugh"/> she she I I I think she's just she's obviously she's very beautiful but I <trunc>thi</trunc> I think she she she's a very intelligent person <unclear>isn't she?</unclear></u>
<u n="55" who="S0404">that's what makes her beautiful mate</u>
<u n="56" who="S0405">yeah <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc>exactly I know why does? why is beauty a physical thing? but erm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0404">doesn't have to be it can be</u>
<u n="58" who="S0405">yeah it can be of course</u>
<u n="59" who="S0404">if you love someone they're always gonna be beautiful</u>
<u n="60" who="S0405">ah Beyonce <vocal desc="laugh"/> no they erm there's arguments towards her erm <pause dur="short"/> her <trunc>fe</trunc> well I was talking to a female friend of mine she she disliked her speech because she's talking to the United Nations and yet she's <trunc>com</trunc>complaining about western feminine issues and yet you look at the Middle East or Africa where I don't know female genital mutilation women are still erm you know expected to be in the kitchen all day and they still are and they're they have much greater setbacks than we do here I mean women are still paid less on average than men here and women are still you know <pause dur="short"/> er objectified but</u>
<u n="61" who="S0404" trans="overlap">I really can't <vocal desc="sigh"/> I just can't understand it do you know what? do you know er the? you know erm er the religion of Islam?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0405">yeah go on</u>
<u n="63" who="S0404">back in the middle ages the religion of Islam was the most forward religion and nation in the world</u>
<u n="64" who="S0405">yeah?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0404">it was seriously you know erm while <trunc>christ</trunc> there have you heard of the <foreign lang="ara">Umayyad caliphate</foreign></u>
<u n="66" who="S0405">I haven't no</u>
<u n="67" who="S0404">well after eh after the prophet Muhammad died</u>
<u n="68" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0404">like in I don't know the exact years</u>
<u n="70" who="S0405">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0404">but I know the <foreign lang="ara">Umayyad caliphate</foreign> was between like the years of eight hundred BC to <pause dur="short"/> no I think it ended it ended around one thousand BC something like</u>
<u n="72" who="S0405">right okay</u>
<u n="73" who="S0404">but erm after the prophet Muhammad died</u>
<u n="74" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0404">his family and his generals</u>
<u n="76" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0404">soon went on to conquer lots of lands</u>
<u n="78" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0404">in the Middle East and North Africa</u>
<u n="80" who="S0405">okay yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0404">and er eventually</u>
<u n="82" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0404">one of the caliphates</u>
<u n="84" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0404">whose family name was the the <trunc>umay</trunc> was <foreign lang="ara">Umayyad</foreign></u>
<u n="86" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0404">hence the name <foreign lang="ara">Umayyad caliphate</foreign></u>
<u n="88" who="S0405">oh I see</u>
<u n="89" who="S0404">conquered all of North Africa</u>
<u n="90" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0404">all of the Middle East and southern Spain and parts of Italy</u>
<u n="92" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0404">southern Italy</u>
<u n="94" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0404">they conquered all of that <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>du</trunc> it was during this time that Christian <pause dur="short"/> er Christian intolerance was reaching its highest peaks and levels</u>
<u n="96" who="S0405">right yeah because the crusades and stuff</u>
<u n="97" who="S0404">yeah the crusades were done in like twelve hundreds</u>
<u n="98" who="S0405" trans="overlap">eleven eleventh twelfth century yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0404" trans="overlap">but <foreign lang="ara">Umayyad</foreign> caliphate was around in maybe eight hundred eight the year eight hundred</u>
<u n="100" who="S0405">yeah okay</u>
<u n="101" who="S0404">AD</u>
<u n="102" who="S0405"><unclear/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0404">and erm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0405">just check that <pause dur="short"/> yeah two minutes go on</u>
<u n="105" who="S0404">yeah and the <foreign lang="ara">Umayyad caliphate</foreign></u>
<u n="106" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0404">at its greatest extent under the caliph I think his name was Abu something</u>
<u n="108" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0404">under his leadership the <foreign lang="ara">Umayyad caliphate</foreign> grew to become one of the wealthiest nations in the world a proprietor of a proprietor of science and maths and modern medicine</u>
<u n="110" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0404">in fact some of the mathematicians in the <foreign lang="ara">Umayyad caliphate</foreign> contributed to things used in modern day mathematics</u>
<u n="112" who="S0405">wow</u>
<u n="113" who="S0404">and modern day medicine</u>
<u n="114" who="S0405">yeah yeah <unclear/> things yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0404" trans="overlap">one of the first one of the first modern historians of the time was Muslim</u>
<u n="116" who="S0405">yeah that's great</u>
<u n="117" who="S0404">and they promoted religious tolerance back then</u>
<u n="118" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0404">religious tolerance and now</u>
<u n="120" who="S0405">I guess that's the confusing <unclear>thing</unclear> to it</u>
<u n="121" who="S0404" trans="overlap">and now Islam is viewed as one of the most intolerant abusive religions in the world</u>
<u n="122" who="S0405">I don't <trunc>th</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> there are <trunc>oth</trunc> I I guess</u>
<u n="123" who="S0404">it's baffling how it took such a turn</u>
<u n="124" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah I I <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know but I don't think it really has taken that much of a turn I think it's just people's views of of what they think <unclear/> in the sense of like</u>
<u n="125" who="S0404" trans="overlap">maybe I'm romanticising it</u>
<u n="126" who="S0405">yeah I mean <trunc>may</trunc>maybe it it wasn't so great then and maybe things are still as they were now just people assume that <pause dur="short"/> is all <trunc>i</trunc> course people assume all Muslims are evil because they're erm backwards and ignorant</u>
<u n="127" who="S0404" trans="overlap">maybe not all people</u>
<u n="128" who="S0405">no I mean some people believe that is what I'm saying</u>
<u n="129" who="S0404" trans="overlap">yeah too many people believe that</u>
<u n="130" who="S0405" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> still too many cos there should be none but</u>
<u n="131" who="S0404">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0405">erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I mean it's a difficult issue because there'll always be <trunc>argum</trunc> I I'd say there are some legitimate arguments for for both sides in almost any argument always two sides of the coin</u>
<u n="133" who="S0404">you know when we were at the mosque?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0404">I asked the erm the imam</u>
<u n="136" who="S0405">oh the imam was crap but go on</u>
<u n="137" who="S0404">I asked the imam er does erm <pause dur="short"/> do I have to follow the principles and fundamentals of Islam</u>
<u n="138" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0404">to go to heaven to go to your heaven?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah good question</u>
<u n="141" who="S0404">and he replied with the only thing you need to do is follow the rules of Allah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0404">and the Islamic religion to get to heaven</u>
<u n="144" who="S0405">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="145" who="S0404">but then it hit me cos that is inherently flawed</u>
<u n="146" who="S0405">yeah cos what about people who are never exposed to Islam?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0404">yeah what about? what Mother Teresa</u>
<u n="148" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0404">perfect example</u>
<u n="150" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0404">one of the most selfless human beings to have lived in the twentieth twenty-first century</u>
<u n="152" who="S0405">yeah but there are erm there are <trunc>ch</trunc> erm I forget their names but there are Christian sects that believe that there are special place there's a special place in heaven for people who erm of other faiths who who you know I mean how can that be fair when <trunc>tri</trunc>tribesmen in in the jungle would have never they can't speak English or any modern language</u>
<u n="153" who="S0404" trans="overlap">I just find it so yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0405">and and the concept of what Islam is <pause dur="short"/> are forced to go to hell cos they don't follow the teachings you know? <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="155" who="S0404" trans="overlap">yeah it's not fair but the <trunc>di</trunc></u>
<u n="156" who="S0405" trans="overlap"><trunc>mo</trunc>most religions aren't like that most religions are you know there's a special place</u>
<u n="157" who="S0404" trans="overlap">yeah Sikhism Sikhism I don't know about Sikhism it just teaches that er you just have to be a good person</u>
<u n="158" who="S0405" trans="overlap">enjoy life yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0404">and that everyone needs to be er needs to follow their own path to god</u>
<u n="160" who="S0405">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="161" who="S0404" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's good that's a good tolerant view of it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0404">and in that everyone is resurrected and well not <trunc>res</trunc> reincarnated and such</u>
<u n="164" who="S0405">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0404">depending upon your karma</u>
<u n="166" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0404">but what I'd like to know is that the man said that you needed to you needed to be to be told</u>
<u n="168" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0404">what the proper way to live was</u>
<u n="170" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0404">so here I am wondering what if you become that person?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0405">what? the person that gets taught</u>
<u n="173" who="S0404" trans="overlap">do <pause dur="short"/> yeah the <trunc>peo</trunc> no the person that teaches</u>
<u n="174" who="S0405">oh right yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0404">do the people that you teach become? <pause dur="short"/> erm well as long as you teach the same fundamentals of being a nice person</u>
<u n="176" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0404"><unclear>agape</unclear></u>
<u n="178" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0404">and being selfless and kind and loving</u>
<u n="180" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0404">if you teach that <trunc>may</trunc> do your followers go to <pause dur="short"/> the equivalent of heaven too? do you think?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0405">they should do</u>
<u n="183" who="S0404">they should</u>
<u n="184" who="S0405">I guess people only know what they're exposed to <pause dur="short"/> you know? there's a fundamental argument there about</u>
<u n="185" who="S0404">I mean if you and I went soul-searching for the rest of our lives</u>
<u n="186" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0404">I still don't think we'd find the answer</u>
<u n="188" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah exactly well the answer is ourselves because everyone's different <unclear/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0404" trans="overlap">oh that's deep dude that is deep <foreign lang="spa">me gusta</foreign></u>
<u n="190" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah may why do we have to find a purpose? <foreign lang="spa">me gusta</foreign> <vocal desc="laugh"/> why do ourselves are <pause dur="short"/> are what you know we all feel like we have to conform to a particular set of views what if it's all a journey of self-discovery in itself you know? just cos we like conforming that's <pause dur="short"/> that's our society <pause dur="short"/> you mention <unclear>agape</unclear> do you think that <unclear>agape</unclear> is is a good virtue in itself? <pause dur="short"/> cos it's <trunc>f</trunc> I I think that <trunc>ob</trunc> it's got to be flawed in some ways</u>
<u n="191" who="S0404">how? how would you? how is it flawed for you?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0405" trans="overlap">in terms of <pause dur="short"/> oh obviously the concept of love is is is good but I mean Christian values of turn the other cheek and you know? let people just get on and be forgiven</u>
<u n="193" who="S0404">mm mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0405">if you're not religious and you don't believe that you'll be rewarded in heaven <pause dur="short"/> then you're basically letting criminals get away with anything so <trunc>y</trunc>you I don't believe that we should unconditionally love rapists and paedophiles and</u>
<u n="195" who="S0404" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> the the thing is <pause dur="short"/> the thing is people should be in the Christian sense an ideal in that <trunc>sen</trunc> in those scenarios of rapists and paedophiles and murderers</u>
<u n="196" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0404">people should be given a chance to repent</u>
<u n="198" who="S0405">yeah okay but</u>
<u n="199" who="S0404" trans="overlap">and if they do solemnly repent</u>
<u n="200" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0404">and if they do swear it and every fibre of their being does repent for the actions of <trunc>whi</trunc>which they did</u>
<u n="202" who="S0405"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0404">then I believe it should be right <unclear>for you</unclear> to accept them back into society</u>
<u n="204" who="S0405">yeah okay but what but what about the situations where you know people aren't prosecuted because you should love everyone anyway? you know? someone slaps you you turn the other cheek that's not oh take them to court if they're <pause dur="short"/> er asking for forgiveness and you forgive them</u>
<u n="205" who="S0404" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="206" who="S0405">that's straight up erm allowing people to get away with stuff you know?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0404">I like to think that if humans <trunc>abo</trunc> abided not abode abided by the laws of Christian agape</u>
<u n="208" who="S0405" trans="overlap">aboded yeah yeah abided <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0404">every person on the planet since the dawn of human history I don't think we'd have paedophiles</u>
<u n="210" who="S0405">no but paedophiles there's there's something <trunc>intre</trunc> <trunc>intre</trunc></u>
<u n="211" who="S0404" trans="overlap">or people like that</u>
<u n="212" who="S0405">they're not they don't choose to be evil they're just intrinsically wrong there are there are you know eh eh psycho killers who there are psychopaths who like killing people cause their brain is made that way in the same way that you and I would like certain things naturally</u>
<u n="213" who="S0404">I'm more <unclear>I guess</unclear></u>
<u n="214" who="S0405" trans="overlap">the only the only issue you know? I believe anyone should follow what they want and then they have a right to enjoy what they like as long as it doesn't hurt other people and that's where it's wrong to be a rapist or a paedophile but</u>
<u n="215" who="S0404">I guess that is true</u>
<u n="216" who="S0405" trans="overlap">so yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0404" trans="overlap">well so you'd allow things like doing drugs</u>
<u n="218" who="S0405" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="219" who="S0404">to the point where you kill yourself from overdose?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0405" trans="overlap">no because then that because then that then <pause dur="short"/> impacts on other people in the way that alcohol can make you endanger other people drugs will I do believe that the government has a responsibility of care to its citizens so you shouldn't let people overdose</u>
<u n="221" who="S0404">the government already spends billions every year trying to fix alcoholics</u>
<u n="222" who="S0405"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah and healthcare and stuff as well so</u>
<u n="223" who="S0404" trans="overlap">yeah and it spends billions just as much on security for drugs <pause dur="short"/> and trafficking and stuff like that</u>
<u n="224" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah exactly yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I mean <vocal desc="misc"/> it's a difficult issue cos you get into an issue about</u>
<u n="225" who="S0404" trans="overlap">humanity is too big I think</u>
<u n="226" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0404">it's too big</u>
<u n="228" who="S0405">so many views in itself anyway even if we took religion out of it there'd be so many ethical views on</u>
<u n="229" who="S0404">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0405">subjects that</u>
<u n="231" who="S0404">people would still be like separated and against certain things</u>
<u n="232" who="S0405">yeah they would</u>
<u n="233" who="S0404">I mean I like the maybe even if people eh <pause dur="short"/> maybe if people we go that way?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0405">yeah sure</u>
<u n="235" who="S0404">oh wait no yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0405" trans="overlap">if you yeah you hold the camera</u>
<u n="237" who="S0404">even if people are <pause dur="short"/> even if you got er rid of religion</u>
<u n="238" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0404">and applied religionless ethics to issues like euthanasia</u>
<u n="240" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0404">I still think people would have a problem with it</u>
<u n="242" who="S0405"><vocal desc="cough"/> oh yeah yeah it's not there <trunc>there</trunc>there's fundamental other issues with euthanasia than that stem from non-religious I mean all of Bentham's ethics stem from a a non-religious erm <pause dur="short"/> or even a non-virtuous you know as in we're born with virtues you know? against that argument so erm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0404">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="244" who="S0405">I guess we need to just protect each other <pause dur="short"/> and when people go wrong</u>
<u n="245" who="S0404">help each other?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0405">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think that's</u>
<u n="247" who="S0404" trans="overlap">what happens if you keep going straight?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0405">er eh there's a path down <trunc>te</trunc> yeah we could go that way then it goes over</u>
<u n="249" who="S0404">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0405">yeah it's a different way erm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0404">nice lights though that's one of the reasons I said we should go</u>
<u n="252" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah oh good choice hold on let me check the time erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah we got ten minutes erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah it's all difficult really <pause dur="short"/> at least erm <pause dur="short"/> at least we're not ignorant</u>
<u n="253" who="S0404">thank goodness we aren't</u>
<u n="254" who="S0405" trans="overlap">some</u>
<u n="255" who="S0404">I couldn't bear to be ignorant</u>
<u n="256" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0404">actually do you think you'd know if you were ignorant?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0405">no it's like the the Socrates <trunc>argum</trunc> well no it was a a Aristotle argument is he better to be? no he said it is better to be a sad Plato than a no a sad Socrates than a <pause dur="short"/> happy pig as in he felt that people with higher erm sorry with eh who had not been exposed to higher pleasures only lower pleasures would naturally be happier as in <pause dur="short"/> basically dumb people would be happier because they <pause dur="short"/> don't know as much of the horrors of the world and aren't as exposed to it but that's an argument my brother once said go yeah go on</u>
<u n="259" who="S0404" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> but then how would you define having lower pleasures? because lower pleasures you could</u>
<u n="260" who="S0405" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0404">lower pleasures are defined as being animalistic</u>
<u n="262" who="S0405">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0404">virtues which do produce some sense of satisfaction and gratification</u>
<u n="264" who="S0405">uhu</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
