<text id="SZBD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:12</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-15</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0266 S0268 S0272 S0273</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>ANON's daughter's new job in publishing; IT work; management consultancy. Holiday trips (travel agent for a big trip? Pre-booking accommodation or not). Retirement and semi-retirement: effect on other partner, role change(s), children living at home, what to do when reaching retirement. Keeping up with friends: organised socialising on a monthly basis (wives meeting in one pub, males in another pub every first Friday of the month at lunchtime).</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about Jobs, Holiday Trips, Thoughts on Retirement and Socialising, over a glass of wine.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0266">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Almondsbury, Gloucestershire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0268">
				<exactage>67</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ramsgate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Arabic -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0272">
				<exactage>56</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Farnborough, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Wooten-under-edge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>education liaison manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0273">
				<exactage>60</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Liverpudlian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0273"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is one of their</u>
<u n="2" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh yes I've heard of that one</u>
<u n="3" who="S0273">er what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does is erm it it's erm very specific not quite textbooks erm she she produces books which don't look anything really they're a bit bigger than paperback they are hardback and she brought some home look I'm mentioned in the acknowledgements <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0272">ah how lovely</u>
<u n="5" who="S0273">erm and these books sell for about eighty pounds a shot cos they're going to university libraries or some specific departments things like Islamic family law women's legal position in China it's all very very specific and specialised erm so what she does obviously is sort of it's not to do with the content but it's to do with making sure it's all done properly</u>
<u n="6" who="S0272" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0273">and properly edited and everybody does their bit at the right time and all so she <unclear>has that</unclear> I think I think eventually she'll have about twenty or thirty books on the go at once but it's taking a while to build up to that</u>
<u n="8" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0273">so er yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0266" trans="overlap">what what degree did she do?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0273">English</u>
<u n="12" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0273">and then she did an MA in publishing</u>
<u n="14" who="S0266">oh right <pause dur="short"/> so where's she worked since then?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0273">well that's it she I mean she's only twenty-four now</u>
<u n="16" who="S0266">oh right of course</u>
<u n="17" who="S0273" trans="overlap">so erm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0266">so she's a baby isn't she really?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0266">compared to <vocal desc="laugh"/> compared to <unclear/> son</u>
<u n="21" who="S0273">erm so she got she went straight from her MA in fact she before she finished it she started this job she started it in June last year and she still had a dissertation to do as well but it was it was a maternity leave she was doing and erm it's one of those sort of double edged things because it got to the point of April this year when this woman who she was replacing would have to decide whether to come back or not and erm the baby was very sick and she decided not to so somebody else's misfortune really that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got a permanent job</u>
<u n="22" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah I know that's a that's a really difficult one is <unclear/> when you get a job <unclear/> those circumstances</u>
<u n="23" who="S0273" trans="overlap">it is yeah erm so yeah but once she was permanent and full time they could start looking for a house and sort themselves out and <unclear/> so I mean she's</u>
<u n="24" who="S0272" trans="overlap">what does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0273">something in computers</u>
<u n="26" who="S0272">oh right</u>
<u n="27" who="S0273">I don't know what <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just know that whenever I'm stuck with something that I cry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="28" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0273">send him an <trunc>emai</trunc> he he's got er what's it called? the remote control access</u>
<u n="30" who="S0272">oh right okay</u>
<u n="31" who="S0273">he he's got that to my computer so</u>
<u n="32" who="S0266">has he? so what's he comes in like when you've got problems? and he <unclear>takes</unclear> over</u>
<u n="33" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh how useful that is</u>
<u n="34" who="S0273">yes he just takes it over</u>
<u n="35" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh you lucky thing</u>
<u n="36" who="S0273">types things in and sorts me out</u>
<u n="37" who="S0272">oh that's great I know it's fantastic at work when I had that happen and you ring up the ring up business systems and this has gone wrong okay you know and they eventually eventually ring you back and it's suddenly somebody else and it's a really odd feeling somebody else</u>
<u n="38" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yes yeah yeah <unclear/> cursor going round</u>
<u n="39" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0273">so</u>
<u n="42" who="S0266">and you wonder what you've got on your desktop</u>
<u n="43" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0266">that they're looking at</u>
<u n="46" who="S0273">but then of course it's always something very simple and you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sort of <vocal desc="sigh"/> god sorted out all this then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0272">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not good with computers then?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0273">no</u>
<u n="49" who="S0272">isn't he?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0273"><unclear>I'm</unclear> better than him with technical things</u>
<u n="51" who="S0272">ah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0266" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0272">that that's not saying very much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0266">but what was his erm profession? was he not in IT?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0273">no no no</u>
<u n="56" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="57" who="S0273">he started life as a chemical engineer and went into</u>
<u n="58" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh I don't think I ever knew that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0273">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0272">oh</u>
<u n="61" who="S0273">he worked at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0272">oh right</u>
<u n="63" who="S0273">which is how we came down here</u>
<u n="64" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0273">erm and then he went to into management consultancy which is where he stayed really he's done specialised in total quality management which is <trunc>ba</trunc>basically it's a bit like what used to be time and motion but it <trunc>bet</trunc> more better than that it it's helping companies work better not not necessarily in the old time and motion way providing better services dealing with customers better etcetera etcetera things like getting the investors in people and qualifications like that</u>
<u n="66" who="S0266">so was that his his own company?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0273">yes erm for well in jointly with <trunc>some</trunc> he started off working for a company called <anon type="place"/> which is one of the big consultancies</u>
<u n="68" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh it's a huge consultancy <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0273">and erm four or five of them broke away and set up their own company which eventually they've sort of backed out of and passed onto other people so he he's just been an employee for the last few years</u>
<u n="70" who="S0272">so did he sell it on? or</u>
<u n="71" who="S0273">sort of er it all got very complicated</u>
<u n="72" who="S0272">oh</u>
<u n="73" who="S0273">erm cos there wasn't really much to sell</u>
<u n="74" who="S0272" trans="overlap">no but the</u>
<u n="75" who="S0273">other than than the name and so on</u>
<u n="76" who="S0272">yeah well that's worth quite a lot though isn't it?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yeah so they yes they sold their shares in it and their good will and so on he's carried on working for them <unclear/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0266" trans="overlap">do you want some more <unclear>wine</unclear>?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0272">no thank you</u>
<u n="80" who="S0273">so there's there's only one of the original five who still well two counting <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but</u>
<u n="81" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0273">he's almost packed up so</u>
<u n="83" who="S0272">he just does a bit as it comes in or</u>
<u n="84" who="S0273">yeah he's done thank you erm he's done three or four days a month on average well that's what it works out at</u>
<u n="85" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> a coffee?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0272">no honestly I'm fine thank you</u>
<u n="87" who="S0266">tea coffee</u>
<u n="88" who="S0272">no no no I'm fine I don't want anything else than you</u>
<u n="89" who="S0266">soft drink</u>
<u n="90" who="S0272">no</u>
<u n="91" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0272">honestly I'm fine</u>
<u n="93" who="S0273">no since since new year he's he's stuck to what he said really</u>
<u n="94" who="S0272">he has</u>
<u n="95" who="S0273">bits and pieces he's in South Africa all week at the moment he's only really doing things that he fancies doing or for companies that he likes and er <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know what I was thinking last <unclear/> no I haven't been anywhere this year <vocal desc="laugh"/> apart from the week in India</u>
<u n="96" who="S0272">I was gonna say <unclear/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0273" trans="overlap">and a week in <unclear/> my god where's my brain going? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0272">I thought you'd been on quite a few holidays</u>
<u n="99" who="S0273" trans="overlap">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yes he <unclear/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0266">mm when you arrived <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling me about her trip</u>
<u n="101" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0266">and we've been to Thailand we've been to Vietnam then we've gone to New Zealand</u>
<u n="103" who="S0273" trans="overlap">New Zealand</u>
<u n="104" who="S0266">so where's after New Zealand?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0273" trans="overlap">and erm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0272" trans="overlap">so exactly is what I mean she'd been to loads of places</u>
<u n="107" who="S0273">no this this is where we're going this is</u>
<u n="108" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh this is where you're going?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0273">this is the big trip</u>
<u n="110" who="S0272">oh the big trip <unclear/> in February</u>
<u n="111" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><unclear/> when I saw you</u>
<u n="112" who="S0272">no no you hadn't booked it</u>
<u n="113" who="S0273">we have booked it we have</u>
<u n="114" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh you have booked it?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><unclear/> ourselves yes so a couple of days in Bangkok week and a half in Vietnam three weeks in New Zealand and then a few days each in Fiji Hawaii Dallas and New Orleans and home</u>
<u n="116" who="S0272">wow</u>
<u n="117" who="S0273" trans="overlap">seven and a half weeks</u>
<u n="118" who="S0272">seven and a half weeks</u>
<u n="119" who="S0273">so mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0272">how wonderful I hope to do that one day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0273">so I've already stipulated to the kids that I want one of them home each weekend <vocal desc="laugh"/> to keep the cats company and make sure everything's alright</u>
<u n="122" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0273">erm yeah haven't booked any accommodation or anything else yet but we've got the flights sorted</u>
<u n="124" who="S0272">so you haven't is it an agent you got an agent to do that or have you done it yourselves?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0273">yeah oh that's really annoying cos my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean she's lovely love her to bits but she irritates me intensely</u>
<u n="126" who="S0272">oh</u>
<u n="127" who="S0273">and her daughter's in New in Australia so she'd been going pretty well every year she goes off to Australia and she kept extolling the virtues of Trailfinders in <anon type="place"/> and how wonderful they are</u>
<u n="128" who="S0272">yes I've used them they were pretty good they were pretty good but I haven't used them for ages</u>
<u n="129" who="S0273" trans="overlap">and I sort of said said mm yeah ah we'll do it ourselves we'll sort ourselves out and we we looked and we we did look at erm I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a Star Alliance loyalty points card whatever and we looked at them and we worked out an itinerary which more or less worked and did what we wanted and I said oh just and I as it happened I was going into <anon type="place"/> erm a couple of weeks ago now anyway said oh I'll just go into Trailfinders just to shut <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up <vocal desc="laugh"/> and of course they found us a very good itinerary it was pretty well exactly the same for about three thousand pounds less in total so she's gloated <vocal desc="laugh"/> and gloated and gloated</u>
<u n="130" who="S0272" trans="overlap">well ah that's amazing isn't it?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0273" trans="overlap">erm but erm yeah they sorted it all out and</u>
<u n="132" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0273">took us through everything we wanted to do and <unclear/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0272" trans="overlap">it's quite good to do it that way <trunc>some</trunc> we did a big trip around eastern Canada last year</u>
<u n="135" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0272">and we flew in we wanted to fly in to Halifax in <trunc>Nov</trunc> in Novo Scotia do a trip around Novo Scotia and then go over to New Brunswick and eventually make our way through to Quebec and fly home from Montreal and erm we went in the end through an er a travel agent and I've never done this before but I came to the conclusion after the last big trip I'd done that where we just landed and sort of just decided</u>
<u n="137" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0272">where we were gonna go each day that actually it became a little bit stressful after a while</u>
<u n="139" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0272">fine thinking by about two o'clock in the afternoon you really really had to start concentrating about where you're gonna sleep that night and it ends up being a little bit stressful of oh will we get somewhere? and then you know you happen to think oh we we'll stay in this place this night and then you start ringing round or stop at an internet café and then look and and realise how much time you are wasting</u>
<u n="141" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0272">and then you are making lots of phone calls and you'd perhaps there was something going on in that town and you couldn't actually get in and oh god so in the end I said to <trunc>s</trunc> I don't think I wanna do that again actually so we went and saw somewhere er somebody up in <anon type="place"/> and just spent a Saturday morning with this woman</u>
<u n="143" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0272">who obviously had been in that area and she was able to work out well you know this'd be quite good if and you'd need two days <trunc>her</trunc> oh sorry you need two days here and you need two days there and and then they so they booked the flights the erm car the ferry rides because we had two</u>
<u n="145" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0272">three-hour ferry rides across from St Lawrence and across the Bay of Fundy which were really long ferry rides and the accommodation in the cities that we stayed in</u>
<u n="147" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0272">but then they came up with the accommodation in various other places that we were going to and and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said anything that starts with quality completely puts me off</u>
<u n="149" who="S0273"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0272">so the Quality Inn in Tadoussac was not somewhere we wanted to stay because we just knew how awful it was gonna be so we then decided that we were gonna we booked our own B and Bs</u>
<u n="151" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0272">and had some fantastic places</u>
<u n="153" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0272">so it worked really well so yeah hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0268">hi</u>
<u n="156" who="S0273">hi</u>
<u n="157" who="S0272">how are you? oh look at those knees</u>
<u n="158" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0268">is it still going?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0266">yeah it's still recording</u>
<u n="161" who="S0272">still recording</u>
<u n="162" who="S0268">I would kiss you but <unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0272">no you've</u>
<u n="164" who="S0268">not recommended</u>
<u n="165" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0268">okay I'll leave you to it <unclear>and go and shower</unclear></u>
<u n="167" who="S0266" trans="overlap">how many how many were playing?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0268">er we got roped in other people so we had four most of the time</u>
<u n="169" who="S0266">oh good</u>
<u n="170" who="S0268">yeah okay so you've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0272">yep</u>
<u n="172" who="S0268">sort of</u>
<u n="173" who="S0273"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0268">right see you later</u>
<u n="175" who="S0272">see you later</u>
<event desc="0268 leaves"/>
<u n="176" who="S0272">so erm I I found them really good and I that worked really really well so in the big cities I found that they were you weren't gonna get a sort of different accommodation</u>
<u n="177" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0272">but so <unclear/>'ll start looking for the</u>
<u n="179" who="S0273" trans="overlap">I had a little bit of a look at erm <trunc>Hawai</trunc> er Hawaii Hanoi Vietnam and there are amazing hotels that you can get for next to nothing</u>
<u n="180" who="S0272">yes that's be</u>
<u n="181" who="S0273" trans="overlap">be spoilt rotten on the first little bit</u>
<u n="182" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh I'm investigating cos this year we always we always promise ourselves to have a big holiday every other year while we can and so next year's our big holiday so time to book it now Vietnam is on one of the things on my list what made you decide you wanted to go to Vietnam?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0273">well I mean from time to time I've heard people say you know it's one of the new upcoming places lots of people going to and it's very nice and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> went there</u>
<u n="184" who="S0272">oh did she?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0273">from Australia</u>
<u n="186" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0273">and really liked it er but as much as anything when you're looking getting from here to New Zealand well we've been to Hong Kong we've been to Singapore</u>
<u n="188" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0273">erm we've sort of done the big the main places the most obvious places that you probably would stop at <unclear>thought</unclear> oh let's do and I said what about Vietnam or Cambodia and we're going to Vietnam</u>
<u n="190" who="S0272">lovely</u>
<u n="191" who="S0273">and there we go we're in Vietnam over tet which is the Vietnamese new year</u>
<u n="192" who="S0272">oh are you?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0273">which is one of those double edged things so it'll be really good to see all the festivals and so on but the transport'll be awful and the service in the hotels'll be awful <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0273">so <unclear/> so we shall see we'll survive</u>
<u n="196" who="S0272">of course you will</u>
<u n="197" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0266">I've got a good Vietnamese phrasebook</u>
<u n="199" who="S0273">oh could <unclear/> a borrow of that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0266">I got quite good</u>
<u n="201" who="S0272">have you have you been there?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0266">no I was teaching a whole load of Vietnamese in prison men and women over the years so I and they knew virtually no English</u>
<u n="203" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0266">so I resorted to not what I usually do but I did in that case</u>
<u n="205" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0266">it's a very difficult language</u>
<u n="207" who="S0272">yeah I expect some of them'll speak English there I expect they'll get away with it that's the trouble everywhere you go these days everybody's being</u>
<u n="208" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> speak English</u>
<u n="209" who="S0272">yeah they do yeah so erm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0266">a cultural sort of er differences of</u>
<u n="211" who="S0273" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0266">very great make it very difficult</u>
<u n="213" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0266">but wonderful people</u>
<u n="215" who="S0272">mm <pause dur="short"/> so why the places in the States? what why New Orleans New Orleans and Dallas?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0273">er well we've been to again we've been to a lot of places and the places we would have quite liked to go perhaps to Boston or Washington but we'd have gone all the way round the southern hemisphere in nice weather and it'll be the end of March</u>
<u n="217" who="S0272">oh so it'll be cold</u>
<u n="218" who="S0273">so don't really want to carry winter clothes <vocal desc="laugh"/> all the way round the world for the sake of two or three days in Boston or Washington particularly if they're going to have a winter like they did last year</u>
<u n="219" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0273">so we thought somewhere where it's gonna be warm and we've done San Francisco and Los Angeles and so <unclear/> New Orleans is somewhere we have always thought we'd like to go</u>
<u n="221" who="S0272" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0273">and then the plane stops over in Dallas whether we like it or not and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to Dallas earlier this year she went to Texas for a week fortnight er cos one of her very good friends on her MA course is from Texas</u>
<u n="223" who="S0272">oh right</u>
<u n="224" who="S0273">and she went to visit and she was very taken with Dallas said it was really nice so we thought well if the plane's gonna stop there anyway</u>
<u n="225" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0273">so we might as well have a couple of days could be <unclear>brilliant</unclear></u>
<u n="227" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah good idea</u>
<u n="228" who="S0273">two nights or something might only be one night actually</u>
<u n="229" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0273">cos it lands early in the morning so we've got all day</u>
<u n="231" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah then the following</u>
<u n="232" who="S0273">all the next day on a lateish flight see something of</u>
<u n="233" who="S0272">seven and a half weeks I I've been away for a month twice</u>
<u n="234" who="S0273">yes a month is the longest I've ever done before</u>
<u n="235" who="S0272">seven and a half weeks gonna be very</u>
<u n="236" who="S0273" trans="overlap">see if we're still speaking <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0272" trans="overlap">was gonna say I I would I still speak be speaking to him after seven and a half weeks? <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's quite intense isn't it that sort of travelling together for that length of time</u>
<u n="238" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0272">but that'll be good fantastic</u>
<u n="240" who="S0273" trans="overlap">be interesting</u>
<u n="241" who="S0272">mm would love to do something like that but I have to give up work first</u>
<u n="242" who="S0266">well you'll have to reach retirement age <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0272">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0266">work a bit harder</u>
<u n="245" who="S0273">see it's all very well being the youngest <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0272">I know I've still gotta work <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I realise that</u>
<u n="247" who="S0266">oh is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> working?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0272">no</u>
<u n="249" who="S0266">not at all?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0273" whoConfidence="low">not at all no?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0272">no no he's given up he's sixty and decided well he absolutely hated the last contract that he did he really really really hated that it so he finished that and decided that he he didn't want to go back to Lloyds ever again he really didn't wanna do that he I think he'd be happy to do something and use his skills but not doing what he was doing under the pressure he was under and the politics what he really likes doing is right he he used to be the way that that the bank worked was that you'd be a project manager and you'd be responsible for <trunc>ot</trunc> <unclear/> I don't know ten twelve million pound project but it was a project you sort of had a start beginning and end and it and it had a sort of boundary round it and that's what you were delivering and that's where he was really good at that and he'd always deliver really well on that but they've changed the whole way it works now so that this project will be involved with this project that's involved in that project so the whole things are running together as one sort of programme and what was happening was that erm he'd spend half the week reporting on what he's supposed to deliver that week to the <trunc>fol</trunc> to the following week into this into this group thing and he said you know all I was doing was spending all my time reporting and I couldn't actually get the work done</u>
<u n="252" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0272">and and it was constant politics and somebody you know lording it over each he just he just I can't deal with it now sorry I want to deliver a project and I know I can I'm good at that I can do do that but I can't deal with all this playing around bit telling people what I'm gonna deliver but I haven't got time to do it because I'm spending all my time reporting and what I'm gonna deliver <vocal desc="laugh"/> and <unclear/> that sort of you know ridiculous thing so in the end erm so he's given up I think if <trunc>someth</trunc> he'd love to do something else part time but nothing's come along</u>
<u n="254" who="S0266">so do you get dinner on the table every night and erm all the housework done and</u>
<u n="255" who="S0272">well sort of in theory</u>
<u n="256" who="S0266" trans="overlap">is he a house husband then?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0272">yeah in theory and we need updating the kitchen actually so he's been doing a lot of work on that it's quite a difficult transition actually I find it quite difficult with him being at home and me going out to work so there are times where it's quite stressful and other times it makes it easier so I wouldn't say it's always plain sailing so it varies really you can get quite resentful on occasions and I don't like that side of myself <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0273">yeah I find it quite difficult having <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> home so much more</u>
<u n="259" who="S0272">yeah mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0266">I I had I went to a party on Saturday night and met an old friend and her husband's retired erm from teaching a head of department or whatever early retirement and he's at home all the time and she's got a job that's fifteen hours a week</u>
<u n="261" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0266">er which she used to do I think in two days and she's not stretched it to four days so that she can be away because he's always in the house</u>
<u n="263" who="S0273">I've been saying for years I have to get a job <vocal desc="laugh"/> when he retires</u>
<u n="264" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I I'll be honest with you that is quite</u>
<u n="265" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and she said it's driving her mad</u>
<u n="266" who="S0272">it is it is quite difficult and and I think the things that erm because because he did this project work for the last eight years I suppose erm he erm you know he'd often do six months or a year and then have a few months off and but at the moment he had the he went back to work all the responsibilities of the house suddenly got handed to me even though I was working full time I never quite understood how this happened but because he was doing a longer journey somehow or another I got it all those responsibilities but I'm sort of adapting but I do find it quite difficult sometimes thinking actually I open the fridge and think there's nothing in here I wanna eat cos I never get to go to the shops and he has and I don't actually I get fed up with that I wanna go and buy my own stuff but somehow or another it doesn't seem to happen and erm certain things I'd you know he does this he's quite a good cook he does the cooking most of the time which is great but actually if I'm retired I don't want him I want to take back some of that I feel as though I've lost my kitchen</u>
<u n="267" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0272">erm so I think there'll be another fight when I'm not working any more so how we work that one I don't know but he just does things in a very different way and I don't always want to do it that way I don't like the way he does it and I just think oh god why can't you do it like this? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0266">and all those years he's put up with you doing it your way</u>
<u n="270" who="S0272">he hasn't known any different has he?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0266">I don't know you might have secretly been wondering why you do it</u>
<u n="272" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0273">you obviously haven't been training him properly because he should he should be doing it your way anyway if it's all been done like that all these years</u>
<u n="274" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I should should I? yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0266">and then do you find things stored in different places?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0272">erm well that's not so bad no that's alright that's okay</u>
<u n="277" who="S0273">that should be very interesting we're having a new kitchen next month</u>
<u n="278" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0273">so I should be very interested cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s still after twenty-three years in that house if he empties the dishwasher on the rare occasions that he does there are little piles around the kitchen</u>
<u n="280" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0273">cos I don't know where they go</u>
<u n="282" who="S0272"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0273">so once everything moves anyway I dread to think what it'll be like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0272">oh dear I know yet he does get</u>
<u n="285" who="S0273" trans="overlap">does he does he cook?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0272">yeah mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0266">not at all?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0273">absolutely not</u>
<u n="289" who="S0272" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="290" who="S0273">he's not interested in cooking at all</u>
<u n="291" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I know that's difficult isn't it? no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is so that's quite good but erm but there are certain things like you know I I just get sometimes the other day he had a sort of thing about I've got these sort of piles of couple of piles of paper will you please sort them out? no I'm not in the mood to sort it I was really tired and I'd had a really long day and I wasn't in the mood and he got in a real strop I said for god's sake it's a pile of paper it really doesn't matter and I do get a bit concerned about that fact that his world's smaller so this has become a big thing in his life and it's so immaterial to me because of all the things I'm doing so that's the erm only thing that I just sort of those sort of things sometimes</u>
<u n="292" who="S0266">and what's it like having no children at home?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0272">oh that's fine</u>
<u n="294" who="S0273" trans="overlap">lovely <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0272">yeah I don't have a problem with that at all really considering they've stayed around for so long really <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos I had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> back for the summer and but at one point for two months we had both of them there and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> moved out and then she's moved out about a month ago <pause dur="short"/> no I'm a great believer in you know they they need to run their own lives</u>
<u n="296" who="S0273">mm yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0272">I actually am not worried about that at all</u>
<u n="298" who="S0273">well all the way through it's never bothered me at all</u>
<u n="299" who="S0272">no it just it's</u>
<u n="300" who="S0273" trans="overlap">I was the mother dancing in the playground while others were crying on the <vocal desc="laugh"/> first day of term</u>
<u n="301" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="302" who="S0273">it's just they've got their lives to live that's the next stage they go onto it and</u>
<u n="303" who="S0272">that's right I'm sort of you know no I don't really and the thing is that I having a daughter is quite good cos they keep in contact you wouldn't know this not having a son</u>
<u n="304" who="S0266">I can see it I observe it</u>
<u n="305" who="S0272">boys don't hear from them <pause dur="short"/> so you can go you know so I I don't get to hear what's going on in his life</u>
<u n="306" who="S0266">and you work in the same place and he lives just down the road?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0272">I know it's funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0273">and even when you hear from them you don't get to know what's going on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0272" trans="overlap">he doesn't work interestingly he supposed to be moving to <anon type="place"/> I mean not that it's a thousand people that work there so I mean he's you know I might pass him at lunch on the odd occasion but it won't make any difference I won't see him any more</u>
<u n="310" who="S0266">what you won't meet him for lunch there or anything?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0272">I can't imagine in a million years he'd want to meet his mother for lunch can you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0266">why not? it'd be nice</u>
<u n="313" who="S0272">I can't imagine he'd want to do that <pause dur="short"/> erm but no I I doubt if that would happen I very much doubt that would happen but yeah he just I I I you know that's the only thing I find if he'd keep in contact a little bit more it'd be quite nice to know what he was doing but no doubt I will if there's something goes wrong <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0272">erm but you know that's fine</u>
<u n="316" who="S0273" trans="overlap">people keep telling me that they get better</u>
<u n="317" who="S0266">mm right</u>
<u n="318" who="S0273" trans="overlap">he must be just about at the point where they get better actually <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0272">yeah he's twenty-three so maybe maybe I don't know we'll see</u>
<u n="320" who="S0273">mm my cousin says that twenty-three is about the point when her son grew up</u>
<u n="321" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah and he has grown up he has grown up and he's fine but you know it's erm but no I'm actually I'm I find it fine did you find it fine when they left?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0273">mm well it was done in stages coming and going</u>
<u n="323" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so I've had that coming and going</u>
<u n="324" who="S0273" trans="overlap">away from university then back after <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0272">yeah yeah I've had the coming and going as well</u>
<u n="326" who="S0273" trans="overlap">away <unclear/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0272">but I do think</u>
<u n="328" who="S0273" trans="overlap">but I do like them <trunc>aroun</trunc> having them around</u>
<u n="329" who="S0272">yeah no I like having them around but I also am very pleased that they have built their own lives and they</u>
<u n="330" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0272">have they did yeah absolutely erm really pleased about that</u>
<u n="332" who="S0273">well and that they're able to cos there are so many kids that are <vocal desc="cough"/> stuck at home because they can't afford to</u>
<u n="333" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0273">or they don't have a job or</u>
<u n="335" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0273">whatever</u>
<u n="337" who="S0272">yeah no I find it okay actually I quite like having the odd occasions where I like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was out playing cricket last night it was lovely I had about four hours on my own ah bliss <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0273">that's a funny one cos even when they're all home I mean I haven't been working for several years now I've had had the house to myself most of the time but there's still always that <unclear>moment</unclear> if they all went out on a Saturday <vocal desc="gasp"/> I've got the house to myself I think I've had the house to myself all week but it's not the same somehow as having it when they should be there or would normally be there</u>
<u n="339" who="S0272">no I think yeah I think that's the only thing that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s around a lot more so but it's just adjusting isn't it? it's a different stage of your life but you just do it</u>
<u n="340" who="S0273" trans="overlap">it's just having to allow for the fact that there's somebody else there because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was away so much</u>
<u n="341" who="S0272">mm yeah he was wasn't he?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0273" trans="overlap">cos it's not as though he was even home every night for his tea so just having he doesn't care what I do but I've you know if I'm going out I've got to say I'm going out to I'm going to Tesco or I'm going up to <anon type="place"/> I'm going to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in in <anon type="place"/> because it's common courtesy to say I'm going out I'm doing this</u>
<u n="343" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0273">but but I feel <vocal desc="gasp"/> I used to be able to just go</u>
<u n="345" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0273">I didn't have to tell anybody <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0272">yeah that's it no it's got it's quite interesting isn't it? the different stages of one's life but you know he he keeps saying oh I'm gonna find some voluntary work or some other work and it just and a year had gone by and he still hasn't so I just wondered but I can't imagine me not wanting to do anything in terms of I want to do some voluntary work and stuff like that</u>
<u n="350" who="S0273">but equally you probably need some time to to think about what you want to do and</u>
<u n="351" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I think you're er there I would think you're absolutely right</u>
<u n="352" who="S0273">and get to the point where you are fed up of being at home and the novelty's worn off and you</u>
<u n="353" who="S0272">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s done that hasn't she?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0273" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0272">she's spent six she spent six months now isn't it?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0273" trans="overlap">is it that long now?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0272">yeah she gave up in <trunc>Mar</trunc> the end of March yes</u>
<u n="358" who="S0273" trans="overlap">course it was yes</u>
<u n="359" who="S0272">so she's had six months now</u>
<u n="360" who="S0273">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0272">and erm of you know so I think that's a very wise thing to give up work at the beginning</u>
<u n="362" who="S0273" trans="overlap">to take stock and decide</u>
<u n="363" who="S0272">of the summer and having the summer off which is exceptionally this is a friend of mine lives in er <anon type="place"/> erm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0273">she would have been here tonight if it wasn't her daughters' birthday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0272">oh it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday isn't it and erm so it's a useful thing and I think to have some time just to think what what you want in life</u>
<u n="366" who="S0273" trans="overlap">not to rush into classes in this and volunteering for that and so <unclear/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0273">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="369" who="S0272">what are you writing on these notes then?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0266">just writing the topics that we've been talking about</u>
<u n="371" who="S0272">oh <unclear>right</unclear> I see</u>
<u n="372" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0273" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0272">so how many minutes have we done? we ought to keep going a bit longer</u>
<u n="375" who="S0266" trans="overlap">we've been talking for twenty I haven't got my glasses on twenty-nine minutes I think</u>
<u n="376" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0273"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well that's never a hardship for us all to talk is it?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0266">so when are you going to retire then? what what age ninety-five?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0272">I'm not gonna make a decision I'm gonna just make a decision at the time I feel like it</u>
<u n="380" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but I mean you know pension wise and things</u>
<u n="381" who="S0272">er well my <unclear>M and S</unclear> pension kicks in when I'm sixty <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has done <trunc>we</trunc>we've been going through all sorts of different scenarios and this that and the other spreadsheets are everywhere so erm ideally for another couple of years but I I'll see I'm basically gonna go on the basis of I'm fine at the moment when I cease to enjoy the job</u>
<u n="382" who="S0266">cos how old are you now?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0272">fifty-six and a half</u>
<u n="384" who="S0266">oh god you're a baby you'll be able to work a few more years <pause dur="short"/> ten at least I'd have thought</u>
<u n="385" who="S0272"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I don't wanna work ten years it's very difficult to work in an environment when you're working for somebody where you're the oldest in the office and you keep going you see it with other people in the in the business where they're all just sort of oh god I wish they'd bloody retire they're too long in the tooth and I do not want to be in that situation so when I feel that I'm it's all got a bit of a trial and I'm repeating too much of the same thing and I'm finding it hard to come up with new ideas and <unclear/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yeah but you won't reach that for ages yet</u>
<u n="387" who="S0272"><unclear/> well I that's why I that's why I'm saying I'm not making a decision on it <pause dur="short"/> I'll see how I feel see what else happens in life</u>
<u n="388" who="S0266">and then you'll retire and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will find some new thing to do</u>
<u n="389" who="S0272">erm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0273" trans="overlap">well then you can have the house to yourself</u>
<u n="391" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> at home</u>
<u n="392" who="S0272">I think if he doesn't find something in the next year he won't erm <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0266">does he does he ever go off for sort of holidays with other people?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0272">mm goes skiing on his own</u>
<u n="395" who="S0266">mm cos that's quite a good thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0272">mm he's always at <unclear>home</unclear></u>
<u n="397" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><unclear/> individual</u>
<u n="398" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0273">holidays <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has no friends</u>
<u n="400" who="S0272">doesn't he?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0273">no</u>
<u n="402" who="S0272">really?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0273"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said <unclear>that earlier</unclear> dad hasn't got any friends has he? all your friends are your friends <pause dur="short"/> well he hasn't kept in touch with anybody</u>
<u n="404" who="S0272">hasn't he?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0273">he's had the you know he's had friends at school he had friends at university and they've all just fizzled out</u>
<u n="406" who="S0272">and he hasn't felt the need for that then?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0273">no</u>
<u n="408" who="S0272">isn't that strange now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got a huge amount of friends</u>
<u n="409" who="S0273" trans="overlap">don't you ever I mean you know if there's <trunc>someth</trunc> if if somebody in <anon type="place"/> has a party and he'll happily talk to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <unclear/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely mm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0273">so on but <trunc>noth</trunc>nothing too</u>
<u n="412" who="S0272">he doesn't search out I mean</u>
<u n="413" who="S0273">no he's quite self sufficient</u>
<u n="414" who="S0272" trans="overlap">no just I came home tonight and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s down the pub with some friends you know having a drink no you know he's very sociable gets involved with lots of</u>
<u n="415" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0272">has lots of friends and things but he's not bothered</u>
<u n="417" who="S0273">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0272">he's very different</u>
<u n="419" who="S0273">partly he says it as you said before he's got to do it all he's got to be so sociable for work</u>
<u n="420" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0273">he's had to be sociable and get on with cos he gets on with he can get on with anybody</u>
<u n="422" who="S0272">mm I know</u>
<u n="423" who="S0273">but he doesn't particularly <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="425" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0272">I think as you get older and your world get becomes smaller because of work I think friends actually are really almost more important aren't they?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0273">whereas I'm forever off with the girls and <unclear/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0273">cos there's a bunch of us we're now the diamond <trunc>di</trunc></u>
<u n="430" who="S0266" trans="overlap">does does he go to this men's erm first Friday of the month?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0273">he's done one</u>
<u n="433" who="S0266">the men's</u>
<u n="434" who="S0273">and he is intending to go again but he didn't really like it <unclear/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0266">oh didn't</u>
<u n="436" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh didn't he?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0266">did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> go?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0273">with I don't know who was there when he went I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there</u>
<u n="440" who="S0272" trans="overlap">no cos he just</u>
<u n="441" who="S0273">cos he said there was nobody really he knew</u>
<u n="442" who="S0272" trans="overlap">cos there's</u>
<u n="443" who="S0273">and he said well they talked about stories from the Daily Mail and I don't <unclear/> he must <unclear/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0272">yeah he doesn't go every time I must admit</u>
<u n="445" who="S0273" trans="overlap">he he said he will give it another go but it just hasn't worked out that he's been about to go but erm he wasn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> impressed that day anyway</u>
<u n="446" who="S0272">oh dear</u>
<u n="447" who="S0266">was that recently or some time ago?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0273">oh</u>
<u n="449" who="S0266">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0273" trans="overlap">must must have been three or four months ago</u>
<u n="451" who="S0272" trans="overlap">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0266">he's he's been twice now</u>
<u n="453" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0272">and how did he like it?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0266">I think I well you'll have to ask him</u>
<u n="456" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0266">I can't speak for him but I think he enjoyed it I mean it's it's funny isn't it? because women we automatically go and</u>
<u n="458" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yeah and just</u>
<u n="459" who="S0266">no no sort of issue or</u>
<u n="460" who="S0272">no</u>
<u n="461" who="S0266">anything but you know they it's all sort of funny about who's going and shall I go shan't I go? and yeah it's like sort of erm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0273">I mean there's a whole bunch of people turn up on Fridays and</u>
<u n="463" who="S0266" trans="overlap">teenagers</u>
<u n="464" who="S0273">I don't know they're people</u>
<u n="465" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0273">you know there's quite a that that lady we were talking <unclear/> her son had just got married I'd never met her before</u>
<u n="467" who="S0272">her son had got married erm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0273">erm he was an actor got married at the <unclear/> the <unclear/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0272">oh erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0273">right yeah there's there's quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0272" trans="overlap">she's just recently retired yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0273">cos it's quite lot of people we don't know</u>
<u n="473" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I looked down the table and thought I'm the only one here working</u>
<u n="474" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0272"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0266">the other problem is of course that you I don't know cos I haven't <unclear/> for years I mean I was in the original <unclear/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0272" trans="overlap">why aren't you gonna come? yeah we used to get you used to come didn't you? yeah well you say you used to come</u>
<u n="478" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well no one used to well in the old days I did</u>
<u n="479" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0266"><unclear/> ever managed it</u>
<u n="481" who="S0272">I know you used to go</u>
<u n="482" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but I'm usually working and then you go and you sit in one seat</u>
<u n="483" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0266">and you don't circulate</u>
<u n="485" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0266">and I mean it's pot luck who you happen to sit next to</u>
<u n="487" who="S0273">mm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0272">mm that is that is the trouble with it</u>
<u n="489" who="S0266">and you know sometimes you don't wanna give up your working time to go and sit there with someone that you don't wanna talk to for two hours well that's rude isn't it?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0272" trans="overlap">well because I because I always don't get there until quarter past one because I don't finish work till one</u>
<u n="491" who="S0266">ah so that's the trick you come in late and sidle in where you want</u>
<u n="492" who="S0272">no you have to end up at the end</u>
<u n="493" who="S0273" trans="overlap">it depends where there's space doesn't it?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0272">that's where there's space so you end up at the end so we'll have to organise to come up</u>
<u n="495" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> go arrive at quarter past one and then that'll be alright you see</u>
<u n="496" who="S0272">that's what you</u>
<u n="497" who="S0273" trans="overlap">why don't you ring a bell and you all change seats</u>
<u n="498" who="S0272">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think that would be a really good idea cos I often look down and think oh I'd really like to catch up with you</u>
<u n="499" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yes yes and or there's some conversation to have and it's oh that sounds interesting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0272">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="502" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but it's a great idea that I think</u>
<u n="503" who="S0273">I think it is because</u>
<u n="504" who="S0266">to to meet once a month definitely on a set time at a set time but I mean how long have the men been doing it now?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0272">mm not very long six months</u>
<u n="506" who="S0273" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0272">I reckon <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been to two or three</u>
<u n="508" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="509" who="S0272">but not</u>
<u n="510" who="S0266">do you think it's working?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0272">mm I think so well the ladies one's been going a lot longer than that</u>
<u n="512" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0272">and I thought I wondered why you weren't <unclear>going</unclear></u>
<u n="514" who="S0266" trans="overlap">the ladies one's been going on and off for about thirty-five years</u>
<u n="515" who="S0272" trans="overlap">well I know it has hasn't it? I mean I used to go a lot when the kids were younger</u>
<u n="516" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0272">we were always my</u>
<u n="518" who="S0266">and the Friday evening one as well when</u>
<u n="519" who="S0272">yeah no I found it very useful because cos your children are all much <trunc>old</trunc>older I know it's not particularly much but quite a number of people were kids were much older I used to find it really all the advice <unclear>you</unclear> used to give me and so forth it was really valuable I remember you giving me one very valuable piece of advice</u>
<u n="520" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0272">mm when the kids were younger erm two actually two pieces of advice one was childcare don't worry about it only worry a year in advance because in the next the following year they would have thought they would have grown up and <trunc>ne</trunc>need something different cos I used to I must have had a conversation with you where I was planning well once I've done that and then they can go onto this and I remember <trunc>turn</trunc> don't worry about it it'll work out and actually I didn't after I just took one year and so that was a very valuable piece of advice</u>
<u n="522" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="523" who="S0272">and the second piece of advice I took from you was erm you know how girls all fall out</u>
<u n="524" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0272">and erm was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that were always falling out or</u>
<u n="526" who="S0266">no that's the wrong years it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0272">right erm</u>
<u n="528" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it would have been</u>
<u n="529" who="S0272">and erm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0266">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0272">and I remember cos I and I remember you saying <trunc>do</trunc> leave it don't ever ring the mothers don't ever ever get yourself involved because they would have gone into school it would have been the end of the earth cos you remember they'd come home and sob their hearts out so and so's been really horrible to me and you listen to the story think <vocal desc="gasp"/> that's absolutely dreadful what this child's done how awful they must have been brought up really bad you know all these stupid things that go through your head and the next day and you just dread them going into school and they're just really in a state and how awful it's gonna be then they skip out of school that evening and you've had a dreadful day</u>
<u n="532" who="S0266" trans="overlap">they're fine they're best friends</u>
<u n="533" who="S0272">and they're best of friends and in the meantime if you're not careful you've rung the mother and had a right go at her and I remember you saying don't ever ever do that</u>
<u n="534" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0272">and I never did so there you are see</u>
<u n="536" who="S0266">oh well that's good well that's yeah that's very erm basic advice isn't it?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0272">I know but when you don't know</u>
<u n="538" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0272">and I've given that advice to a few other people as well</u>
<u n="540" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm it's good</u>
<u n="541" who="S0272">who've also said thank god I never did</u>
<u n="542" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0272">erm but erm but yeah I always remember</u>
<u n="544" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and then and then the same thing arises when you kids start doing erm jobs you know school jobs <trunc>ho</trunc>holiday jobs and they get treated really badly</u>
<u n="545" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0266">then you think should I jump in? shouldn't I? should I jump in? shouldn't I?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="548" who="S0273">it's back to they've got to live their own lives and sort themselves out haven't they?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but I have on one occasion when one of them was at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0272">oh right</u>
<u n="551" who="S0266">waitressing and she was being constantly sworn at by the chef she was only about fourteen</u>
<u n="552" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh that <unclear/> mm was that the South African</u>
<u n="553" who="S0266">I don't know it must have been a long time ago</u>
<u n="554" who="S0272" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="555" who="S0266">and there was someone called <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who owned the whole chain</u>
<u n="556" who="S0272" trans="overlap">oh yes that was that was right at the beginning yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0266">the whole chain of restaurants and I just rang him up I'm I'm not taking this why should and I had a long you know very interesting discussion I said look you've got children would you allow your children to be treated like that? he said certainly not my so then why do you allow my children to be treated like that? and he said well I'm really really sorry but that's the way catering is I said that's no excuse</u>
<u n="558" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0266">and he was very decent about it but I shouldn't have interfered probably</u>
<u n="560" who="S0272">mm <pause dur="short"/> well there are some</u>
<u n="561" who="S0273" trans="overlap">cos sometimes you just feel you have to don't you?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0272">mm I know mm mm</u>
<u n="563" who="S0266">but kids do get exploited sometimes</u>
<u n="564" who="S0272" trans="overlap">mm they do I agree I think if they're with a real exploitation like like I when I several times</u>
<u n="565" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they have been treated really badly</u>
<u n="566" who="S0272">several times I've you know sat there given them</u>
<u n="567" who="S0266" trans="overlap">sworn at the whole time</u>
<u n="568" who="S0272">a lot of advice and say this and do that and you know I've never had to intervene never been quite that bad but erm but yeah <pause dur="short"/> see so those those lunches were very <unclear/> actually had a very useful thing over the years</u>
<u n="569" who="S0273" trans="overlap"><unclear>font</unclear> of all wisdom and you didn't know it</u>
<u n="570" who="S0266">well no I'd learnt it from somewhere else it was all just passing down the chain it was just really useful</u>
<u n="571" who="S0272" trans="overlap">well yes exactly but it is certain things like that because <unclear/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0266" trans="overlap">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> her children are much older than mine</u>
<u n="573" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0266">I used to learn quite a lot from her cos she's very direct and <unclear>sussed</unclear> I learnt quite a lot from her</u>
<u n="575" who="S0272">yeah but I had it you know there was a group of people that I was sort of I don't know six eight ten years younger than that I somehow seem to get involved and like really always enjoyed that the friendship I had with all of them you know you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and all of that sort of group of people that I found it was really valuable to have your experience erm of of having gone through all of the this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know those sort of people</u>
<u n="576" who="S0266" trans="overlap">had to deal with the different teachers at <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0272">yeah absolutely all of those things I found I found</u>
<u n="578" who="S0266" trans="overlap">cos that's quite important isn't it?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0272">really really useful erm over the years</u>
<u n="580" who="S0266">mm and I find it useful also when they went to secondary school</u>
<u n="581" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0266">cos I used to worry about things <unclear>then</unclear></u>
<u n="583" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="584" who="S0266">you know what streams they were in or what they were <unclear/> for or whatever</u>
<u n="585" who="S0272" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely all of those sort of stuff yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0266">or how they did sport or whatever</u>
<u n="587" who="S0272">mm but yeah so</u>
<u n="588" who="S0266">yeah so I must try to get there more often on a Friday first Friday of the month</u>
<u n="589" who="S0272">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0273" trans="overlap">I'll come and winkle you out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0266">mm like I usually don't come cos genuinely I have something on but I will</u>
<u n="592" who="S0272">well you need to put it in the diary and then work round it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="593" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it's that much of a <trunc>prior</trunc> I mean it is a priority but it's not that much of a huge priority</u>
<u n="594" who="S0272">mm</u>
<u n="595" who="S0266">right shall I press the button?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
