<text id="SZBN">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:19:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0679 S0681</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s kitchen, Hardwick Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Planning the day visits to Open Farm Sunday, Booking European rail train, Crossing Paris, Planting out tomato plants, Planning the following day, Library charges and paying fines, Issues with ‘down sizing’ and placement of specialist items, Recycling electrical equipment</topics>
		<activity>Planning the next couple of days</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0679">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kent, Margate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired (University manager)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0681">
				<exactage>69</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Surry</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Dutch -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0681">so I think we need to have a quick discussion about erm planning for both today and the next few days</u>
<u n="2" who="S0679">yes what do you think you are going to do today?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0681">well I'm <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite keen to go on this open farm day erm and er <pause dur="short"/> and er was it <anon type="place"/>? it's about an hour away erm there is another farm about four miles away from the big tomato growing place it's open at four o'clock so I might go <pause dur="short"/> they open at ten eleven o'clock it closes at four o'clock</u>
<u n="4" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I thought four was a bit late to start I thought they might be doing cows or something different with that</u>
<u n="5" who="S0681">erm well no no this is just tomatoes tomatoes this place you know it's a huge</u>
<u n="6" who="S0679">the tomato place is ten to four</u>
<u n="7" who="S0681">yeah and the main farms <trunc>ar</trunc> <unclear>open at</unclear> eleven no eleven to four and the main farm from eleven to five so there is another one an arable farm about four miles to go if we wanted to go to that now how does that hang with you?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I'd like to come but</u>
<u n="9" who="S0681">I knew there would be a but in there</u>
<u n="10" who="S0679">well <pause dur="short"/> I would like to come very much I mean I've always wanted to get into <anon type="place"/> and I think it's broadly similar</u>
<u n="11" who="S0681">oh yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0679">but <vocal desc="sigh"/> if I do that I'm putting myself under a heck of a lot of pressure and you might be able to do it but I'm not sure how much turn of speed I know I've got more energy than I've had but I just don't know if I can do it and I'm sorry not to come to keep you company and I'm sorry for me because I'm missing out on something I want to do and I thought yesterday was a bit of a bummer of a day I managed to get some things done in the end but I couldn't really energise myself and having not slept very well last night I'm a bit concerned I might flake out when I get back</u>
<u n="13" who="S0681">right okay</u>
<u n="14" who="S0679">how do you feel about going on your own?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0681">well that's alright what I might do is I'm fairly certain she's not interested in going I might ring up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she's the great horticulturist so</u>
<u n="16" who="S0679">she was a bit dismissive about going to a farm wasn't she?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0681">she was yes yes so that might <trunc>I</trunc> I'll give her the option the other thing I've got to do today erm I've got to do this erm chasing of all these people on the Heidelberg trip but I'm gonna ring the guy who is normally the organiser <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and erm see if he's got the contact details for this rather mysterious Italian lady that's came with us the one where all my emails are bouncing because I'm obviously I'm not spelling her name right but if I do that I can send her the email but then this evening I'm gonna ring them all and see if they are interested and I might get a bit <trunc>sna</trunc> snappy because</u>
<u n="18" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> well it would be useful if they know if they want to or not I mean you are not saying they have to you just want to know don't you? I mean there's not there's not a wrong decision there's not a wrong answer it's just not having a decision is awkward</u>
<u n="19" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's right <pause dur="short"/> yes as far a <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0679">have you given up on your group discounts?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0681">yeah I do I contacted European rail and the group discount was not a you can't save any money you marginally save something on Eurostar but nothing on German railways in fact I've got a cheaper fare on German railways going by a different route than they seem to be get be able to get</u>
<u n="22" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> so what way do you think you're going now?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0681">well this will be down to London Eurostar to Paris across Paris well cross it's only a few hundred yards</u>
<u n="24" who="S0679">oh which stations?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0681">you come into Paris Nord and go out of Paris Est and they are only a few hundred yards apart apparently according to our sources</u>
<u n="26" who="S0679" trans="overlap">Nord <pause dur="short"/> nord <pause dur="long"/> oh because the first time I went to Paris I had never well I had mastered the London Underground <pause dur="short"/> but I thought oh I don't know if I could manage doing it so I got a map because I I understand maps and roads even if I don't understand metros</u>
<u n="27" who="S0681">well I've got maps of Paris</u>
<u n="28" who="S0679">and I <trunc>w</trunc> I and my then boyfriend walked across and I suppose we had luggage but whichever one we went to I think we went to <anon type="place"/> is there a <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0681"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0679">because we were going down to <anon type="place"/> which is in the south it's in the middle</u>
<u n="31" who="S0681" trans="overlap">but fine yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0679">and it seemed quite a long walk but I mean it was a doable walk because I had</u>
<u n="33" who="S0681" trans="overlap">no <trunc>the</trunc>these people reckon it's literally three or four hundred yards <unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0679" trans="overlap">are you thinking of a wheelie case?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0681">oh yeah I'll be taking a wheelie case <trunc>eve</trunc>even if it's only the small one but erm but the the the issue about that is there's a formal reception I will have to take at least one set of smart clothes you know</u>
<u n="36" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0681">erm <pause dur="short"/> so that's that's sort of today <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing tomorrow?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0679">tomorrow well that rather <trunc>depen</trunc> everything I haven't done today basically</u>
<u n="39" who="S0681" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0679">erm what I think I might do today you're promising me sunshine aren't you?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0681">well that's what the weather forecast yesterday says I'll check it in a few minutes</u>
<u n="42" who="S0679">it's quite early yet it might it might erm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah it said by the middle of the day it was going to be twenty-two degrees</u>
<u n="44" who="S0679">well it was pretty warm by yesterday evening I mean warm for an evening</u>
<u n="45" who="S0681">but brilliant sun as well the sky is still quite grey</u>
<u n="46" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> if I can <pause dur="short"/> I want to finish a bit of admin here <pause dur="short"/> which I just won't do for very long and I thought between about ten and two I might try and go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="48" who="S0679">including travelling</u>
<u n="49" who="S0681">right I'm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0679">and then come back and do some more admin and if I can do any paperwork tidying up all to the good with a view to doing my washing in the late afternoon so to be out of your washing arena and then tomorrow set aside the whole day with thinking through what I need to take where and any extra time I get I can go I can continue filling up that recycling box I'm not short of things to do but I fear there may not be other time and I may have to pause that activity that's oh erm I might like to go to the the library as well tomorrow my only thoughts on the library tomorrow is that one of my books on its third renewal is erm <pause dur="short"/> due back on the twenty-first so something has to happen and what I thought I might do is if I can take the book in check it in and then if no one wants it I'll check it out again if if I don't manage to do that are you au fait with that technique?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> check it out again yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh just</u>
<u n="52" who="S0679">I'll tell you the other thing that's really important that might take a bit of time is I ought to write to <anon type="place"/> hospital about my pain clinic appointments but I've got to get my head in the right space to do that because I don't want to become across as erm Ms angry of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right on Monday I'm I've got the <trunc>poe</trunc> I'm <trunc>run</trunc> I'm doing poetry so that will be finished at that'll be finished at half eleven so what I could do is come from there then come to <anon type="place"/> if that's useful? right it'll have to be it'll be indirect because I'll have to come via the park and ride because I'm going in on the park and ride but that's possible</u>
<u n="54" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well er the only thing I could mention is depending on what the weather is like a you don't want it too hot but you don't want it torrential storms you've got those tomatoes</u>
<u n="55" who="S0681">tomatoes to put in yeah I don't want to leave them particularly in the car all the morning while I'm at poetry so you could if I packaged them you could take them in yeah?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0679">what? only if I go over on Monday</u>
<u n="57" who="S0681">yeah yeah if you don't go on Monday <unclear/> I will come back here pick them up and take them over because I need to get shot of them effectively because they'll need one or two days of TLC while they are over there to bed in with lots of slug pellets <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> I'm afraid there's lots of</u>
<u n="59" who="S0681">knowing your knowing your population of snails</u>
<u n="60" who="S0679">if you ever need them when they are over there do you know where to find them?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0681">have you got some over there?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0681">oh I didn't know you had</u>
<u n="64" who="S0679">erm if you go into my utility room and look on the shelves there's erm it's like an ice not an ice cream container erm the one that has the <trunc>pow</trunc> cleaning powder in it it's got a label on that says slug pellets but just to give you an idea of what shape and it's if you stand up it's about there</u>
<u n="65" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh right <pause dur="short"/> so just above head height</u>
<u n="66" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0681">right</u>
<u n="68" who="S0679">I think it's on the shelf above where I keep the keys</u>
<u n="69" who="S0681">right Tuesday erm when have I got to get you to the station?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm we wrote in the diary the other day nine forty</u>
<u n="71" who="S0681">leaving here at nine forty right okay</u>
<u n="72" who="S0679">because because earlier is better for you because then you you you need to drop me off and I had a little thought about that actually because erm we can go to the disabled car park and put use my blue badge and then you could walk me we could or we could</u>
<u n="73" who="S0681" trans="overlap">well that's that's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> ah but you might need your blue badge in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0679">yes and <trunc>th</trunc> then could you drive round if I wait outside the station could you drive round and drop off the</u>
<u n="75" who="S0681">badge yeah that's possible</u>
<u n="76" who="S0679">otherwise I did check the front of the station and there are some dropping-off spaces we could try for one of those but as a fall back option possibly do that oh you know we were talking about libraries?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I know where they are <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm not under so much pressure from that don't forget because the venue has been of the exam has been moved to <anon type="place"/> rather than being in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh right oh well <pause dur="short"/> you could drop me off at twenty past one then couldn't you?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0681">I could do yeah it's not a problem</u>
<u n="80" who="S0679">erm I think you might want some lunch so that's what we tried to <trunc>fact</trunc> factor in</u>
<u n="81" who="S0681">oh that's not a problem I can dance around that whatever</u>
<u n="82" who="S0679">oh you could go to the erm sandwich shop for old times' sake</u>
<u n="83" who="S0681">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think that one's open anymore is it?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0679">I don't know</u>
<u n="85" who="S0681">I think I think the blue one is open but the old one is not open I don't think</u>
<u n="86" who="S0679">erm <pause dur="long"/> if you go to <anon type="place"/> tomorrow I'd like you to register my new prescription card at the chemist because if I go to <anon type="place"/> with my prescription he I mean they they know of me they know of me and they just say don't worry about it but they are a bit funny in well they're a bit more particular I mean they are probably more correct because they've got this electronic system and things but I mean that Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is very nice</u>
<u n="87" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I've I've got plenty of time on Monday afternoon in principle</u>
<u n="88" who="S0679">yeah and that would enable me to have the card registered there erm in case because it's always useful I don't know what they'd <trunc>s</trunc> you you don't want to be there and them say go away you haven't got your card I don't know they would but</u>
<u n="89" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> you are avoiding the possibility of that</u>
<u n="90" who="S0679">the thing I wanted to tell you that came through on my <anon type="place"/> library news which I think is a bit shocking erm because I always say how great our library service is one of the features I very much like has gone free <trunc>res</trunc> reservations</u>
<u n="91" who="S0681">oh are they going to start charging?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0679">a quid</u>
<u n="93" who="S0681">yeah that's what they used to charge years ago</u>
<u n="94" who="S0679">yes erm but I thought the free reservations were the pay-off for not giving us a choice of very much choice of library books and they said in order to maintain services we have to charge you a pound it wasn't just targeted at me saying because you have been overusing the service erm you can have <trunc>fir</trunc> I mean I I think it would be very encouraging to say you can you can have your first fifty a year free or I don't know how many books should you read in a year?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> ten for the price of five <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that's too difficult programming into the system</u>
<u n="96" who="S0681">well I don't know but trying to collect pounds off everybody when you do things online it presumably isn't simple</u>
<u n="97" who="S0681">well no it just goes onto your account the same as your erm overdue charges doesn't it? if a book goes overdue you can log it in and it says you owe them money but you don't have to pay it then you can carry on taking books in and out but at some stage it starts blocking you and says give us the money and I'm sure that's how it will work because it's just an extension of that system then isn't it?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0679" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0681">and I'm sure that's the system they used to use</u>
<u n="100" who="S0679">sometimes they don't make you pay the the fine immediately do they?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0681">no well that's your choice you can either pay immediately or defer it</u>
<u n="102" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> because erm I years and years ago when libraries were much friendlier places I took these library books back for erm er our person who was working as a caretaker you know we used to have students in and erm and I didn't and I forgot to take them I took them in I got them said I would drop them in and I didn't for a couple of days and they went overdue and there were some fines to pay on them and er they said oh you don't have to pay if it's not your book if you are just returning them but as this guy had gone off to work in erm where his country he came from or his mother came from erm Finland I think because er I thought it was a bit mean to leave him with a fine as I had <trunc>enca</trunc> I'd engendered the fine</u>
<u n="103" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> it was your fault</u>
<u n="104" who="S0679">yeah but they seemed to think it was quite erm very good of me to pay the fine <unclear/> but if know if you say you are going to take a book it seemed a bit mean not and he didn't come back to the country for a while but he did come back because he did his PGCE in <anon type="place"/> he liked it up there because erm erm he liked it up because er he was a mountaineer and he had more things to climb</u>
<u n="105" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0679">well you can go out to all the</u>
<u n="107" who="S0681">well I suppose you can go out to the Peak District</u>
<u n="108" who="S0679">I mean how far away is the <anon type="place"/> and people are always shinning up that I mean what have you got here? the climbing wall at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0681" trans="overlap">that's true <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> well there's not much climbing there is there unless you do horizontal climbing yeah mm mm mm so do you know what what you've got in mind erm to do when you are at your sister's? are you still gonna be clearing out junk?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0679" trans="overlap">who knows? <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know I mean the trouble is I I fear <trunc>y</trunc> you know what I'm doing at the moment with paperwork if it's junk it's quite easy to dispose of if it's old broke and tatty it's when it's pretty good but not wanted replacement er not you know not replacement what the word is you know new rehoming rehoming is a more difficult scheme</u>
<u n="111" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it takes a lot more effort I think you can</u>
<u n="112" who="S0679">for example these big speakers especially when they are things that take two people to move</u>
<u n="113" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well don't forget you could always contact if you would have to find the right one I know how to do it in <anon type="place"/> the Red Cross for instance so phone them up and tell them you've got them they might well</u>
<u n="114" who="S0679">oh I've got I've got a list of phone numbers of contacts for like furniture but specialist equipment that is used that is heavy bulky and only used in certain situations probably by a particular sort of person I'm going to see how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> feels but erm I might well email <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because her husband erm partner husband I think erm he I don't he may have retired completely now but he used to have quite a good living being a bit retro going around to popstars and people of the older generation who still had recording equipment that you couldn't you know he could mend it and do some of that so I don't know it's the right sort of era</u>
<u n="115" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> analogue equipment yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's that's a good source <pause dur="short"/> and the right sort of thing as well yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0679">yeah not quite not quite I mean I don't think they'll be playing but I mean <trunc>h</trunc> he I think I I spoke to somebody and oh I think it might be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually and because she didn't have a contact but I have now got a contact another thing you have to send <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> birthday card today she said if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saw an email for that she probably wouldn't pass it on because she's having a heck of a job trying to get wean him down because he's got really quite a big jukebox in the living room you know he's that sort of person and he erm he was going to get rid of his great big carp which are well most of the garden was a <trunc>con</trunc> a <trunc>c</trunc> a sort of shed thing to keep his carp in at I suppose at night time I don't know perhaps they stay in all day but you know big carps they need a lot of space to swim around</u>
<u n="117" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh right yeah yeah oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> the remember the Red Cross is one of the few places that will take electrical equipment a lot of places won't because if they take it if they are gonna resell it they have to test it which means quite a lot of extra work that's why a lot of the charity shops won't take electrical equipment but you know the big Red Cross shop in <anon type="place"/> has got a lot of electrical equipment televisions video recorders and things like that</u>
<u n="118" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh right I don't know <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> also if you need to recycle stuff electrical stuff I I assumed you could take it to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0681">oh yeah you could take it there</u>
<u n="120" who="S0679">but it says in the erm WhatsOn in somewhere well one of these things we get news things possibly the <anon type="place"/> library thing but it's a bit out of their sort of thing for them that they are doing <trunc>y</trunc> you can there's a date in July you can take it to <anon type="place"/> park and ride and there's <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> all over the all over the <trunc>pl</trunc> all over the county</u>
<u n="121" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> is is this specific for electrical equipment?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0681">oh right okay you know it's not that charity again is it?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0679">no no they well I don't think it is</u>
<u n="125" who="S0681">they got their fingers burnt because they ended up with so much stuff</u>
<u n="126" who="S0679">no no they they just didn't they they used to come round <anon type="place"/> because they used to give the parish council some money for doing it they used to advertise they used to collect it take it away but they said the price of scrap has gone down to such a rate that it's just not viable they didn't say <anon type="place"/> response is overwhelming because everybody found they had a garage full of rubbish</u>
<u n="127" who="S0681" trans="overlap">money yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> electrical rubbish they wanted to get rid of</u>
<u n="128" who="S0679">but also when that happened they apparently allegedly didn't get everything they should do because somebody else came round in a white van and</u>
<u n="129" who="S0681">helped themselves</u>
<u n="130" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="131" who="S0681">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0679">erm but I mean at the moment the the way they're writing like you know you'd have to pay these people in white vans to take it away any way you look as though you need to hurry off now</u>
<u n="133" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0679">okay erm what time? do you think you'll <vocal desc="misc"/> what's the earliest you might go out so we can liaise as necessary?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0681">about eleven o'clock I think</u>
<u n="136" who="S0679">oh okay so er that's a little while yet isn't it?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've got to make these phone calls first to see if I can set up these contacts</u>
<u n="138" who="S0679">right catch up with you later then</u>
<u n="139" who="S0681">right</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
