<text id="SZJ5">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:21:52</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0072 S0161</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>University library, Salford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics>Holidays</topics>
		<activity>Librarians Talking about Holidays</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0072">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Oldham, Greater Manchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North West</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Salford, Greater Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0161">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Eastbourne, East Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cheadle, Greater Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services Assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; Russian -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0072">when was your first holiday?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0161">mine? When? What when I was growing up <trunc>whe</trunc> when on my own or when I was growing up or what?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0072">when you were growing up yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0161">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think the first one I ever did without family was going to Italy with a friend of mine in nineteen seventy-six and it was manic it was absolutely manic <pause dur="short"/> cos she didn't speak any Italian</u>
<u n="5" who="S0072">right</u>
<u n="6" who="S0161">and I was busking it through everything else <pause dur="short"/> and she nearly drove me nuts because she insisted on looking at silk scarves when I wanted to go and <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0161">not popular <pause dur="short"/> how about you?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0072">eh the first time on my own was probably Glastonbury</u>
<u n="10" who="S0161">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="11" who="S0072">I don't know cos I always see Glastonbury as being a holiday</u>
<u n="12" who="S0161">oh yeah well it would be wouldn't it yes</u>
<u n="13" who="S0072">so yeah I've been</u>
<u n="14" who="S0161">when did you go?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0072">well I was seventeen so two thousand and seven <pause dur="short"/> that was the first time</u>
<u n="16" who="S0161">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="17" who="S0072">and I've been every year since <pause dur="short"/> but obviously it's not on this year they're giving the ground a rest and cos of the Olympics so</u>
<u n="18" who="S0161">right <pause dur="short"/> that's right of course <pause dur="short"/> who was on?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0072">last year? Em <pause dur="short"/> beyoncé eh</u>
<u n="20" who="S0161">thank you</u>
<u n="21" who="S0072">I can't remember I've been so many times <pause dur="short"/> beyoncé who was on it? U2</u>
<u n="22" who="S0161">oh not the dreaded Bono</u>
<u n="23" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're actually good</u>
<u n="24" who="S0161">oh they are</u>
<u n="25" who="S0072">they are actually good</u>
<u n="26" who="S0161">I mean I don't mind listening to U2 <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I could stand putting up with <trunc>Bo</trunc> with Bono prancing round the stage with his pink specs <pause dur="short"/> but I like the  I like the I like the  basis of eh material <pause dur="short"/> I like <unclear/> I don't mind watching them perform at all</u>
<u n="27" who="S0072">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a huge fan but they were <trunc>ama</trunc> oh and Coldplay as well <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't see Coldplay which I kind of regretted because we walked past them performing and and it just looked amazing <pause dur="short"/> the light show was fantastic <pause dur="short"/> they had the whole stage lit up</u>
<u n="28" who="S0161">yeah sometimes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0072">yeah I mean it there's been quite a wide variety over the years of people that have</u>
<u n="30" who="S0161">yes <pause dur="short"/> I think with it been the first one this is what they tended to do wasn't it? Keep it as wide as they possibly could <pause dur="short"/> I've never actually done one <pause dur="short"/> it's on my to do list <pause dur="short"/> l</u>
<u n="31" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0161">but the thing I think I the one I would <trunc>re</trunc> everybody says Glastonbury but I actually quite fancy WOMAD because I love world music</u>
<u n="33" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> smaller festivals are</u>
<u n="34" who="S0161">yeah that's true <pause dur="short"/> besides I've got</u>
<u n="35" who="S0072">I'd I'd quite like to go to a small one cos that's one of the problems I think with Glastonbury is it's just the size</u>
<u n="36" who="S0161">it's just so big isn't it? Yes</u>
<u n="37" who="S0072">having to queue for like six hours and</u>
<u n="38" who="S0161">that's not on is it? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has been to WOMAD two or three times</u>
<u n="39" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> whereabouts is it?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0161">is <trunc>i</trunc> is it Dorset? It's down in the south west somewhere I think but I can't remember exactly where yeah <pause dur="short"/> you lined up for anything this year?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0072">no well my parents have got a house in Spain <pause dur="short"/> so I'm well off</u>
<u n="42" who="S0161">oh good <pause dur="short"/> you are well off</u>
<u n="43" who="S0072">but cos it's I've been that many times now it's kind of <pause dur="short"/> it's still a holiday but it's</u>
<u n="44" who="S0161">yes but it's it's not</u>
<u n="45" who="S0072">but it's sort of also <unclear/> seeing them and my Granddad lives in Spain as well</u>
<u n="46" who="S0161">I see yes</u>
<u n="47" who="S0072">so it doesn't seem as much like a holiday</u>
<u n="48" who="S0161"><unclear/> something else <pause dur="short"/> I must admit this year because of that that sit that was in the eh that guy was advertising on marketplace <pause dur="short"/> you know the one who is doing the the cheap flat on the Costa del Sol <pause dur="short"/> hundred and fifty quid a week between January and May</u>
<u n="49" who="S0072">right yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0161">two bedroomed apartment <pause dur="short"/> five minutes' walk from the beach <pause dur="short"/> ria del Sol <pause dur="short"/> so we thought right we'll give that a bit of a try no problems <pause dur="short"/> cos I like Spain and Spanish is one of my languages so I can actually get round on it</u>
<u n="51" who="S0072">so have you already been?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0161">em <pause dur="short"/> we've been to  We've been to  Barcelona twice and we've been to Valencia <pause dur="short"/> eh Barcelona was partly with the family one year on an architect's trip on the occasion as the Valencia one was which is great <pause dur="short"/> married my own guide book very handy don't have to worry about that <pause dur="short"/> but we've never actually done the Costa del Sol so we thought we'd give it a try and we're going in June so it's not too hot</u>
<u n="53" who="S0072">too <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="54" who="S0161">which is a thing for me <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> love heat I wilt <pause dur="short"/> no good with it at all</u>
<u n="55" who="S0072">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's the same with with my nan cos she she lived in Spain for eleven years</u>
<u n="56" who="S0161">right</u>
<u n="57" who="S0072">my parents bought the house last year and they're retiring in June and they're moving they're there at the moment to try and set all things up so we've just got</u>
<u n="58" who="S0161">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're going to be there permanently</u>
<u n="59" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they just got a phone line installed yesterday</u>
<u n="60" who="S0161">wow</u>
<u n="61" who="S0072">and some broadband</u>
<u n="62" who="S0161">excellent</u>
<u n="63" who="S0072">so but that's the problem with my nan <pause dur="short"/> she has she always used to come back and stay at my mum and dad's house in August</u>
<u n="64" who="S0161">right so she's going to have to find somewhere</u>
<u n="65" who="S0072">Cos she's too hot <pause dur="short"/> but their house has got air conditioning in in Spain so I've got a feeling she'll go and stay with them</u>
<u n="66" who="S0161">that's fair enough it's not a problem is it?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0072">throughout August</u>
<u n="68" who="S0161">yes yes I must admit I don't think I could do anywhere in the med eh in say July August possibly September <pause dur="short"/> I'd just wilt cos I don't do you know</u>
<u n="69" who="S0072">I I prefer it <pause dur="short"/> october is my favourite time</u>
<u n="70" who="S0161">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="71" who="S0072">we went to em <pause dur="short"/> we went to Greece a couple of years back and we went in July cos we had to because Lou was going on em placement and I was absolutely wiped out <pause dur="short"/> there we were in Greece and it as absolutely gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> it was a dry heat but July was was too warm for me <pause dur="short"/> and we thought to come back after and the lass behind the lass in the hotel reception said don't come in August she said <pause dur="short"/> even the flies are too hot but she said you you I know you need to be there before October because they close everything down in October when we were in Pefkohori I was talking to the lady who ran the one of the souvenir shops and she said they all close up completely at the beginning of October beginning to middle and they all go back to Chalkidiki which is where most of the live <pause dur="short"/> but Peph <trunc>ko</trunc> is gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> little you know very small coastal town really really nice <pause dur="short"/> and the best one of the nicest small town squares I've ever seen in my <pause dur="short"/> and lots of mini supermarkets <pause dur="short"/> as soon as the kids found the cold beer <pause dur="short"/> and they got a  they got a  free cool band with it <pause dur="short"/> so they used to fill it with cans and waft down to  down to  the beach</u>
<u n="72" who="S0072">sounds good</u>
<u n="73" who="S0161">so you've done any do you tend to go to Spain cos your parents have got a place there?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0072">no yeah I mean we've not been <pause dur="short"/> me and Paul went in two thousand and ten was the last time we went over <pause dur="short"/> it was his twenty-first <pause dur="short"/> so we went to New York which was amazing</u>
<u n="75" who="S0161">oh yes I bet it was</u>
<u n="76" who="S0072">I was still only twenty so I couldn't go to any bars or anything</u>
<u n="77" who="S0161">oh right yes of course <pause dur="short"/> yeah that stupid eh that stupid yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0072">it was still go though <pause dur="short"/> so we were there for five days</u>
<u n="79" who="S0161">excellent</u>
<u n="80" who="S0072">but I'd quite like to go to New York not to New York City to the state and see all the quiet parts rather than</u>
<u n="81" who="S0161">yeah <pause dur="short"/> somebody I used to teach with <pause dur="short"/> he and his wife went down the Eastern Seaboard for their twenty-fifth wedding anniversary and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it was amazing <pause dur="short"/> he said the time is <unclear/> then you get all the trees and it's really good <pause dur="short"/> I've not done the states <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been <pause dur="short"/> again he went down the Eastern Seaboard <pause dur="short"/> and again we have a friend of a friend a musician plays keyboards for <anon type="place"/> when <anon type="place"/> is on tour <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives in Tulsa lives in Oklahoma somewhere? He's a head case <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> silver smithing from <unclear/> that and doors the way the em <pause dur="short"/> it it it's what they don't <unclear/> hats indoors and everybody is raising an eyebrow it <pause dur="short"/> this is what the man does but he has this most fantastic silver banner which he made in <unclear/> coloured card definitely <pause dur="short"/> it was really nice <pause dur="short"/> I would like to go to the States but I think we're going to have to win the lottery to do it</u>
<u n="82" who="S0072">that that's my dream too <pause dur="short"/> win the lottery and the six months buy a clapped out old banger and just drive around for</u>
<u n="83" who="S0161" trans="overlap">oh that would be good yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah one of my colleagues from Stockport <pause dur="short"/> she and her partner they did Colorado <pause dur="short"/> and they went through maybe where the big bats are <pause dur="short"/> you know what are they called? You know the desert there? Oh what's it's called? Where they film all the Westerns <pause dur="short"/> you know the one I mean don't you?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0072">I think</u>
<u n="85" who="S0161">got the bloody great hunks of rock <pause dur="short"/> what what's it called? South west isn't it? Is it down there? Is it Montana it's in?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0072">not sure</u>
<u n="87" who="S0161">ah but you you know the place I mean <pause dur="short"/> and her her photographs were to die for</u>
<u n="88" who="S0072">yeah it must be amazing</u>
<u n="89" who="S0161">absolutely yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I think we will probably be going to eh to Sussex <unclear/> we've got friends down there <pause dur="short"/> so we go on a camping holiday and <unclear/> for a week</u>
<u n="90" who="S0072">that's what I'm looking to do cos we've never been to Cornwall</u>
<u n="91" who="S0161">Cornwall is great</u>
<u n="92" who="S0072">and with not going to Glastonbury this year <pause dur="short"/> I I kind of I like the fact Glastonbury does feel like a holiday <pause dur="short"/> definitely is normally it is nice weather although this past year it was horrible <pause dur="short"/> but I I was thinking maybe instead of going abroad</u>
<u n="93" who="S0161">Cornwall is nice</u>
<u n="94" who="S0072">this year yeah might be having a British holiday <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="95" who="S0161">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you decide you want to do that let me know cos I we've got friends who have just moved back from Bermuda to just outside St Oswald <pause dur="short"/> so if you want to go down there let me have a word with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for you and find out what it's like <pause dur="short"/> it's good <pause dur="short"/> oh no Cornwall <pause dur="short"/> anywhere down the south west <pause dur="short"/> dorset's got quite a lot to recommend it and that's not just because I grew up there <pause dur="short"/> em you've got more more prehistory than you can throw a stick at <pause dur="short"/> I mean I was wandering round a medieval site when I was a kid and don't <pause dur="short"/> not a medieval like a stone bronze age site it was Badbury Rings it was called <pause dur="short"/> and eh completely unaware of the significance <pause dur="short"/> I mean now Ill be back there <pause dur="short"/> one of life's ambitious to get on Time Team if I'm to still still steal fill <unclear/> hat</u>
<u n="96" who="S0072">I think that's the thing about this country that</u>
<u n="97" who="S0161">we've got the weather</u>
<u n="98" who="S0072">it's like <pause dur="short"/> yeah once you've got the weather</u>
<u n="99" who="S0161">you need <pause dur="short"/> yeah if you got the weather you wouldn't need go anywhere <pause dur="short"/> I mean the southwest of Scotland is fantastic <pause dur="short"/> all that all of that <unclear/> from Argyle down to <unclear/> shire is absolutely stunning <pause dur="short"/> it's beautiful but you</u>
<u n="100" who="S0072">there are so many places</u>
<u n="101" who="S0161">yeah but you need the weather</u>
<u n="102" who="S0072">yeah I mean that's the thing you can book for</u>
<u n="103" who="S0161">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0072">five days and then if it was raining</u>
<u n="105" who="S0161">and Northumbria is nice <pause dur="short"/> the north-eastern coast is great <pause dur="short"/> em we took Louise when she was a baby she could only have been about eighteen months we took her we went up to em was it Annock? Went up to Annock <pause dur="short"/> stayed in this sort of converted country house <pause dur="short"/> you could kind have a party in the bathroom <pause dur="short"/> absolutely great</u>
<u n="106" who="S0072">we we a couple of years ago my friend got a house is Abesoth</u>
<u n="107" who="S0161">oh Abersoch makes me laugh</u>
<u n="108" who="S0072">we were there for for a week <pause dur="short"/> it rained the whole time</u>
<u n="109" who="S0161">of course of course</u>
<u n="110" who="S0072">but <pause dur="short"/> it was a really good holiday</u>
<u n="111" who="S0161">I went <pause dur="short"/> we we <trunc>wor</trunc> we've got a friend who's got a caravan down on  which is just a bit north of Abersoch on the coast <pause dur="short"/> and we went to Abersoch and I'm thinking why is everybody raving about this place? It's got one main street <pause dur="short"/> you know I grew up in Sussex <pause dur="short"/> eastbourne you've got a pier to go at you've got Beachy Head you've got Langley Point <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm thinking this is not a sea side resort this is a small town that everybody has made a fuss about <pause dur="short"/> but it was quite good fun watching watching the juvenile Cheshire set play <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ol</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> taking the boat out <pause dur="short"/> but in fairness to them they were lovely kids and they were really nice with each other small brothers and sisters <pause dur="short"/> manners immaculate nice people <pause dur="short"/> no <unclear/> nothing <pause dur="short"/> beautifully behaved kids</u>
<u n="112" who="S0072">yeah it was  it was  yeah nice there</u>
<u n="113" who="S0161">you <trunc>pe</trunc> you people spot in Abersoth <pause dur="short"/> people spot</u>
<u n="114" who="S0072">well I mean if the weather was nice it would have been amazing <pause dur="short"/> we went</u>
<u n="115" who="S0161">oh yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0072">yeah on the beach for about half an hour to an hour just to</u>
<u n="117" who="S0161">ah no</u>
<u n="118" who="S0072">we felt we had to</u>
<u n="119" who="S0161">yes quite to make a point</u>
<u n="120" who="S0072">but then we just walked</u>
<u n="121" who="S0161">yes</u>
<u n="122" who="S0072">and just went to the pub and <unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0161">I'll tell you where's good for that <pause dur="short"/> we went down to St David's <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I went down on a riding holiday last summer <pause dur="short"/> and there was a beach just not far out of St David's called new something or other <pause dur="short"/> I'd have to look it up <pause dur="short"/> and it's three miles end to end <pause dur="short"/> and it was hardly <unclear/> island <pause dur="short"/> it was quite chill it was July but it was quite chill <pause dur="short"/> and we just walked <pause dur="short"/> we went that end and we went right the way back down again <pause dur="short"/> and it was gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> because I mean stick my feet in the water and you've lost me <pause dur="short"/> I have paddled in the Baltic just on principle <pause dur="short"/> by god it was cold <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't find any amber so I had to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to buy me some <pause dur="short"/> I think we've run out of steam Hal? Is that enough? <event desc="recording skips"/> I was when my kids were small they used to go to a Methodist ah playgroup which was based in a Methodist church and eh <pause dur="short"/> I was in there and they were discussing fundraising <pause dur="short"/> and they were talking about they were <trunc>ha</trunc> you know they're having a springier or something like discussing fundraising and I said eh <pause dur="short"/> why don't you have a raffle?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0072">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0161">well of course Methodist view of raffles is gambling <pause dur="short"/> now if you mean holy roman everybody will be in raffles nobody thinks about it</u>
<u n="126" who="S0072">that's true</u>
<u n="127" who="S0161">it's gambling I said no it's not it's a raffle <pause dur="short"/> vera wouldn't talk to me for about the next three weeks <pause dur="short"/> I mean we do the lottery here but we do it as a syndicate</u>
<u n="128" who="S0072">what what happened when it launched? Cos I never really thought about this</u>
<u n="129" who="S0161">absolutely no idea <pause dur="short"/> absolutely</u>
<u n="130" who="S0072">Cos is it ninety-four when it?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0161">oh got is it that far back? I was bringing up children at that stage so I can't remember but eh</u>
<u n="132" who="S0072">it must have been controversial <pause dur="short"/> but you are right though cos they don't think of em raffle or Bingo</u>
<u n="133" who="S0161">no no no Bingo is <pause dur="short"/> you know bloody <pause dur="short"/> some some some of the Methodists <unclear/> I think they do it for I mean I would never <pause dur="short"/> I'll chop that it because basically what we do is if we save save money it goes in the deposit for the Christmas meal</u>
<u n="134" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0161">so really it's quite an effective way of saving for something that we all want to do and keep the price within an intelligent limit</u>
<u n="136" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0161">so if you view it as a saving thing and also <unclear/> the way interest rates are at the moment you know you might as well put it in the lottery before you get a</u>
<u n="138" who="S0072">you might yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0161">of course apparently the bigger the syndicate you have the more chance you have of winning but eh <pause dur="short"/> we have a flutter on the Grand National but being of Irish stock I don't do gambling I've got to say <pause dur="short"/> but what would you do if you won it?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0072">I've I've been asked this question a lot and I think buy an old banger drive round America</u>
<u n="141" who="S0161">that'd be good</u>
<u n="142" who="S0072">eh I wouldn't be particular flash <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't go go crazy</u>
<u n="143" who="S0161">no no no <pause dur="short"/> no no no I don't think I would either</u>
<u n="144" who="S0072">I think I'd just buy <pause dur="short"/> maybe buy a house <pause dur="short"/> buy a house in Didsbury which would obviously be nice</u>
<u n="145" who="S0161">what for? Buy in Didsbury? There's more interesting places than Didsbury <pause dur="short"/> but yeah yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0072">I suppose yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I it just be strange to win like the Euro Millions</u>
<u n="147" who="S0161">oh good grief yes</u>
<u n="148" who="S0072">eh that lady in Ireland Dolores wasn't it? She won a hundred and eighteen million</u>
<u n="149" who="S0161">wow <pause dur="short"/> what would you do with it?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0072">I definitely wouldn't go public</u>
<u n="151" who="S0161">oh no no</u>
<u n="152" who="S0072">which is what she did</u>
<u n="153" who="S0161">I must be quite honest I think a lot of mine <pause dur="short"/> I think I would set my kids up</u>
<u n="154" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0161">with with a house each and give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> enough to finish his <unclear/> training and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> maybe two or three years money to keep going for two or three years <pause dur="short"/> I'd make sure we'd got enough I'd make sure they'd got enough money to look after <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> and I got a decent pension <pause dur="short"/> and then frankly I would give a load of it away</u>
<u n="156" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0161">and it go to the cancer charities to place like Christies and St Anne's you know I some of my favourite ones <pause dur="short"/> you know animal charities things like that <pause dur="short"/> cos what you know what can you spend it on?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0072">yeah what can you do? I I <pause dur="short"/> I think I'd open a business</u>
<u n="159" who="S0161">oh that'd be a good idea</u>
<u n="160" who="S0072">but I wouldn't want to just fritter my money away and not do anything there <pause dur="short"/> I'd find it weird</u>
<u n="161" who="S0161" trans="overlap">no no no absolutely not <pause dur="short"/> what <trunc>is</trunc> what kind of business would you?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0072">I'd probably open a bar or a restaurant or something like that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0161">oh good <pause dur="short"/> good good <unclear/> You'd probably get business off this place wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0072">well exactly</u>
<u n="165" who="S0161">what sort of bar? Just a bar? Any <trunc>part</trunc> would you would you theme it?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0072">like a nice cocktail bar I think</u>
<u n="167" who="S0161">that'd be good <pause dur="short"/> middle of town or?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0072">yeah middle of town <pause dur="short"/> an old  An old  bank or an old building <pause dur="short"/> jamie's Oliver has just opened an Italian hasn't he? In eh</u>
<u n="169" who="S0161">that's right yes and it's a <unclear/> apparently that building which I didn't know although I should have guessed looking at it <pause dur="short"/> now I think what I would do the other thing I would do is put enough money on one side to be able to do a post grad course in creative writing</u>
<u n="170" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> same I'd go yeah I'd go back to uni <pause dur="short"/> definitely <pause dur="short"/> do a master's in</u>
<u n="171" who="S0161">what would you do?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0072">yeah politics <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what <pause dur="short"/> not sure what but something to do with <pause dur="short"/> cos my undergrad was in politics</u>
<u n="173" who="S0161">right I see</u>
<u n="174" who="S0072">em yeah definitely</u>
<u n="175" who="S0161">yeah oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> and places I would have to go <pause dur="short"/> definitely Moscow and St Petersburg <pause dur="short"/> definitely Cairo for the pyramids <pause dur="short"/> and definitely Madrid for the Plada <pause dur="short"/> and probably Paris as well <pause dur="short"/> but em and I of and the other place Easter Island cos I love <trunc>eas</trunc> I love Easter Island heads <pause dur="short"/> they're my favourite statues <pause dur="short"/> ever since I saw and utterly brilliant cartoon <pause dur="short"/> little little carton in one of the I the student rad rad mag <pause dur="short"/> at Glasgow</u>
<u n="176" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0161">and it was a there's this Easter Island paper just in profile <pause dur="short"/> and then an Indian comes up bends down puts a bunch of flowers in front of the Easter Island head and the next picture it's got a smile on its face <pause dur="short"/> and I've been a fan of  Easter Island  Easter Island heads ever since so just <pause dur="short"/> I like the way some of them have got hats some of them have got no hats and nobody's got a flaming clue how they got there <pause dur="short"/> and the other thing I'd do I think I would em I'd ask nicely if I could go and join Time Team for at least one programme <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm an archaeology nut</u>
<u n="178" who="S0072">why not a series <pause dur="short"/> it would be too much work</u>
<u n="179" who="S0161">no I wouldn't mind that actually <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm married with two children you know <pause dur="short"/> work's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> but em <pause dur="short"/> I think I'd like I want to steal Phil Harding's hats or one of Phil Harding's hats and possibly Nick Aston's jumper <pause dur="short"/> but I just  I just  love it <pause dur="short"/> I'm eh you know and in fact one of them down at em AHA <unclear/> I stuck my head round Prof <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s door and said do they ever take volunteers on the digs <pause dur="short"/> and he was actually quite you know this was obviously quite <unclear/> with this <pause dur="short"/> who is they mad person want to go and dig for? Because he</u>
<u n="180" who="S0072">they're em they're doing a dig in Hume at the moment where em</u>
<u n="181" who="S0161">so I believe</u>
<u n="182" who="S0072">on Stretford and Berley fields</u>
<u n="183" who="S0161">right? What did they find?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0072">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> they it's part of MM they <unclear/> in Didsbury and moving it to Hume</u>
<u n="185" who="S0161">yes yes yes yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0072">em so they've just <pause dur="short"/> I can see that there is something there <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a road or the remains of a building or something <pause dur="short"/> that they dug up</u>
<u n="187" who="S0161">well given that Manchester was a Roman was was a Roman settlement wasn't it? Because they must obviously have had a camp here <pause dur="short"/> hence hence the Chester castra yes <pause dur="short"/> cool what aren't there bits of down at Castlefield?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0072">yes <pause dur="short"/> there's the Roman <unclear/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0161">yeah so the chances are if you went to the outlayer and Chester was a a Roman camp as well <pause dur="short"/> you might have had a connecting link as well <pause dur="short"/> hey how Time Team can come back and look for a row between <trunc>Chest</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but no I was em did you? There was one last week <pause dur="short"/> and em Tony Robinson was telling Phil Harding off for coming on in a ripped shirt <pause dur="short"/> and Phil Harding said it's clean what's the problem <pause dur="short"/> which one? Nick Aston rolls up and Phil Harding is complaining to him about the fact Tony Robinson is grumbling about this eh this ripped shirt <pause dur="short"/> nick Aston says well he say  he says  when it's ripped beyond use he said you cut the buttons off and use it for something else <pause dur="short"/> at which point Tony Robinson went and walked away</u>
<u n="190" who="S0072">sustainable</u>
<u n="191" who="S0161">absolutely sustainable <pause dur="short"/> yes yes</u>
<u n="192" who="S0072">reuse recycle</u>
<u n="193" who="S0161">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and there was the did you see the <unclear/> one program where they would they'd made them cocktails for some reason <pause dur="short"/> and Phil Harding took one mouthful and these faces quite clearly said can somebody get me a proper drink <pause dur="short"/> the man seems to like his beer <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> you'd open a bar you'd go round America and anything else?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> travel <pause dur="short"/> I'd always travel</u>
<u n="195" who="S0161">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0072">I think the danger with having a big win like that is that you'd get bored</u>
<u n="197" who="S0161">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0072">unless <pause dur="short"/> bored of travelling <pause dur="short"/> but if you didn't do anything</u>
<u n="199" who="S0161">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0072">just bought a big house and</u>
<u n="201" who="S0161">I couldn't be doing with that</u>
<u n="202" who="S0072">I just couldn't imagine what would you <trunc>con</trunc> what would you concern yourself with? What would your day be filled on</u>
<u n="203" who="S0161">yes exactly exactly <pause dur="short"/> I think that that's why I said I I think I would give a pretty high percentage of it away</u>
<u n="204" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0161">you know <trunc>se</trunc> <trunc>se</trunc> have it  have it go and  have it go and do something useful for other people</u>
<u n="206" who="S0072">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> partly I think probably cos that's the way I was brought up</u>
<u n="207" who="S0161">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0072">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> people must get so bored <pause dur="short"/> when they win I they don't do anything win a huge amount</u>
<u n="209" who="S0161">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0072">em and I remember that <trunc>wo</trunc> the woman in Ireland she has to have security twenty-four seven following her and her children round just cos obviously people around her know where she lives because she lived em</u>
<u n="211" who="S0161">yes yes <pause dur="short"/> oh no I mean <pause dur="short"/> I'd get rid of it</u>
<u n="212" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I definitely wouldn't go public</u>
<u n="213" who="S0161">I I would I I would  I would  get rid of it and then there's no reason for anybody to come pursue in you because you can't give them anything</u>
<u n="214" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's programme on at the moment on BBC One called The Syndicate <pause dur="short"/> which is a drama about eh a syndicate of people</u>
<u n="215" who="S0161">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> and and the whole thing seems the whole lives the inference was that their whole lives all apart</u>
<u n="216" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0161">well if you em there was that amazing documentary well drama doc docu drama form eh about Vivienne Nicholson</u>
<u n="218" who="S0072">right</u>
<u n="219" who="S0161">who was the first <pause dur="short"/> and they called it spend spend spend</u>
<u n="220" who="S0072">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0161">and she just got rid of the whole lot <pause dur="short"/> juts just blew it and <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0072">there's a sixteen year old girl from Workington that won the lottery <pause dur="short"/> she she spent it all <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well he eh</u>
<u n="223" who="S0161">oh that's right <pause dur="short"/> I remember him</u>
<u n="224" who="S0072">he spent it all as well</u>
<u n="225" who="S0161">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0072">em but sixteen and winning that much money</u>
<u n="227" who="S0161">well unless you've got very sensible parents how the hell are you going to know what to do with it <pause dur="short"/><unclear/> I think also the thing is if you've got other people to spend to spend it on as I have <pause dur="short"/> you know two kids a horse <pause dur="short"/> em and I think I'd probably spend the money to to get our own house really which <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is going to do anyway but if we've got other people to do it for us we could probably do it a bit faster <pause dur="short"/> which would be good but no <pause dur="short"/> I I suspect that having lot of money is is more responsibility than anything else and it's not one I think I I would do my utmost to get  to get  rid of it you know</u>
<u n="228" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's all relative isn't it? You'd soon get used to</u>
<u n="229" who="S0161">yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0072">what originally you thought was amazing just become boring after</u>
<u n="231" who="S0161">which I I think is probably what would <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> in fact we were talking about it this morning <pause dur="short"/> we all said we reckoned say quarter a million or half a million would probably do us  do us  quite nicely <pause dur="short"/> cos I think you could do most of what you wanted to do seriously</u>
<u n="232" who="S0072">definitely</u>
<u n="233" who="S0161">and then just have a bit of and incentive <pause dur="short"/> I certainly wouldn't stop working</u>
<u n="234" who="S0072">no</u>
<u n="235" who="S0161">I'd get bored</u>
<u n="236" who="S0072">I'd get bored</u>
<u n="237" who="S0161">and also probably kill my husband <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether you'd kill your partner but I would definite kill my husband</u>
<u n="238" who="S0072">probably</u>
<u n="239" who="S0161">which is one of the reasons why I've gone on working cos I love him to death but twenty-four hours a day <pause dur="short"/> oh no</u>
<u n="240" who="S0072">I think my dad's worried about that when he retires in June about he <pause dur="short"/> he does he's a Yoga teacher as well</u>
<u n="241" who="S0161">right</u>
<u n="242" who="S0072">he started yoga about five years ago and he teaches teaches science and maths and he went on a yoga teaching course <pause dur="short"/> he does that now <pause dur="short"/> two evenings a week</u>
<u n="243" who="S0161">he can do that when he goes over there</u>
<u n="244" who="S0072">yeah I think when he goes over there he's just going to</u>
<u n="245" who="S0161">I think the expats will probably bite his hand off</u>
<u n="246" who="S0072">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do it <pause dur="short"/> a few days a week <pause dur="short"/> cos it cos it's a bit strange to retire and then</u>
<u n="247" who="S0161">well I reckon  I reckon  <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> reckons he doesn't know I am how he had time to go work <pause dur="short"/> I remember my dad saying that <pause dur="short"/> but you know I'm I'm regularly a beer widow</u>
<u n="248" who="S0072">right</u>
<u n="249" who="S0161">because they they saw big <unclear/> in <trunc>to</trunc> recognised a good organising talent when they saw one <pause dur="short"/> so he is now quiet heavily involved in organising the <anon type="place"/> beer festival <pause dur="short"/> so we don't go anywhere at the end of May beginning of June <pause dur="short"/> cos my husband is running the beer festival</u>
<u n="250" who="S0072">how big is  How big is  it?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0161">it's quite big <pause dur="short"/> they use <anon type="place"/> County's ground <pause dur="short"/> and you know the the runway underneath <pause dur="short"/> they've put it down there which means it's absolutely like a furnace <pause dur="short"/> it really is <pause dur="short"/> do you need to deal with that bod</u>
<u n="252" who="S0072">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> can do</u>
</body>
</text>
