<text id="SZME">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:50:22</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Campervan journey from Białka Tatrzańska to Tarnow, Poland – part 3.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Eating before the gym, driving, time, gym (again), being English, gender issues, sexism, silence.</topics>
		<activity>Two friends talking about various topics (see 9 above) while driving in a campervan from Tarnow to Białka Tatrzańska, Poland – part 3.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0618">so we're back in the room here we are right</u>
<u n="2" who="S0619">I've eaten too much and I've got to eat again</u>
<u n="3" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="4" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0619">in an hour</u>
<u n="6" who="S0618" trans="overlap">you'll manage you'll manage <pause dur="short"/> yeah it will be in an hour and your metabolism'll still be racing away after your</u>
<u n="7" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah I hope so hope so hope so</u>
<u n="8" who="S0618">strenuous gym session today</u>
<u n="9" who="S0619">it was awful it was really bad and I hadn't eaten enough breakfast and er I felt it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0618">mm that's not so good</u>
<u n="11" who="S0619">but he's nice he said it was okay he high-fived me</u>
<u n="12" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it is difficult though isn't if you're gonna have a workout I'm remembering this from dim and distant memory</u>
<u n="13" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0618">but if you're gonna have a workout and you haven't eaten enough but you know that before you go so you want to eat but then you end up wanting to boke while you're exercising</u>
<u n="15" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so it's you know er trying to eat erm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0618">it's getting the balance isn't it?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0619" trans="overlap">eat enough but leaving enough time for you to start digesting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0618">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0619">erm and in the mornings</u>
<u n="20" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0619">it's not so easy to get the timings right</u>
<u n="22" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh my worst one one time I quite often used to have a smoothie or a shake or whatever before I went to the gym and and I I only needed to <trunc>ha</trunc>have it forty minutes before or something that was fine I was extra starving one day so I thought I know what I'll do I'll put some oats in with it</u>
<u n="23" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0618">so I mixed up some oats in my smoothie and oh my god I nearly threw up quite a few times it was really hard going</u>
<u n="25" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0618">so never have an oaty smoothie before gym time</u>
<u n="27" who="S0619">yeah it's good for after</u>
<u n="28" who="S0618">yeah right clear left</u>
<u n="29" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh go go go go bloody hell yes</u>
<u n="30" who="S0618" trans="overlap">come on then</u>
<u n="31" who="S0619">well done road fairies</u>
<u n="32" who="S0618" trans="overlap">thank you traffic pixie <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0618">yay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0619">road fairies <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0618">road fairies and traffic pixies I love it</u>
<u n="37" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0619">I was like <unclear/> had a <trunc>s</trunc> has a saying but I can't remember what it is</u>
<u n="39" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0618">well road</u>
<u n="41" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> road fairy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0618">road fairies is pretty cool I like that</u>
<u n="43" who="S0619">er yes</u>
<u n="44" who="S0618"><unclear/> seems this traffic seems to be a little bit stop start actually and I wonder is it with the hairpin bends and stuff that we might be encountering?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0618">there might be some slippery bits or skiddy bits or bits where lorries need to go a bit slower</u>
<u n="47" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I don't know if it is or if it is just er oh I don't know</u>
<u n="48" who="S0618">well there's one just back there which I imagine is every time someone pulls in or out of the car park</u>
<u n="49" who="S0619">yeah possibly</u>
<u n="50" who="S0618">as we've just done that's bound to hold traffic up a little bit cos it only takes one car to brake and come to a stop to let somebody in and</u>
<u n="51" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah or <unclear>try and</unclear> turn left</u>
<u n="52" who="S0618"><trunc>y</trunc> uhu and then there's a massive queue behind so</u>
<u n="53" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0618">anyway erm Simon says we'll be there at ten to three so another forty minutes</u>
<u n="55" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh okay okay okay</u>
<u n="56" who="S0618">and thirty-eight kilometres thirty minutes well we're not really doing <vocal desc="laugh"/> a kilometre a minute at the moment Simon so actually it's gonna be gone three have you got your Polish phone handy? would you text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0618">to let her know</u>
<u n="59" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0618">I guess five past three <pause dur="short"/> maybe just say traffic's slow</u>
<u n="61" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0618">I did text her from erm the restaurant to say that we'd be there I think we said ten I said ten to three something like that I'm just thinking just so they're not rushing to get off the piste and get changed to meet us</u>
<u n="63" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0618">probably get a another an extra ski run in or something</u>
<u n="65" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> what am I typing? erm hi in traffic <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh well there are worse places to be in traffic it is rather pretty <pause dur="short"/> at least it's moving the other way so <pause dur="long"/> hang on let me pause this conversation <vocal desc="laugh"/> while you're doing that cos no one's saying anything</u>
<u n="67" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> because <unclear/> I've sent it now I've sent it</u>
<u n="68" who="S0618">oh okay</u>
<u n="69" who="S0619">sorry</u>
<u n="70" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0618">that's alright</u>
<u n="72" who="S0619">er you know I'm so used to it now that I've forgotten that it's there</u>
<u n="73" who="S0618">I know</u>
<u n="74" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I feel like I don't need to talk because it's I just forget about it</u>
<u n="75" who="S0618">yeah pros and cons you know it's it's we're probably getting much more natural conversation cos we forget it's there</u>
<u n="76" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="77" who="S0618">but at the same time</u>
<u n="78" who="S0619">yeah <unclear/> voice</u>
<u n="79" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just fast forward this bit yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0619">sorry I'm just thinking</u>
<u n="82" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0619">what an interesting car what make is that?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0618">that is a Chrysler I do believe but I'm not sure I've heard of the <unclear/> before now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no I've not</u>
<u n="86" who="S0618">it's a Polish thing</u>
<u n="87" who="S0619">it's an interesting car to have</u>
<u n="88" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm I think it's Chrysler anyway a similar logo if not</u>
<u n="89" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0618">that's an American make I think</u>
<u n="91" who="S0619">big car big wheels</u>
<u n="92" who="S0618">not that big</u>
<u n="93" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0618">what have you been driving?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0619">er Toyota Yaris <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> say no more</u>
<u n="97" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="99" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0619">but I haven't driven for five years six years</u>
<u n="101" who="S0618">oh my god you need to do that thing</u>
<u n="102" who="S0619">er</u>
<u n="103" who="S0618">do you not do it when you go on holiday? hire a car?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="105" who="S0618"><unclear/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0619">don't do it when I go to England erm should but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I'd have to have driving lessons again I've got such bad anxiety now about driving myself</u>
<u n="107" who="S0618" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0619">and this is exactly what my mum did she learned to drive when she was in her twenties and then didn't drive until she was forty something</u>
<u n="109" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0619">and she had to have lessons</u>
<u n="111" who="S0618">same with my dad</u>
<u n="112" who="S0619">and I imagine that's what's gonna happen to me er it doesn't help that I'm never in the country erm or never you know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0619">er I mean I wouldn't wanna drive abroad anyway</u>
<u n="115" who="S0618">so actually you could just forget about that now forget about the anxiety and just say</u>
<u n="116" who="S0619">start again</u>
<u n="117" who="S0618">I am not a driver <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0619">yes I can't drive <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and then if at some point where your life situation circumstances make you think oh I'd like to drive again</u>
<u n="120" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0618">get some lessons then <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0619">it was you know I really wanted to do it last summer</u>
<u n="123" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0619">but I just simply wasn't</u>
<u n="125" who="S0618">what? to drive to go places?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0619" trans="overlap">or just to sort of drive myself around the town</u>
<u n="129" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0619">see my friends or whatever erm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I've gotta say Poland isn't easy</u>
<u n="132" who="S0619">no yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0618">erm it is if you think erm if you kind of get in your head nobody's thinking anything about me nobody's judging me and once you get that in your head you're fine you can get on and drive but but there is like I was saying to you before you expect it on motorways you pull out to overtake at the last possible minute and you get in again at the <trunc>l</trunc></u>
<u n="134" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0618">at the <trunc>s</trunc> the first available opportunity so you're kind of cutting vehicles up as you're pulling in and you're almost sometimes pulling out in front of people <trunc>b</trunc>but that is expected</u>
<u n="136" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0618">so you know I kind of feel sometimes I'm driving like a dickhead but that's</u>
<u n="138" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it's normal</u>
<u n="139" who="S0618">it's expected that's the culture that's the custom so really in just being in Rome and doing as the Romans do but it is pretty anxiety-inducing sometimes</u>
<u n="140" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0618">so no probably not the best country</u>
<u n="142" who="S0619">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I don't think the Spanish are much better are they? <unclear/> little crazy drive a little fast</u>
<u n="144" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I wouldn't yeah I wouldn't drive abroad erm anywhere er but I really want to</u>
<u n="145" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I recommend Ireland Ireland's really chilled</u>
<u n="146" who="S0619">yeah I <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="147" who="S0618" trans="overlap">north and south</u>
<u n="148" who="S0619">really just need to start driving in England <vocal desc="laugh"/> but you know last summer when I was at home I was like right this is the year</u>
<u n="149" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0619">and I just wasn't there enough to</u>
<u n="151" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0619">warrant getting lessons or paying for insurance</u>
<u n="153" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0619"><unclear>it's been a little while</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and there's not much point if you're gonna leave the country again</u>
<u n="156" who="S0619">yeah exactly so but I really wanted to do it just for me more than anything else <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0619">but was not to be</u>
<u n="159" who="S0618">it will come back it's a bit like the skiing there's a big degree of muscle memory I think er</u>
<u n="160" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0618">once you start making your body perform those manoeuvres as it were it erm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="163" who="S0618">becomes unconscious again pretty quickly</u>
<u n="164" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0618"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0619">I was saying that to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> this morning</u>
<u n="167" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0619"><unclear>with some of the</unclear> things I just need to learn how to <trunc>d</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> how to do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0619">or my body needs to understand what it's supposed to do</u>
<u n="171" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> and it's not that something's particularly heavy or particularly difficult it's just I'm not used to doing it so</u>
<u n="173" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah it feels a little alien to your body perhaps</u>
<u n="174" who="S0619">mm yeah I just need some practice</u>
<u n="175" who="S0618"><unclear/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0618">hang on a minute this looks like my <anon type="place"/> turn off</u>
<u n="178" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="179" who="S0618">this looks like the junction where I would normally turn right</u>
<u n="180" who="S0619">ah so you've been here before</u>
<u n="181" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm erm isn't it funny? I don't remember ever seeing that restaurant we've just been to</u>
<u n="182" who="S0619">ah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0618">probably because it's not</u>
<u n="184" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it's <unclear/> I guess</u>
<u n="185" who="S0618">in my <unclear>sort of</unclear> expectations or anything</u>
<u n="186" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0618">this is really pretty oh light's green now I was gonna take a <trunc>m</trunc> photograph out of my window</u>
<u n="188" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I thought there would be traffic lights <unclear/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0618" trans="overlap">see Father Christmas there?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0619">oh bless</u>
<u n="191" who="S0618">oh erm my neighbours in <anon type="place"/> had one of those and when I first moved there it was just so lovely cos you'd look out of the the bedroom window or the front window and there's just this Father Christmas blowing out in the gales</u>
<u n="192" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0618">waving at you it's just really nice and they had a wooden Rudolph and his sleigh as well that was about ten feet from left to right and er yeah that was all lit up it was really nice</u>
<u n="194" who="S0619">right now we're through those lights we might</u>
<u n="195" who="S0618" trans="overlap">which is why we have <unclear/> before</u>
<u n="196" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah we might cos it was so sort of consistently stopping and starting wasn't it?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0619">erm claw back some time</u>
<u n="199" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're hilarious</u>
<u n="200" who="S0619">I'm just obsessed</u>
<u n="201" who="S0618" trans="overlap">your obsession with time it doesn't exist there's nothing to claw back</u>
<u n="202" who="S0619">no I know</u>
<u n="203" who="S0618">ah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0619">I can't help it <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0618">I'm kind of at the stage in life now as well where if I'm running late and I say to someone oh I'm sorry running late if I think I'm gonna be there at five past I'll message and say oh I'll see you about quarter past and then I just really relax and don't drive like a dickhead</u>
<u n="206" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0618">and the person the other end isn't anxiously looking out of the window or whatever if people do that sort of thing I don't know</u>
<u n="208" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0618">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah and it and I kind of think well late is late so whether it's five minutes or fifteen minutes it's still late so</u>
<u n="210" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0618">you might as well just be late in a relaxed kind of a way</u>
<u n="212" who="S0619">I can't er I hate being late <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0618">but would you rather</u>
<u n="214" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I'd rather</u>
<u n="215" who="S0618">rush around like an idiot and get there at five past or three minutes past and still be late</u>
<u n="216" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0618">but be all anxious and stressed?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0619">it depends who er or what I'm doing</u>
<u n="219" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0619">what who I'm meeting I suppose but you know in the mornings I hate rushing</u>
<u n="221" who="S0618">yeah me too</u>
<u n="222" who="S0619">er and in the mornings before work I would much rather wake up at I don't know six fifteen to start work at eight fifteen</u>
<u n="223" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0619">and just really casually have a shower</u>
<u n="225" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0619">eat something</u>
<u n="227" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0619">and do a bit of preparation er</u>
<u n="229" who="S0618">drink tea</u>
<u n="230" who="S0619">drink tea maybe watch something or listen to something</u>
<u n="231" who="S0618" trans="overlap">read a book yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0619">er rather than</u>
<u n="233" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0619" trans="overlap">see this is me waking up at six fifteen and doing whatever</u>
<u n="235" who="S0618">last minute clean teeth wash dress out</u>
<u n="236" who="S0619" trans="overlap">whereas <pause dur="short"/> yeah whereas <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if we <trunc>s</trunc> he <trunc>w</trunc> he was starting at eight he wouldn't leave his bedroom until sort of twenty-five to</u>
<u n="237" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0619">er er er have a shower</u>
<u n="239" who="S0618">and he's still got a ten minute walk? <vocal desc="laugh"/> wow</u>
<u n="240" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah have a shower get dressed</u>
<u n="241" who="S0618">that's impressive</u>
<u n="242" who="S0619">and go</u>
<u n="243" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0619">but I just can't not eat in the mornings <pause dur="short"/> still waking up hungry every morning</u>
<u n="245" who="S0618">you wow</u>
<u n="246" who="S0619">yeah so that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0618">that's good <pause dur="short"/> yeah I <trunc>m</trunc> think you're doing magnificently you really seem to be feeling on a buzz and</u>
<u n="248" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0618">what?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0619">that's where we're going oh no it's not</u>
<u n="251" who="S0618">where are we going?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0619">there's a swimming pool there</u>
<u n="253" who="S0618">oh <unclear/> go there then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> looks like a nice hotel <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0618">oh shit I forgot my swimming goggles ah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I <trunc>g</trunc> I've not got any here I couldn't find any when I was leaving England</u>
<u n="257" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh well</u>
<u n="258" who="S0619">never mind</u>
<u n="259" who="S0618">oh what's the limit here? I'm just going extra slow cos of that speed camera <vocal desc="laugh"/> everyone else going extra slow okay erm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0618">yeah no I have got some here</u>
<u n="262" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0618">but actually no I don't really like swimming that much I used to go <pause dur="short"/> I used to go a lot it's funny in different phases that you have in life when my partner was really sick with cancer and I was still going to work every day rather than come home faff about and go to the gym of an evening</u>
<u n="264" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0618">I used to bunk off work quite a bit actually I used to say I'm going to this shop in this part of the country and maybe I would go but maybe I'd leave an hour before I was really meant to or they thought I was</u>
<u n="266" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0618">and then I'd go to the gym in <anon type="place"/> on the way home and go for a swim erm <vocal desc="sigh"/> or go and run cos I was running at that point before my knees completely gave up</u>
<u n="268" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0618">and <pause dur="short"/> yeah I found it really necessary to have that time and that space and when <trunc>m</trunc> I was in England with my mum and her cancer and going between her flat and the hospice a lot I was forever getting Groupon deals for local gyms to go and run</u>
<u n="270" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0618">and it just seemed so necessary to have that outlet for myself and that time <pause dur="short"/> that was selfish time</u>
<u n="272" who="S0619">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0618" trans="overlap">for me and nobody else</u>
<u n="274" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="275" who="S0618">really really necessary</u>
<u n="276" who="S0619">and you know it's so good for you too</u>
<u n="277" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's all them dolphins innit?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0619">endorphins and I know people sort of say oh it's so cathartic it's therapeutic you know you get out all of your anger and stress and you think well I don't really know if I agree with that but</u>
<u n="281" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0619">I agree with you're doing something on a regular basis in which you are trying to improve you know</u>
<u n="283" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0619">and over time you will because that's how that's how <trunc>h</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> the the human body works</u>
<u n="285" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0619" trans="overlap">you know you'll be able to go faster or lift something else up and that is I think good for your mind</u>
<u n="287" who="S0618">yeah that's interesting</u>
<u n="288" who="S0619" trans="overlap">setting goals and meeting them</u>
<u n="289" who="S0618">I don't do that</u>
<u n="290" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0619">yeah well that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0618" trans="overlap">different personality type I suppose</u>
<u n="294" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah that's how I sort of er see it I don't really like <pause dur="short"/> erm competition necessarily with other people cos I'm not very good <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I <trunc>w</trunc> don't usually win anything</u>
<u n="295" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0619">but with myself I'm excellent</u>
<u n="297" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0618">no I just like to go because it feels good</u>
<u n="300" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0618">and I like I used to get to that point with running where I felt I could run forever</u>
<u n="302" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0618">and it just felt so good</u>
<u n="304" who="S0619" trans="overlap">what sort of distances?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0618">I used to only do I used to do five K</u>
<u n="306" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0618">so three miles in about thirty-eight minutes</u>
<u n="308" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0618">or forty minutes</u>
<u n="310" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0618">erm which is incredibly slow but I didn't care <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0619">yeah if you like <unclear>it then</unclear></u>
<u n="313" who="S0618">yeah I <trunc>th</trunc> I think <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh shit I thought I was gonna stall then erm yeah I think I'm just generally a slow laid-back take it easy kind of a person</u>
<u n="314" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0618">and even in my movement and my doeyness I'm it's very unusual I just don't get <vocal desc="misc"/> that</u>
<u n="316" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0618">rush that some people get with their exercise oh what's for sale here? it looks like my fire extinguisher man <pause dur="short"/> oh no it's socks</u>
<u n="318" who="S0619">oh it's regional socks and cheese</u>
<u n="319" who="S0618"><trunc>s</trunc> oh and where's the cheese?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0619">in that little cabin</u>
<u n="321" who="S0618">oh cool <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0619">socks and cheese</u>
<u n="323" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0619">a winning combination gets a lot of passing trade</u>
<u n="325" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah what more do you need? yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0618">so yeah I just it's all I don't get that <vocal desc="misc"/> with a workout I I get a buzz and I get high from it but in a still in a chilled out kind of a way</u>
<u n="328" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0618">just in a <trunc>f</trunc> almost a floaty kind of a way yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah spin classes I love spin bike classes</u>
<u n="330" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0618">but <pause dur="short"/> I mean in my arse end of nowhere gym there were two types of instructor it's usually the young men erm who <pause dur="short"/> every track whether it's a hill track or a sprint track is bloody fast</u>
<u n="332" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0618">and it was always a faster faster faster and I used to think fuck off fuck off fuck off</u>
<u n="334" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0618">I'll go at my own speed and I used to get a bit stubborn then and</u>
<u n="336" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0618">go really slow and not enjoy it and then it was usually women erm not always older women but often older women running the spin classes that lull you into a false sense of security with making sure you warm through properly at the beginning you might have a running track erm rather than sprint</u>
<u n="338" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0618">and you just kind of warm into it gradually and within about twenty minutes I'd be working incredibly hard and I'd be knackered <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0618"><unclear>and I'd think</unclear> how did you get me to do that? <vocal desc="laugh"/> without you know screaming and shouting and doing all of that</u>
<u n="342" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0619">with spinning</u>
<u n="345" who="S0618">business</u>
<u n="346" who="S0619">I used to sort of I used to go spinning erm when I was at uni and I'd look at the clock and it'd be like quarter past I'd be like fuck I've got to do this for another thirty minutes? I'm gonna die <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0619">I'm not gonna make it <vocal desc="laugh"/> and we yeah when I used to go to the gym and do erm you know all these conditioning classes or whatever</u>
<u n="349" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0619">and there was this trainer called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this was in <anon type="place"/> last year and she was brutal <pause dur="short"/> she was the fittest strongest woman I've ever seen</u>
<u n="351" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0619">you know <trunc>l</trunc> huge muscles and really kind of great body erm and I've spoken to her about her body once and she said that she hated it and she hated that she she always wanted to wear a jacket or cover her arms or</u>
<u n="353" who="S0618">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="354" who="S0619">er and people</u>
<u n="355" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0619">stared at her</u>
<u n="357" who="S0618">well they probably do in Poland</u>
<u n="358" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0618">maybe less so in England</u>
<u n="360" who="S0619" trans="overlap">cos it's just a different type of body</u>
<u n="361" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0619">cos people are so slim erm <pause dur="short"/> but no good for her it's like well I'd do anything to sort of well I am doing some things to get that sort of body</u>
<u n="363" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> I want to ideally I want to look like someone who could beat you up in a fight</u>
<u n="365" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0619">I'll never be able to beat anyone up in a fight I'd be crap but if I looked oh I'm not gonna mess with her she looked like she</u>
<u n="367" who="S0618" trans="overlap">you strike me more a lover than a fighter</u>
<u n="368" who="S0619">I am absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0619">but I really want to give the impression of</u>
<u n="371" who="S0618">why?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0619">I just think that's the sort of ideal body that I want someone who's you know sort of not tough looking</u>
<u n="373" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> who could potentially get violent</u>
<u n="374" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0619">no that's not I'm not really phrasing this very well</u>
<u n="376" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0619"><unclear/> just to look fit and to look strong erm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I understand that yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and a body that looks like it can handle you know handle itself or handle</u>
<u n="380" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the rigours of life</u>
<u n="381" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> handle</u>
<u n="382" who="S0618">the rigours of teaching English as a foreign language</u>
<u n="383" who="S0619"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0618">ah dear yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0619">I think that's rather a male thing that men wouldn't actually sort of articulate which is you know you're looking you wanna look big so no one messes with you</u>
<u n="389" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0619" trans="overlap">er but I don't think</u>
<u n="391" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0619">I'm really saying that <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="393" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear>you call them</unclear> meatheads <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0619">I wanna be a meathead <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0618">you want to be a meathead</u>
<u n="396" who="S0619">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm so bored of men in the gym and he was like I am a man in the gym</u>
<u n="397" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0619">I was like I know but</u>
<u n="399" who="S0618">yeah used to get a lot of those at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0619" trans="overlap">hate them</u>
<u n="401" who="S0618">the I know the type that you mean <vocal desc="laugh"/> look like they're possibly not so articulate <vocal desc="laugh"/> is probably</u>
<u n="402" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0619">that's very kind</u>
<u n="404" who="S0618">I know possibly a fair bit of grunting <vocal desc="laugh"/> going on</u>
<u n="405" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="407" who="S0619">mm and they're just in the way</u>
<u n="408" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0619"><unclear>you know</unclear> have got no manners it's really funny in gyms here a man'll come in and before he does anything he goes round to every other man in the gym and shakes their hand</u>
<u n="410" who="S0618">yeah?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0618">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="413" who="S0619">it's not you know before it before he can start</u>
<u n="414" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="415" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so sometimes they do like a full loop you know before they begin properly whereas with girls they just ignore them they don't even look at me it's like I don't exist er</u>
<u n="416" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I'm just tempted to join your gym just so I can come and shake your hand <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> in</u>
<u n="418" who="S0618">yo sister <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0619">in <anon type="place"/> I got so sick of it I'd always just be like <trunc>sh</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> shall I stick my hand out? when someone was coming past</u>
<u n="420" who="S0618" trans="overlap">did you? <pause dur="short"/> and make them shake your hand</u>
<u n="421" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and see if they'd shake it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0618">did they?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0619"><trunc>th</trunc>they er look like alarmed</u>
<u n="426" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0619">no they'd shake it erm so just</u>
<u n="428" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so were there other women in the gym at the time?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0619">no usually not no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0618">oh okay</u>
<u n="431" who="S0619">I once went to the gym on the Saturday before Easter Sunday</u>
<u n="432" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0619">and I was there for er I don't know ninety minutes and not another single woman was there cos they were all I don't know cooking and cleaning in preparation for Easter Sunday</u>
<u n="434" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0619">and it was packed I think they'd the women had sent men</u>
<u n="436" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0619">and it was like men and their sons as well</u>
<u n="438" who="S0618">oh wow</u>
<u n="439" who="S0619">er to the gym just to get them out of the house and obviously I wasn't gonna be cooking and preparing a family meal so I was there</u>
<u n="440" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0619"><unclear>really felt</unclear> <unclear/> stand out <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> yes it really annoys me why don't you say hello to me in the gym? only one man does</u>
<u n="442" who="S0618">yeah?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0619">only one man says hello to me in this gym yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0618">is it cos you're a foreigner?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0619">they don't know I'm a foreigner</u>
<u n="446" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="447" who="S0619">I suppose more cos I wouldn't <trunc>nev</trunc> I'd say hi but erm they wouldn't</u>
<u n="448" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0619">know necessarily but now that I've got this trainer and we're talking in English I think more people are clocking on or not caring at all</u>
<u n="450" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh one point two degrees <anon type="place"/> is seventy-four minutes well we're not going that far</u>
<u n="451" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="452" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> thirty minutes we are going that far</u>
<u n="453" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="454" who="S0618">and then we're branching off</u>
<u n="455" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so what time did we leave? it was about twenty past eleven wasn't it? and then we <unclear/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it was half eleven at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0618" trans="overlap">was it half eleven?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0619"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s house yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0618">and we stopped for about forty minutes</u>
<u n="461" who="S0619">did we? <pause dur="short"/> well it was</u>
<u n="462" who="S0618">or half an hour</u>
<u n="463" who="S0619">worth it for the er for the fire</u>
<u n="464" who="S0618">ah the fire was great yeah I don't think I've ever been in a public toilet where my piss is steamed cos it's so cold</u>
<u n="465" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it was bloody cold in those toilets</u>
<u n="467" who="S0618" trans="overlap">that was pretty impressive</u>
<u n="468" who="S0619">I sat down and thought</u>
<u n="469" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="470" who="S0619">oh my god er this seat's wet but it was just really cold</u>
<u n="471" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> my bum was gonna get frozen to the seat</u>
<u n="472" who="S0619" trans="overlap">peel off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0618">I was grateful it wasn't a metal seat</u>
<u n="474" who="S0619" trans="overlap">leave half of your bum <unclear/> seat</u>
<u n="475" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0619">your insides flop out down the toilet</u>
<u n="478" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0618">oops</u>
<u n="480" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0618">maybe that's why there are so many plastic toilet seats here</u>
<u n="484" who="S0619">I've not seen a metal toilet seat I don't think in my whole life</u>
<u n="485" who="S0618">oh I have in Northern Ireland but they're the sort of</u>
<u n="486" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0618">metal where it's not really a seat it's just metal <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> in really sort of shitty public toilets so you</u>
<u n="489" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0619">make yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0618">so want to take a guess as to what the speed limit might be? I just haven't a clue</u>
<u n="492" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="493" who="S0618">there's a picture of silhouetted buildings with a cross through it</u>
<u n="494" who="S0619">so maybe it's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so it's either seventy or ninety <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I think it's seventy or ninety I'll do seventy <pause dur="short"/> where'd all the traffic go?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0619">I don't know it's rather suspicious isn't it?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0618">that's weird <pause dur="short"/> but this is gorgeous I like this it's so pretty</u>
<u n="498" who="S0619">yeah it looks a little bit brighter here doesn't it?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I just suppose it's cos of all of the snow as much as anything <pause dur="short"/> oh sixty thank you</u>
<u n="500" who="S0619">was a good guess</u>
<u n="501" who="S0618">no that's just for round the bend I think</u>
<u n="502" who="S0619"><vocal desc="cough"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> do do do do <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh have we gotta turn left up here? what's erm Simon saying? oh</u>
<u n="504" who="S0619">no no it's just saying follow the bend</u>
<u n="505" who="S0618" trans="overlap">go round the bend</u>
<u n="506" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="507" who="S0618">and then another seventeen K before we think about doing anything</u>
<u n="508" who="S0619"><vocal desc="cough"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yes so <pause dur="short"/> it's all coming together</u>
<u n="509" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0619">I just keep reading about my nose and what's happening now is the capillaries or whatever are really swollen <vocal desc="laugh"/> so that's why I'm so congested but hopefully <pause dur="short"/> soon soon soon soon</u>
<u n="511" who="S0618">can you build a picture in your mind as to what your nasal passages will look like in six months time when?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I'm not really sure what what nasal passages look like</u>
<u n="513" who="S0618" trans="overlap">or a week or whatever</u>
<u n="514" who="S0619">but if I just keep visualizing I don't know I think like a waterfall is what I'm thinking of and just like this sort of gushing water that is clearing everything out</u>
<u n="515" who="S0618">okay so that's what you're wanting in the interim then I can join you in this creative visualisation if you like?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just think about</u>
<u n="517" who="S0618">we'll just imagine your nose gushing but then</u>
<u n="518" who="S0619">no not actually <vocal desc="laugh"/> gushing but just this sort of clearing out</u>
<u n="519" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="520" who="S0619">it's very symbolic <vocal desc="laugh"/> in my life at the moment clearing out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0618" trans="overlap">like a sort of <unclear/> like a well exactly it is and <pause dur="short"/> I always say this</u>
<u n="522" who="S0619" trans="overlap">like nose like love life <vocal desc="laugh"/> clearing out</u>
<u n="523" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> is where things er always last manifest</u>
<u n="524" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0618">so yeah your nose will be perfectly clear when you've had a good clear out on the emotional and spiritual levels</u>
<u n="526" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="527" who="S0618">yeah and because it's to do with the breath erm and it comes back to lungs again it's lung chi and spleen chi</u>
<u n="528" who="S0619">what does the spleen do?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0618">I think that was all incorporated in the lung thing do you remember</u>
<u n="530" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0618">the photocopy or photograph <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0618">yeah it's cool so it's all about your boundaries <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="534" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="535" who="S0618">and the give and take in life so at the moment you've still got all of this in so if you're wanting to be visualising this streaming nose then that's getting everything out getting all of the toxic substances out</u>
<u n="536" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0618">the toxic emotions the toxic whatever so I imagine your nose will piss like Niagara Falls for a day or two and then it'll be clear as the Swiss Alps</u>
<u n="538" who="S0619" trans="overlap">air</u>
<u n="539" who="S0618">or something</u>
<u n="540" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0619">good good good</u>
<u n="543" who="S0618">yay <pause dur="short"/> oh we're getting high</u>
<u n="544" who="S0619">getting high getting more <unclear/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> er that's cos it's on there oh yes it was on <unclear/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0619"><vocal desc="cough"/> <shift new="singing"/> do do do do <shift new="normal"/> careful slippy</u>
<u n="547" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so <foreign lang="pol"/> what?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0619"><foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0618"><foreign lang="pol"/> is that?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0619">slippy</u>
<u n="551" who="S0618">slippiness okay</u>
<u n="552" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0618">so I still <vocal desc="laugh"/> still remember my mum <vocal desc="laugh"/> when I was a child driving in the car so highest gear possible use your gears to slow down gradually and not your brakes thanks mum steer into a skid</u>
<u n="554" who="S0619">steer into a skid yes</u>
<u n="555" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0619">good advice steer into a corner as well</u>
<u n="557" who="S0618">steer into a corner?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0618">what?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0619">I suppose if you're turning a corner you are steering</u>
<u n="561" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0619">I don't know what I'm saying</u>
<u n="563" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah no I know what you mean if you're going round a bend you decelerate</u>
<u n="564" who="S0619">yeah and so and speed out of a corner this corner <unclear/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and then yeah once you're passed the halfway point foot on the accelerator to power out</u>
<u n="566" who="S0619">what a strange place to wait for a bus I wonder where he came from?</u>
<u n="567" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0618">that's a good question there are no houses and a big hill <vocal desc="laugh"/> so where did he come from?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <unclear/> maybe he got sick and had to get off the last bus and now he's looking for the next one like</u>
<u n="570" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0619"><unclear>me</unclear> coming back from the airport <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0618">oh I saw that once there was erm no but I was in Australia and there was a guy on the opposite platform got out of a bus <vocal desc="laugh"/> no out sorry out of a train threw his guts up repeatedly erm and then was sort of waiting for the next train and obviously looked at it and thought oh better not carried on throwing up for a while and then eventually got on another train</u>
<u n="573" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="575" who="S0619">it's happened to me and I got on three buses <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0618">oh god</u>
<u n="577" who="S0619">and then I had to get off <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then waited twenty minutes for the next one</u>
<u n="578" who="S0618">oh jeez</u>
<u n="579" who="S0619">oh I was really sick</u>
<u n="580" who="S0618">that's bad</u>
<u n="581" who="S0619">we've had this conversation before</u>
<u n="582" who="S0618">oh yes that's right</u>
<u n="583" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0618">you were moving to Poland</u>
<u n="585" who="S0619">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0619">er but I've also done it when I was really hung-over and I was going from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> to go to the cinema er and I thought jesus I am gonna have to get off this bus otherwise I'm gonna die er on it</u>
<u n="588" who="S0618" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0619">and cover the person in front of me in sick</u>
<u n="590" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0619">but I really had to do mind over matter and lots of breathing</u>
<u n="592" who="S0618">wow well done</u>
<u n="593" who="S0619" trans="overlap">er <trunc>t</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> to get there it was awful</u>
<u n="594" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and you got all the way there?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0619">I got all the way there</u>
<u n="596" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0619">cos I thought I don't know where I am if I get off this bus</u>
<u n="598" who="S0618">yeah and there might not be another one until Tuesday yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0619" trans="overlap">there might not be another one <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah er and I was really sort of in the middle er</u>
<u n="600" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0619">just had to <unclear>wait</unclear> it was awful it's because well one I was really hung-over but two <vocal desc="laugh"/> two they have buses really hot and everyone has all of their coats on</u>
<u n="602" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh yeah they do I noticed that</u>
<u n="603" who="S0619">why? right so</u>
<u n="604" who="S0618" trans="overlap">scarves sometimes hats all of their outerwear thick coats with fleece linings and</u>
<u n="605" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0618">fur on the hoods</u>
<u n="607" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I just don't think</u>
<u n="608" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> hour jeez</u>
<u n="609" who="S0619">how those people can feel any temperature they can stand outside in really cold temperatures and not feel it</u>
<u n="610" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0619">but then they can sit on boiling buses</u>
<u n="612" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0619">I</u>
<u n="614" who="S0618">in the same clothes</u>
<u n="615" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0618">and not break a sweat amazing</u>
<u n="617" who="S0619">I have to on a bus take off everything down to like my</u>
<u n="618" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0619">first layer</u>
<u n="620" who="S0618">me too almost down to the vest and I'm still sweating</u>
<u n="621" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's too hot especially when it's crowded</u>
<u n="622" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0619">awful <pause dur="short"/> absolutely awful</u>
<u n="624" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah I've felt almost sick on a bus before now</u>
<u n="625" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0618">and had to keep pressing my bare forearms against the cold window to try and get some cool</u>
<u n="627" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0618">its been so unbelievably hot on a bus where was that? that was <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> I think the last bus I was on like that</u>
<u n="629" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it's just crazy <unclear/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0618">and Polish people were there for more than an hour in their winter clothes</u>
<u n="631" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0618">I really don't know how they do it</u>
<u n="633" who="S0619">I'm saying this you know with my coat on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="634" who="S0618">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0619">but</u>
<u n="636" who="S0618">oh yeah getting me to turn the turn the temperature down you've got your coat on</u>
<u n="637" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh sorry</u>
<u n="638" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0619">I don't wanna take it off now I'm comfortable</u>
<u n="640" who="S0618">fair enough</u>
<u n="641" who="S0619">ah I will do <unclear/> if you're getting <unclear/></u>
<u n="642" who="S0618" trans="overlap">do you know what? I'm not sure if I can be arsed skiing this evening I might just fancy a steam and then ski in the morning tomorrow</u>
<u n="643" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm I definitely wanna do some sparry stuff</u>
<u n="644" who="S0618">and then steam again</u>
<u n="645" who="S0619">but I wouldn't mind just sitting in a chair and reading my book</u>
<u n="646" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0619">and sort of looking out the window</u>
<u n="648" who="S0618">no I I've just got this steam idea in my head I haven't had a steam since probably July or August probably July realistically speaking</u>
<u n="649" who="S0619">I think this'll be really good for me in terms of getting stuff out toxins and that</u>
<u n="650" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely and steam's incredibly good for that I am good friends with the a woman who used to work in one of the gyms that my Northern Ireland card erm worked for <vocal desc="laugh"/> and and so actually I think I had a cold that wasn't shifting or something like that so I was wanting to steam it out and so I'd just send her a text and she would ring the gym and get them to change the menthol thing that they put through the pipe</u>
<u n="651" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh nice</u>
<u n="652" who="S0618">so it's all nice and really strong and I'd say I'll be down about three <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then by the time I got there it's really pumping out the menthol eucalyptus that was perfect</u>
<u n="653" who="S0619" trans="overlap">nice</u>
<u n="654" who="S0618">really perfect <pause dur="short"/> no I miss her she's a really nice woman she had a campervan as well erm <pause dur="short"/> but she's funny because we're we're both quite similar in a way we've been on campervan adventures but we've both taken our own vans and followed each other</u>
<u n="655" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0618">it's like she likes her space and I like my space</u>
<u n="657" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0618">and I suppose things can get a little bit intimate in a campervan</u>
<u n="659" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="660" who="S0618">and er you know I know her well enough to share a small bed with her it wouldn't be a problem erm but yeah I suppose you just <pause dur="short"/> yeah also I like my van</u>
<u n="661" who="S0619">yeah she likes hers yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0618" trans="overlap">she likes her van <vocal desc="laugh"/> so yeah creature comforts</u>
<u n="663" who="S0619">for sure for sure <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0618">yeah that was lovely we had a fabulous trip around <anon type="place"/> actually in erm <pause dur="short"/> in Ireland and we were looking for a stone circle and a lot of places in Ireland you can read about them but you can't find them there's</u>
<u n="665" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0618">no no there are no signposts so <vocal desc="cough"/> I <trunc>r</trunc> it was Easter I think it might even've been Easter Sunday <vocal desc="laugh"/> driving in rural <anon type="place"/> and just I stopped and asked somebody do you know where these standing stones are? and they pointed me to the correct field but looked a bit confused and it was only afterwards that <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said you know it's Easter Sunday? and they'd just come out of chapel having had you know one of the most holy masses of the year</u>
<u n="667" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0618">and you you pagan <vocal desc="laugh"/> are asking where the stones are the standing stones</u>
<u n="669" who="S0619" trans="overlap">that's lovely</u>
<u n="670" who="S0618">so but I could get away with a lot being English that she couldn't being Irish so</u>
<u n="671" who="S0619">I wouldn't you know being English I wouldn't want to be from anywhere else</u>
<u n="672" who="S0618">I think it opens doors</u>
<u n="673" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and it can close them a bit as well sometimes</u>
<u n="675" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="676" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I had a guy I worked with in Northern Ireland erm part of my role was to help a charitable organisation be more profitable and I'd only just arrived and said hi how are you? to everybody and this older guy came up to me and said and you can just fuck off <vocal desc="laugh"/> because I was English</u>
<u n="677" who="S0619">oh my god</u>
<u n="678" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0619">yeah in when I lived in Scotland and worked in Scotland <unclear>they erm</unclear> did say stuff to me</u>
<u n="680" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0619">said <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> someone once called me a wee English tart</u>
<u n="682" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0618">that's fantastic</u>
<u n="684" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well you are correct on all counts</u>
<u n="685" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="686" who="S0618">what are you doing later?</u>
<u n="687" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0619">you know and stuff like that <unclear>it was</unclear></u>
<u n="689" who="S0618" trans="overlap">that's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> ah dear</u>
<u n="690" who="S0619">I don't really mind <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0618">no I used to get a lot of friendly abuse from my friends in Northern Ireland</u>
<u n="692" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah friendly abuse as well</u>
<u n="693" who="S0618">you know from the</u>
<u n="694" who="S0619" trans="overlap">get back over your own side <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="695" who="S0618" trans="overlap">the troubles and yeah and I worked for a Catholic organisation and lived in a Catholic community</u>
<u n="696" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="697" who="S0618">so even not being a Christian I was still the Prod <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="699" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and then at work <vocal desc="laugh"/> they used to joke sometimes to say right cultural diversity oi Prod girl what do you think to this? and then ask me a question and get my view on whatever so</u>
<u n="700" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0618">yeah I suppose I could of perceived it as workplace bullying but</u>
<u n="702" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0618">instead I'd quite often tell them to fuck off so it was fine</u>
<u n="704" who="S0619"><unclear/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0618">are you really hot still?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0619">I'm no my temperature's fine I'm just</u>
<u n="707" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="708" who="S0619">this window's going a bit steamy</u>
<u n="709" who="S0618">steamy <pause dur="short"/> you've got your own erm yellow and blue thing down there</u>
<u n="710" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0618" trans="overlap">in fact you've got the clean one and I've got the dirty one <pause dur="short"/> so you can have my dirty one if you wanna</u>
<u n="712" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0618">give it a wipe in fact poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's filthy so she is she really needs a bloody good clean erm I dunno there's just something about the design of this particular model of Volkswagen where <pause dur="short"/> and actually I <trunc>m</trunc> had a Honda Accord that was just the same that you got shite on the outside of the windows so you can't see out your mirror</u>
<u n="714" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0618">you'd think well you'd think they'd've tested that in the aerodynamic tunnel thing at the testy place to</u>
<u n="716" who="S0619"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="717" who="S0618">I don't know put some mud through it on occasion to see where it ends up</u>
<u n="718" who="S0619">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0618">it's like a little winter wonderland here I think the difference between here and <anon type="place"/> is there is a lot more snow stuck to the trees</u>
<u n="720" who="S0619">yeah it looks great doesn't it?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0618"><vocal desc="cough"/> mm</u>
<u n="722" who="S0619">what time was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> leaving as erm after she'd been to yours?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0618">yeah I think she'd called at mine a little bit before nine</u>
<u n="724" who="S0619">uhu okay</u>
<u n="725" who="S0618">picked up her helmet and goggles and came away</u>
<u n="726" who="S0619">oh good she's just lovely</u>
<u n="727" who="S0618" trans="overlap">she's so lovely isn't she?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0619">she's just perfect</u>
<u n="729" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0619">at everything</u>
<u n="731" who="S0618">I wonder though I see a lot of this with Polish women in particular and I suppose I was quite like that myself and I do wonder if it's a female thing is having to be ten times better than anybody else to get the same recognition that an average man gets</u>
<u n="732" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0618">and whether there's any truth in that or whether that's just a perception</u>
<u n="734" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0618">I don't know and it was weird being magnificent and being the best in England</u>
<u n="736" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="737" who="S0618"><unclear>at erm</unclear> you know business things and making shed loads of money and taking unprofitable shops and making them profitable and blah blah blah and doing really great and then</u>
<u n="738" who="S0619"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0618">going over to Northern Ireland <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm back in a</u>
<u n="740" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="741" who="S0618">back in a I dunno you think England's a patriarchy move to Northern Ireland mate bloody hell</u>
<u n="742" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="743" who="S0618">I was working with committees of sort of sixty to ninety-year-old Catholic men who didn't have a fucking clue about business and were trying to tell me what they wanted</u>
<u n="744" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0618">erm <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="746" who="S0619"><vocal desc="misc"/> I think with <unclear/> teaching though it's slightly different in that it is erm a female-dominated industry</u>
<u n="747" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="748" who="S0619">and directors of schools and headmistresses and English er <trunc>n</trunc>not English er are women</u>
<u n="749" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0619">er I used to hate <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> giving me sort of advice on how to teach <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="751" who="S0618" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0619">I'd be like no really shut up really don't have any <pause dur="short"/> any need</u>
<u n="753" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and don't you have more experience than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="756" who="S0619">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> by by far</u>
<u n="757" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0619">so</u>
<u n="759" who="S0618">curious</u>
<u n="760" who="S0619">it is curious curious</u>
<u n="761" who="S0618">yeah I suppose teaching has tended to be a profession that's pretty piss poor paid as well</u>
<u n="762" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="763" who="S0618">apart from in <vocal desc="sigh"/> a lot of northern European countries</u>
<u n="764" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="765" who="S0618">I think Denmark in particular teachers are very well respected and Germany to some extent have a <vocal desc="laugh"/> female erm friend who teaches in a school in Germany erm I actually have a male friend who also teaches in a school in Germany and they're treated like civil servants</u>
<u n="766" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0618">and once they have so many years in the role they get extra tax breaks and big pensions and things like that it's very well respected <pause dur="short"/> I think they get a lot more shit from the students than</u>
<u n="768" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh for sure</u>
<u n="769" who="S0618">erm you know perhaps further northern countries</u>
<u n="770" who="S0619">there's nothing in front of this van oh yeah there is there's er some cars going very slowly</u>
<u n="771" who="S0618">that yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0619">black car what's it doing?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0618">I wonder if that's just <vocal desc="laugh"/> an English person keeping a good braking distance between it and the slower vehicle in front</u>
<u n="774" who="S0619">but there isn't a vehicle in front is there?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0618">I don't know yet we might find out when we're round this corner yeah there are I can see cars are snaking down slowly</u>
<u n="776" who="S0619">ah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0618">so yeah see what I mean? about this is the culture here do you see the blue Punto?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm how close that car is yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="779" who="S0618">behind it is getting in the boot and that is exactly the culture but the Punto as far as I'm aware is thinking nothing bad or you know</u>
<u n="780" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0618">nasty about the car that it's trying to get into the boot of so as a driver you just kind of need to accept that people are gonna drive right up your arse and that it's nothing personal it's like being in a car with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="783" who="S0618">with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="785" who="S0618">and they all drive like that and they're</u>
<u n="786" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0618">they're not swearing at the car in front they're just going about their business</u>
<u n="788" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it's just normal uhu</u>
<u n="789" who="S0618">it's just what they do erm but as a driver that's more accustomed to having <vocal desc="laugh"/> much more space</u>
<u n="790" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="791" who="S0618">between vehicles erm you can take it a bit personally if you don't know that's what I meant about if you do decide to do some driving lessons</u>
<u n="792" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="793" who="S0618">here it's</u>
<u n="794" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="795" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> goodness me <vocal desc="yawn"/> didn't sleep well at all last night I was just kind of fretting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0618">about?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0619">oh loads of things but I think <pause dur="short"/> in a couple of days I'll be right</u>
<u n="799" who="S0618">mm you probably have a bit of purging to do</u>
<u n="800" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="801" who="S0618">after</u>
<u n="802" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="803" who="S0618">the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> conversation of yesterday</u>
<u n="804" who="S0619">sweat it out I <trunc>nee</trunc> yeah I think I need a little bit of time to sort of process <unclear/> I'm not really that bothered</u>
<u n="805" who="S0618">it's the universe showing you a sign</u>
<u n="806" who="S0619">yes I'm</u>
<u n="807" who="S0618">detox and therapia <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0619">oh I was looking at the pregnant one</u>
<u n="809" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0619">I was like what?</u>
<u n="811" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0618">what is she trying to say? <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that I'm pregnant I know</u>
<u n="814" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0619">god I could be but I don't think I am</u>
<u n="816" who="S0618">no</u>
<u n="817" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0618">no the sign to the right of that one</u>
<u n="819" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0618">oh well</u>
<u n="821" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0619">you <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> see this is what I mean about the subjective nature of reality</u>
<u n="824" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0618">we could both look in the same direction and have completely different perceptions</u>
<u n="826" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0619">I just looked at the first one</u>
<u n="828" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0619">ah that's so funny</u>
<u n="830" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0619">but yes let's ring that number and see what happens</u>
<u n="832" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0619">ah detox and therapy that's what I need</u>
<u n="834" who="S0618">yeah I think you're gonna have a couple of days of that</u>
<u n="835" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="836" who="S0618">it's gonna be great</u>
<u n="837" who="S0619">yeah <unclear/> those</u>
<u n="838" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh wow look at how that snow's falling off that roof</u>
<u n="839" who="S0619">oh yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0618">that's really weird it's almost like it's created a new roof just of snow</u>
<u n="841" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0618">it's sort of hanging on there</u>
<u n="843" who="S0619">no I think if I went skiing today it'd be really dangerous so</u>
<u n="844" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I don't yeah</u>
<u n="845" who="S0619">and my mind's not in it you know my <trunc>ha</trunc> mm head's not in it <pause dur="short"/> even</u>
<u n="846" who="S0618" trans="overlap">do you fancy popping <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> another message? just to say traffic is still really slow I wonder if it's gonna speed up when we get to <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="847" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm I dunno</u>
<u n="848" who="S0618">erm and maybe let her know I don't wanna go skiing this afternoon <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wanna get in the steam room erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I mean if if she and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> want to go skiing this afternoon I really don't mind it's not a not a bother then we can meet up for our evening meal <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose just so she knows</u>
<u n="849" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="850" who="S0618">oh my good god and there's a billboard or a woman in a bikini and a Santa hat jesus <pause dur="short"/> you don't get half so much sexist bollocks like that in the UK now I suppose you get big bra adverts but</u>
<u n="851" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah but they're advertising <trunc>b</trunc>bras she's advertising er</u>
<u n="852" who="S0618">motor goods</u>
<u n="853" who="S0619">yeah like the</u>
<u n="854" who="S0618" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0619">the walkie-talkie bit in a taxi</u>
<u n="856" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0619">traffic's still bad</u>
<u n="858" who="S0618">you used to get all of that when I was younger Pirelli calendars were still in when I was younger I think the latest Pirelli calendar that American woman whose name I've completely forgotten who's an amazing photographer has photographed for example Serena Williams and</u>
<u n="859" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it's erm Andy Schumer yeah er Andy <vocal desc="laugh"/> Amy Schumer</u>
<u n="860" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0619">erm yeah I saw them</u>
<u n="862" who="S0618"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah which is cool</u>
<u n="863" who="S0619">yes yes yes yes</u>
<u n="864" who="S0618">have you ever seen Life on Mars? the TV series</u>
<u n="865" who="S0619">I've seen bits but not the whole thing</u>
<u n="866" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="867" who="S0619">the police <trunc>s</trunc>sort of <trunc>s</trunc> time thing</u>
<u n="868" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah that sexism was</u>
<u n="869" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="870" who="S0618">I had all of that growing up I remember my mum erm growing up with all of that and there was a phase in my mum's life I was reminded of it cos I you know I'm going through my stuff at the moment cos I don't wanna be taking everything</u>
<u n="871" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0618">back to England again to store at my uncle's so I'm <vocal desc="sigh"/> chucking stuff out and I got into old photos and old letters last night and I was reading some letters that my mum had sent me and she'd been talking about how happy she was at a particular phase of life and she'd never felt so confident and really enjoyed going out dancing</u>
<u n="873" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="874" who="S0618">didn't worry about her figure or how she looked or how people perceived her she was just dancing meeting men online <vocal desc="laugh"/> and having fun</u>
<u n="875" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0618">erm and this was a phase erm after she and her second husband had split up and I'd given her a computer computers were quite new so this computer was the size of a small town but seemed to fit in her house okay and she discovered chat rooms and starting chatting with men and meeting men and</u>
<u n="877" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="878" who="S0618">going out and having a good time and I <unclear>went</unclear> good for you mother</u>
<u n="879" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="880" who="S0618">and but I used to cringe sometimes when I saw her around men being quite flirty and accepting a lot of what I perceive as really sexist language and sexist banter</u>
<u n="881" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="882" who="S0618">from these guys but yeah it was a really generational thing and there's still absolutely no excuse for it</u>
<u n="883" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0618">but</u>
<u n="885" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no there isn't</u>
<u n="886" who="S0618">my mum used to engage in it and I <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="887" who="S0619">I you know I can't do it</u>
<u n="888" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I always feel she was letting the side down sometimes</u>
<u n="889" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah and <pause dur="short"/> depending on the situation <unclear>I'll just</unclear> call people out on it</u>
<u n="890" who="S0618">mm yeah me too</u>
<u n="891" who="S0619" trans="overlap">erm I don't have a problem and I think</u>
<u n="892" who="S0618">and I pull myself up sometimes <unclear>you know</unclear> throwing like a girl what does that mean?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0619">yeah exactly yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0618">and when it comes out I'm suggesting that somebody hasn't thrown very well but</u>
<u n="895" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="896" who="S0618">that's bollocks</u>
<u n="897" who="S0619">yeah <unclear>or you know</unclear></u>
<u n="898" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I had a school record for throwing the rounders ball</u>
<u n="899" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="900" who="S0619">but yeah things like man up or</u>
<u n="901" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="902" who="S0619">get some balls all this stuff I just think</u>
<u n="903" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I say man up but I also say woman up</u>
<u n="904" who="S0619">woman up</u>
<u n="905" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="906" who="S0619">woman up yeah so it's difficult especially when things are just sort of ingrained in language and you can't</u>
<u n="907" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="908" who="S0619">erm <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> er sort of realise you know you big girl's blouse or whatever <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <unclear/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="910" who="S0619">it is just sort of such a natural turn of phrase that everyone knows that it you know don't <unclear>I suppose</unclear> sort of</u>
<u n="911" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0619">consider it but it is er a bad thing that you shouldn't say you should be saying something else</u>
<u n="913" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="914" who="S0619">you wet lettuce which is sort of gender neutral <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0618">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0618">that's funny</u>
<u n="918" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="919" who="S0618">you wet lettuce</u>
<u n="920" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0618">I like that wet lettuce that's great</u>
<u n="922" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's very northern</u>
<u n="923" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0619">yes anyway I'm doing</u>
<u n="925" who="S0618" trans="overlap">damp squib</u>
<u n="926" who="S0619">yeah nice</u>
<u n="927" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="928" who="S0619">squib should</u>
<u n="929" who="S0618" trans="overlap">that's a great word squib</u>
<u n="930" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> a squid <vocal desc="laugh"/> you damp squid</u>
<u n="931" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0618">I suppose squid would be quite damp on account of the <vocal desc="laugh"/> quite watery habitat so</u>
<u n="933" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="935" who="S0619"><vocal desc="cough"/> <unclear>ah that's funny</unclear></u>
<u n="936" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="937" who="S0619"><unclear/> right we're doing very well</u>
<u n="938" who="S0618">we are and it's right wintery round here</u>
<u n="939" who="S0619" trans="overlap">fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="940" who="S0618">I can feel from the sheer volume of buildings creeping up around us bit by bit that we're gonna be in <anon type="place"/> pretty soon</u>
<u n="941" who="S0619">yeah well I've texted and said I reckon quarter past</u>
<u n="942" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="943" who="S0619">might be longer than that now but</u>
<u n="944" who="S0618">yeah erm</u>
<u n="945" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="946" who="S0618">Simon sat nav says twelve minutes past but he doesn't really know how slowly we've been crawling along</u>
<u n="947" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear>crawling</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> er and I said also that we weren't thinking of skiing today but we will tomorrow</u>
<u n="948" who="S0618">yeah perfect <pause dur="short"/> oh er all those giant football things that's really weird are they bean bags?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0619"><unclear/> I think it's some sort of <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="950" who="S0618" trans="overlap">someone's built an outdoor display of colourful football-shaped beanbags</u>
<u n="951" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0618">plonked in the snow that's very strange</u>
<u n="953" who="S0619">ah</u>
<u n="954" who="S0618" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="955" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="956" who="S0619">I don't have anything else to say I just thought</u>
<u n="957" who="S0618" trans="overlap">we're great entertainment value aren't we?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0619">we'd make a just if we make noises then we're it's not silent</u>
<u n="959" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="960" who="S0619">oh yes so</u>
<u n="961" who="S0618" trans="overlap">isn't that curious? how people often like to fill a silence</u>
<u n="962" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I do yeah I usually hum</u>
<u n="963" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="964" who="S0619">even if it's just like me and another person <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>and then</unclear> I've got nothing to say to them I just hum <shift new="singing"/> da da da <shift new="normal"/> yeah so <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="965" who="S0618">that was I found a great weapon for business meetings</u>
<u n="966" who="S0619">what? accepting silence?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0618">yeah and I'm I think quite good at accepting silence and</u>
<u n="968" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="969" who="S0618">people get themselves into all sorts of verbal difficulties</u>
<u n="970" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="971" who="S0618">through their discomfort</u>
<u n="972" who="S0619">yeah and it's a good thing to do for <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> or <trunc>t</trunc> it's a good skill to have teaching as well</u>
<u n="973" who="S0618">mm yes</u>
<u n="974" who="S0619" trans="overlap">you've just gotta sit in silence and wait sometimes</u>
<u n="975" who="S0618">yep</u>
<u n="976" who="S0619">even if it's awful and you want to</u>
<u n="977" who="S0618" trans="overlap">thump them?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0619">say something</u>
<u n="979" who="S0618">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="980" who="S0619">no you just wanna I just wanna speak erm</u>
<u n="981" who="S0618">shake your teenagers gently by the throat and make them communicate with you?</u>
<u n="982" who="S0619">yeah er sometimes just waiting it out will do no matter how painful it is</u>
<u n="983" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0619">so <anon type="place"/> is this a big place? or a medium sized place?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0618">I think by Polish terms it's relatively sizeable larger than <anon type="place"/> smaller than <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0619"><unclear/> ah is it?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0618">erm but <pause dur="short"/> yeah I wonder if it's more a transient kind of a everything</u>
<u n="988" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it's a good sort of</u>
<u n="989" who="S0618"><unclear/> passes through kind of place</u>
<u n="990" who="S0619">yeah central spot</u>
<u n="991" who="S0618">not sure what the speed limit is loads of vehicles behind me and none in front of me</u>
<u n="992" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="993" who="S0618">so I'll just pull over here there we are jolly good</u>
<u n="994" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh traffic going the other way I wonder where they're all going</u>
<u n="995" who="S0618">I think it seems to be erm quite similar though I think they've got traffic lights going the other way</u>
<u n="996" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> traffic <unclear/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so do you mind passing my demisty thingy back over? <unclear/></u>
<u n="998" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I gave it you back</u>
<u n="999" who="S0618">oh did you? oh so you did thank you</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0618"><unclear/> a wipe there <pause dur="long"/> shall we turn that off and have a bit of</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0618">peace?</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0619">sorry <unclear/></u>
<u n="1005" who="S0618" trans="overlap">that's alright</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0619">bye</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0618" trans="overlap">bye</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0619">what do I do? press stop?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0618">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
