<text id="SZNA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:55:45</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-15</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0519 S0520 S0521</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Hunsonby, Cumbria</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>mobile phones, technology, Israel, Judaism, Jewishness, Middle east, Christianity, naming</topics>
		<activity>Family discussing the Middle East</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explainnig, inquiring, complaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0519">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Dublin, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith, `</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Recently retired maths teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0520">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead, UK`</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>India/Thailand/UK (Hunsoney</hab_city>
				<hab_country></hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Transcriber, Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0521">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Walsall, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Former role as technical esport of development planning in oil industry</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0521">when it's still plugged in</u>
<u n="2" who="S0519">she does she got</u>
<u n="3" who="S0520">well I do that thrills and spills</u>
<u n="4" who="S0519">she got the erm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0520">I'm not convinced that you can really</u>
<u n="6" who="S0519" trans="overlap">the metal pincers to go into the toast to get it out</u>
<u n="7" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0521">horrendous</u>
<u n="9" who="S0520">I always have a little alarm bell in my <trunc>mi</trunc> in my mind which is like mum more or less screaming no don't put the knife down the toaster</u>
<u n="10" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0521">she's very good at screaming isn't she?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0520">she <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0519">oi</u>
<u n="14" who="S0521">none of this <unclear/> lunch you know</u>
<u n="15" who="S0520">no that's the recording I have to leave it on the table</u>
<u n="16" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0520">I'm not allowed to check my emails or anything it get told off</u>
<u n="18" who="S0521">get told off for doing that's called quality of life <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0520">well I agree but I'm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0519">but</u>
<u n="21" who="S0520">a hundred million percent less addicted to my phone than most people</u>
<u n="22" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0520">I don't have it on most of the time</u>
<u n="24" who="S0521">that's good to hear</u>
<u n="25" who="S0520">at the moment I do because<anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I chat on the Viber that is our long-distance means of communication</u>
<u n="26" who="S0519" trans="overlap">love affair</u>
<u n="27" who="S0520">and love affair which is a valid thing to do</u>
<u n="28" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0520">but I get annoyed with him because he when he's in Israel is just constantly looking at that thing</u>
<u n="30" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0521">there you go</u>
<u n="32" who="S0520">and it does my head in and he can't multitask so if I want to say anything to him of any nature it's not</u>
<u n="33" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0521">is he a bit touchy?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0520">no he just doesn't <trunc>li</trunc> he just doesn't hear what I'm at <trunc>al</trunc> listen at all or hear any of it because he's staring at his phone and it's going bing bong burr it does my head in</u>
<u n="36" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0520">to be honest no if there's anything <unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0521" trans="overlap">you should give him a book on living in the now</u>
<u n="39" who="S0520">well exactly</u>
<u n="40" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0520">you can say that to him<anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a big fan of the old er total living concept</u>
<u n="42" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0520">he's in to it but I he could do without his phone</u>
<u n="44" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but he needs to put his phone down</u>
<u n="45" who="S0520">yeah well I've <trunc>sa</trunc> he knows it he knows it's out of hand out of control and he's very busy so fair enough there's a lot of messages coming in from all his</u>
<u n="46" who="S0521">yeah that's not the point though is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0520">no it's addictive is the point and he's much more inclined towards those type of things you know like erm I was going to say obsessive but that's a bit of a strong word</u>
<u n="48" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0520">he just can't you know can't keep it under control very well sometimes I think</u>
<u n="50" who="S0521">oh oh</u>
<u n="51" who="S0520">and he does just switch his phone off in the evening</u>
<u n="52" who="S0519">good</u>
<u n="53" who="S0520">which I think is the best solution you know? cos then you're not tempted to kind of play with it and look at things</u>
<u n="54" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="long"/> my approach is to switch off your phone the whole day and then deal with the emails at the end of the day</u>
<u n="55" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0519">not if you're waiting on something specialist removal company Pickford's have you given up on them?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0521">no I haven't given up on them</u>
<u n="58" who="S0520">well I mean there are two things on the phone there's business and there's social your social life you know</u>
<u n="59" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0521">same thing</u>
<u n="61" who="S0519">not your social life</u>
<u n="62" who="S0520">your social life <vocal desc="laugh"/> which is mum</u>
<u n="63" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0520">I don't ever see you on trawling Facebook and</u>
<u n="65" who="S0521">no</u>
<u n="66" who="S0520">chatting with your</u>
<u n="67" who="S0521">not my thing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0520">cronies but erm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0519">I'm getting fed up with it now I've got too many friends that aren't friends that post nonsense</u>
<u n="70" who="S0521">well that's the thing isn't it? just becomes a general picture</u>
<u n="71" who="S0519">you've got to cull your friends that's the way to do it</u>
<u n="72" who="S0521"><unclear/> it's a little bit sad really people spending their day on Facebook</u>
<u n="73" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0521">they're lacking something</u>
<u n="76" who="S0519">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> cheek of it</u>
<u n="77" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0519">mm that toast is delicious</u>
<u n="79" who="S0520">it's very nice yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0521">it's good</u>
<u n="81" who="S0520">do you make that toast dad? was that expertly made by you?</u>
<u n="82" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0519">did you cut another onion?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I'm not sure about your sarcasm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I learnt from the master dad</u>
<u n="86" who="S0521">could be a bit subtler I think</u>
<u n="87" who="S0520">I believe it's a inherited genetic condition</u>
<u n="88" who="S0519" trans="overlap">shall I put another couple on? <pause dur="short"/> oh no</u>
<u n="89" who="S0520">erm yeah I'll have one more <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think you have to erm keep the role of electronic devices in your life in check</u>
<u n="90" who="S0521">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0520">I think it's bad for your well-being because it is addictive clearly for everyone</u>
<u n="92" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0521">it's a thing of who controls who isn't it? what controls what</u>
<u n="94" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and it's and it affects your attention</u>
<u n="95" who="S0519">it does and although I know you're joking about the Facebook thing but you do the looking things up thing and then you go on and on and on to another thing and another thing and then it's the same idea that you you've always got a device on your lap</u>
<u n="96" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0521">mm that's true</u>
<u n="98" who="S0520">yeah it doesn't matter what you're doing with it really it's just it is</u>
<u n="99" who="S0519">it's still idle wanderings</u>
<u n="100" who="S0520" trans="overlap">kind of like an open door to all kind of</u>
<u n="101" who="S0521">interesting trivia</u>
<u n="102" who="S0520">interesting things that may be social or knowledge or whatever</u>
<u n="103" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0520"><unclear/> it's important not to lose the ability to engage with your environment <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was talking to erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother-in-law about it his sister is quite strict with all of those stuff with her kids she doesn't let them watch telly she they don't have devices to play on and they the two of them don't do it either like they don't have Iphones and all these things cos they <trunc>a</trunc> and they actually made a decision about it together saying that they didn't feel it was good for their kids and</u>
<u n="105" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0520">you know they it's important that you go out and your children are in the car you're not they're not staring at a DVD they're looking out the window and you're talking about the environment and you know just having a conversation with your children instead of I mean I I have had I er don't have kids so I can't I wouldn't at all venture to say and I have absolute sympathy for the stick the TV on method cos it's exhausting isn't it?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0520">but they're very total about it and I think it's basically a much healthier way to grow up</u>
<u n="109" who="S0519">mm excuse me I do too and</u>
<u n="110" who="S0520">and too much TV and Ipads and what have you for young children I think it's quite bad news like a degree of it I think is wonderful cos it's educational</u>
<u n="111" who="S0521">of course yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0520">and it develops all kind of cognitive faculties and you have to be able to use technology nowadays anyway so you need to be proficient but there's such a <trunc>ea</trunc> it's so easy to go over the line and it's just like I think it's just over stimulating and it's that kind of like very very fast kind of change of imagery and stimulation that children get used to and if that's your like kind of tender development stage I don't know I feel like it's can create a problem psychologically</u>
<u n="113" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm it will certainly create the erm <pause dur="short"/> addiction to something happening all the time</u>
<u n="114" who="S0521">my worry is</u>
<u n="115" who="S0519">that that's that you don't have the space to just sit</u>
<u n="116" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0520">you need to sit and do nothing sometimes it's really important</u>
<u n="118" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0521" trans="overlap">my my worry that it it's it it creates an atmosphere of instant gratification and you don't have the capacity</u>
<u n="120" who="S0520">or the patience</u>
<u n="121" who="S0521">to learn things properly develop skills and use them</u>
<u n="122" who="S0520">yeah and also you haven't got appreciation that comes from you have to learn to appreciate things it's like you can go out on a beautiful walk for instance and you can be like completely preoccupied with your worries that are going on in your mind or looking at your phone and doing things and you know you don't you don't see you don't feel good about what's around you and appreciate where you are and with who you are</u>
<u n="123" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0520">and you sort of lose and there's a sort of art in that you don't it's not naturally necessarily there's a certain I feel like there's a certain switch that you have to turn on you know</u>
<u n="125" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0520">you just relax inside yourself and then you start to appreciate what you what you're experiencing more</u>
<u n="127" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0520">you know this is the total living sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0521" trans="overlap">look at people in restaurants</u>
<u n="130" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you know but I really think it's</u>
<u n="131" who="S0521" trans="overlap">look at people in restaurants and there's a full table of six of eight people and they've all got a Iphone</u>
<u n="132" who="S0520">I know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0521">I mean it's it's sort of bizarre</u>
<u n="134" who="S0520">killing the being connected</u>
<u n="135" who="S0521" trans="overlap">what can you possibly be doing?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0519">no it's on Facebook <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent a a picture of three people at breakfast and they all had a laptop up</u>
<u n="137" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there were lots of jokes like can someone email my scrambled egg</u>
<u n="140" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0520">there's so many advantages I don't think it's er a negative thing I just think you have to set limits for on yourself with it</u>
<u n="142" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0520">and I think everybody has a problem more or less everybody has a problem with that</u>
<u n="144" who="S0519">mm we've tried to well we got fed up with each other as well with the devices so we we'd sort of say right we'll have you know a few hours in the morning with no device on and a few hours in the afternoon with no devices on we try and just say right let's have a you know an hour here and an hour there instead of just the constant flow <vocal desc="cough"/> pardon me mm yum scrum I enjoyed that</u>
<u n="145" who="S0520">this is Israeli hummus I'll have you know</u>
<u n="146" who="S0519">Israeli hummus</u>
<u n="147" who="S0520">I'm not sure</u>
<u n="148" who="S0519"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>hu</trunc></u>
<u n="149" who="S0520">how the Israelis would feel about it</u>
<u n="150" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0521">is it Israeli in origin? or just Middle Eastern in origin</u>
<u n="152" who="S0520">no it's er it's <trunc>Ar</trunc> er Arabic food but there's a lot of Jewish Arab er Jewish people that came from <pause dur="short"/> the Middle East</u>
<u n="153" who="S0521">Jewish that came from the Middle East they're Arab then?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0520" trans="overlap">meaning yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0521">they're Middle Eastern</u>
<u n="156" who="S0520">well there's I think I've told you this before there's kind of broadly speaking two groups of Jews in Israel one are called Ashkenazi Jews and the other</u>
<u n="157" who="S0521" trans="overlap">you're talking about the returning Jews</u>
<u n="158" who="S0520">the returning Jews and the other group are Hassidic Jews that came from Iraq Yemen Iran and North Africa Egypt Tunisia Morocco and so forth and they brought with them</u>
<u n="159" who="S0519">hummus</u>
<u n="160" who="S0520">hummus <vocal desc="laugh"/> thank you for that not to mention there's a lot of Arabs actually in Israel meaning Arab Arabs but er</u>
<u n="161" who="S0521">quite interesting that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so</u>
<u n="162" who="S0520">but they've brought all the they've brought a very different cultural influences you know into Israel than the <trunc>ash</trunc>Ashkenazi Jews</u>
<u n="163" who="S0521">when you when you said there were Arabs in Israel you Jews are mainly sort of erm unique in a way aren't they? that you identify somebody as a Jew which is his religion</u>
<u n="164" who="S0520">well it's not only</u>
<u n="165" who="S0521">whereas you can be <trunc>A</trunc> you can be an Arab and have a Jewish religion and you could be an Arab and have a <trunc>m</trunc> Muslim religion</u>
<u n="166" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0521">you call one an Arab but you call the other one a Jew</u>
<u n="168" who="S0520">well that's the things <trunc>Jew</trunc> Judaism is like Jewish means religious <trunc>Je</trunc> because of the religion but it's also the cultural term</u>
<u n="169" who="S0521"><unclear/> so so</u>
<u n="170" who="S0520">in fact you don't have a differentiation</u>
<u n="171" who="S0521" trans="overlap">ethnically is there any difference between Jews and Arabs?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0520">which ones? what do you mean? in Israel you mean?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0521">in origins are the Jews not a just a band of Arabs ultimately?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0520">oh do you mean did they originate in the Middle East?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0520">I actually don't know the answer to that question I don't know I I mean I wouldn't I mean the Jews that came from Europe to Israel in</u>
<u n="177" who="S0521">but that's much later</u>
<u n="178" who="S0520">I know it's much later but I'm saying I wouldn't I'd say I don't know if they're ethnically Middle Eastern any more</u>
<u n="179" who="S0521" trans="overlap">right whether they moved whether they all moved and then you know came from the Middle East and then there was a sort of diaspora from there</u>
<u n="180" who="S0521">cos I'm curious about erm Bronowski's thing because he said he talked about agriculture as being the beginning of civilisation and he said that er agriculture there's evidence for agriculture in Jericho which we now know is on the West Bank up to ten thousand years ago</u>
<u n="181" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0521">he was saying that that it was evidence of civilisation but then he went on to talk about the Old Testament and erm I was just curious whether he was trying to suggest that Jericho really was the beginning of civilisation in that area</u>
<u n="183" who="S0520">yeah that wasn't really clear but it's not fair to say is it? because Egyptians as we then found out were earlier</u>
<u n="184" who="S0521">well he said ten thousand year ago didn't he?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0521">whereas Egyptians it's they start about four and a half four thousand years BC</u>
<u n="187" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0519">they don't start then do they? cos they're building pyramids then</u>
<u n="189" who="S0520">I thought it was eight thousand</u>
<u n="190" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0521">really?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0519">it's four thousand for the pyramids isn't it?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0521">is it?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0521">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="197" who="S0519">I do where's the er phone?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0520">where's the phone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0521">anyway there's a there's a big difference between ten thousand years ago and four thousand BC</u>
<u n="200" who="S0520">ten thousand years ago is six thousand BC</u>
<u n="201" who="S0521">six thousand BC</u>
<u n="202" who="S0519" trans="overlap">four yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0520">I don't know I don't know if the implication was that</u>
<u n="204" who="S0519" trans="overlap">what? no it's eight eight thousand</u>
<u n="205" who="S0521" trans="overlap">what? eight thousand</u>
<u n="206" who="S0519">what you like you two?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0521">what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0520">well I don't think the idea was that the first <trunc>pe</trunc> the people to have found Jericho were Jewish were they?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0521">well that comes back to my question doesn't it?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0521">were the Jews a specific race of people or were they just a tribe of Arabs?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0520">I don't know to be honest</u>
<u n="213" who="S0519">what do you mean a tribe of Arabs?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0520">if they originally Middle Eastern</u>
<u n="215" who="S0519">sounds rude</u>
<u n="216" who="S0520">it does sound a bit rude dad</u>
<u n="217" who="S0521">what?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0519">well the way you were saying it sounds</u>
<u n="219" who="S0520">a tribe</u>
<u n="220" who="S0519">derogatory</u>
<u n="221" who="S0521">that's not actually that's that's the word that's used for the Israelites the Israelites and the what do you call? nomadic nomadic life is a tribe</u>
<u n="222" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0521">that's not I didn't just use that word</u>
<u n="224" who="S0519">mm okay it's</u>
<u n="225" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm talking about like <unclear/> cultural kind of origin I have no idea</u>
<u n="226" who="S0519">yeah but <trunc>ev</trunc>even in so in Christ's time or in two four thousand year excuse me</u>
<u n="227" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0519">two thousand years ago</u>
<u n="229" who="S0521">time of Christ</u>
<u n="230" who="S0519">so then there was a Jew</u>
<u n="231" who="S0521" trans="overlap">that's not the era we're talking about</u>
<u n="232" who="S0519">yes but then there was a Jewish people weren't there?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0520">yeah but the question is where did they come from originally <trunc>eth</trunc>ethnically speaking?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0519">yes so well I'm so far removed from understanding that I don't want to start so I'm thinking where I do understand so so when they were the Jewish people then they they were they were Jewish <trunc>pe</trunc> they were Arabs but they were Jewish because of their</u>
<u n="235" who="S0521" trans="overlap">Jewish by religion well exactly</u>
<u n="236" who="S0520">I think so and I think I have the sense that it evolved into an ethnicity</u>
<u n="237" who="S0519">over time</u>
<u n="238" who="S0520">but originally it was kind of a religious belief system</u>
<u n="239" who="S0519">mm so they were they were all the same people in the same area of the land but there were <trunc>dif</trunc> there were Jews and non-Jews</u>
<u n="240" who="S0521">so it's an Arab tribe with a particular religion</u>
<u n="241" who="S0520">Arab you could say is an ethnicity rather than a religion whereas Islam is the religious part you know what I mean and there's Christian Arabs as well</u>
<u n="242" who="S0521" trans="overlap">that was even later</u>
<u n="243" who="S0519">exactly and so</u>
<u n="244" who="S0520">but Arab <unclear/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0519" trans="overlap"><unclear/> big interest there isn't it? but but at that time so again because I don't understand it really but at that time there was an area of the world that was probably bigger in in</u>
<u n="246" who="S0521"><unclear/> you mean?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0519">no in in sorry just in in that area that's <trunc>i</trunc> that's Biblical</u>
<u n="248" who="S0520">mm yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0519">in the Middle East but it was it all the different countries at that time or was it just one country? now we have Jordan and?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0520">I don't know if there were</u>
<u n="251" who="S0519">I think Jordan was much later</u>
<u n="252" who="S0520">such borders at that time</u>
<u n="253" who="S0519">no cos</u>
<u n="254" who="S0520">I think there were probably like kingdoms and then there was like nomadic people</u>
<u n="255" who="S0521" trans="overlap">Jordan is modern</u>
<u n="256" who="S0519">but there was the river Jordan</u>
<u n="257" who="S0521">the river Jordan yeah but Jordan the state of <trunc>af</trunc> after the First World War</u>
<u n="258" who="S0519">okay erm so</u>
<u n="259" who="S0521">cos you've got the</u>
<u n="260" who="S0519">but there was Egypt the people are Egypt</u>
<u n="261" who="S0521" trans="overlap">the Syrians the Canaanites and the</u>
<u n="262" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="263" who="S0521">Egyptians</u>
<u n="264" who="S0520">all different sort of</u>
<u n="265" who="S0521">all your different er civilisations</u>
<u n="266" who="S0519">okay that's that's kind of where I'm coming from erm so it's it oh dear I can't get my head round it but it's like what you were saying is is that all Arab but they're already culturally different</u>
<u n="267" who="S0520">yeah maybe that's <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0519" trans="overlap">already slightly different and so that's not really fair because it's like saying all of Europe was Europeans whereas actually they there are quite different ethnicities within that</u>
<u n="269" who="S0520">mm that's true mum</u>
<u n="270" who="S0521">well I'm still coming back to the same question is is Jewish is identified by ethnicity or purely by its religion?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0520">well that yeah at the moment it's both I mean currently it's both because there are plenty of secular secular Jews in Europe in Israel rather they don't subscribe to the Jewish religion but they follow erm heritage and a certain type of cultural observances and erm ancestry I guess</u>
<u n="272" who="S0519">yeah I think that would be similar to here that people say that they're unless they've particularly chosen not to be Christian or not to be a believer</u>
<u n="273" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0519">they probably generally say they're they're Christian and they have Christenings and they have Easter holiday and it's it's a a <unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah but it's much stronger</u>
<u n="276" who="S0519">much stronger mm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0520">I think just because of the historical historical context of having come from erm <pause dur="long"/> erm how to say? having <trunc>t</trunc> having come from a very distinct cultural history</u>
<u n="278" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="279" who="S0520">in in Europe for instance where they did you know they they maintain they were religious Jews in Europe you know in the ghettos they were they were observing the Jewish religion they weren't secular people</u>
<u n="280" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0520">there's a bit of first of all it's a bit of a new development to be Jewish but not to be religious</u>
<u n="282" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0520">but that comes from yeah I think just that very distinct kind of history of the Jewish people and identification with that history and certain kind of cultural practices that go with it</u>
<u n="284" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0520">like<anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family none of them are religious but they observe all of the Jewish holidays Jewish New Year Sukkot what have you Hanukkah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0521">I mean presumably</u>
<u n="287" who="S0520">Passover you know and there's certain like traditional way of behaving and some <trunc>pe</trunc> erm on like in a Pesach meal or whatever there's all kind of <trunc>reli</trunc> rituals and things that they do as well</u>
<u n="288" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0520">sings songs that they sing you know like we would do at Christmas but it's even more so on top of that some people sort of halfway they believe in certain aspects of the religious erm story let's say and they and they are kind of they carry some of those things with them and like for instance Saturday in Israel is observed a hundred times more strictly that</u>
<u n="290" who="S0521" trans="overlap">the Sabbath</u>
<u n="291" who="S0519">Sunday is here</u>
<u n="292" who="S0520" trans="overlap">Sunday is here it used to be like that here didn't it?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0521">yes it did</u>
<u n="294" who="S0520">but Saturday even if you're not religious a lot of people take it as the Sabbath and don't do anything and like religious people you're not supposed to use your <trunc>cook</trunc> you're not you're not supposed to create anything so you're not supposed to turn on your car or switch the lights on or there's loads and loads of stuff that you're not supposed to do but most people I mean really Saturday nothing happens in Israel everything is closed and even people who aren't religious consider that to be part of their cultural life</u>
<u n="295" who="S0521" trans="overlap">is that is that enforced by law?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0520">to a degree yeah I mean there are there is quite a strong influence of Orthodox Jews inside the government and and so forth so there are there are things which you're not allowed to do but like for instance I arrived in Tel Aviv last time on Sunday there were no trains from the airport running</u>
<u n="297" who="S0519">on the Saturday</u>
<u n="298" who="S0520">on the Saturday sorry things like where you go okay but what I'm saying is that the even the <trunc>pe</trunc> the secular people which is a large proportion of the population in Israel</u>
<u n="299" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0520">especially in Tel Aviv they're much they're much more erm closely observing their Jewishness</u>
<u n="301" who="S0521">yeah I see what you mean</u>
<u n="302" who="S0520">than people here who consider themselves sort of secular but with some Christian influence</u>
<u n="303" who="S0521">well maybe maybe they</u>
<u n="304" who="S0520">and also they're very er they have a very strong erm emotional attachment to their identity as Jewish and the history of the Jewish people that's why <unclear/> like especially the recent history but you know their grandparents most of them were in the were erm survivors of the Holocaust you know and it's an enormous thing to carry</u>
<u n="305" who="S0521" trans="overlap">Holocaust yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0519">yeah it is</u>
<u n="307" who="S0520">and they came over they escaped that horrific situation and most of their family was dead and they came to Israel to start a new life this was two generations ago</u>
<u n="308" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0519">very close isn't it?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0520">so and that was a war that was waged against Jewish people Jewishness you know</u>
<u n="312" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0520">and I think you know people really build a very strong sense of identity around that history it's really <unclear/> you know it's not like you know even people who like<anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's just like quite on the periphery really of Jewishness still</u>
<u n="314" who="S0521" trans="overlap">well that's understandable yeah isn't it ironic that the <trunc>Sy</trunc> isn't it ironic that the Syrian's are clambering to get into Germany</u>
<u n="315" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0521">as the great er open society for migrants I wonder what the Israelis think of that</u>
<u n="317" who="S0520">I'm sure they have a lot of thoughts about that</u>
<u n="318" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0520">yeah it's interesting I mean I see it you know now that I've met<anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family they're not they're very erm <trunc>li</trunc> you know very kind of modern they're not they're non-religious people for instance they don't have any objection to the fact that I am not Jewish</u>
<u n="320" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="321" who="S0520">whereas your average family might</u>
<u n="322" who="S0521">really?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0520">not might would have</u>
<u n="325" who="S0519">oh would they?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0520">yeah I mean it's not really the done thing</u>
<u n="327" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0520">but you know they for them that's completely you know their family have travelled a lot and what have you and</u>
<u n="329" who="S0521">well they objected to me for being a non-Catholic</u>
<u n="330" who="S0520">exactly you had to convert</u>
<u n="331" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I had to do lessons yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0519">no you have to have lessons</u>
<u n="333" who="S0520">I mean if I wanted to convert to Judaism which I don't and will never erm it's a serious undertaking oh my goodness</u>
<u n="334" who="S0521">I can imagine</u>
<u n="335" who="S0520">you don't want to be doing it</u>
<u n="336" who="S0519">do you have to learn the language?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0521">you've got to be pretty serious have you?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0519">and be able to read the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no it's a serious business they don't I mean this is the fascinating thing about Judaism they don't want you to convert</u>
<u n="340" who="S0519">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0521"><unclear/> no evangelism</u>
<u n="342" who="S0520">no nothing they really want to make it difficult for you to be Jewish if you weren't born into it</u>
<u n="343" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0521">completely opposite to Christianity isn't it?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0520">and Islam</u>
<u n="346" who="S0521">and Islam do they are they evangelists?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0519">they do</u>
<u n="348" who="S0520">I get that impression I mean Christianity is probably more it's more pronounce isn't it? what I understood as well is that erm there's a lot of tension in within the Jewish part of Israeli society between these two Hassidic and Ashkenazi erm Jews</u>
<u n="349" who="S0521">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0520">it's actually quite a source of social problems</u>
<u n="351" who="S0521">oh</u>
<u n="352" who="S0520">because the Hassidic Jews tend to be in lower income</u>
<u n="353" who="S0521">okay</u>
<u n="354" who="S0520">erm jobs and tend to be poorer and in poorer neighbourhoods and tend to be responsible for a lot more of crime you know crime and stuff that happens erm and they also just have quite different value systems you know because they didn't come from Europe</u>
<u n="355" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="356" who="S0520">and and then in the nineteen nineties there was a huge influx of Russian Jews into Israeli about a million Russian Jews and they are like uber Ashkenazi <vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean I was asking I said what does it mean by Ashkenazi apart from the fact that you're kind of you know white and they <unclear/> erm have a tradition of being very very educated very very cultured you know erm upper class let's say there's a kind of class issue built into it</u>
<u n="357" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yes I remember that oh yeah right cos Jew Jews have a reputation for being business-minded don't they?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0520">merchants yeah bankers weren't they?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0520">in Europe but yeah I noticed I noticed this to be true <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm but yeah so many people there often say you know if erm if we weren't united by a common enemy</u>
<u n="361" who="S0519" trans="overlap">is this plastic recycling?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0521">I put those in the plastic yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0519">you put the orange plastic bags in the plastic</u>
<u n="364" who="S0521">what's wrong with that?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0519">you can't they're not recyclable</u>
<u n="366" who="S0520">you can't put the plastic bags dad?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0521">what do they do with it?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0520">chuck it in a landfill</u>
<u n="369" who="S0521">well exactly I think plastic is <unclear>I understand</unclear> plastic is a great issue because nobody knows what to do with it</u>
<u n="370" who="S0519">no and there's also the fact that there are <trunc>di</trunc> lots of different types aren't there? as it were</u>
<u n="371" who="S0521">I don't think it's any better just just putting your plastic bottles there it doesn't end up anywhere different I don't think does it? unless they recycle the bottles but I can't imagine them doing that plastic bottles</u>
<u n="372" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's what they do isn't it?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0521">so they recycle plastic bottles?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0519">I don't know what they do with them</u>
<u n="375" who="S0521">don't think so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0520">yeah somebody needs to invent a new material that has the same properties but is biodegradable</u>
<u n="377" who="S0521">it's one of the great offshoots of the oil industry</u>
<u n="378" who="S0520">what plastic? mm yeah I saw that in India actually when I first went to India they didn't have plastic really they had glass and they had paper bags</u>
<u n="379" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="380" who="S0520">and when you had a <trunc>ch</trunc> tea it was served in a clay cup</u>
<u n="381" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="382" who="S0520">which they would then just break onto the ground and that was that</u>
<u n="383" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0520">but of course plastic is a wonderful thing and erm and very convenient so you can see that <vocal desc="cough"/> it's sort of become a huge problem now they're because there's so many people</u>
<u n="385" who="S0521">you can't destroy it no</u>
<u n="386" who="S0520">who have no concept of recycling</u>
<u n="387" who="S0521">have you seen that picture of the Pacific in that little <unclear/> Pacific with a little but huge actually they're just full of plastic cos the currents they contrive to concentrate the thrown away plastic into specific areas and it it's enormous</u>
<u n="388" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0521">I haven't thought about the Jews actually</u>
<u n="390" who="S0520">we can ask well I don't know if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would know I wouldn't say are you ethnically Arab?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0521">so is he Ashkenazi then?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0520">yes his family are Ashkenazi classic</u>
<u n="393" who="S0521">and where do they originate then?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0520">erm Romania Germany and Poland I think and Russia his father's Russian</u>
<u n="395" who="S0521">yes sorry I mean his specific family come?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0520">that's what I'm talking about yeah they're usually a mixture you know because someone would come from Russia someone would come I think his mum is from Romania and his father is Russian</u>
<u n="397" who="S0521">oh right okay</u>
<u n="398" who="S0519">are they like the Americans where they they think that that</u>
<u n="399" who="S0520">I'm like Romanian Israeli</u>
<u n="400" who="S0521">take pride in their <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0519">you say oh I'm Irish and they say oh</u>
<u n="402" who="S0521">I'm an Irish American</u>
<u n="403" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think it's quite like that</u>
<u n="404" who="S0519">erm you're not your possible uncle fifteen times removed</u>
<u n="405" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> not it's not really got to that point yet it's all quite recent isn't it?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0520">erm people identify as Ashkenazi or as <trunc>e</trunc> as they call Eastern that for sure</u>
<u n="408" who="S0521">Eastern Europe</u>
<u n="409" who="S0520">Eastern they call them Eastern Jews meaning they come from they came from east of east of Israel</u>
<u n="410" who="S0521" trans="overlap">oh I see oh okay</u>
<u n="411" who="S0520">countries that lie east of Israel yeah and er there's quite a lot of racism I think in on that level</u>
<u n="412" who="S0519">is there?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0519">about where you came from as a Jew?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0519">oh</u>
<u n="417" who="S0520">it's bit of a disaster isn't it? well that's what everyone says is that if if Israelis weren't united against a common enemy they would start fighting amongst themselves instead because there's so many factions there's this thing and there's also <trunc>we</trunc> religious Jews versus secular Jews</u>
<u n="418" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0520">which is a big source of tension cos they do think about things very differently</u>
<u n="420" who="S0521">interesting the term racism because I mean is it a race? so there's there's prejudice of one set of Jews against another because of their</u>
<u n="421" who="S0520" trans="overlap">because of their ethnicity</u>
<u n="422" who="S0521">their ethnic origin</u>
<u n="423" who="S0520">yeah well they call them black because they have dark skin in comparison as well you know they look like Middle Eastern people look very dark skinned and dark eyed</u>
<u n="424" who="S0521">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0520">and erm you know they just have a very you know they have a different look about them whereas Ashkenazi are typically white you know white people</u>
<u n="426" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="427" who="S0519">in erm in Judaism then is there a is there no sort of like you we're the only ones going to heaven kind of malarkey?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0520">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0519">well I I just sorry but I just was thinking religiously that that's why</u>
<u n="430" who="S0521">like the Christians</u>
<u n="431" who="S0519">the Christians and the Muslims want to people to come to their religion because they're the only ones going to heaven</u>
<u n="432" who="S0520" trans="overlap">who are going to be saved</u>
<u n="433" who="S0521" trans="overlap">the chosen people</u>
<u n="434" who="S0520">actually I must say I don't know very much about Judaism at all and I don't know the answer to that question I know that they call themselves the chosen people and</u>
<u n="435" who="S0519">I do</u>
<u n="436" who="S0521">yes</u>
<u n="437" who="S0520">and I think that they believe like most religious groups that they're the only people who god has really communicated with</u>
<u n="438" who="S0521">the <trunc>dir</trunc> the direct link with god</u>
<u n="439" who="S0520">but I don't think there I don't think there's an apocalyptic erm prophesy like in Christianity but I don't know do you know?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0521">erm interesting you should say that <pause dur="long"/> the end of the world? does that appear in the</u>
<u n="441" who="S0520">you know like the second coming and all of that and</u>
<u n="442" who="S0521" trans="overlap">that's Revelations isn't it? I don't think it's in the Old Testament at all</u>
<u n="443" who="S0520">I don't think so either I'm not really sure what's in the Old Testament apart from a lot of</u>
<u n="444" who="S0521" trans="overlap">no probably not</u>
<u n="445" who="S0519">a lot of scary stuff</u>
<u n="446" who="S0520">scary scary mythological stories about stuff and it's also like an origin myth isn't it? the Old Testament it's like where did the Jewish people come from and erm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0521">so we thought Abraham was about two thousand BC did we?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0520">that's what it said yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0521">so he was quite close to <unclear/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0520">no not Abraham <trunc>Ja</trunc> Jacob</u>
<u n="451" who="S0521">yeah but</u>
<u n="452" who="S0520">same same</u>
<u n="453" who="S0521">that's his grandson isn't it?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0521">and they're more or less the same time</u>
<u n="456" who="S0520">yeah it was about two thousand BC</u>
<u n="457" who="S0521">Abraham is supposed to be the father of the family isn't he?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0520">of the family yeah the tribe they actually call themselves a tribe the Jew the Jewish people</u>
<u n="459" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0521">actually there are twelve tribes of Israel aren't there?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0520">oh yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0521">they were the brothers weren't they?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0520">I should really learn about it I was all quite surprised about the Pesach story and the ten plagues and</u>
<u n="464" who="S0521">Israel had five sons</u>
<u n="465" who="S0519">Passover</u>
<u n="466" who="S0520"><trunc>Pe</trunc>Pesach yeah is Passover</u>
<u n="467" who="S0519">is it Pesach?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0520">Pesach is the Hebrew version yeah there's a lot of erm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0519">yeah so they'll be thinking you're very ignorant cos you don't now the Christian <trunc>re</trunc> you know <unclear/> it's the same story for the Christians and the Jews</u>
<u n="470" who="S0520">what for the Easter?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0519">no not well it but it's all in the Old Testament so that's part of Christianity</u>
<u n="472" who="S0520" trans="overlap">Passover yeah exactly there's just more focus on the New Testament</u>
<u n="473" who="S0519">yeah well that's the <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0520">they don't recognise the New Testament</u>
<u n="475" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="476" who="S0521">no of course not <pause dur="short"/> despite the fact that he was a Jew</u>
<u n="477" who="S0520">that's all they have to say on the matter yeah Jewish Jesus was a Jew</u>
<u n="478" who="S0521">a Jew that got it wrong</u>
<u n="479" who="S0520">a Jew that betrayed the tribe</u>
<u n="480" who="S0521">well that's interesting that</u>
<u n="481" who="S0519">no they think he's a good bloke and all that don't they?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0520">I dunno I don't think they even think he existed</u>
<u n="483" who="S0521">I'm <trunc>do</trunc> I think you may be flattering yourself there</u>
<u n="484" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0520">I'm not sure how much er friendliness there is towards the whole thing to be honest</u>
<u n="486" who="S0521">well Mr Mohammed said er that Christ was a prophet</u>
<u n="487" who="S0519" trans="overlap">oh yeah he they're chums</u>
<u n="488" who="S0520">they were both yeah they're both in a lot of stories aren't they? well William Blake reckoned he came to England</u>
<u n="489" who="S0521">yes the green and pleasant land</u>
<u n="490" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah there's some funny theories about it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0521">they think that Paul might have got to Spain <pause dur="short"/> on his journey</u>
<u n="492" who="S0520">that sounds possible</u>
<u n="493" who="S0521">cos he he certainly got to Rome it's not all that far to</u>
<u n="494" who="S0520">I just wonder how long after the actual events themselves these things were written as well same with the Bible</u>
<u n="495" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I think people know that it <trunc>e</trunc> erm there's a there's an excellent book by excellent book</u>
<u n="496" who="S0520">is this that woman er</u>
<u n="497" who="S0521">called the four <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0520">that nun</u>
<u n="499" who="S0521">no</u>
<u n="500" who="S0520">that you read Karen Armstrong mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0521" trans="overlap">not that one not that one erm it's called the Four Gospels but it's not called the Four Gospels it's called the four something the four anyway it's a guy who's written a a whole book about the historical context of the writing of the gospels</u>
<u n="502" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0521">and it's pretty it's pretty clear actually that they were written between the sixty-sixty AD and a hundred erm Matthew was apparently was it Mark Mark Mark was the first one who apparently was erm in Rome</u>
<u n="504" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0521">so saying it's thirty year or so after the crucifixion that the first gospel was written</u>
<u n="506" who="S0520">you're not allowed to say AD any more are you?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0521">are you not?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0520">what do you say again?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0519">I don't know</u>
<u n="510" who="S0521">it's modern era something isn't it?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0519">what's this for?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0520">you're not allowed to say BC and AD as in as a kind of mainstream way of talking about time</u>
<u n="513" who="S0519">oh</u>
<u n="514" who="S0520">yeah because not everyone's time is orientated around Jesus</u>
<u n="515" who="S0519">oh lordy lordy</u>
<u n="516" who="S0520">so it's kind of a colonial supremacy thing</u>
<u n="517" who="S0521">so well</u>
<u n="518" who="S0519">oh I didn't know there was another word for it</u>
<u n="519" who="S0520">no there's another way what is it again dad? after something</u>
<u n="520" who="S0519">it's some something about years years of that modern era</u>
<u n="521" who="S0520">no no no as in theirs is a there is an <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="522" who="S0521">there's an acronym B O or something</u>
<u n="523" who="S0520">we use it now instead of BC and AD you know if you're an Indian why would you</u>
<u n="524" who="S0519">well</u>
<u n="525" who="S0520">well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0519">but it some things become our erm they become part of the culture and the way you say something you know you don't have to believe in Christ to know that your clock's been based on him</u>
<u n="527" who="S0520">no that's true but it's like GMT as well</u>
<u n="528" who="S0521">yeah they're changing that now aren't they?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you're not allowed to say GMT</u>
<u n="530" who="S0519">flipping heck</u>
<u n="531" who="S0521">they're changing that</u>
<u n="532" who="S0520">you say</u>
<u n="533" who="S0519"><unclear/> vocab</u>
<u n="534" who="S0520">you say UTC universal coordinated time</u>
<u n="535" who="S0519">oh get lost</u>
<u n="536" who="S0520">no it's not get lost it's a it's a symbol of erm colonial</u>
<u n="537" who="S0519">colonial whatnots oh lord</u>
<u n="538" who="S0520" trans="overlap">what do you call it oppression that we have to all measure ourselves according to British</u>
<u n="539" who="S0519">well the whole latitude and everything goes through it so</u>
<u n="540" who="S0520">no well no</u>
<u n="541" who="S0521">that's because it was it's longitude actually longitude</u>
<u n="542" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's cos the Brits made it up</u>
<u n="543" who="S0519" trans="overlap">well <vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry</u>
<u n="544" who="S0521">it it was arbitrarily chosen to be zero longitude</u>
<u n="545" who="S0520">it's like you know when the colonials went over to India and renamed everything they said this is Bombay and this is Calcutta and this is blah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0519">alright yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0520">and then since then the Indians have said wait a minute what all this?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's not what it's called</u>
<u n="549" who="S0520">that's not what it's called let's call it what we call it instead and that's how the world should say our places in India and not you know cos some British idiot</u>
<u n="550" who="S0521">what about India is that the right name?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0520">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know actually yeah it gets a bit ridiculous but I mean fair enough there's a whole play about it erm that we were forced to read a school which is actually really good it's er a <trunc>Br</trunc>Brian Friel play called Translations</u>
<u n="552" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0519">oh yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0520">and it's actually about the British occupation of Ireland</u>
<u n="555" who="S0519">oh I never knew that</u>
<u n="556" who="S0520">and they change all the place names</u>
<u n="557" who="S0519">right</u>
<u n="558" who="S0520">as a way of Anglicising the country but in doing so like the place place names contained <trunc>with</trunc> within them a lot of cultural history why people had called them that in the first place</u>
<u n="559" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0520">and through renaming them you kind of that that is lost it's kind of erased you know so symbolically it has quite a big effect</u>
<u n="561" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0519">no so I wasn't being and I I mean I I <trunc>lo</trunc> none of that's lost on me of course in terms of the names of the country but I the country and the and the cities but erm ooh no erm</u>
<u n="563" who="S0520">I saw that</u>
<u n="564" who="S0519">but er I wasn't thinking Greenwich Mean Time was anything</u>
<u n="565" who="S0520">well Greenwich Mean Time I mean in fairness things were being measured in Greenwich because the Brits probably</u>
<u n="566" who="S0521">invented it</u>
<u n="567" who="S0520">created the system but</u>
<u n="568" who="S0519">well there you go</u>
<u n="569" who="S0520">so fair enough</u>
<u n="570" who="S0519">that's fair enough it doesn't mean we've you know</u>
<u n="571" who="S0521"><unclear/> longitude</u>
<u n="572" who="S0519">we didn't ruin somebody's life for it</u>
<u n="573" who="S0520">was it?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0519">oh heck what on earth's that thing there?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0521">erm but you just I mean it does get a bit ridiculous like for instance the West Indies they're called the West Indies by a a gross error because it wasn't the West Indies at all <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was America</u>
<u n="576" who="S0520">it was a mistake</u>
<u n="577" who="S0521">but no one's thought to change the name of the West Indies</u>
<u n="578" who="S0520">well they probably will eventually</u>
<u n="579" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0520">in fairness</u>
<u n="581" who="S0519">what is that? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0520">oh weirdies it looks like a little bit of</u>
<u n="583" who="S0521">what is it?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0520">rot or something doesn't it?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0519">yeah like a</u>
<u n="586" who="S0520">or like a er mould or something</u>
<u n="587" who="S0519"><unclear/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0521">very strange</u>
<u n="589" who="S0519">I'm giving the kitchen a an <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> clean</u>
<u n="590" who="S0520">you don't need to do that</u>
<u n="591" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0519">not really you know it needed a clean anyway it needed a woman's touch</u>
<u n="593" who="S0520">yeah er they just had the New Year celebrations</u>
<u n="594" who="S0519">oh yes</u>
<u n="595" who="S0520">and there's a lot of eating involved</u>
<u n="596" who="S0519">uh</u>
<u n="597" who="S0520">so I keep getting pictures of cake and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/> and er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who is<anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s stepmother is is quite an amazing cook and she was apparently cooking till three o'clock in the morning the day before she's a bit <vocal desc="laugh"/> she's a bit serious</u>
<u n="598" who="S0519">woah</u>
<event desc="0521 leaves"/>
<u n="599" who="S0520">yeah she's really good at it <pause dur="long"/> do you want some tea?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0519">no I'm going to have a coffee later</u>
<u n="601" who="S0520">mm coffee mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm not sure the Lavazza is the way for the coffee machine</u>
<u n="602" who="S0519">no it doesn't seem to be tasty</u>
<u n="603" who="S0520">in general I just think it lacks a certain richness the coffee</u>
<u n="604" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0520">maybe it's the erm it's the way it's poured</u>
<u n="606" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but I'm hopeful now with the erm with the latest adjustment</u>
<u n="607" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0519">that we can get that <trunc>ni</trunc> the nice Taylor's coffee to taste nice again cos it used to</u>
<u n="609" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="611" who="S0520">well they do just get worn and erm dirty inside and then you get a weird taste</u>
<u n="612" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="613" who="S0520">even though it self cleans maybe there's a kind of major cleaning</u>
<u n="614" who="S0519" trans="overlap">erm no there is a clean you have to do periodically a proper clean you have to put <trunc>i</trunc> er a sort of some sort of chemical in</u>
<u n="615" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0519">erm and run a whole procedure</u>
<u n="617" who="S0520">yeah I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did it regularly</u>
<u n="618" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="619" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0519">I I think he was so good to his machine that he's ruined it for life</u>
<u n="621" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0519">now</u>
<u n="623" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0519">a certain amount of healthy neglect is required</u>
<u n="625" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he's always kind of like semi in shock to see how I treat my belongings</u>
<u n="626" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0520"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is as well actually he's very careful with things <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0519"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0520">it's really good that the erm music course went well for dad</u>
<u n="630" who="S0519">it's amazing isn't it?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0520">I'm very happy for him</u>
<u n="632" who="S0519">yeah me too</u>
<u n="633" who="S0520">that was you're doing</u>
<u n="634" who="S0519">it was my little surprise it could have gone any way couldn't it but I was really pleased</u>
<u n="635" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no you were good to take a risk for him</u>
<u n="636" who="S0519">yeah I did ring them up you know and ask all those questions cos it was clearly you know erm a risky venture</u>
<u n="637" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah of course mm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0519">but I you know I convinced myself that it was going to be good so that was good</u>
<u n="639" who="S0520">yeah don't want his confidence to be knocked</u>
<u n="640" who="S0519">no and and it was all <trunc>m</trunc> you know meant to be just an enjoyable experience</u>
<u n="641" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="642" who="S0519">erm so yes I don't know what I think of this it was eight</u>
<u n="643" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I'm shaking it out</u>
<u n="644" who="S0519">yeah it was eight quid you know it was I thought oh it'll be jolly but it's not quite jolly is it? I wanted a check one really like a little blue check</u>
<u n="645" who="S0520">got to get to JLs</u>
<u n="646" who="S0519">no it's from JL but <unclear/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0520">do you want to wash it? or put it back on</u>
<u n="648" who="S0519">erm we'll put it back on for now and er I've got quite a bit of white washing if there's enough room I'll put it in I think these are all pretty much done now</u>
<u n="649" who="S0520">oh cool</u>
<u n="650" who="S0519">give them a last little dry off</u>
<u n="651" who="S0520">zhuzh</u>
<u n="652" who="S0519">thanks <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0520">what what's the idea?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0519">I was going to pull it out cos the three of us really hardly fit</u>
<u n="655" who="S0520">that's true <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0519">okay lovely</u>
<u n="657" who="S0520">there's a dead fly on the sticky thing</u>
<u n="658" who="S0519">oh yo</u>
<u n="659" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0519">somebody bit the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="661" who="S0520">kind of hoping there's going to be more than one a day though</u>
<u n="662" who="S0519">no I mean I they do completely fill up it's horrible</u>
<u n="663" who="S0520">grimness yeah flies disaster <pause dur="long"/> I'm not sure this guy with his rebellious antics is really going to take very well this Corbyn guy</u>
<u n="664" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="665" who="S0520">I mean there are people that you know think the national anthem and the queen and all of that is a load of old rubbish</u>
<u n="666" who="S0519">of course there are</u>
<u n="667" who="S0520">and in fairness we all do to a degree but it's there's something like a bit schoolboy childish in that kind of <trunc>acti</trunc> action</u>
<u n="668" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="669" who="S0520">it's not very</u>
<u n="670" who="S0519">no it's not</u>
<u n="671" who="S0520">responsible <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="672" who="S0519">so if he was in government he has to he has to be accepted by the queen it's all a rigmarole but you know</u>
<u n="673" who="S0520">it is</u>
<u n="674" who="S0519">it's part of the</u>
<u n="675" who="S0520">I explained this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he was in shock and said why do people accept this?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0520">I said I'm not sure but if you look at like how people responded to the royal wedding and stuff you know you don't you can't say that people don't have a sort of emotional relationship with the whole rigmarole</u>
<u n="678" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no no that's right it's a bit scary isn't it?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0520">like billions of people wasn't there?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0519">erm so yeah so choosing to already be disrespectful and but <trunc>y</trunc> he would have to be accepted by the queen and have to accept her even if he wanted to chuck her out the week after he can't even be be in government without</u>
<u n="681" who="S0520">her permission</u>
<u n="682" who="S0519">her permission</u>
<u n="683" who="S0520" trans="overlap">her royal permission she should chuck him out</u>
<u n="684" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's not a good start is it?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0520">yeah it's just things like that I just don't think it's going to wash really you never know</u>
<u n="686" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no ring up the</u>
<u n="687" who="S0520">oh no this internet problem is annoying me</u>
<u n="688" who="S0519">it's very annoying</u>
<u n="689" who="S0520">I had to I turned off the booster but then I don't get internet in my room</u>
<u n="690" who="S0519">no you could sit in our room it's clean</u>
<u n="691" who="S0520">mm I mean in a way it's good for me not to have internet in my room because then I actually work instead of chatting and faffing about</u>
<u n="692" who="S0519">but if you sit on it</u>
<u n="693" who="S0520">but then when I'm working I also need to look things up and stuff so</u>
<u n="694" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="695" who="S0520">you know I need to do two things one is to print the visa form I'm saying this now cos I know the next four days are going to be pretty busy</u>
<u n="696" who="S0519">no that's good</u>
<u n="697" who="S0520">and also erm that will require ink for the printer</u>
<u n="698" who="S0519">erm I could get ink today</u>
<u n="699" who="S0520">and I need to get my photographs for the</u>
<u n="700" who="S0519">yeah well we could go in later</u>
<u n="701" who="S0520" trans="overlap">erm form which is American fifty by fifty</u>
<u n="702" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and we can get ink I think Sainsbury's even have the ink</u>
<u n="703" who="S0520">I imagine they probably do and I can get the photographs done at Timpson's</u>
<u n="704" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0520">I can also do that if we go out on Friday to <anon type="place"/> or somewhere I can do it then</u>
<u n="706" who="S0519">yeah but if we get the ink it'll be nice well I can I can get ink without you coming and you could get the</u>
<u n="707" who="S0520">I'll be in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> anyway and see what's what she thinks about it yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0519" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
