<text id="SZNP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0266 S0268</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>How to overcome problem of strings breaking; methods involved (including using cable ties); materials/dimensions/positioning/weight; costing; trailing the ideas; discussion on the use of the word ‘fleet’; use of product in primary school v. secondary school; cutting ear lobe and stripe in hair by mistake; marketing the idea; Dragons’ Den; resulting new haircut...</topics>
		<activity>Discussing business (badminton racket repair) while having a home haircut</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, requesting, making arrangements, apologising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0266">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Almondsbury, Gloucestershire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0268">
				<exactage>67</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ramsgate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dursley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Arabic -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0266">so as I'm cutting your hair</u>
<u n="2" who="S0268">oh yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0266">do you want to tell me about erm the new phase of your business plan or or the troubleshooting of your business plan</u>
<u n="4" who="S0268">well I've yeah I discovered that there's another erm element to things not just the standard area that I'm doing which is the bulls</u>
<u n="5" who="S0266">no what I <trunc>m</trunc> what I mean is that <trunc>h</trunc>how are you going to overcome this problem of the strings breaking at the bottom of the rackets your latest I suggested the PVA glue you've slightly poo pooed that</u>
<u n="6" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well they're <unclear/> well I didn't really erm the problem with that is that if you just use the glue then I don't think there's any much protection really there's not a lot of protection so I think it's belt and braces I think you need the glue and the tape and then the tape would be quite difficult to get off</u>
<u n="7" who="S0266">but I thought you said the tape was no good because they pick it off</u>
<u n="8" who="S0268">well I think they would they could well pick it off</u>
<u n="9" who="S0266">so what's? what's this new?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0268">well the new thing is these you had to put so to <trunc>p</trunc> to protect the frame to <trunc>pro</trunc>protect the strings it's to eh somehow put cable ties around in a way that we lift the racket from the ground by about a millimetre <unclear/> only a millimetre I think</u>
<u n="11" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0268">and these cable ties are that's all the thickness they are they're about a millimetre two millimetres and by putting a series of cable ties around the top then it's going to be protected the strings are going to be protected the strings are going to be protected and <trunc>tha</trunc>that should do the job the only problem is that it takes quite a few of these cable ties per racket I think maybe six or seven and even though these are very cheap to buy</u>
<u n="13" who="S0266"><trunc>wh</trunc>why <unclear/> six or seven if they surely they're only hitting the end <unclear/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well well yes but <trunc>they</trunc>they're hitting well as you look at the racket what I've found is that from the the strings go mainly between eleven o'clock and one o'clock as you look at the racket okay? but quite a few go between ten o'clock and two o'clock so if they go between ten and two o'clock that means you need more ties more of these cable ties to protect a a a larger perimeter so I mean you could just say right all the damage is going to be right at the end it's going to be between eleven o'clock and one o'clock and then you can get away with four or five ties if you extend that slightly to ten from ten o'clock till two o'clock then you need two or three more ties which means more work ties are very very cheap so it doesn't really matter about the ties at all then the cost of the ties cos they're ridiculously cheap it's just</u>
<u n="15" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well <trunc>ho</trunc><trunc>ho</trunc>how? what what erm cost would it <unclear/> racket?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well I've looked on well I looked on the internet and I think you can get a hundred for sixty P so so if they're that cheap</u>
<u n="17" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh right it's minimal</u>
<u n="18" who="S0268">well it's it's very little it's less it's less than five P a racket</u>
<u n="19" who="S0266">but what about?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0268"><trunc>r</trunc> and then so you're charging for the labour <unclear/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0266">yeah what about the labour?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0268">well that's the next stage I've got to research because the I've been on the internet and where you can get the cable ties from you can also buy these machines eh they look a bit like a gun really like a staple gun but you <trunc>mo</trunc> you put the ties into the gun erm the eh I think you would have to put both ends in oh no no it's it's a way of tensioning the tie so hopefully the the machines get near enough to the edge of the racket so it can tie it fairly tight so they won't sort of move around when the the racket's being swung they should just be tight enough not to move when they're they're being played with like this one here is moving</u>
<u n="23" who="S0266" trans="overlap">but but</u>
<u n="24" who="S0268">but the this is not moving <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I can't look because I'm cutting your hair</u>
<u n="26" who="S0268">okay right</u>
<u n="27" who="S0266">we should be having conversations about holidays if I'm the hairdresser not about</u>
<u n="28" who="S0268" trans="overlap">okay but it's yeah it's fine well this is much more interesting</u>
<u n="29" who="S0266">is it?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0268">but there's only these ones that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> put on the other day there's only one that's very loose the rest are all quite tight or tight enough so I think that might be the answer to the answer to the problem</u>
<u n="31" who="S0266">but what about changing the erm eh aerodynamics of the of the racket</u>
<u n="32" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well that's that's I just think that they're just so liked these things I don't think it'll make any difference at all</u>
<u n="33" who="S0266">have you played with one?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0268">no I haven't but I will do that's a very good point so what I'll do tomorrow when I'm going to badminton I'll put five on mind you there's a lot of difference between</u>
<u n="35" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it might improve your game</u>
<u n="36" who="S0268"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there's a lot of difference between the badminton I play and school badminton because my racket's a lot lighter than school rackets you might I might notice it but I'm still that's still quite a good idea I could put five or six on and see whether I can still play it also the other thing we'll see if anybody notices it there see whether you know or I could actually say can you notice anything about this racket I think they would because they they do stand out a bit but if I put some very small ties on like these erm <trunc>invis</trunc> not invisible ones clear ones and you could show it to someone and say can you see anything notice anything about this racket? and it could well be the case that they won't see anything because they're clear they can and from a distance and seeing as they're they're all getting on and their eyesight is not that good</u>
<u n="37" who="S0266">who's? who? the</u>
<u n="38" who="S0268">the the players that I play with</u>
<u n="39" who="S0266">what? they can't see?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0268">well yeah they can actually a bit of a joke now</u>
<u n="41" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0268">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0266" trans="overlap">sorry I missed that</u>
<u n="44" who="S0268">you missed that but I think they could they could erm they'd have a job to see once it's like more than than the racket's more than about two or three metres away from you I don't think you can see them if you're <trunc>cl</trunc>close up within a metre or two metres you'd see them but further than that you wouldn't so erm but I think it's a good idea to to play with one it's a very good idea <unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I'm just going to put the light on so I can see actually see what I'm doing</u>
<u n="46" who="S0268">so I can I can do that for tomorrow it's a very good idea play with one and see see if it <trunc>ma</trunc> I I'm pretty sure because erm I'm not very good on weights but I would think that one one of these ties would weigh probably about two grams maybe less I think the shuttlecock weights about five grams so if this weighs only erm so say it's a gram or gram and a half I reckon each tie that would be you would be putting like seven grams seven or eight grams on the racket and the racket weighs eighty grams so you're actually increasing the weight by a nominal ten percent something like that <pause dur="short"/> and that should be</u>
<u n="47" who="S0266">yeah but for aerodynamics that can</u>
<u n="48" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well it could be that you'll notice it yeah it could be I'll notice it but</u>
<u n="49" who="S0266">could be quite serious</u>
<u n="50" who="S0268">but for schools is doesn't really matter I don't think I don't I don't think that you know that I that isn't an issue in <trunc>sc</trunc> because most school players are not club or county players they're not particularly good they wouldn't notice it I'm sure they wouldn't notice it but but what maybe well they they wouldn't notice it when they're playing but it's a question of whether the teachers will accept it as <trunc>a</trunc>an addition or there might be a slight health and safety issue aswell I think you mentioned that to me before</u>
<u n="51" who="S0266" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0268">well these things protrude don't they? slightly if they're tight and are kept inside but I <trunc>do</trunc> I think they can still be revolved you can still revolve them around you see what I mean? you can still so kids will probably do that</u>
<u n="53" who="S0266">yeah but they can't pick them off</u>
<u n="54" who="S0268">they can't pick them off they are tamper proof exactly</u>
<u n="55" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0268">there's no way you can get those out except with a pair of erm tin snips</u>
<u n="57" who="S0266">so who who had this idea?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0268"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0266">really?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0268">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0266">what did he immediately?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><unclear/> cheesed me off really that he had the idea and I didn't</u>
<u n="63" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0268">he he he mentioned cable ties first and I I couldn't quite see what he was getting at and then he explained it and then he he then I went to his house didn't i? went to his garage and then he he got all these cable ties out and we had a look at them all and we took some into the kitchen and then we spent about half an hour three quarters of an hour experimenting he out these on and he also did this as I said this thing with a pipe but that's I think if anything's loose or slightly erm vulnerable the kids will find it out that's why the table cable ties are such a good idea cos they cos they cannot be taken off at all there's no way they can come off except with a tool so the two things that we did that we got quite excited about neither of them is student proof so we'd go back to the idea of just putting the ties on with nothing <trunc>wi</trunc>with them holding nothing on the racket whatsoever so you just have <trunc>th</trunc>the raw cable ties</u>
<u n="65" who="S0266">so</u>
<u n="66" who="S0268">five or six of them and and that will lift the racket far enough off the floors for them never to for the strings to never come in contact with the floor that's that's what it's all about</u>
<u n="67" who="S0266">so are you doing a erm a sort of eh trial <unclear/> trial at that school</u>
<u n="68" who="S0268" trans="overlap">yeah I think I will I think I will I think I'll say it to him that I've got a better idea or I've eh potentially</u>
<u n="69" who="S0266" trans="overlap">what what have you given him at the moment to try?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0268">why? that's a good question I've given him three types of racket and they're all colour coded one is just with PVA glue which is which was your idea</u>
<u n="71" who="S0266" trans="overlap">sorry <unclear/> ear</u>
<u n="72" who="S0268">so one has just got glue on and I've colour coded it on but it two <trunc>w</trunc>well colour coded it and also marked the racket in case the tape comes off I it's double indemnity er another one was erm PVA glue and then allowed to dry and then tape put on the PVA glue and the third category was PVA glue and immediately put tape over the PVA glue so it's put on when when wet so there's the three types of our trialling he knows all about that</u>
<u n="73" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and when are you? when you going back to?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0268">well I'll leave it a few months I think it's it's got to be over time hasn't it? but I can I can actually get it I think I've got plenty of rackets in the garage I can give him a couple of these or maybe more and say could you could you erm keep this in your fleet of rackets as it were</u>
<u n="75" who="S0266">fleet? is that what it's called? a fleet of rackets?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0268">well it's a fleet yeah they use the word fleet not just taxis you got like wind turbines a fleet of wind turbines yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0268">yeah fleet is used quite a bit as a compound</u>
<u n="79" who="S0266">fleet of cars</u>
<u n="80" who="S0268">fleet of cars fleet of taxis fleet of lorries so fleet of rackets</u>
<u n="81" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no</u>
<u n="82" who="S0268">well</u>
<u n="83" who="S0266">is that you or?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0268">well I'm I'm I'm christening our return here</u>
<u n="85" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> your turn it's not an official</u>
<u n="86" who="S0268">well I think you can use it feature practice</u>
<u n="87" who="S0266">have you heard it before?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0268">no</u>
<u n="89" who="S0266">well I think you're making it up as you go along</u>
<u n="90" who="S0268">well I am yeah but I think that I think it's an excellent use of the word</u>
<u n="91" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="92" who="S0268">so if I give him like three of these rackets three or four or I could just go back and say which rackets are gone I'll mend them and then I'll I'll put this this device on cos he's up for it he says it's a good plan and he's willing to help</u>
<u n="93" who="S0266">is he not the stressed out teacher?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0268">he probably is a stressed out teacher but he's at least got time to email me occasionally so he can't be that stressed out</u>
<u n="95" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> primary school?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0268">pardon?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0266">primary school is it?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0268">no no it's a secondary school</u>
<u n="99" who="S0266">oh</u>
<u n="100" who="S0268">second of course it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0268">but it's in <anon type="place"/> so yeah they you you wouldn't have the problem in a primary school because A the kids don't play badminton in the same way that they do in secondary school and B if they and and that assumes they're playing the majority won't play badminton in a primary school but those that do play they the level would be very low and they they wouldn't be swinging the rackets around on the floor like they do in secondary school which is where all the damage takes place so it's it's purely a secondary school idea this primary schools you can do the erm you can do the the <unclear/> of the rackets and not that's what I did with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is that alright</u>
<u n="103" who="S0266">what? with her school?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0268">er yeah well with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm she gave me I she gave me I think she gave me something like thirty hockey sticks and about thirty rackets and not one of those cases did you think well obviously not for the hockey sticks but for the tennis rackets not one set of strings had gone it was just pure erm grips that needed replacing so had she gone to her catalogue and got erm tennis rackets new which is what she was going to do they would have <trunc>ch</trunc> they would have cost anywhere between nine and fourteen pound and I <trunc>me</trunc> I gave a special rate but I mended them for under three pounds okay so she was very grateful so</u>
<u n="105" who="S0266">so that proved to you that primary schools don't <unclear/> same problem</u>
<u n="106" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well I'm <trunc>pr</trunc>pretty sure because I mean that school does a lot of sport and they they do tennis they erm I don't think the badminton rackets would ever wear out really unless they played every day with them but I'm sure they don't I've just actually given <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> thirty-two rackets so erm but I I'm confident that they won't wear out because I I know the way that badminton is taught and she uses <unclear/> balls as well so I I know that they won't be it's just a completely different ball game as it were</u>
<u n="107" who="S0266">I've cut your ear you know there's blood there</u>
<u n="108" who="S0268">dreadful</u>
<u n="109" who="S0266">I'll just get the tissue</u>
<u n="110" who="S0268">how did you do that?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0266">I don't know they must be very sharp the scissors</u>
<u n="112" who="S0268">oh well I I said</u>
<u n="113" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I said I nearly cut your ear</u>
<u n="114" who="S0268">I said be careful but you've got three lots of scissors here four lots of scissors and you've probably chosen the sharpest one</u>
<u n="115" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I <trunc>s</trunc> I suppose you could sue me really</u>
<u n="116" who="S0268">no I wouldn't do that so going back to this now you know quite a lot about the whole thing would you would you say this is a <trunc>sol</trunc> good solution to the problem? these</u>
<u n="117" who="S0266">I yeah I think it is</u>
<u n="118" who="S0268">right well that's good</u>
<u n="119" who="S0266">I just I think it's the best you've had so far</u>
<u n="120" who="S0268">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0266">looks best</u>
<u n="122" who="S0268">it's just you need quite a few of these ties I think you need probably seven</u>
<u n="123" who="S0266">I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0268">just so that is a bit labour intensive isn't it?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0266">well you'll just have to up the price</u>
<u n="126" who="S0268">yeah well what you do you'd explain it it's future-proof I think that's quite a good term future-proof you're <trunc>frui</trunc> future-proofing the rackets and you'd have a guarantee that if they went to the <trunc>to</trunc> if the strings went to the top within say a few months six months then you would do the job for nothing you would <trunc>me</trunc> and you're not losing anything there cos I'd I'm pretty sure they would never go they and they don't go in the middle I know that from mending about three hundred rackets</u>
<u n="127" who="S0266">but if you get okay let's imagine you get all this sorted out</u>
<u n="128" who="S0268">mm yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0266">erm what about your marketing? is that? <unclear/> getting lots of orders?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0268">no not getting very many at the moment I've got to have a I've got to have another campaign on marketing cos I a lot of a lot of flyers have gone out but not many people have erm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's that's sorry that setting on that trimmer is that's just shaving the whole head</u>
<u n="132" who="S0268" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="133" who="S0266">I <trunc>didn</trunc> didn't want that I need a number</u>
<u n="134" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well you know you've got to got to put these on</u>
<u n="135" who="S0266">well can you put it on? you usually do that</u>
<u n="136" who="S0268">it's this one I think</u>
<u n="137" who="S0266">it'll have a stripe up the back cos it's taken all the hair off</u>
<u n="138" who="S0268">well that's great</u>
<u n="139" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I cut your ear <unclear/> spike in your hairdo</u>
<u n="140" who="S0268" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>d</trunc> oh dear what about that then?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0266">not well you need</u>
<u n="142" who="S0268">that's about right</u>
<u n="143" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0268" trans="overlap">not that <unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0266" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="146" who="S0268" trans="overlap">alright</u>
<u n="147" who="S0266">I'll do another stripe</u>
<u n="148" who="S0268">well don't cos you <unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0266" trans="overlap">I'm afraid <unclear/> bald bit there I've cut</u>
<u n="150" who="S0268">could you start at the other end? sorry <pause dur="short"/> how does that go?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0266">it's not it's not short enough</u>
<u n="152" who="S0268">not short enough? okay give it back</u>
<u n="153" who="S0266">it's not</u>
<u n="154" who="S0268">well that's that's as far as it can go</u>
<u n="155" who="S0266">can you take your glasses off?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0268">yeah sure</u>
<u n="157" who="S0266">right sorry I distracted you what erm you you were talking about the marketing</u>
<u n="158" who="S0268" trans="overlap">marketing yeah well I think maybe I've just got to concentrate on local schools and just pick the rackets up that's something doesn't seem</u>
<u n="159" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it doesn't seem to want to power through</u>
<u n="160" who="S0268">why is that?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0266" trans="overlap">maybe it's too short for I just <unclear/> cut the hair quite long quite short I mean</u>
<u n="162" who="S0268">well maybe that's it maybe <unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0266" trans="overlap">and there's a load of hair in there could you?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0268"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0266">eh don't you're putting it all over the floor now</u>
<u n="166" who="S0268">well give that a whirl</u>
<u n="167" who="S0266">can you pick up that bits of hair <vocal desc="misc"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0268">but I think</u>
<u n="169" who="S0266" trans="overlap">sorry yeah go on</u>
<u n="170" who="S0268">well the thing is to to convince schools that they would be saving money and if they're</u>
<u n="171" who="S0266">yeah but how are you?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0268"><unclear/> well in two ways to mend to mend their <trunc>ra</trunc></u>
<u n="173" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh it's not <trunc>switche</trunc> this thing isn't switched on</u>
<u n="174" who="S0268">oh right</u>
<u n="175" who="S0266">that's why I haven't got the power right we're in business now</u>
<u n="176" who="S0268">oh</u>
<u n="177" who="S0266">sorry I keep interrupting you yeah go on marketing how are you going to get customers?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well I think the main the main marketing really is the practicality of the idea and the economy of the idea if I can convince them that would they would save like hundreds of pounds a year on rackets then I think it's a given that they would they would go for it but one idea might be to actually talk on the phone to not the PE department but the bursar or the person who picks up the phone who's in charge of money and say I can save your school a hundred two hundred pounds a year every year by a very simple measure would you like to hear about it? how would that be?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0266">well I don't know anything <unclear>about string</unclear></u>
<u n="180" who="S0268">because if they if the string goes then they have to replace the racket which would cost them anywhere between five and ten pound <pause dur="short"/> okay? and that's what schools do they don't they don't mend them so I mean that school the other day that erm they'd got in touch with me when we were on holiday they they he said he thought it was a very good idea but all these rackets had gone er and then I went over when we came back from holiday and I picked them up and I had a look at them all and they had all gone in the same way in the same place and then I got back in touch with him and I <trunc>sa</trunc> I explained exactly what had happened erm and that's when I thought of using that school as a kind of erm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0266">guinea pig</u>
<u n="182" who="S0268">guinea pig research project and he was very willing to take part in it but things had moved on so we'd moved on from glue to tape</u>
<u n="183" who="S0266" trans="overlap">so are you charging him for this stuff? or are you?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0268">well I I said you know in because you're going to help us with this project I'll do these rackets for nothing he was <trunc>wi</trunc> very willing to pay for them but I the trade off was that he's going to take part in this project</u>
<u n="185" who="S0266">well that's good</u>
<u n="186" who="S0268">so I thought well that's that's means it's free from he thinks he's getting something for nothing and I think I'm getting something for nothing or very little so if he keeps an eye on the rackets I've colour coded them and marked them so I'll know exactly what's happened so he can see whether the ones that I've given him are you know have more protection and I'll slip in four or five more rackets into his fleet</u>
<u n="187" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/> fleet</u>
<u n="188" who="S0268">fleet of rackets and and see what <unclear/> I will actually phone him up eh in <trunc>a</trunc>after half term and say have you got any rackets? and I'll put these this additional measure on and see whether it works the best solution though as I explained to you is to have the rackets made properly so that the strings don't protrude</u>
<u n="189" who="S0266">well that's a huge business project</u>
<u n="190" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well it's a good project that that means a trip to <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> you've got contacts in <anon type="place"/> maybe you could chat up some of your contacts?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0266" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0268">have you?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0266">well I don't think they'd be much good at making rackets</u>
<u n="194" who="S0268">well they might be able to introduce me to the people who might be able to do it or at least do some research in their own language no?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0266">mm well it would cost you so much money to pay <unclear/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0268" trans="overlap">I know but but but it solves the problem that's and maybe they're aware of it and they just want to carry on with these rackets knowing that they're going to keep coming back with repeat orders because the strings are going to break maybe they know all about that maybe they're very canny or maybe no maybe it's just one of those things they never bothered to address</u>
<u n="197" who="S0266">but it's been happening for years hasn't it?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0268">I presume it will be <unclear/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0266" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0268">presumably it has they just need protection that's where the cable ties come in it's like such a good idea but I I think there might be something that you can put some kind of guard that you could put and lock on so it was tamper proof which would be one operation well one operation as opposed to six or seven operations</u>
<u n="201" who="S0266" trans="overlap">no but why? you you just need to mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0268">that's all I'm saying</u>
<u n="203" who="S0266">you just deeper grooves don't you?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0268">well that's yeah no ideally that's what they need deeper grooves exactly but there might be <trunc>some</trunc>something that you can clip on cos you you said that you can remember when you were playing tennis at a high level that you used to clip something on to your racket plastic and I I can</u>
<u n="205" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah a guard but it affected it affected the play that's why <unclear/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well yes but you're you're a very advanced player you see so</u>
<u n="207" who="S0266">oh yeah yeah yeah oh yeah yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0268">well it's a very good question to ask but I will I will do that erm it's it's worth cos you've got to experiment haven't you? you've got to do your research</u>
<u n="209" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0268">and know that like they will stay on they won't rattle about and eh they won't after their playing so I'll do that tomorrow I'll put the very light ones on I think not the these ones are smaller <unclear/> see these these are narrower and shorter</u>
<u n="211" who="S0266" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0268">so they they're even better maybe</u>
<u n="213" who="S0266" trans="overlap">erm so yeah can you just make this machine go so that I can do a</u>
<u n="214" who="S0268">I need to put my glasses on for that</u>
<u n="215" who="S0266">well they're erm a shave without any numbers</u>
<u n="216" who="S0268" trans="overlap">oh I see I see what you mean have you finished?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0266">no I've just got to do the back of the neck</u>
<u n="218" who="S0268">oh right okay well that's what I meant but you can still does it look alright?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0266">it's too short and you've got a bleeding ear but otherwise it's very good</u>
<u n="220" who="S0268" trans="overlap">oh ah otherwise it's fine yeah well that's good I'll come back to this salon in future then</u>
<u n="221" who="S0266">sorry about that but I don't know what happened really</u>
<u n="222" who="S0268" trans="overlap">that's alright mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0266">right erm it's okay I'll just do this last bit</u>
<u n="224" who="S0268">yeah that was a good idea to try it out first but if I can get these rackets in the hands of these kids erm the next half the next half of the term I'll have a really good idea about how they work maybe I'll put different types you can actually get quite thick ones so if you had <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="225" who="S0266">sorry can you not move and look the other way it's like it's like look slightly to the right</u>
<u n="226" who="S0268">oh right okay so it's possible to have thicker ones but that's quite a lot more expensive</u>
<u n="227" who="S0266">can you look that way? thank you</u>
<u n="228" who="S0268">so</u>
<u n="229" who="S0266">head that way but down no that's it</u>
<u n="230" who="S0268">you can have like double double the width but it's interesting obviously the the more plastic they put in the more they're going to charge you so</u>
<u n="231" who="S0266">and the other way thank you</u>
<u n="232" who="S0268">and the other thing is the more plastic you have at the top of the racket the erm the heavier it's going to be and erm <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> anyway it could be it's a Dragon's Den type of idea but I don't think <unclear/> would go for it did you know he used to coach tennis? that's how he started making money</u>
<u n="233" who="S0266">who?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0268"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was a very good tennis player</u>
<u n="235" who="S0266" trans="overlap">oh the Dragon's Den man</u>
<u n="236" who="S0268">yeah so when he was fifteen or sixteen he coached tennis for money and that's what put the entrepreneurial bug into him I think</u>
<u n="237" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0268">that's how he started making money he's a big tall bloke isn't he?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0266">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0268">so maybe he'd go for this idea</u>
<u n="241" who="S0266">right that completes the hairdressing don't look in the mirror cos I don't think you'll be very pleased</u>
<u n="242" who="S0268" trans="overlap">oh thank you very much <pause dur="short"/> what am I'm balder now?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0266">a bit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0268">really?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0266">well you shouldn't have let it grow so long erm and then it would have been easier somehow to cut or I need to go to evening classes in haircutting</u>
<u n="246" who="S0268">so what <trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="247" who="S0266" trans="overlap">it it was so long that it I had to cut with scissors</u>
<u n="248" who="S0268" trans="overlap">why don't you ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's or she hasn't got who's got level three? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0266" trans="overlap">well you'd have you'd have you'd have to go the salon and pay twenty-five quid</u>
<u n="250" who="S0268"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got level three so</u>
<u n="251" who="S0266"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0268">so or maybe I should go there do you think she'd do <unclear/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0266">well yeah and pay and pay twenty-five quid</u>
<u n="254" who="S0268">is that how much they charge?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0266">no you'd probably get about fifteen</u>
<u n="256" who="S0268">but even so I can remember paying no when I was about I think two shillings was about the going rate</u>
<u n="257" who="S0266" trans="overlap">anyway <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0268">and that's what ten P in today's money</u>
<u n="259" who="S0266">mm times have changed haven't they? and I need I need a big tip as well ten percent</u>
<u n="260" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><unclear/> really? do you do you tip when you go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0266">yep</u>
<u n="262" who="S0268">do you? and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0268">well don't they build that into the price?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0266">no it's an English tradition to being a hairdresser anyway that's enough for now</u>
<u n="266" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well they should do ah right have they got a fleet of scissors?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0266">I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0268">there we are</u>
<u n="269" who="S0266">right</u>
<u n="270" who="S0268">so are you are you supportive of this idea? do you think it's going to work</u>
<u n="271" who="S0266">yeah I think you should just try it out and see how it goes</u>
<u n="272" who="S0268">well I will do</u>
<u n="273" who="S0266">and with a new haircut you might <unclear/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0268" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I'll be aerodynamic</u>
<u n="275" who="S0266">yep</u>
<u n="276" who="S0268">so in some ways you know that that's good because the total package means I'm probably lighter even with the ties in the racket</u>
<u n="277" who="S0266">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0268">but I haven't got as much hair</u>
<u n="279" who="S0266">erm if you're approaching business men in discussions they'll probably prefer the shorter hair cut</u>
<u n="280" who="S0268" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> you reckon?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0266">maybe let's let's take the positives</u>
<u n="282" who="S0268" trans="overlap">well I don't <unclear/> I think you done it sort of you butchered me a bit</u>
<u n="283" who="S0266">mm best not to look in the mirror</u>
<u n="284" who="S0268">mm okay</u>
<u n="285" who="S0266">okay I'm going to turn off the machine now</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
