<text id="SZP6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:59:43</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0519 S0520 S0521</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Hunsonby, Cumbria</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>moving house, house prices, southern vs northern England</topics>
		<activity>talking about the VW scandal</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0519">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Dublin, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith, `</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Recently retired maths teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0520">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead, UK`</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>India/Thailand/UK (Hunsoney</hab_city>
				<hab_country></hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Transcriber, Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0521">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Walsall, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Former role as technical esport of development planning in oil industry</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0521">in the nineteen twenties to produce a vehicle which was <pause dur="short"/> universally affordable in Germany</u>
<u n="2" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0521">during the nineteen thirties Hitler got to hear about the project</u>
<u n="4" who="S0520">oh yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0521">and he desperately wanted to rival the Americans and be able to afford cars and erm they he they settles on an amount of money that the car would be built for which A was totally unrealistic</u>
<u n="6" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0521">in the sense that they couldn't build it for that small amount and B was still way above the heads of most of the German population to buy</u>
<u n="8" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0521">so in fact the whole project was a disaster and it says that erm the only reason that Volkswagen succeeded was due to the corruption of the Nazi party</u>
<u n="10" who="S0520">meaning what? they subsidised or?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0521">presumably sold money to fund it</u>
<u n="12" who="S0520">quite a history for the company isn't it? I don't think that many people associate with the Nazi party any more <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0521">and they <trunc>desi</trunc> they devised a payment system <foreign lang="ger">fünf mark die woche musst du sparen</foreign> <trunc>fi</trunc>five five marks a week</u>
<u n="14" who="S0520" trans="overlap">five marks a week</u>
<u n="15" who="S0521">so they were supposed people were supposed to save five marks a week and eventually buy the car three hundred and thirty-six thousand people signed up to it but none of them <trunc>a</trunc>actually ever got every got a car <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0519">oh no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="short"/> people didn't really start driving cars until when? like normal people the fifties?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0521">did you know that Volkswagen the Beetle was designed by Porsche</u>
<u n="19" who="S0520">was it?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0521">Porsche a man called Porsche who of course famously started up the the Porsche make but erm he was responsible for the design and subsequently took a share of the Volkswagen company and now today he own Porsche the Porsche family owns fifty-one percent of Volkswagen</u>
<u n="21" who="S0520" trans="overlap">of Volkswagen? mm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0521">which is the biggest <trunc>co</trunc> car company in the world</u>
<u n="23" who="S0520">is it? <pause dur="long"/> you don't see German cars in Asia at all imagine they're having some competition now</u>
<u n="24" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you can't believe they can have cheated like that</u>
<u n="25" who="S0521">I was just saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that there's</u>
<u n="26" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's quite a disaster</u>
<u n="27" who="S0521">a a there's a BBC and they've actually looked into the the history of the managing director who apparently two things first of all was desperate to get into the US market</u>
<u n="28" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0521">and he publiclysaid that the emissions that they the US demanded to to satisfy were too expensive to develop the technology for so he's quoted as saying that some time ago</u>
<u n="30" who="S0520">America have stricter emissions laws that we do?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0521" trans="overlap">stricter emissions than Europe yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0520">really? <pause dur="short"/> that's surprising <vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't notice in Houston that anyone was really that worried</u>
<u n="33" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no they well the they call buy a car</u>
<u n="34" who="S0520">four by fours</u>
<u n="35" who="S0519">so huge that it would cancel that out</u>
<u n="36" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0521" trans="overlap">well it's a little bit to do with diesel because Americans don't like diesels never have and of course they always had a reputation of being polluters</u>
<u n="38" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="39" who="S0521">whereas in Europe the diesel is a lot more popular</u>
<u n="40" who="S0520">isn't it more efficient diesel?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0519">it's a a a less polluting</u>
<u n="42" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I thought it was better yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0519">in the modern diesels but now we're hearing that in fact the the thing that they used to measure pollutants against diesel now has a different one that is worse</u>
<u n="44" who="S0520">oh cool <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0519">so erm sadly we went down that road and now fifty percent of the cars in Britain are diesel</u>
<u n="46" who="S0520">because of Volkswagen lies or because of a general deception?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no because we the perception at that time was that certain things were the worst pollutants and diesel had less of those</u>
<u n="48" who="S0520">oh</u>
<u n="49" who="S0519">erm but now</u>
<u n="50" who="S0521">that's true it's its CO two emissions whereas</u>
<u n="51" who="S0520" trans="overlap">measuring a different</u>
<u n="52" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0521">diesel is apparently very bad because it it spews out particles little particles</u>
<u n="54" who="S0519">and they didn't know about those at the time</u>
<u n="55" who="S0520">I bet they did <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0521" trans="overlap">which which are exactly very damaging to the lungs</u>
<u n="57" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I bet they looked at the report and stuck it in the bottom drawer somewhere</u>
<u n="58" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/> developed a computer programme to annihilate it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0520">so it creates smog doesn't it? diesel that's what I've heard</u>
<u n="60" who="S0521">yeah so it's these particles which sort of are in the in the air that people breathe in</u>
<u n="61" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0521">which they think are really bad for you</u>
<u n="63" who="S0520">mm thanks mum it's nice that bread</u>
<u n="64" who="S0519">it's lovely bread isn't it?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0519">I I really quite like it chunky as well if you know if you have an if you have it like with some soup of something it feels</u>
<u n="67" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh yeah I do as well but I don't enjoy the fact that I have to slice it before I eat it it's like one more step in the process</u>
<u n="68" who="S0519" trans="overlap">ah I must say I do usually have it sliced but sometimes I just can't be bothered to stand in the queue and wait for the little lady to notice my existence</u>
<u n="69" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0519">and they don't have a erm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0520">they should have like a self-service shouldn't they?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0519" trans="overlap">they don't have a bell or something you know they just er all you can do is wait</u>
<u n="73" who="S0520">no that's true they should build a machine that normal folk can use just put it there</u>
<u n="74" who="S0519">slice their hands off</u>
<u n="75" who="S0520">it was quite hard to use I remember when I worked in the bakery in <anon type="place"/> it was quite hard to use the bread slicer properly like you know it had it sort of had there was a certain technique</u>
<u n="76" who="S0519">it's getting it out the other end keeping it all together</u>
<u n="77" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah keeping the slices together</u>
<u n="78" who="S0519">and lifting it onto the</u>
<u n="79" who="S0520">and then it all gets a bit squished</u>
<u n="80" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0520"><foreign lang="dut">bakkerij Stijnman</foreign></u>
<u n="82" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I bet it's all still there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0519">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0520">have you ever had a Volkswagen then? no</u>
<u n="86" who="S0519">I've driven one</u>
<u n="87" who="S0520">Mini's are Volkswagen now aren't they?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0521">sorry?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0520">Mini's?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0519">BMW</u>
<u n="91" who="S0520">oh BMW</u>
<u n="92" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0520">cool <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was showing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the the <trunc>fa</trunc> the photo album by photo album that dad made</u>
<u n="94" who="S0519">mm mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0520">one of the pictures was us in standing outside somewhere with this with the with the old really old BMW the white one <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was funny to see it had it forever didn't we?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0519">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0521">the Granada was the best car wasn't it?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0519">the Granada was cool at the beginning <vocal desc="laugh"/> it just er lost ground</u>
<u n="99" who="S0520">the Granada oh you had a Mini and you had a <trunc>ve</trunc>Viva is it?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0520">what was that? was that a Ford?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0521">Vauxhall</u>
<u n="103" who="S0520">Vauxhall yeah <pause dur="long"/> and a Sierra I remember that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0520">got stolen <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0519">did he like the pictures of you when you were little</u>
<u n="108" who="S0520">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm I told him about a gazillion time that I'm the youngest child but he always goes oh you're the youngest</u>
<u n="109" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0520">I don't know what it is he can't quite register it somehow</u>
<u n="111" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0520">he's in the middle so</u>
<u n="113" who="S0521">he had a complicated family didn't he?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0520">yeah lots of mothers and fathers all over the shop</u>
<u n="115" who="S0521" trans="overlap">lots of step relationships going on</u>
<u n="116" who="S0520">yeah the amazing part is how they all get together every Friday</u>
<u n="117" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0520">all the various wives of his dad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0519">quite incredible</u>
<u n="120" who="S0520">I know they're all really normal about it I mean it's not that simple <trunc>a</trunc>and his mother is a character as he put it she does make problems sometimes but erm somehow it evolved to be that you know she's sort of stayed involved which is really good it's her children and it's her grandchildren</u>
<u n="121" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0519">mm mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0520">and erm <pause dur="short"/> and she kind of needs support she's a bit well she's very ill for a start but she's also just kind of vulnerable mentally but for instance <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was the one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is the stepmother</u>
<u n="124" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0520">the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was the one who kind of said I mean not the one but kind of said that for the holiday that she'd prefer it if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum wasn't wasn't coming to Thailand</u>
<u n="126" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0520">you know like we could it was obviously never said that that was case but we could infer that it was her choice not only because she's a quite difficult person to have around but also you know probably there's lots of they are friends but I think there's lots of complications under the surface</u>
<u n="128" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0520">they were friends originally as well</u>
<u n="131" who="S0519">oh god</u>
<u n="132" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so it was quite difficult and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is</u>
<u n="133" who="S0519">so remind me again</u>
<u n="134" who="S0520">really different to her as well</u>
<u n="135" who="S0519">let's have a recap</u>
<u n="136" who="S0520">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mother was married to this guy</u>
<u n="137" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0520">and had a child with him a son he that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the oldest brother</u>
<u n="139" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0520">they then separated and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum married <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s real father <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0519" trans="overlap">dad mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0520">they had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and they had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sister <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they had two children together</u>
<u n="143" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0520">and then but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad assumed the role of father fully over <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because the other guy disappeared basically so really <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s father completely raised</u>
<u n="145" who="S0519">brought up the three children</u>
<u n="146" who="S0520" trans="overlap">brought up the three <trunc>child</trunc> brought the older son up as well as his own in every sense</u>
<u n="147" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0520">and he was fully inside their family</u>
<u n="149" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0520">although he does have a relationship with his father now his real father kind of came back into the picture but it's quite sort of erm and I think sometimes I have the sense he has a bit of a chip on his shoulder about now being the real son</u>
<u n="151" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0520">of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and the don't get along that well now</u>
<u n="153" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0520">not because of any blood reason I think you know it's more just different personalities isn't it?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0520">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the oldest brother he's a bit of a character as well he's quite arrogant sometimes and he's a little bit awkward with people he's not that easy to get along with at the best of times you know he has a sweet side but he's kind of no a bit bit different so that I think adds to it's because erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad in my from my perspective clearly prefers <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his youngest son or <trunc>cl</trunc> you know clearly wants to wants to spend time with them or whatever you can tell in by</u>
<u n="157" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0520">so then they broke up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was about seven years old I think? and then erm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0519">did he stay with his mum?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0520">he stayed with his mum and it was a really hard time</u>
<u n="161" who="S0519">and of the three all three stayed with the mum?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0520">they all stayed with the mum and I don't know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did I know that him and his sister stayed with the mum but it was very very bloody and awful</u>
<u n="163" who="S0519" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0521">oh dear what the divorce you mean?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0520">the divorce it was really not nice and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum kind of was awful really</u>
<u n="166" who="S0521">oh dear</u>
<u n="167" who="S0520">and she was very erm broken like you know so it wasn't a good time but somehow it's ended up even despite that being quite mended which is amazing really and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad continued to see the all the time but he was much less <trunc>in</trunc> around you know he also works extremely hard he's a doctor a very high profile doctor and he's all I mean what it was funny <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s always not you know said that he wasn't there that much but like I I was talking to him and I was like so what was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like when he was a child you know? and he sort of like gave a funny answer and passed it on you know and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>wa</trunc> said to me later you know my father couldn't answer that question cos he couldn't remember <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0521">he didn't know</u>
<u n="169" who="S0520">he just didn't he just wasn't there</u>
<u n="170" who="S0519">mm mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0520">you know but it's that kind of thing not that there's any resentment on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s part they actually get on really well and his father's a very <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> I don't know how to describe <pause dur="short"/> he's a very moral principled good solid</u>
<u n="172" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0520">person you know he's really unusually so he's got a lot of integrity he's provided a lot of he's provided a lot of good example you know as well and I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really admires him in certain things</u>
<u n="174" who="S0519">mm mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0519">so then he married</u>
<u n="177" who="S0520" trans="overlap">so then he married again and it just so happened that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had previously been the girlfriend of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mother's first husband</u>
<u n="178" who="S0519">oh my god</u>
<u n="179" who="S0520">and they were friends subsequently so and then it again happened that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came into the picture</u>
<u n="180" who="S0519">oh gosh</u>
<u n="181" who="S0520">and by that stage they were quite <trunc>o</trunc> like in their early forties so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> immediately had a child</u>
<u n="182" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0520">and that's the youngest son and he I mean then the now the three of them are kind of</u>
<u n="184" who="S0519">so when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes back really the person he grew up with is his mum</u>
<u n="185" who="S0520">more or less but as time went on I think he spent more time with his father as well</u>
<u n="186" who="S0519">okay</u>
<u n="187" who="S0520">so it doesn't seem to em that he's closer to her in fact it might even be the opposite</u>
<u n="188" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no it's a right and so he would <trunc>of</trunc> he would potentially stay with the dad if he needed to</u>
<u n="189" who="S0520">he stays with the dad if he stays he doesn't stay with his mum cos it's just too difficult for them personally but they he sees his mum a lot and he's the most caring of her of all the children because the other children find it too her too difficult as a character and just have a lot of difficult you know problems really and I can see why she's very <pause dur="short"/> er erratic kind of person and she's quite and can be quite unpleasant</u>
<u n="190" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0520">to she's manipulative you know she's got things where it's like mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just a good boy and he's able he he grew <trunc>o</trunc> grew out of it and now he you know he just tries to take care of her the best he can and and er be around cos she's she has emphysema</u>
<u n="193" who="S0521">oh right <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0520">and you know she's</u>
<u n="195" who="S0521">what's his surname?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0520"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0521"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> I think I remember you telling me that yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0520"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah I don't know what her surname is so yeah it is quite complicated and there are a lot of internal her the sister and the mother have a lot of er tension between them but they still get together every week you know and she still is is very much part of the grandchildren's lives as well I suppose when you have your own children there's a</u>
<u n="199" who="S0519">it's easier</u>
<u n="200" who="S0520">you want them to have the grandparents and not to want to keep them and values the family values are very strong in Israel like the the kind of bond is is is is erm very you know whatever has gone on as you can see in that whole mess of a scenario you know there's still a very strong sense of everyone having a certain commitment to each other</u>
<u n="201" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0520">which is how it always is family it's just different cultural</u>
<u n="203" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0521">they all live close together then?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0520">yeah they all live in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0521">same part of <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0520">within striking distance and the kids as well growing up in <anon type="place"/> which is nice although they have considered leaving er both of the couples well no I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a and his wife are kind of celebrities in Israel and they love this life of urban life you know they're kind of that's their context</u>
<u n="209" who="S0521" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="210" who="S0520">but the his sister is very much thought about <trunc>le</trunc> you know moving out to a kibbutz or having more of a cos it's you know it's like bringing I see that in cities in England you know bringing your children up in the middle of the city it's quite er</u>
<u n="211" who="S0519">and that's a special city you know with a lot more complications</u>
<u n="212" who="S0520">mm well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> grew up in <anon type="place"/> as well and so has his brother his younger brother goes to an anthroposophical school</u>
<u n="213" who="S0521">anthro what?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0520"><trunc>anthro</trunc><trunc>antr</trunc> anthroposophical anthroposophical?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0521">anthroposophical</u>
<u n="216" who="S0520">you know er Rudolph Steiner it's a bit like</u>
<u n="217" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's like in</u>
<u n="218" who="S0520">we</u>
<u n="219" who="S0519" trans="overlap">Camphill</u>
<u n="220" who="S0520">Camp oh it is Camphill</u>
<u n="221" who="S0521" trans="overlap">Camphill oh right yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0520" trans="overlap">in fact but it's also like what's it called in Holland? m m m</u>
<u n="223" who="S0521">Montessori</u>
<u n="224" who="S0519">Montessori</u>
<u n="225" who="S0520">Montessori</u>
<u n="226" who="S0519">it's a little bit like</u>
<u n="227" who="S0520">there are similarities</u>
<u n="228" who="S0519">there are relations</u>
<u n="229" who="S0520">yeah so not only because of that but he is quite an unusual sixteen-year-old I've met other children who grew up within that system and it's quite an alternative approach to development and education</u>
<u n="230" who="S0519"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s son went to a Steiner school</u>
<u n="231" who="S0520">really? so he's also a bit different isn't he?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0519">yeah <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc> <trunc>no</trunc> <trunc>e</trunc> not er very bright</u>
<u n="235" who="S0520" trans="overlap">normal yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0519">not erm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0520">no I don't mean <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't mean</u>
<u n="238" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you know there's but the Camphill community in <anon type="place"/> is specifically for people will educational learning difficulties</u>
<u n="239" who="S0520">mm that can be an aspect but no this is a normal school</u>
<u n="240" who="S0519" trans="overlap">this is yeah the same for theirs was a also a dual language so it was English-Dutch</u>
<u n="241" who="S0520">cool mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0519">and they loved that and they liked that it wasn't just your average school</u>
<u n="243" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0520">it's a great system erm and they in Israel they make sure that at the end you there's a kind of diversion with the normal school curriculum and the normal school system so that you do end up qualified to go to university</u>
<u n="245" who="S0519">totally yeah well he went he's got doing maths at Leiden</u>
<u n="246" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm Leiden yeah I remember you saying but from what I I've met a few people who went to those kind of schools and what I've I've just noticed that they're more innocent</u>
<u n="247" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0520">like you know when I was <trunc>si</trunc> you know we when we were sixteen there was a lot going on</u>
<u n="249" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0520">well you've worked with sixteen-year-old you know what they're like</u>
<u n="252" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0520">ninety percent of time you're thinking about going out and having fun and boys and all of this but he's not like that at all</u>
<u n="254" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0520">he's got lovely friend but he's quite a sort of innocent naive boy</u>
<u n="256" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0520">he's a really sweet boy</u>
<u n="258" who="S0519">I think that can happen as well if you're an only child</u>
<u n="259" who="S0520">of older parents</u>
<u n="260" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and you haven't got of older parents</u>
<u n="261" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0519">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be just the same</u>
<u n="263" who="S0520">agreed it's like a very protected environment isn't it?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0519">and even though she in a an an <trunc>or</trunc> an ordinary school I think she'll be very protected and erm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0520">yeah there's something there isn't it? like he's very adult and very used to adult company like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad is seventy so similar to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really</u>
<u n="267" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0520">he's sixteen and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a bit younger but she's in her sixties and they're both erm great</u>
<u n="270" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0520">you know still very living and both have their careers going on and whatever but they're they're erm they're little family situation is just the three of them most of the time so it does make a difference I think</u>
<u n="272" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0520">but they're a sweet little family</u>
<u n="274" who="S0519">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0520">so yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yes so I was interested so so you were saying the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad is seventy so he was born in forty-five but that was already in Israel</u>
<u n="277" who="S0520">yes so</u>
<u n="278" who="S0521">they they they set up there was some sort of state then before the official it was forty-eight wasn't it? after the war</u>
<u n="279" who="S0520">forty-eight yeah I don't know exactly how it worked</u>
<u n="280" who="S0521" trans="overlap">so something must have happened before that</u>
<u n="281" who="S0520">it did and there were</u>
<u n="282" who="S0521" trans="overlap">cos they had already migrated <trunc>immigra</trunc>immigrated</u>
<u n="283" who="S0520">erm there was a Zionist movement in Europe in the nineteen thirties which wasn't directly connected to the Holocaust it started before that</u>
<u n="284" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0520">so people had already started to go over in the thirties and set up farms and cooperatives Jewish farms and cooperatives they bought land from the Palestinians</u>
<u n="286" who="S0521">okay</u>
<u n="287" who="S0520">who live there at the time I don't know what the country was called before it was Israel</u>
<u n="288" who="S0521">be Palestine</u>
<u n="289" who="S0520" trans="overlap">Palestine yeah so they went over bought land and started up communities and this was happening already before the Second World War</u>
<u n="290" who="S0521" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="291" who="S0520">and then obviously in the lead up to the Second World War and during it a lot more people started to move and travel and emigrate to emigrate? migrate? I'm not sure to Israel to escape the persecution and I don't know what happened in these intervening years I think there was a lot of people in nineteen forty-five nine when the camps were liberated almost all of those people went to Israel</u>
<u n="292" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="293" who="S0520">and erm I don't know why but I imagine it's almost similar to what's happening now it was like this is where our new home is this is where our better life can be you know because Zionism wasn't common necessarily it was like a movement that started up later but</u>
<u n="294" who="S0521">but erm his grandfather was was a prisoner of war in Hungary was it?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0520" trans="overlap">was it I think they were both in a concentration camp his grandparents in Hungary and they escaped</u>
<u n="296" who="S0521">oh yeah it's not the right word prisoner of war is it?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0520">yeah no that's never mind</u>
<u n="298" who="S0521">but they they they escaped rather than they were liberated in forty-five</u>
<u n="299" who="S0520" trans="overlap">they were they escaped</u>
<u n="300" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0520">and they erm went to Israel in nineteen forty-four forty-five and then immediately I guess had a child but they joined one of these communities cooperative communities that had already been set up which were later called the kibbutz but the people that originally went were Zionists and very staunch socialists they were like <trunc>com</trunc></u>
<u n="302" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0520">had a <trunc>com</trunc> almost like a communist ideology of of</u>
<u n="304" who="S0521">no</u>
<u n="305" who="S0520">and they wanted to establish this kind of utopian life in Israel that was their vision and that was the beginnings of Israel really I mean it became an official state only afterwards but a lot of land was bought from the Palestinian's before anyone drew any lines and started to make things complicated and I don't even really know I'm sure I've been told I don't really know how the the concept of the occupied <trunc>t</trunc>territories came about I think it was slightly later there was a war</u>
<u n="306" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="307" who="S0520">that erm the Jewish or Israeli army won and they claimed land during the war and that was the occupied what the occupied territories are now</u>
<u n="308" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0520">and ever since then they've wanted it back</u>
<u n="310" who="S0521">I've got the feeling that was in the sixties actually</u>
<u n="311" who="S0520">I think it was yeah so I guess in the first ten fifteen years there was just a kind of erm beginnings of the Jewish state</u>
<u n="312" who="S0521">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0520">and you know building it up and infrastructure and so forth and some very idealistic leaders who came and then there was a retaliation from the neighbouring countries</u>
<u n="314" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0519">that's the hugely sad thing isn't it? that it's really hard to understand why all the neighbours want Israel</u>
<u n="316" who="S0520">I know anti-Semitism?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and Israel has retaliated and fought for their rights</u>
<u n="318" who="S0521">anti-Jewish</u>
<u n="319" who="S0519">and so on and you know you you only have to meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and remember that he's saying that his grandparents lost all of their family to just feel that impact you know that this is a young man who has this history</u>
<u n="320" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0519">and he he's now he still had that history it's his grandparents it's not</u>
<u n="322" who="S0520">yeah there are still people living in Israel who who erm escaped from concentration camps in in Germany they're still alive you know?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0519">and erm so you know you you can't underestimate the impact of that but of course they show a terrible face to the world in their fight back</u>
<u n="324" who="S0520">yeah aggressive</u>
<u n="325" who="S0519">aggressive <trunc>e</trunc>erm it it now feels the opposite it feels like they don't want the Palestinians to have any land and that's not you know that's how it feels but it it's not the whole truth</u>
<u n="326" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0519">and we know that but it's erm it's it's really hard really hard to you know you just you don't understand why everybody why does Iran and Syria and all of these people why do they hate the Jews?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0520">just anti-Semitic means they only want there's only that's the only reason</u>
<u n="329" who="S0519">but why? where does it come from?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah exactly it's true</u>
<u n="331" who="S0519">why do you have to hate someone?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0520">it's really just silly isn't it?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0519">but then I mean it's huge I mean imagine say it was us if there's same country next door</u>
<u n="334" who="S0520">next door yeah or all of them frankly</u>
<u n="335" who="S0519">and they think you all should die</u>
<u n="336" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0519">that's that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0520">well I think that's the justification between behind one of the justifications behind their aggressive military show</u>
<u n="339" who="S0519">mm mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0520">you know whenever they are attacked form one side they show with incredible force that they're not going to sit down and not retaliate and why? because</u>
<u n="341" who="S0519">and you understand that history their history was that they were totally persecuted almost to the point of annihilation</u>
<u n="342" who="S0520">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0519">so now they're going to say</u>
<u n="344" who="S0520">we are here</u>
<u n="345" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you won't be doing that again here we are</u>
<u n="346" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and it's the it's the kind of enormity you know Iran Syria Lebanon Egypt Jordan is the only kind of slightly neutral sitting on the fence</u>
<u n="347" who="S0521" trans="overlap"><unclear/> peaceful aren't they?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0520">no idea why that is</u>
<u n="349" who="S0519">thank god for them you know</u>
<u n="350" who="S0520">you know all of these countries don't want Israel to exist it's not like you know erm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0519">we don't get on we'll just</u>
<u n="352" who="S0520">we don't get on or we want to negotiate our borders you know they say they want to annihilate it</u>
<u n="353" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0520">and it's kind of like if you don't show yourselves to be a very strong military force that's what's going to happen in that's their that's the idea you know</u>
<u n="355" who="S0521">I suppose there's also the connection with the West isn't there? cos the Americans massively support Israel don't they?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0520">they have done historically I mean Obama less so</u>
<u n="357" who="S0521">armaments</u>
<u n="358" who="S0520">but Clinton did very much so</u>
<u n="359" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0519">you can <trunc>un</trunc> I I don't</u>
<u n="361" who="S0520" trans="overlap">there's a huge Jewish population in America that has to be erm part of the reason</u>
<u n="362" who="S0519" trans="overlap">has been</u>
<u n="363" who="S0521">I believe so yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0520">but not only not particularly large but let's say influential</u>
<u n="365" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0519">well yes but I mean <trunc>hi</trunc>historically it's always been so but I I you can understand Obama stepping back at the moment because</u>
<u n="367" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm because yeah well Netanyahu's a bit off the loop</u>
<u n="368" who="S0519" trans="overlap">Israel appear to never want to have peace with the Palestinians and you think you think they could they could try harder</u>
<u n="369" who="S0520">you do yeah but then if you look historically they did try harder</u>
<u n="370" who="S0519">I know you've said that and explained it before but</u>
<u n="371" who="S0520">and you have and it didn't work out why?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0519" trans="overlap">the other side also say you know well maybe they weren't ready then but they are now you know who who knows you can't</u>
<u n="373" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm it's difficult I mean like with Gaza for instance first of all they were firing rockets into Israel you're talking about the war last year you know that is what started the you know fight</u>
<u n="374" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="375" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0519">we know that but the the</u>
<u n="377" who="S0520">so they are much weaker but they're also</u>
<u n="378" who="S0519" trans="overlap">the little the little rockets are like you know throwing a cricket ball</u>
<u n="379" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not quite like that they're landing in people's home towns and stuff then who is in charge of Gaza? a terrorist organisation</u>
<u n="380" who="S0521" trans="overlap">the Hezbollah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0519">I know but what can the and the Palestinians have voted for them</u>
<u n="382" who="S0520">so why would Europe stand for that? why would Europe stand in support of a terrorist organisation that doesn't make sense</u>
<u n="383" who="S0519" trans="overlap">they but they they're were vote elected</u>
<u n="384" who="S0520">so? it's ridiculous you know</u>
<u n="385" who="S0521" trans="overlap">they were elected yeah it's not not it's not Hezbollah is it?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0520">they represent a completely wrong value system <trunc>a</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> whether they've been elected or not you know? they are the same erm <pause dur="short"/> let's say er <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0519">well we want</u>
<u n="388" who="S0520" trans="overlap">group of people more or less that have been attacking America and Europe and you know in in a way of of of complete violence it doesn't to me it makes very little sense that Europe takes their side that side because of the history</u>
<u n="389" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0520">of why Israel was established in the first place you know we have a responsibility</u>
<u n="391" who="S0519">Europe takes the side of the the huge underdog</u>
<u n="392" who="S0520">it's no I just don't think it's an excuse it's an underdog but it's you know it's essentially</u>
<u n="393" who="S0519">it's it's the same way like erm you know the</u>
<u n="394" who="S0520">and they shouldn't I mean it doesn't make sense that to call them the underdog either in the wider picture because Israel is a tiny country in the Middle East</u>
<u n="395" who="S0519">no you only have to look at the pictures on the television <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can't you can't deny that Palestine is a very poor place and a place with erm where people are living in ruins and there's no education and hospitals and all of these things and that they're throwing you know grenades at Israel</u>
<u n="396" who="S0520">it's not no</u>
<u n="397" who="S0519">and Israel are throwing bombs back</u>
<u n="398" who="S0521" trans="overlap">rockets</u>
<u n="399" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it's not true at all</u>
<u n="400" who="S0519">in in times at night</u>
<u n="401" who="S0520" trans="overlap">the only reason why the the only reason why we didn't see the devastating effects of the missiles that were being thrown directed at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no but they're still huge I'm just saying in terms of size</u>
<u n="403" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it's not an argument</u>
<u n="404" who="S0519">it's because that's what they've got erm so they are the underdog they are the the weaker erm they don't have that might they don't have the er capacity to inflict they have capacity to inflict some deaths</u>
<u n="405" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's the nature of terrorism though is that these that is is they're groups which are less powerful in terms of military force</u>
<u n="406" who="S0521">terrorism is the right word isn't it? yeah <unclear/> nation</u>
<u n="407" who="S0520" trans="overlap">they take other types of violent actions because they they're not they can't they're not an organised army</u>
<u n="408" who="S0521" trans="overlap">so it's terrorist against a nation</u>
<u n="409" who="S0519">well I don't I don't understand that word</u>
<u n="410" who="S0521">what?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0519">because <trunc>Pa</trunc>Palestine wants to be a nation but Israel won't let them</u>
<u n="412" who="S0520">that's not how simple it is at all</u>
<u n="413" who="S0519">but it's the truth</u>
<u n="414" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it's not no but what happen listen to what happened in the with Rabin in the nineteen seventies they made an agreement</u>
<u n="415" who="S0519">they told me that before I know</u>
<u n="416" who="S0520">they gave the whole of Palestine</u>
<u n="417" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but we can't go back to the seventies</u>
<u n="418" who="S0520">no but listen to what happened they gave the whole of Palestine er to as er as a country they withdrew the Jewish settlers from from the West Bank they split Jerusalem in half this was the deal what happened? the Palestine's the day after attacked Israel they didn't want that agreement they wanted Israel to be gone you know so they're not just wanting their own land and then we're all happy you know that's what the sensible good people on both sides want but the not cool and not sensible people on both sides want the other people to be gone</u>
<u n="419" who="S0519" trans="overlap">don't <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="420" who="S0520">so that's the problem</u>
<u n="421" who="S0519" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0520">you know cos those that those two extremities will never find a peaceful solution now why did people give up you know in Israel in terms of and they haven't completely I mean the left still <trunc>s</trunc> represents those people who want a peaceful two-state solution</u>
<u n="423" who="S0519">but like you like you're saying the trouble is that the majority of people in Israel are voting for the right who won't negotiate</u>
<u n="424" who="S0520">now they are</u>
<u n="425" who="S0519">and the <trunc>volun</trunc> <trunc>ma</trunc> majority of people in Palestine are voting for the terrorists</u>
<u n="426" who="S0520" trans="overlap">terrorists yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0519">who won't negotiate and there we are</u>
<u n="428" who="S0520" trans="overlap">well yeah there we are buggered <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0519">stymied</u>
<u n="430" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> stymied I mean I'm not</u>
<u n="431" who="S0519">but</u>
<u n="432" who="S0520">justifying everything I'm just trying to put it in perspective because the media in Europe comes gives a very biased perspective of the situation</u>
<u n="433" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no I I I mean I started by saying it does remind us of the truth of what's in the people just to meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and remember that his grandparents lost their whole family</u>
<u n="434" who="S0520" trans="overlap">not only that yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0519">erm because it makes it real again you know that this is the the reality for Israel</u>
<u n="436" who="S0520">mm and since then how many people have lost their sons and brothers and fathers in various wars and situations and I know it's the same for the Palestinians but that's you know a continuing wound isn't it?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it is the same for the Palestinians times a thousand</u>
<u n="438" who="S0520" trans="overlap">of course much worse yeah absolutely there's also always a lot more deaths and so forth but yeah for sure</u>
<u n="439" who="S0519">and they don't have a normal life left they there's no</u>
<u n="440" who="S0520">in Gaza no they don't</u>
<u n="441" who="S0519">in Gaza there's nothing left for a normal life they're living in a a war zone</u>
<u n="442" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0521"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0519">erm which like you say you just can't understand why they can't vote for the right people and make a make a solution</u>
<u n="445" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah well that's what people feel in Israel as well you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family considered leaving Israel after the last elections seriously because they are</u>
<u n="446" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no I understand that</u>
<u n="447" who="S0520">like the people who want there to be a constant effort towards a peaceful agreement and Netanyahu is not on that boat</u>
<u n="448" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="449" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0520">he's just not interested but the point the problem is is that people are disillusioned about the ability of <trunc>poli</trunc>politicians to negotiate</u>
<u n="451" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0520">that kind of deal and people are distrustful of the Palestinian's because they're maintaining a</u>
<u n="454" who="S0519" trans="overlap">quite rightly</u>
<u n="455" who="S0520">extremist government who aren't really not nice people</u>
<u n="456" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I find it's erm quite quite comparable with Northern Ireland in a lot of respects</u>
<u n="457" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I have always yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0521">it's just full of hatred each side blaming the other no progress <trunc>a</trunc> <trunc>a</trunc> and it's sort of a perpetual animosity isn't it? which never gets resolved</u>
<u n="459" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm yeah and it's just like you know in South Africa as well you know every day there are things happening to people which are racial as such in nature you know like encounters between Arabs and Jews within Israel or whatever that erm are negative and people develop this opinion of each other this very hateful and negative opinion</u>
<u n="460" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm yeah that's right</u>
<u n="461" who="S0520">and there's no er that's very difficult to heal it's very difficult to change you know and that's what I see most Israelis erm they even the best ones who have the most <trunc>magnamin</trunc> <trunc>nam</trunc> magnanimous vision <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0521">yes that word</u>
<u n="463" who="S0520">and ability to kind of see beyond the all those feelings</u>
<u n="464" who="S0521">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0520">you know they still feel very powerless really to <pause dur="short"/> but they don't feel like they have to defend their actions even like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for instance and his family who are as left as it gets basically and have always supported the party and leaders who are dedicated to find a peaceful solution erm they still don't they're not apologetic about how Israel responds to various aggression from <trunc>Pales</trunc> Palestinians</u>
<u n="466" who="S0519">but the world is turning against them daily</u>
<u n="467" who="S0520" trans="overlap">the world is unsympathetic I know but you saw that in <trunc>Is</trunc> and I thought it was a sort of very sad thing like in the Gaza war last year obviously it was a disaster but what you did see happening in was anti-Semitic demonstrations and it's like how do people move into that?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0521">where where are you talking about?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0520">no in Germany in France</u>
<u n="471" who="S0521">oh in Germany</u>
<u n="472" who="S0519">but it's <trunc>beca</trunc> it's well</u>
<u n="473" who="S0520">what's it got to do with the fact that they're Jewish for a start?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0519">well that's who's doing it</u>
<u n="475" who="S0520">I know but it can't like</u>
<u n="476" who="S0519">so there isn't there's isn't <trunc>we</trunc> we've said this and you said it it you it's really difficult to differentiate between Israel and Judaism it because the people have come together <trunc>a</trunc>as Jews from all over the world what do they have in common they're <trunc>Hu</trunc>Hungarian Jews they're Jews so so there's something in in the <trunc>his</trunc> in the history even if it's not the religion so that's maybe people's ignorance but what they were saying no to was the perception that erm the terrorists from Palestinian dropped two bombs and</u>
<u n="477" who="S0520" trans="overlap">this is completely not fair representation of what's happening but I'm just saying you're exaggerating it in a way that's not fair</u>
<u n="478" who="S0519">no I'm I'm just going to say they bombed I don't know how how long and how much but then the Israel bombed for ten days or six days or something just all day and all night so it's like a</u>
<u n="479" who="S0520">it's not really what happened</u>
<u n="480" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you know the people it is it was on the news on the television all day the reporters standing there</u>
<u n="481" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no but</u>
<u n="482" who="S0519">in Palestine and the place is just under <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc> constant bombing for days and days and days and days and days and it's like how many bombs do they need to throw to say stop</u>
<u n="483" who="S0520" trans="overlap">the first thing no fair enough it was a lot</u>
<u n="484" who="S0519" trans="overlap">well it was a lot erm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0520">the first thing is is that they were constantly shooting missiles at Israel</u>
<u n="486" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and it was for most people in the world to much yeah but it's still</u>
<u n="487" who="S0520">and Israel has this enormous defence dome over Tel Aviv</u>
<u n="488" who="S0519">I know</u>
<u n="489" who="S0520">but they're shooting missiles constantly towards Tel Aviv whether they hit things is another question but saying that they dropped two bombs over the border is not really</u>
<u n="490" who="S0519">no they're trying to but they're not successful</u>
<u n="491" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0519">because Israel is mighty but just because they're trying then Israel obliterates them for days and days and days and days and days</u>
<u n="493" who="S0520" trans="overlap">they were targeting</u>
<u n="494" who="S0519">you can't you can't justify that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's not justifiable that's why people stood up against it it's it's a you know it's sending a a sledgehammer to hit an ant it that's what it is and that's what people are saying for god's sake yes we appreciate you're under fire yes it's not right yes something should be done but is that it?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0520">it's a very big ant when it's the whole more or less Arab world who wants Israel to be gone</u>
<u n="496" who="S0519">yeah but they're not fighting the whole Arab world there fighting</u>
<u n="497" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yes but they are in a way you have to see that</u>
<u n="498" who="S0519" trans="overlap">Palestine</u>
<u n="499" who="S0520">no but you have see that it's all connected in that way as well</u>
<u n="500" who="S0519">well I <trunc>er</trunc><trunc>e</trunc> that's not what they're doing when they bomb Palestine they're not</u>
<u n="501" who="S0520">it's partly what they're doing it's partly what they're doing</u>
<u n="502" who="S0519">well it's not the world is quite rightly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saying that's not the way</u>
<u n="503" who="S0520">yeah I know but I don't know that the world has a very fair perspective and it's not the world it's Europe America have always been in support of it</u>
<u n="504" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and I think the world's right no no</u>
<u n="505" who="S0520">yes they have</u>
<u n="506" who="S0519">there was not there was not support for the bombing there were talks against it and there there was a lot of quiet from America</u>
<u n="507" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah that's true</u>
<u n="508" who="S0519">which was noted and erm even words that this needs to stop now er</u>
<u n="509" who="S0520">honestly I don't know what is justifiable any more I've seen too much</u>
<u n="510" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but when was it ever that you can't justify that</u>
<u n="511" who="S0520">I think you can if you look at the greater picture</u>
<u n="512" who="S0519" trans="overlap">there's no justification in war</u>
<u n="513" who="S0520">that's a very idealistic thing to say</u>
<u n="514" who="S0519">well it's true though and it's why</u>
<u n="515" who="S0520">was it not justified to fight against the Nazis of course it was I'm not saying that's analogous I'm just saying</u>
<u n="516" who="S0519">yeah but then they thought the same was true to get rid of erm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0521">Saddam</u>
<u n="518" who="S0519">the Saddam Hussein you know he was a cruel erm dictator who would gas bomb people and they thought that erm apart from the torture and the misery inflicted on the people they thought that he had they the weapons so they they went and fought him and and caused havoc</u>
<u n="519" who="S0520">of course</u>
<u n="520" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0520">I I know I'm just saying that in certain people's eyes there are justifications for those type of actions you know whatever from whatever side and and it's very complicated to say what's just and what isn't in that situation it's very very complicated and it's very deep in terms of <trunc>hi</trunc> like how far it goes back and what the overall implications are it's not just one thing you know that's all I'm saying I don't agree with it I'm just saying like from my perspective there's such a more complex picture and I find that the way that things are presented in our in in European English media let's say are unfair</u>
<u n="522" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no I the trouble is is that you think well I I've no idea that <trunc>ho</trunc>how unfair they are I think the BBC is reasonable but probably erm the trouble is that it it was the same in Ireland that both sides believe themselves to be right</u>
<u n="523" who="S0520">of course</u>
<u n="524" who="S0519">and the weight of history is behind both sides in a different way</u>
<u n="525" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="526" who="S0519">and therefore unless you can stop looking back and look forward and stop relying on history's evidence to support your argument and your justification for carrying on killing people nothing ever changes</u>
<u n="527" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="528" who="S0519">and so I hate people saying this is justified because of A B and C because it's not justifiable to kill people for any reason and</u>
<u n="529" who="S0520">ultimately that's true but it's not the way that things work is it?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0519" trans="overlap">well but then it it the how do you ever go forward if all you say is these are all of the reasons why I have to carry on being a murderer erm that's what they did in Ireland for generations</u>
<u n="531" who="S0520">well I think honestly if Israel would do that it would be gone</u>
<u n="532" who="S0519">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="533" who="S0521">why would it be gone?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0519">why would it be gone?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0520">because because the if <trunc>wha</trunc> if they <trunc>d</trunc> if they stopped as if defending the their borders and saying we're not going to like let's say some some country attacks Israel and they don't retaliate they say no we're not going to do this any more what's going to happen?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I think that's a different <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I I we were talking about terrorism here and you're talking about war</u>
<u n="537" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah but that's okay so two different things but</u>
<u n="538" who="S0521">we're not talking about invasion I mean who who want to invade Israel</u>
<u n="539" who="S0520">well all of the Arab leaders not all of them but the majority of them would would have spoken about <trunc>in</trunc> er invading Israel and in fact annihilating it entirely so</u>
<u n="540" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0520">and they have I mean Syria has invaded Israel Lebanon Egypt all in the last forty years</u>
<u n="542" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0520">so it's not like a <trunc>un</trunc>un anyway it's a slightly different issue but</u>
<u n="544" who="S0519" trans="overlap">so yeah that's</u>
<u n="545" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I think it's a different issue to the Palestinian</u>
<u n="546" who="S0520">I'm just saying if</u>
<u n="547" who="S0521">because they are clearly erm relatively defenceless aren't they?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0521">and they do resort to small scale terrorism which is the only thing they can do</u>
<u n="550" who="S0520">mm yeah agreed agreed I mean the thing two things are mixed together as well because and as many people say they no</u>
<u n="551" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it's a miserable <unclear/> not not for the outside world and that's why there are demonstrations against Israel</u>
<u n="552" who="S0520">I understand why there are demonstrations but I also feel that people have a very like Europeans that I've spoken to over over the years and with in the company of Israelis who want to talk about the situation have a very naive idea about this whole situation they don't know the history at all they don't know what's happened they don't know when even when Israel was established and why you know and it's like they have this kind of nice European left wing kind of approach to things</u>
<u n="553" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="554" who="S0521" trans="overlap">oh could be yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0520">but they're not realistic you know you have to know the facts and you have to know the the historical context of that kind of a situation to understand why Israel acts like it does and <trunc>wh</trunc> and then decide whether it's justified or not you know on the surface on the face of it it seems like crazy behaviour agreed but erm you know</u>
<u n="558" who="S0519">the the the only thing is that there's there's will never be a way out unless the change what they're doing</u>
<u n="559" who="S0520">mm agreed agreed</u>
<u n="560" who="S0519">so</u>
<u n="561" who="S0520">and I think that's what people feel as well but like <trunc>pr</trunc> there's a I mean within Israel there's a problem of erm I guess increasing bitterness and also erm a stronger and stronger religious minority who are the people who are much who refuse to leave the settlements in the West Bank and who would refuse to withdraw from Jerusalem and so forth I mean they're the people who have the opposite view you know? and they are becoming stronger because are increasing in numbers a lot faster <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="563" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0520">mm so I mean the people who want who who have always wanted to seek a peaceful two-state solution erm are being erm becoming outnumbered and they feel desperate too you know? nobody wants to live like that do they?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0520">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family really thought about moving away to America because they thought there's no hope left for this place you know?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0520">and what's going to happen now in a few years' time?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0520">it's not optimistic and now ISIS and everything</u>
<u n="572" who="S0519" trans="overlap">horrible</u>
<u n="573" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0520">I obviously have a lot of sympathy for them because you now these are my friends and they've been in army they're not like we just bystanders they you know have their whole lives have been affected by this situation and</u>
<u n="576" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="578" who="S0520">and they've had to fought fight for their country in war situations and go to the West Bank and see what people are like and see and be and see how people are treated on either side and so forth you know?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0520">so it's pretty real erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0520">but</u>
<u n="583" who="S0519">horrible</u>
<u n="584" who="S0521">cos who are the people in control in Palestine it's not Hezbollah is it? it's the other one</u>
<u n="585" who="S0520">Hamas isn't it?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0521">Hamas yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0520">yeah Hezbollah is</u>
<u n="588" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah I was going to say hummus but can't be hummus</u>
<u n="589" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> quite like hummus oh Hezbollah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0521" trans="overlap">Hamas</u>
<u n="591" who="S0520">Hezbollah is the Lebanese er terrorist group</u>
<u n="592" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah that's right yeah Hamas</u>
<u n="593" who="S0520" trans="overlap">Hamas yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0521">is that Mr Mr tea towel's party</u>
<u n="595" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> er</u>
<u n="596" who="S0519">he was a laugh a minute</u>
<u n="597" who="S0520">Arafat you mean?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0521">he was the on the news all of the time in the seventies and eighties</u>
<u n="599" who="S0520">he yeah he wasn't the best was he?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0521">Yasser Arafat and he said</u>
<u n="601" who="S0520">yeah well he he he was in a way one of the best hopes despite his er extreme behaviour he was the one who erm entered negotiations you know and Camp David was it?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I remember Ramallah is it Ramallah?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0520">Ramallah yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0521">where's that?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0520">it's in the West Bank</u>
<u n="606" who="S0521">the West Bank</u>
<u n="607" who="S0520">mm and was it Rabin in at the time?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0521">Rabin yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0520">and he was assassinated</u>
<u n="610" who="S0521">and Shimon Peres was it Shimon Peres?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0520">yes</u>
<u n="612" who="S0521">was he around that time?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0520">yeah I think so yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad was very close friends with Rabin</u>
<u n="614" who="S0521">was he?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0520">yeah he was his doctor</u>
<u n="616" who="S0521">oh</u>
<u n="617" who="S0520">and they were very good friends from they served in the army together so from quite a young age</u>
<u n="618" who="S0521">oh wow</u>
<u n="619" who="S0520">and erm yeah it was interesting to hear he didn't speak about it much but you know he was just saying you know he was also Sharon's doctor and erm you know he was telling me stories about how <trunc>d</trunc> how they were personally and how that changed his perspective as well you know to see what kind of people</u>
<u n="620" who="S0521">was it Rabin who got assassinated?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0520">Rabin got assassinated yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0520">and er Sharon went into a coma didn't he?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0521">did he?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0520">he went into a coma and I think I don't know if he's still alive or whether he's still in a coma</u>
<u n="626" who="S0521">mm I think I remember <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0520">mm have you read that Amos Oz book that you've got?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0521">the whicher?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0520">Amos Oz you should have a read of that I don't know if it's the <trunc>on</trunc> there's a couple of his but he Amos Oz is a one of the great voices of the left in Israel</u>
<u n="630" who="S0521">okay I didn't know that's what it was about</u>
<u n="631" who="S0520">and he's yeah he's written quite lot of book about er Israeli history and also novels but he writes very beautifully and he's er quite a figure of erm representing the will to for peace in Israel like he does a lot of public campaigning and stuff</u>
<u n="632" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0520">but he also writes beautifully and there's a book <pause dur="long"/> mm what's it called? they've just made a film out of it as well? something about darkness love and darkness</u>
<u n="634" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0520">which is about erm his family coming to Israel in the forties</u>
<u n="636" who="S0521">okay</u>
<u n="637" who="S0520">it's good you've got one down there</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
