<text id="SZPS">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:16</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Film, literature, food</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0179">american society</u>
<u n="2" who="S0058">yes no it was um</u>
<u n="3" who="S0179"><unclear/> that is what the entire thing was so sort of massive inequality um</u>
<u n="4" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah the haves and the have not</u>
<u n="5" who="S0179">the countryside versus rich cities</u>
<u n="6" who="S0058">yep</u>
<u n="7" who="S0179">and the whole sort of the er the sort of states versus federal government</u>
<u n="8" who="S0058">mhm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0179"><trunc>W</trunc> which was the central <unclear/> of the entire thing</u>
<u n="10" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="12" who="S0058">and I quite like the idea of taking sort of Jerry Springer like a step too far</u>
<u n="13" who="S0179">oh yes it did <pause dur="short"/> it was</u>
<u n="14" who="S0058">the idea of entertainment sort of yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> entertainment through watching other people's</u>
<u n="15" who="S0179">suffering</u>
<u n="16" who="S0058">suffering <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0179">well that I mean that's nothing new <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="18" who="S0058">yep</u>
<u n="19" who="S0179">they've done shows er they've done films and television programmes based on taking reality TV too far</u>
<u n="20" who="S0058">oh yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0179">before</u>
<u n="22" who="S0058">I don't think that was the main point but it did sort of made me think of that actually that bit which was</u>
<u n="23" who="S0179">yeah indeed</u>
<u n="24" who="S0058"><unclear/> interesting</u>
<u n="25" who="S0179">oh police cars</u>
<u n="26" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0179">waiting for</u>
<u n="28" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Unfortunate <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0179">that would be really funny if the <unclear/> just in front of them now</u>
<u n="30" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0179">sorry can't get out</u>
<u n="32" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh dear</u>
<u n="33" who="S0179">um that was yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0058">yeah it was um <pause dur="short"/> so presumably it's called The Hunger Games because there's er very little food?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0179">well I think the idea</u>
<u n="36" who="S0058">or</u>
<u n="37" who="S0179">of being which was only mentioned very briefly that you can trade sort of increased odds for food</u>
<u n="38" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="39" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="40" who="S0058">which was presumably why that guy had so many?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="42" who="S0058">I didn't know if it was a kind of punishment</u>
<u n="43" who="S0179">no I think it was</u>
<u n="44" who="S0058">yeah yeah I think it's supposed to be buying them <pause dur="short"/> but um yeah fascinating</u>
<u n="45" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> indeed <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0058">and <trunc>ve</trunc> very kind of captivating I think <pause dur="short"/> like the it was <vocal desc="laugh"/> really quite gripping I think <pause dur="short"/> and the way they built it up as well was really nice <pause dur="short"/> so you had all the bits at the beginning and sort of really interesting costumes and and stuff</u>
<u n="47" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0058">all that kind of idea and the sort of um playing the media <pause dur="short"/> an image <trunc>s</trunc> kind of idea about it <pause dur="short"/> the sort of Miss Congeniality question bit</u>
<u n="49" who="S0179">er yes er <unclear/> of course Miss Congeniality would have probably done fairly well in that situation</u>
<u n="50" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="52" who="S0058">she'd have been fine <pause dur="short"/> um followed by the quite you know the sort of horrible bit <pause dur="short"/> and I thought it <trunc>w</trunc> just works really you know really quite well <pause dur="short"/> so I <trunc>w</trunc> I wonder what happens in the sequels? Cos presumably there's gonna be something with this love triangle going on?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0179">I've no idea <pause dur="short"/> and all the politics of it</u>
<u n="54" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="55" who="S0179">um but it</u>
<u n="56" who="S0058">I I was just like as I was watching it I I wasn't sure whether it was gonna be kind of say three films for for the whole story or whether they were gonna stop halfway through the game <pause dur="short"/> um but I couldn't really see them</u>
<u n="57" who="S0179">well no that would've <unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0058">doing that cos that would've been yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0179">far too <unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0058">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="61" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="62" who="S0058">er and then I didn't know if it was different people each time and just a sort of different storyline <pause dur="short"/> but I thought well how different could you make it?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0058">so I assume it's gonna be the same people</u>
<u n="65" who="S0179"><unclear/> the political upheaval following <unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I mean I was wondering if they were gonna put the same two back in?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0058">as a sort of</u>
<u n="69" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0058">just a to keep  to keep  sort of milking that one <pause dur="short"/> I love the idea of it being like a a computerized thing they could put in little</u>
<u n="73" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0058">you know sort of play with it <pause dur="short"/> quite creepy</u>
<u n="75" who="S0179">what was I gonna say? Um <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> well I just find it fascinating as an exercise in tactics</u>
<u n="76" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> but I just don't understand why you'd form an alliance with someone <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0179">well no but there's obvious reasons for it <pause dur="short"/> I mean it keeps you a it it gives you if you're the strongest half</u>
<u n="78" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0179">then that means you have good odds of surviving the first half</u>
<u n="80" who="S0058">and then you</u>
<u n="81" who="S0179">which you then split split up again</u>
<u n="82" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0179">um but</u>
<u n="84" who="S0058">it relies on other people playing fair though <pause dur="short"/> cos surely</u>
<u n="85" who="S0179">well indeed you have to</u>
<u n="86" who="S0058">someone could gather all the strong people to then kill them all</u>
<u n="87" who="S0179">well it would be inherently quite difficult to kill them</u>
<u n="88" who="S0058">but then that's the hard bit <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0179"><unclear/> Um <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> lights today</u>
<u n="90" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah there's that awkward er thing where like you said is that <trunc>y</trunc> um little girl has saved her the trouble of</u>
<u n="91" who="S0179">killing her</u>
<u n="92" who="S0058">killing her herself cos everyone else was doing it</u>
<u n="93" who="S0179">I think that's quite predictable</u>
<u n="94" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="95" who="S0179">but I assumed that the friend was gonna be killed</u>
<u n="96" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I did</u>
<u n="97" who="S0179">it was a surprisingly yeah that was a very sort of yeah this is a book for sort of children as in this is that was a very positive ending to it</u>
<u n="98" who="S0058">yes exactly <pause dur="short"/> and I mean as it was a book for teenagers in that the love kind of idea and it was <trunc>ve</trunc> you were right it was very Twighlight <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0179">um similar strong female lead</u>
<u n="100" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0179">and um two potential male love interests <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="102" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="104" who="S0058">who look like they would actually murder each other <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0179">well no but who</u>
<u n="106" who="S0058">one gets a bit hairy at night</u>
<u n="107" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0058">one's a bit pale <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I love Twilight <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> I thought Twilight was finished <pause dur="short"/> so that's why I was surprised when that trailer came on <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know whether it was gonna be a spoof but then I thought well no it's actually them so <unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0179">no she's finally a vampire now <pause dur="short"/> life is superb</u>
<u n="110" who="S0058">I love that we're the same temperature <pause dur="short"/> great <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Really chilly</u>
<u n="111" who="S0179"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0058">know what I mean <pause dur="short"/> I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0179">yes we've got markedly different thermal capacities</u>
<u n="114" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0179">so therefore we contain different amounts of stored energy</u>
<u n="116" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0179"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0058">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="119" who="S0179">it was a bit unfortunate <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="120" who="S0058">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> twighlight's just funny <pause dur="short"/> oh it's such a good idea <pause dur="short"/> get in touch with <unclear/> and go and see it with him in Oxford</u>
<u n="121" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0058">oh hilarious <unclear/> you know not in a cinema</u>
<u n="123" who="S0179"><unclear/> in a cinema yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0058">yeah you no not in a cinema <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Such a good experience <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0179"><trunc>L</trunc> um what was I gonna say? Tut</u>
<u n="126" who="S0058">yeah um apart from being quite Twightlighty it was good <pause dur="short"/> or rather despite being quite quite Twighlighty it was good</u>
<u n="127" who="S0179">yeah indeed it was <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="128" who="S0058">as in it wasn't all er while they had that element of it it wasn't all moony and kind of oh I love you</u>
<u n="129" who="S0179">no it was very good</u>
<u n="130" who="S0058">it was  it was  kind of and I mean is the interesting thing is as well that she's was she playing it? Was she doing it to survive? And what's gonna happen cos</u>
<u n="131" who="S0179">no I don't think so because if she was doing it to survive she would have killed him at the end</u>
<u n="132" who="S0058">no but I mean she could</u>
<u n="133" who="S0179">no but she <unclear/> There were two opportunities for her when she could</u>
<u n="134" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh no entirely <pause dur="short"/> but I mean</u>
<u n="135" who="S0179"><unclear/> survivor that doesn't make sense</u>
<u n="136" who="S0058">she she could've not wanted him to die but she I mean she might not be in love with him <pause dur="short"/> she might <trunc>th</trunc> he she might be a very very close friend</u>
<u n="137" who="S0179">well no but that's quite a step to <pause dur="short"/> yeah well she was willing to kill herself to avoid him dying <pause dur="short"/> I think that's sort of a serious er level of commitment</u>
<u n="138" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> I I mean I'm just wondering if it would be more interesting if um</u>
<u n="139" who="S0179">I think you might be overthinking this a bit</u>
<u n="140" who="S0058">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> just cos that's what that was the point like that he told her all the way along he she was being told you've got if you play this you'll be you'll survive <pause dur="short"/> because that's what it's it's an angle <pause dur="short"/> and she did it <pause dur="short"/> which made me think that maybe she was doing it for that reason <pause dur="short"/> because she did ultimately</u>
<u n="141" who="S0179">yes but no but she knew that she was going to survive even she knew she had better odds of survival if she didn't do that <pause dur="short"/> that's the point <pause dur="short"/> that which so disproves that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0058">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I just <trunc>d</trunc> never got the feeling that she was that into him <pause dur="short"/> I think that's maybe gonna be the the sort of the interesting thing for the next film that she's maybe not that into him but because they've got this</u>
<u n="143" who="S0179">I think you're just</u>
<u n="144" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> fair enough</u>
<u n="145" who="S0179">completely taking that the wrong way <pause dur="short"/> I think she's into both of them <pause dur="short"/> which is where the conflicting interest comes in</u>
<u n="146" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> fair enough</u>
<u n="147" who="S0179">it'd be far too boring if she wasn't <pause dur="short"/> no?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0058">fair enough <pause dur="short"/> maybe <pause dur="short"/> could always read the books <pause dur="short"/> cos presumably the books are finished?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0179">no as in <unclear/> just run better <pause dur="short"/> if she was just playing and she wanted to survive she would've A shot one or both of her men <unclear/> both have gone off the edge or secondly she'd have just shot him at the end</u>
<u n="150" who="S0058">no but I'm saying she maybe wasn't doing it just to survive <pause dur="short"/> she might not be head over heals in love with him wanting to spend the rest of her life with him <pause dur="short"/> she might just not have wanted to kill him</u>
<u n="151" who="S0179">well then</u>
<u n="152" who="S0058">and thought well I don't want this game to be like you know cos they said at the beginning um that if they could do something</u>
<u n="153" who="S0179">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0058">to make a stand</u>
<u n="155" who="S0179">I know <pause dur="short"/> but that's a hell of a risk to take unless you've got a <unclear/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0058">no but I'm saying maybe she wasn't willing to die to not let the games win</u>
<u n="157" who="S0179">yeah possibly</u>
<u n="158" who="S0058">do it like that's the</u>
<u n="159" who="S0179">probably not because she was very keen to get home to her sister <pause dur="short"/> that was the <unclear/> priority throughout <pause dur="short"/> so it would have to have been a much stronger reason than sort of general social</u>
<u n="160" who="S0058">but I</u>
<u n="161" who="S0179"><unclear/> that just doesn't fly <pause dur="short"/> I'm sorry</u>
<u n="162" who="S0058">I just wasn't convinced <pause dur="short"/> I didn't <trunc>th</trunc> I</u>
<u n="163" who="S0179">well that's probably the acting</u>
<u n="164" who="S0058">well yeah possibly <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0179">or the scripting</u>
<u n="166" who="S0058">it was possibly just like yeah possibly slighty kinda</u>
<u n="167" who="S0179">or the fact that you're not a teenager</u>
<u n="168" who="S0058">maybe</u>
<u n="169" who="S0179">in natality at least</u>
<u n="170" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> well it'll be interesting to see what does happen slash Wikipedia it when we get in <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> No we can't look up what happens <pause dur="short"/> that's bad <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so I assume the are the books finished? Has there <trunc>th</trunc> has there been three?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0179">no idea</u>
<u n="172" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0179">well I yeah cos I got that free sample of the first book in with the DVD awards thing</u>
<u n="174" who="S0058">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> you did <pause dur="short"/> how was it?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0179"><unclear/> first chapter <pause dur="short"/> it was good</u>
<u n="176" who="S0058">was it <trunc>qui</trunc> quite well written?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0179">it seemed to be <pause dur="short"/> it was interesting <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> cos of course now there's gonna be a massive spike in the er book sales</u>
<u n="179" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="180" who="S0058">but I mean there's I used to read stuff like not maybe not stuff quite as dark as that but I used to read sort of teen fantasy type stuff quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> but most of it</u>
<u n="181" who="S0179"><unclear/> dark material to sort of give to children</u>
<u n="182" who="S0058">but of course in a book you can  you can  er you can really either play it up make it quite graphic or you can play it down and just have them dying <pause dur="short"/> you don't need to put so much detail about it <pause dur="short"/> but the</u>
<u n="183" who="S0179">well that was really played down <pause dur="short"/> it was ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't even</u>
<u n="184" who="S0058">yep <pause dur="short"/> there was very little blood</u>
<u n="185" who="S0179"><unclear/> tell who'd died</u>
<u n="186" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I mean the book could be like that <pause dur="short"/> really quite clean <pause dur="short"/> um but just the idea's quite horrible but sort of suitable for for teenagers kind of kinda book <pause dur="short"/> um but</u>
<u n="187" who="S0179">what cos teenagers are quite horrible?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> No teenagers could handle that idea <pause dur="short"/> like that's not you know</u>
<u n="189" who="S0179">I find it difficult handling that idea <pause dur="short"/> it's quite a disturbing one</u>
<u n="190" who="S0058">no but as in like</u>
<u n="191" who="S0179">the people particularly it's particularly disturbing in the opening sequences as in people you were training you were</u>
<u n="192" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0179">sort of you know trying to kill like it's <trunc>w</trunc> it's a very different thing fighting in a war where you're don't know your enemy</u>
<u n="194" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0179">your enemy becomes a uniform target</u>
<u n="196" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="197" who="S0179">in this particular case you know you get to know people you are going to try to kill</u>
<u n="198" who="S0058">yeah that was what I found <unclear/> I I wouldn't have talked to anyone <pause dur="short"/> cos that was kind of potentially decreases your</u>
<u n="199" who="S0179">it would impair</u>
<u n="200" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0179">your ability to kill them</u>
<u n="202" who="S0058">exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna decrease your exactly your um ability to see them as an enemy</u>
<u n="203" who="S0179">targets</u>
<u n="204" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0179">yep</u>
<u n="206" who="S0058">Cos yeah I just wouldn't be talking to <vocal desc="laugh"/> any of them if it had been me</u>
<u n="207" who="S0179">ah that leads me</u>
<u n="208" who="S0058">but</u>
<u n="209" who="S0179">to the next question <pause dur="short"/> firstly so how do you think you would've coped?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0058">I think I would've been very quickly killed <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh my phone just buzzed <pause dur="short"/> oh it's it's that alarm I set <pause dur="short"/> aha <pause dur="short"/> flight sale <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> There we are</u>
<u n="211" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0058">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> um yeah I think a lie in tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="213" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="214" who="S0058">what were we saying?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0179">the other thing you were saying was</u>
<u n="216" who="S0058">oh yeah how how would I cope?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0058">well I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I think I'd have done better than the very small children <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Just <trunc>f</trunc> from the perspective of being relatively physically fit <pause dur="short"/> but I think I'd have been quite dreadful at the sort of psychological element of it</u>
<u n="219" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> you may have been clever enough not to light a fire</u>
<u n="220" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I'd have maybe worked it out not too badly <pause dur="short"/> but yeah when it came down to it I'm not sure I'd have been any good at it <pause dur="short"/> I would have taken the hide and wait for it to end sort of approach</u>
<u n="221" who="S0179">that may have actually worked pretty well</u>
<u n="222" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I would've literally like yeah dug a hole <pause dur="short"/> sat in it until everybody else had gone home <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um which might have worked <pause dur="short"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="223" who="S0179">well it would be difficult to search an area that large</u>
<u n="224" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0179">definitely yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0058">but would they have</u>
<u n="227" who="S0179">you'd last for a few days <pause dur="short"/> you could last for you know twenty-four forty-eight hours without water</u>
<u n="228" who="S0058">exactly</u>
<u n="229" who="S0179">over a week without food <pause dur="short"/> you know you realistically could wait it out</u>
<u n="230" who="S0058">um but of course would they let you <pause dur="short"/> like for the whole point your your idea about running to the edge and just being the fastest <pause dur="short"/> she did <pause dur="short"/> but they stopped her by the fire <pause dur="short"/> so that if like if you'd hid underground they'd be like oh well she's obviously gonna win let's <trunc>s</trunc> sort of get her out <pause dur="short"/> and they'd have come up with something <pause dur="short"/> some way of getting you out</u>
<u n="231" who="S0179">this is true <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="232" who="S0058">which is the problem with any strategy</u>
<u n="233" who="S0179">but</u>
<u n="234" who="S0058">though they can <trunc>f</trunc> you can <unclear/> it</u>
<u n="235" who="S0179">but I assumed that they'd leave it in as fair and I was surprised that they interfered because they'd think that would be unpopular</u>
<u n="236" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0179">mind you of course they're trying to make it interesting so it's just like reality TV <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0058">sort of fiddling with it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="241" who="S0179">er <pause dur="short"/> well I think it was definitely the right policy to run at the start <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="242" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> would you grab the right kit?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> but I think she should've more actively tried to hunt them <pause dur="short"/> as in</u>
<u n="244" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0179">don't want to let your enemy come to you <pause dur="short"/> you want to come you want to find them on your terms</u>
<u n="246" who="S0058">well while she was up in the tree could she not have shot them?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0179">yeah but she didn't have an arrow</u>
<u n="248" who="S0058">oh she didn't have a bow and arrow at that point did she</u>
<u n="249" who="S0179">no no that's right <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="250" who="S0058">yeah she really should've taken more opportunities <pause dur="short"/> like when she was gonna destroy the um the what's it? She could've surely shot the guy with a spear <unclear/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0179">what guy? This was</u>
<u n="252" who="S0058">um so when the they left the stuff all piled up and there was one guy left on guard</u>
<u n="253" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> well she should've killed him</u>
<u n="254" who="S0058">she should've killed him <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just you know and she should've killed the um the guy who let her live <pause dur="short"/> if possible <pause dur="short"/> you know when he sort of ran off <pause dur="short"/> like that kinda thing like I think there's a point she wasn't really playing like that which</u>
<u n="255" who="S0179">oh er</u>
<u n="256" who="S0058">she <trunc>ha</trunc> she obviously wouldn't really have worked as a character and stuff</u>
<u n="257" who="S0179">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0058">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> I agree</u>
<u n="259" who="S0179">er to take it to another extreme <unclear/> All of that actually the character thing does kind of work because you want people who are watching to like you</u>
<u n="260" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0179">to help you</u>
<u n="262" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0179">um so but leaving that aside I mean basic things so er the girl who died</u>
<u n="264" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0179">food</u>
<u n="266" who="S0058">well yeah indeed <pause dur="short"/> horrible but true</u>
<u n="267" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="268" who="S0058">but again that gesture may be made unpopular</u>
<u n="269" who="S0179">you well it wouldn't have occurred to her but then that's why she's not</u>
<u n="270" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0179"><unclear/> quite a lot of things so <pause dur="short"/> yeah just sequences of small things like that</u>
<u n="272" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0179">you should be</u>
<u n="274" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0179">prepared to take advantage <pause dur="short"/> as in I think the odd</u>
<u n="276" who="S0058">in all fairness I mean the <trunc>who</trunc> er if people are into that kind of like programme if you like that kind of entertainment then you'd think they'd be  they'd be  quite you know they wouldn't mind so much if you were killing people cos</u>
<u n="277" who="S0179">no but no they wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> if you're too efficient <pause dur="short"/> if you're too good</u>
<u n="278" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0179">then that wouldn't that count in your favour <pause dur="short"/> er people fundamentally like an underdog <pause dur="short"/> it's it but it you know <unclear/> chance</u>
<u n="280" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0179">because that makes it entertaining</u>
<u n="282" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0179">and unpredictable</u>
<u n="284" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0179">that's why Out of the Question always worked well cos it's always not <unclear/> expect it to be</u>
<u n="286" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0179">or at least if it is it's <unclear/> to the fact that</u>
<u n="288" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0179">they are who you</u>
<u n="290" who="S0058">so obvious</u>
<u n="291" who="S0179">expect it to be</u>
<u n="292" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0179">um <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="294" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0179">I speak sense</u>
<u n="296" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0179">now I'm a little bit concerned about going back on the <anon type="place"/> bypass because it's that sort of time on a Saturday night where you might get boy racers up there</u>
<u n="298" who="S0058">oh okay</u>
<u n="299" who="S0179">we'll see</u>
<u n="300" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> we could always just stay out of the way</u>
<u n="301" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0058">I guess</u>
<u n="303" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> just <unclear/> a little bit of forward planning</u>
<u n="304" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes indeed <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I would never have thought of that <pause dur="short"/> I'd have thought great you know late night clear</u>
<u n="305" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> that may be what they're thinking</u>
<u n="306" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes</u>
<u n="307" who="S0179">ah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0058">ah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0179">anyway</u>
<u n="310" who="S0058">yeah anyway</u>
<u n="311" who="S0179">so how do you think I would've done?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0058">I think you'd have won <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Quite simply <pause dur="short"/> um yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> But you're good at that sort of it's exactly your kind of game</u>
<u n="313" who="S0179">it's er yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0058">of survival plus strength</u>
<u n="315" who="S0179">hunting</u>
<u n="316" who="S0058">plus hunting <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="317" who="S0179">I'd have wanted a rifle</u>
<u n="318" who="S0058">I don't think that's the idea <pause dur="short"/> I I don't think people are like I want a rifle okay there's one <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0179">there's a <unclear/> Um</u>
<u n="320" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> true <pause dur="short"/> they'd wouldn't have fitted in one of those little balloon things though <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> A full dart rifle</u>
<u n="321" who="S0179">A handgun would've done</u>
<u n="322" who="S0058">yep</u>
<u n="323" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="324" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I liked the kind of weird post-apocalyptic old-fashionedness of it <pause dur="short"/> the sort of really old-fashioned clothes and stuff</u>
<u n="325" who="S0179">you never saw a gun out of the entire film</u>
<u n="326" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="327" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0058">that's what I was just what I was thinking it was all bows and arrows and swords <trunc>i</trunc> in this kind of</u>
<u n="329" who="S0179">no but even the enforcers didn't seem to have firearms</u>
<u n="330" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="331" who="S0179">which I found kind of funny <unclear/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I guess the the sort of the tone of it <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't say that the tones clashed anyway <pause dur="short"/> that was the point <pause dur="short"/> er that their kind of shiny multi-coloured weird world wasn't the same as the kind of</u>
<u n="333" who="S0179">I mean again there were a few other factors so I wouldn't I'm just thinking about them showing <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="334" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0179">I would've if I'd been her I'd have cut my hair off very quickly</u>
<u n="336" who="S0058">yep</u>
<u n="337" who="S0179">um potentially used it as a bow string <pause dur="short"/> um that would've been very suitable actually <pause dur="short"/> um I would have made damn sure that my fairly light skin was mudded up as soon as possible</u>
<u n="338" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you could see all of the the white skin in the <trunc>lea</trunc> the er <vocal desc="laugh"/> surely first thing to do <vocal desc="laugh"/> bit of camouflage</u>
<u n="339" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="340" who="S0058">it was interesting er I mean one thing that did irked me a little bit was that amazingly blended in rock thing <pause dur="short"/> er how did he do that? Do you know what I mean? He's not magic <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0179">well if a rock was covered in a particular material it wouldn't be that difficult to</u>
<u n="342" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it was just a little bit too good</u>
<u n="343" who="S0179">oh shush</u>
<u n="344" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But the idea was good</u>
<u n="345" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean I also think there's other things they could've done <pause dur="short"/> so particularly with the two of them it would have been a very effective lure and hunter combination</u>
<u n="346" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="347" who="S0179">so even if he was wounded that could've worked quite well</u>
<u n="348" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0179"><unclear/> headlights would make life easier</u>
<u n="350" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0179">anyway</u>
<u n="352" who="S0058">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> no I agree <pause dur="short"/> that could've worked quite well <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="353" who="S0179">but needless to say <unclear/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0179">it wasn't me</u>
<u n="356" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> if it had been everything would've been alright</u>
<u n="357" who="S0179">well no but I</u>
<u n="358" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0179">wouldn't want to end up killing children</u>
<u n="360" who="S0058">fair enough <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah you saw some of the little ones when they're sitting on the plane going there and so their feet didn't the <trunc>gr</trunc> floor and you just thought oh my God <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Pff you know</u>
<u n="361" who="S0179">but that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a children's book cos <trunc>c</trunc> children <trunc>ju</trunc> just read it and see it at face value <pause dur="short"/> but if they actually start to think about what it would actually involve if it I think it's that's why it's almost more disturbing for someone who's actually a bit older and thinks</u>
<u n="362" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0179">actually hold on a second</u>
<u n="364" who="S0058">no I know what you mean</u>
<u n="365" who="S0179">this is quite sick</u>
<u n="366" who="S0058">that's that's the thing with children <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="367" who="S0179">and that's why there's I think that works with children who are young enough not to think about what it actually means</u>
<u n="368" who="S0058">but having said that though teenagers are quite capable of thinking about that kind of thing</u>
<u n="369" who="S0179">no they're not <pause dur="short"/> they think they are but they're not <pause dur="short"/> um so you know but war is one thing and that's horrific but that's a whole new level of disturbed <pause dur="short"/> because you are having to you are being put in a position where you are being forced to kill in order to survive but you're not but no er yeah as a soldier in a war you are fighting er yeah you are fighting an <trunc>e</trunc> an enemy for a purpose</u>
<u n="370" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0179">you're fighting to you know often for a country or to</u>
<u n="372" who="S0058">yeah an ideology or</u>
<u n="373" who="S0179">exactly</u>
<u n="374" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0179">and there's something driving you</u>
<u n="376" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0179">but here er you are killing in order to just to survive <unclear/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0058">yeah not <unclear/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0179">yep <pause dur="short"/> which is</u>
<u n="380" who="S0058">I guess the I mean the idea is that it it kind of forces you to become an animal</u>
<u n="381" who="S0179">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> but that's why it's disturbing</u>
<u n="382" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0179">and</u>
<u n="384" who="S0058">and I guess that's</u>
<u n="385" who="S0179">no but but er I don't think unless you really make an active effort to put yourself in their shoes I don't I think it would be very easy to gloss over that film <pause dur="short"/> but you know there's sort of twelve-year-olds in there and they can't possibly understand <pause dur="short"/> and I think  I think  very few um to be fair almost no one could understand exactly what that was like but I think that there's levels of understanding isn't there <pause dur="short"/> because er I'm very I'd be very disturbed frankly if a lot of the twelve-year-olds in there</u>
<u n="386" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0179">understood it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0058">but</u>
<u n="389" who="S0179">and <trunc>th</trunc> thought about it in <unclear/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0058">but I mean that's okay like</u>
<u n="391" who="S0179">yeah but I'm not sure it's okay to I'm still not sure if it's an appropriate film for a appropriate film for that age range</u>
<u n="392" who="S0058">really?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why I don't think it yeah it it's just</u>
<u n="394" who="S0058">no but you could say that so you could say okay so Pirates of the Caribbean <pause dur="short"/> actually if you think about it piracy's really quite horrendous and</u>
<u n="395" who="S0179">no but not like <unclear/> That's a sort of that's a <unclear/> setting for a storyline which is fun and fantasy <pause dur="short"/> this is <trunc>ent</trunc> this is entire premise <pause dur="short"/> the entire er er there is no plot around it <pause dur="short"/> this is the plot</u>
<u n="396" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0179">um it's not just a setting and it's yeah disturbed</u>
<u n="398" who="S0058">also a bit like Noughts and Crosses</u>
<u n="399" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0058">um have you do do you know Noughts and Crosses by Malorie Blackman?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="402" who="S0058">um well it's a series of books <pause dur="short"/> the first one's Noughts and Crosses and it's a kind of um the idea is it's a a universe where um black people are the crosses I think and they're the  they're the  superior race <pause dur="short"/> they're the  they're the  haves <pause dur="short"/> and the whites are noughts um and they're they're nothing <pause dur="short"/> they're they're they're completely rejected and second class citizens and slaves basically</u>
<u n="403" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="404" who="S0058">um and that's</u>
<u n="405" who="S0179">oh I see what they did there with the noughts</u>
<u n="406" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> um and that's a similar kind of um it's quite disturbing and people get killed and um</u>
<u n="407" who="S0179">yes but it's one thing to have people being killed <pause dur="short"/> it's another thing to no I don't think that was different <pause dur="short"/> that was something <unclear/> And again it's very effective <pause dur="short"/> but I think it would've been far better you know <trunc>i</trunc> huh in that film it wasn't the graphicness of the violence that was the disturbing thing <pause dur="short"/> it was the concept</u>
<u n="408" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0179">and I think the fact that it was clean <unclear/> you know there wasn't any blood</u>
<u n="410" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0179"><unclear/> ringing</u>
<u n="412" who="S0058">ah it's probably your mum <pause dur="short"/> no it's you <pause dur="short"/> um I mean I can</u>
<u n="413" who="S0179">are you sure? Right well I'll wait till we get there <unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0058">yeah yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> ah it's probably cos you didn't let your mum know till we got back <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0179">well we haven't got back</u>
<u n="416" who="S0058">no exactly <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> but she will think we set off at half five and haven't got back to <anon type="place"/> yet</u>
<u n="417" who="S0179">that's entirely accurate</u>
<u n="418" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes <pause dur="short"/> she wouldn't have known that we stopped somewhere</u>
<u n="419" who="S0179">as soon as we get up to speed you can um pass me the phone <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> can you check the text? Probably delete it</u>
<u n="420" who="S0058">it's probably a voicemail</u>
<u n="421" who="S0179">well whatever <pause dur="short"/> delete it</u>
<u n="422" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> one new voice message <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> shall I just leave it or?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0179">no listen to it and then delete it <pause dur="short"/> tell her to stop leaving me fucking voicemails</u>
<u n="424" who="S0058">it said voice mailbox number <pause dur="short"/> is that nine O one?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0179">yeah should be</u>
<u n="426" who="S0058">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> um <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think it must be Liam <pause dur="short"/> it's very loud and I can't hear what's being said <pause dur="short"/> it's just kind of voices</u>
<u n="427" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="428" who="S0058">yeah it's it's not your mum <pause dur="short"/> it's um</u>
<u n="429" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="430" who="S0058">one missed call <pause dur="short"/> show <pause dur="short"/> liam <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that's fine then</u>
<u n="431" who="S0179">oh alright</u>
<u n="432" who="S0058">do you wanna just leave it or?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just leave it</u>
<u n="434" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if he rings again I can um</u>
<u n="435" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I heard another voice and I thought oh my God what's happened? Where's Peter's mum? Oh hang on it might not be <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> She did sort of when she  when she  was um mentioning it she did say oh yeah if you remember you know she didn't seem terribly concerned so</u>
<u n="437" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="438" who="S0058">ah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0179">so yes er film</u>
<u n="440" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="441" who="S0179">yeah so</u>
<u n="442" who="S0058">Good</u>
<u n="443" who="S0179">that was fine just fine <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it was like that's why I think it was a little bit a wasted opportunity for far more thought-provoking</u>
<u n="444" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0179">for far more sort of it was a brilliant concept for er could of been taken a lot further</u>
<u n="446" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0179">but in some ways</u>
<u n="448" who="S0058">but that would be an entirely different book</u>
<u n="449" who="S0179">yeah but it wasn't as in</u>
<u n="450" who="S0058">but</u>
<u n="451" who="S0179">like I said fundamentally disturbing thing was the concept <pause dur="short"/> and I think that was <unclear/> think about it <pause dur="short"/> like in every scene it's not like in every  in in every  scene where two of them were together like any two of them or two or more it's like well at any point you're just gonna start killing each other</u>
<u n="452" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="453" who="S0179">and the fact they chose not to go into that and to make it very simplistic didn't remove that threat or that menace</u>
<u n="454" who="S0058">hm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0179">the fact most people wouldn't be aware of <pause dur="short"/> certainly not a lot of the younger audience who wouldn't think of it like that</u>
<u n="456" who="S0058">but yeah I mean you could've done that <pause dur="short"/> but then it's just a different story <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="457" who="S0179">well no it's the same story <pause dur="short"/> it's just more</u>
<u n="458" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> but it's not the same market</u>
<u n="459" who="S0179">it's not</u>
<u n="460" who="S0058">it's it's it's about markets <pause dur="short"/> and it's not it wasn't for that <pause dur="short"/> it was for</u>
<u n="461" who="S0179">but that's the point</u>
<u n="462" who="S0058">the teenage market</u>
<u n="463" who="S0179">it isn't like that</u>
<u n="464" who="S0058">possibly</u>
<u n="465" who="S0179">I know and I understand what you're saying</u>
<u n="466" who="S0058">actually</u>
<u n="467" who="S0179">but it should I'm saying it shouldn't have been</u>
<u n="468" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="469" who="S0179">because in reality I think it was actually virtually</u>
<u n="470" who="S0058"></u>
<u n="471" who="S0179">no less disturbing like that</u>
<u n="472" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0179">but and therefore I don't know that it was really appropriate for that audience <pause dur="short"/> and it was relying on the audience's naivety to protect them from being disturbed by it <pause dur="short"/> which I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0058">I think twelve-year-olds are fine <pause dur="short"/> like I think they're capable of not being too disturbed <trunc>b</trunc> they're they're capable of being disturbed by things in <trunc>o</trunc> in understanding in a more <trunc>sophistica</trunc></u>
<u n="475" who="S0179">no er you see I <trunc>disag</trunc> you see the older like</u>
<u n="476" who="S0058">I mean I say twelve-year-olds</u>
<u n="477" who="S0179">but you see but</u>
<u n="478" who="S0058">like fifteen-year-olds they could</u>
<u n="479" who="S0179">yeah but okay so</u>
<u n="480" who="S0058">er like sixteen-year-olds be seeing that as well</u>
<u n="481" who="S0179">sh sh sh shut up for a minute <pause dur="short"/> so I find actually that films that I watched when I was younger I watch them again now and they disturb me far more</u>
<u n="482" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0179">as an adult who actually thinks about it in more depth than because when I was a child I just sort of glossed over <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>b</trunc> but when you're sort of like oh it's er oh it's Austin Powers who said you know it's just a um you know henchman's family sort of thing</u>
<u n="484" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0179">you start thinking actually you know in this scene you know ten people just got killed</u>
<u n="486" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0179">and actually that's really disturbing and tragic <pause dur="short"/> um but as a child you just gloss over it <pause dur="short"/> oh people just died it's fine <pause dur="short"/> and you don't really understand what that means or think about it in that way</u>
<u n="488" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0179">but certainly for me if I'd watched that film when I was fifteen or I dunno twelve I would've found it much less odd than I do now</u>
<u n="490" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's probably true</u>
<u n="491" who="S0179">and hence yet again like I said to you um they rely on the naivety of the audience to protect them from being disturbed <pause dur="short"/> which I think is a very odd thing to do <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="492" who="S0058">well that's a bit odd but aren't you also just presenting young minds with a very difficult situation to think about? Which surely is the point of the book to to give you something to think about? And I think that's quite a good thing to be thinking about <pause dur="short"/> um it's <trunc>qui</trunc> it's a very difficult story to um get your teeth into and to to think about <pause dur="short"/> even if you're not thinking about it necessarily in the same way you would or I would or you know somebody who's fought in a war would <pause dur="short"/> it it's kind of I don't think it's a er er wrong to</u>
<u n="493" who="S0179">well I do</u>
<u n="494" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> I mean I I <trunc>th</trunc> I think so for example at the age of how old would I have been? Thirteen maybe I read a book about the death of God <pause dur="short"/> and that's inappropriate material for a child of that age <pause dur="short"/> they can't think about theology in that kind of way</u>
<u n="495" who="S0179">I dunno</u>
<u n="496" who="S0058">but that image struck with me and it I thought about it and it I grew up and thought about it <pause dur="short"/> and it it disturbed me at the time and I <trunc>th</trunc> you know and the <trunc>mo</trunc> er I got more out of it as I got older <pause dur="short"/> that that idea <pause dur="short"/> that story <pause dur="short"/> and I think  I think  it's good <pause dur="short"/> even if people aren't you know like I said I you know you get something from it at the time and then you revisit it as you get older and I think that's what the best kind of teenage young people's literature can do <pause dur="short"/> can mean something to you when you're that age and it can keep growing <pause dur="short"/> and it means obviously literature means different things to different people anyway <pause dur="short"/> I don't think there's a a twelve-year-old brain <pause dur="short"/> well <vocal desc="laugh"/> well it would be nice if there was in <trunc>t</trunc> in terms of marketing things</u>
<u n="497" who="S0179">yes and all of what you're saying is completely true</u>
<u n="498" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0179">but <unclear/> isn't quite as disturbing as that concept <pause dur="short"/> it was a very very warped</u>
<u n="500" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="501" who="S0179">very strange</u>
<u n="502" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0058">okay well I mean think about the film Matilda <pause dur="short"/> which is essentially about child abuse</u>
<u n="505" who="S0179">again</u>
<u n="506" who="S0058">so</u>
<u n="507" who="S0179">it's a far less disturbing concept</u>
<u n="508" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="long"/> But did you enjoy it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0179">yes I enjoyed it <trunc>tr</trunc></u>
<u n="510" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0179">tremendously <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was fucking good</u>
<u n="512" who="S0058">Good</u>
<u n="513" who="S0179">just marred</u>
<u n="514" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0179">I'd have said you shouldn't have it was brilliant <pause dur="short"/> it was well-made <pause dur="short"/> it was a very good premise <pause dur="short"/> it just wasn't executed in either a way that either it was appropriate or that was fulfilling its potential</u>
<u n="516" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> but like I said an eighteen isn't good for <vocal desc="laugh"/> money um cos a lot of the people who go to the cinema are quite young</u>
<u n="517" who="S0179">yes well I think that's <trunc>f</trunc> again a problem for ratings um mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0058">well it's like Borat um not Borat um Bruno <pause dur="short"/> so Sacha Baron Cohen made two versions <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> An eighteen and a fifteen <pause dur="short"/> so that all the adults would be like oh well I'm gonna go and see the eighteen <pause dur="short"/> it'll be rude and crude or whatever <pause dur="short"/> um but it also meant you could get another three years worth of <trunc>thr</trunc> yeah three years worth of cinema-going public in there paying money for it <pause dur="short"/> which people did sort of <trunc>m</trunc> say well they can't you know not great <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="519" who="S0179">why not?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0058"><trunc>Y</trunc> yeah he was just being awkward about the fact that that's what people do except they only release the nicer one normally <pause dur="short"/> um so yeah that was a a toned down version cos it would've I think they <trunc>prob</trunc> what they probably do is give it a sort of rough rating and then they can</u>
<u n="521" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="522" who="S0058">yeah do things <vocal desc="laugh"/> to it and soften things and <trunc>s</trunc> do a little bit of tweaking</u>
<u n="523" who="S0179">well to be fair it was very formulatic formulaic <pause dur="short"/> as in there was probably very you know it was probably for the tight guidelines</u>
<u n="524" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0179">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0058">and you can stick to it <pause dur="short"/> but I know that they did take things out that they'd shot <pause dur="short"/> so maybe they shot it watched it and went uh uh uh yeah this isn't gonna this is ticking these boxes for a fifteen <pause dur="short"/> I mean there must be quite tight guidelines because otherwise how would you <trunc>d</trunc> you know you <trunc>cou</trunc> you couldn't be subjective</u>
<u n="527" who="S0179">mm some of it might be but yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> to a certain extent it has to but it's like marking an exam <pause dur="short"/> an English exam <pause dur="short"/> because you know obviously it's gonna be a bit subjective but you <unclear/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0179">the boxes aren't subjective but the things that you are choosing for the boxes are</u>
<u n="530" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0058">I think that's a really fascinating topic actually <pause dur="short"/> how films are rated <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="533" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> I mean er</u>
<u n="534" who="S0058">and <trunc>y</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="535" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And you you notice at the beginning they had the sort of fancy old-fashioned um sort of certificate</u>
<u n="537" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0058">to mark the hundred years of it <pause dur="short"/> which is interesting in itself</u>
<u n="539" who="S0179">well they were rating silent films</u>
<u n="540" who="S0058">er nineteen twelve first talkie I believe was nineteen twelve <pause dur="short"/> so hitting there was some maybe something about different people thinking about films in a different way <pause dur="short"/> and the oh I love the history of cinema <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Or was it slightly earlier? Was it nineteen O seven? Anyway <pause dur="short"/> never mind <pause dur="short"/> um but yes <pause dur="short"/> oh I did <trunc>f</trunc> find interesting when we were buying tickets did you see the um sort of big sign behind the desk which er had the ratings on it? Um it was one saying you know um eighteen no change fifteen</u>
<u n="541" who="S0179">fuck</u>
<u n="542" who="S0058">so where's he going?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0058">er yeah <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> um what was I saying? Um <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah that was it yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it had sort of all the ratings and then and um in the middle it had the new twelve A rating <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh that was how many years ago? Ten years ago?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0179">about that</u>
<u n="546" who="S0058">about ten years ago</u>
<u n="547" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0058">so it's a very old sign <pause dur="short"/> actually no I think it came out about the same time as the second Lord of the Rings film</u>
<u n="549" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0058">I'm <trunc>f</trunc> I'm fairly certain that it did cos that was why they were thinking about it</u>
<u n="551" who="S0179">no it's sensible except when you pointed out you know it made it very difficult for people with kids <pause dur="short"/> sort of between ten and twelve to go to the cinema because there was very little they could see</u>
<u n="552" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0179">they didn't want to see the PGs</u>
<u n="554" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0179">but <unclear/> fifty <pause dur="short"/> I really should know that</u>
<u n="556" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Possibly</u>
<u n="557" who="S0179">oh well</u>
<u n="558" who="S0058">er</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="559" who="S0179">take that non-intuitive speed limit</u>
<u n="560" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah cos if it was all films like Spiderman that which I think was a twelve a um</u>
<u n="561" who="S0179">just killing the beams because as we go over the hill</u>
<u n="562" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0179">if we approach that <unclear/> that's gonna really blind <unclear/> Back up <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="564" who="S0058">mhm <pause dur="short"/> um yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I mean Spiderman yeah I think it was one of the ones where it was kind of well you know parents can have a say you know have a say in this because it's kind of disturbing but not too much so</u>
<u n="565" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0058">so it's you know it's a bit violent but not horrendously so <pause dur="short"/> but I remember seeing um you know the the bad Batman film?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0058">um with Arnold Schwarzenegger</u>
<u n="569" who="S0179">well all <unclear/> films are a bit interesting</u>
<u n="570" who="S0058">well yeah true <pause dur="short"/> but I mean I can't remember what it's called <pause dur="short"/> but it had um Uma Thurman in it as Poison Ivy and Arnold Schwarzenegger as the ice-man or something <pause dur="short"/> and he froze things <pause dur="short"/> um and he had catchphrases like ice to meet you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It was just dreadful <pause dur="short"/> um and I saw that when I was really young and it was just not nice <pause dur="short"/> it's cos that was a PG <pause dur="short"/> and we must've said yeah let's go and see that <pause dur="short"/> mum was like I dunno you might not like it <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't we didn't particularly <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Mostly because it wasn't very good</u>
<u n="571" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0058">I think even at the time <vocal desc="laugh"/> we realized</u>
<u n="573" who="S0179">you see the first Lord of the Rings I can't believe that's a PG</u>
<u n="574" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0179">that film disturbed me <pause dur="short"/> I was about sixteen when I watched it</u>
<u n="576" who="S0058">first Lord of the Rings? I don't think you were that old cos I wasn't fifteen <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="577" who="S0179">er in that ballpark anyway <pause dur="short"/> fifteen sixteen</u>
<u n="578" who="S0058">well I saw all of them before sixth form <pause dur="short"/> so the <trunc>f</trunc> and they came out three successive years so</u>
<u n="579" who="S0179">I I don't actually care</u>
<u n="580" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> fair enough <pause dur="short"/> I think we were a bit younger than that <pause dur="short"/> but yeah um no I mean the first film was um</u>
<u n="581" who="S0179">but it it</u>
<u n="582" who="S0058">presumably it stayed</u>
<u n="583" who="S0179">scared me <pause dur="short"/> I remember that</u>
<u n="584" who="S0058">oh no it was very scary <pause dur="short"/> presumably it just stayed just the right side of it to be given the PG <pause dur="short"/> whereas the second and third ones didn't <pause dur="short"/> they <trunc>s</trunc> presumably skipped over the line</u>
<u n="585" who="S0179">the first one was by far the scariest</u>
<u n="586" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought so <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>th</trunc> the threat</u>
<u n="587" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0058">I thought was so strong in the first one <pause dur="short"/> um whereas after that it was just more downright kind of evil rather than just yeah threat <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc> menace <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="589" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0058">but</u>
<u n="591" who="S0179">sort of the idea er theme er split personality Golem</u>
<u n="592" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0179">very strange</u>
<u n="594" who="S0058">but that's the second film though</u>
<u n="595" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="596" who="S0058">you er</u>
<u n="597" who="S0179"><unclear/> in the first film <unclear/> Er</u>
<u n="598" who="S0058">but you don't really see Golem though <pause dur="short"/> cos they hadn't properly um kind of finished designing him <pause dur="short"/> so you see his eyes and his hands <pause dur="short"/> in the <trunc>m</trunc> Mines of Moria <pause dur="short"/> but you don't actually see him <pause dur="short"/> you find out what happens but you don't see his final final form</u>
<u n="599" who="S0179">yeah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0058">until the second film <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm yeah nerd <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="601" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0058">yeah I mean that's that's pretty bad yeah <pause dur="short"/> um even that's not one of the obvious things either <pause dur="short"/> that was still quite yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0179">what are we gonna do about food?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0058">um do you wanna go and I mean <trunc>p</trunc> yeah <unclear/> gonna be eleven or twelve I think <pause dur="short"/> so do you wanna go and see if the Chinese is open?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0179">three quarters of an hour <pause dur="short"/> that's probably <unclear/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty close</u>
<u n="607" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0058">it's pretty close <pause dur="short"/> it's not too far <pause dur="short"/> bit too far to you know just to pop along <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="609" who="S0179">what are you talking about? Oh the cinema</u>
<u n="610" who="S0058">the <unclear/> Yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0179">it's only of the order of twice the time to get to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0179">slightly more but</u>
<u n="614" who="S0058">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="615" who="S0179">and of course there is no traffic at this time of night</u>
<u n="616" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0179"><unclear/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but in all fair actually no for <anon type="place"/> cinema I reckon we could get back in fifteen minutes at this time of night</u>
<u n="618" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0179">particularly if one wasn't too bothered about speed limits</u>
<u n="620" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="622" who="S0058"><trunc>S</trunc> um do you wanna go to the Chinese see if it's open? If it's not go to Domino's?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0179">oh we could park on</u>
<u n="624" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="625" who="S0179">the double yellow lines outside</u>
<u n="626" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0179">living dangerously <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="628" who="S0058">might be a policeman hiding somewhere</u>
<u n="629" who="S0179">er I was gonna say the police will have nothing better to do tonight <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="631" who="S0179">so <trunc>l</trunc> let's not do that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="633" who="S0179">um</u>
<u n="634" who="S0058">did yeah do you wanna go and see if that's open?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="636" who="S0058">domino's is probably midnight</u>
<u n="637" who="S0179">do you know we could just park outside Domino's</u>
<u n="638" who="S0058">yeah and walk up <pause dur="short"/> what do you think? Do you wanna do that?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0179">um <pause dur="short"/> I'm not hugely hungry</u>
<u n="640" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0179">I might like a bit of something savoury</u>
<u n="642" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="643" who="S0179">actually yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0058">I I wouldn't mind something to eat <pause dur="short"/> and we could just go back and bung something in the microwave out of the freezer <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="645" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0058">if you want <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="647" who="S0179">not very appetizing</u>
<u n="648" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0179">I wouldn't <trunc>mi</trunc> er my personal favourite would probably be to share a cod and chips or something but um</u>
<u n="650" who="S0058">pff <pause dur="short"/> I'm not mm I find fish and chips a little bit difficult to kind of stomach <unclear/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0179">could you possibly signal?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0058">wow</u>
<u n="653" who="S0179">that's just</u>
<u n="654" who="S0058"><unclear/> he signalled once he turned which</u>
<u n="655" who="S0179">it's just</u>
<u n="656" who="S0058">is just insane</u>
<u n="657" who="S0179">I wish when it was blatantly obvious what you were doing</u>
<u n="658" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0179">Christ <pause dur="short"/> some people are ignorant</u>
<u n="660" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean yeah if <trunc>tha</trunc> if you don't fancy</u>
<u n="661" who="S0179">yeah well I'd beat myself up if I realized that I'd missed a signal that would've been marginally beneficial to someone <unclear/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah you were right behind him</u>
<u n="663" who="S0179">well let's not make it sound like it was tailgating him <pause dur="short"/> but yes</u>
<u n="664" who="S0058">no no but I mean er you were blatantly there <pause dur="short"/> he must have seen you and knew you were there <pause dur="short"/> he's he did bother to signal afterwards <pause dur="short"/> he clearly realized at some point along that process that you were there</u>
<u n="665" who="S0179">but might not of</u>
<u n="666" who="S0058">he might not yeah he maybe he was just signalling out of habit at the point he normally signals <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Wouldn't be surprised</u>
<u n="667" who="S0179">there was literally zero point in that signal</u>
<u n="668" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="669" who="S0179">er so what looks open?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> fish and Chicken is shut</u>
<u n="671" who="S0179">domino's?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0058">domino's looks like it could well be open <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> the lights is on <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so pizza or Chinese <pause dur="short"/> I think are probably the best <pause dur="short"/> looks like a Domino's employee <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0179">I'd be surprised if they are shut</u>
<u n="674" who="S0058">what Fish and Chicken?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0179">maximum stay four hours <pause dur="short"/> probably alright then</u>
<u n="676" who="S0058">probably manage yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0179">right</u>
</body>
</text>
