<text id="SZR7">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:13:44</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0255 S0256</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Friends and socialising, traffic/driving etiquette.</topics>
		<activity>Catch up with daughter while making tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, inviting, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0255">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Boston, Lincs</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Boston/London/Peterborough</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>account manager - sales</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0256">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Grantham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Civil servant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0255">right there you go so what were you saying? you've got plans for Halloween?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0256">yeah I'm going to a murder mystery</u>
<u n="3" who="S0255">where's that?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0256">at erm Holiday Inn sort of near <anon type="place"/> I think but it's it's through work it's well it's <trunc>n</trunc> it sort of is and sort of isn't there's like a group thing that they put on events or they they get tickets certain amount of tickets going for er certain events and things like that</u>
<u n="5" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="6" who="S0256">and then if you're part of this group you get them extra discounted if you're not part of the group you get them discounted <vocal desc="cough"/> so twenty pounds and you get a three course meal and a murder mystery evening and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> mentioned it and said did we wanna go? erm and so I'm going <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gonna go and so's erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her boyfriend and then a couple of other people are going as well</u>
<u n="7" who="S0255">so is it just something that comes round on like a work email that shows?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0256">yeah er well it's there's like a folder like erm of events that er they have cos er they do all sorts like trips to erm France like for the Christmas markets</u>
<u n="9" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh right?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0256">and they do all sorts of bits</u>
<u n="11" who="S0255">so er so could you do it so like if one person decided they wanted to go from work they could go and join in cos it's a group like as in like the murder mystery's on?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0255">so you don't have to get a certain amount of people?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0256">yeah usually yeah I think that's what it normally is</u>
<u n="15" who="S0255">mm that sounds really good</u>
<u n="16" who="S0256">yeah so it'll be good I mean erm I might sign up to the actual group cos that gets you er a lot cheaper and I think it's like fourteen pounds if you're part of the group or</u>
<u n="17" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="18" who="S0256">or whatever or eleven pounds or something it's only like one pound a month but</u>
<u n="19" who="S0255">oh sounds really good</u>
<u n="20" who="S0256">yeah so it should be good fun <vocal desc="cough"/> so yeah I'm doing that instead of just sitting in for Halloween like I normally do</u>
<u n="21" who="S0255">and giving sweets out to the few children that might come this far</u>
<u n="22" who="S0256">yeah but no one ever does</u>
<u n="23" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0256">not really</u>
<u n="25" who="S0255">look marinated tuna</u>
<u n="26" who="S0256">I can't really smell anything not properly</u>
<u n="27" who="S0255">mm smells nice</u>
<u n="28" who="S0256"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0255">smells nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0256">yeah I'm sure it smells nice I'm sure it tastes nice</u>
<u n="31" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you just have the confidence in my cooking</u>
<u n="32" who="S0256">I yeah I just can't verify that right now</u>
<u n="33" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0256"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0255">well I went to a murder mystery although er it's a few years ago now gosh a lot of years ago actually</u>
<u n="36" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0255">I can't even remember <unclear>who</unclear> I went with it was a group a group of er group of women and it was for for someone's birthday I think they'd just decided let's do something different and it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0255">and you went for the weekend and you actually had the time to go round <anon type="place"/> as well as stay at the hotel and the actual murder mystery was just erm like one evening of it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0255">erm but you can do them where you actually go for a whole week I think or not a whole week a weekend</u>
<u n="42" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0255">and it starts and goes over the weekend</u>
<u n="44" who="S0256">that sounds good</u>
<u n="45" who="S0255">but I tell you something actually bit of a tip erm what they actually said was afterwards we could've actually gone and asked them questions not as in who was it? but we could've maybe asked the people that were doing it and the characters you you could actually ask them some quite obvious questions I can't even think what it was but they said that if we'd asked this they would've told us so and so or if the if we'd asked so and so</u>
<u n="46" who="S0256">yeah because I think you all tend to get like a card don't you? with information on it</u>
<u n="47" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0256">about who you are and what you're doing</u>
<u n="49" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0256">and the idea is to go round and to speak to people obviously and find out information</u>
<u n="51" who="S0255">yeah that's it</u>
<u n="52" who="S0256">erm I have done er a little one before <trunc>w</trunc>with the guides</u>
<u n="53" who="S0255">oh yeah what was that? with er?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0256">on a guide camp</u>
<u n="55" who="S0255">oh <trunc>o</trunc>okay</u>
<u n="56" who="S0256"><unclear/> it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0256">sorry</u>
<u n="59" who="S0255">I think when we did it the people <trunc>ca</trunc> people came round and we had sort of ten minutes to question each of the people</u>
<u n="60" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0255">with what was happening when you've been told the scenario</u>
<u n="62" who="S0256">yeah yeah and I don't</u>
<u n="63" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><unclear/> we were going to do one again for er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she was forty this year</u>
<u n="64" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0255">and we'd planned to do something and somebody came up with the idea of it but it <trunc>en</trunc> it was a really expensive one</u>
<u n="66" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0255">and then actually we we said we'd do it and we were gonna go and stay at the hotel as well but it got it was cancelled cos there weren't enough people</u>
<u n="68" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0255">it's certainly something I would like to do again</u>
<u n="70" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it I think it'll be good hopefully</u>
<u n="71" who="S0255">yeah I think you'll you'll have a laugh with er so who did you say is going? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0256"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then there's erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's also on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s team she's new</u>
<u n="73" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0256">and er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who was on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s team but's gone downstairs now and then a couple of the their partners are coming along as well I think by the sounds of it mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0256">so yeah should be good</u>
<u n="77" who="S0255">sounds alright</u>
<u n="78" who="S0256">yeah so no should be good fun erm <vocal desc="cough"/> have you heard the new Iphone sixes are bending?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0256">in everyone's pocket</u>
<u n="81" who="S0255">oh I <trunc>hear</trunc> yes I heard that I think there's no official response yet so I might hold off getting mine for another few days until they just er</u>
<u n="82" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0256">yeah make sure it's not gonna snap</u>
<u n="84" who="S0255">cos it if you <trunc>ha</trunc> if you end up having to have a case er or cover on it that sort of defeats the object doesn't it? of having</u>
<u n="85" who="S0256" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="86" who="S0255">well I know you always do but I never do do I? I've never</u>
<u n="87" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="88" who="S0255">I never have a a cover cos I like it</u>
<u n="89" who="S0256">I have a cover cos I drop it</u>
<u n="90" who="S0255">and I</u>
<u n="91" who="S0256">I dropped mine under my car today</u>
<u n="92" who="S0255">did you?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0256">literally like not even just just slightly under like in the middle under my car</u>
<u n="94" who="S0255">oh god</u>
<u n="95" who="S0256">bearing in mind it had been raining and I'm like how am I gonna get that back?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0256">and I had to get my the mac that I've got in the back of my car not obviously an Apple Mac like er you know coat mac</u>
<u n="98" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0256">and I put that on the floor leant on it and then like leaning right under my car to get my phone back</u>
<u n="100" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0256">cos I had to decide like do I really slowly creep forward cos it wasn't near any wheels</u>
<u n="102" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0256">so do I like really slowly creep forward and risk driving over it? or do I erm do I lean under my car?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0255">like like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="105" who="S0256">er yeah exactly yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0255">that was</u>
<u n="107" who="S0256">and I didn't didn't really fancy doing that cos the thing is I've only had it like a couple of days</u>
<u n="108" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh no gosh I'd forgotten that as well yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0256">yeah so I'm like erm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0256">can we trade back? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0255"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh goodness</u>
<u n="113" who="S0256">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then erm the other <trunc>f</trunc>other funny thing on the way to work I was driving down the road and I was driving down the main road</u>
<u n="114" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0256">and this woman was coming out from one of the side roads</u>
<u n="116" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0256">and she <trunc>deci</trunc> one of those people that decided they were gonna start pulling out</u>
<u n="118" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0256">even though nobody was letting them in but they hadn't been there long</u>
<u n="120" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0256">they'd only just sort of pulled up</u>
<u n="122" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0256">but they were edging out and out of principle I never let anyone in if they're edging out because I think it's rude</u>
<u n="124" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0256">so I didn't let her out and she was right alongside me and she flashed her lights at me</u>
<u n="126" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0256">because I didn't let her out</u>
<u n="128" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0256">and then she pulled in behind me and <trunc>p</trunc> like flicked her hazards and I'm like I'm under no obligation to let you in love</u>
<u n="130" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="131" who="S0256">my I have right of way here</u>
<u n="132" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0256">I don't have to let you in if you'd have waited patiently I would've let you in</u>
<u n="134" who="S0255">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="135" who="S0256">because you didn't I didn't but she was like and then she had her lights on and they were on like full beam and I'm like you're really annoying me now</u>
<u n="136" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0256">so I was like yeah that's all that's the that's the fun of driving my route to work though cos it's</u>
<u n="138" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0256">always really busy so like</u>
<u n="140" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0256">there's people coming out everywhere</u>
<u n="142" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0256">so you get some muppets</u>
<u n="144" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0256">people that think they own the roads and they don't I own the roads</u>
<u n="146" who="S0255">I think that time of the morning everyone it's like rush hour isn't it?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0256" trans="overlap">school run</u>
<u n="148" who="S0255">everyone's going to work going to school got to be somewhere dropping someone <trunc>t</trunc> on the way</u>
<u n="149" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="150" who="S0255">and and they do people get all wound up you think the the best thing is if everyone just chilled and relaxed and like yeah you let</u>
<u n="151" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0255">somebody in and you don't</u>
<u n="153" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0255">try and push in and and then everything would move a lot better wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0256" trans="overlap"><unclear/> if people don't cos then about five minutes down the road there was a car waiting patiently at the side in like one of the parking bits</u>
<u n="156" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0256">indicator on just waiting</u>
<u n="158" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0256">so I stopped and let him in</u>
<u n="160" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I bet she was behind you going oi oi <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0256" trans="overlap">no she'd gone the other way by that point I think erm it was no actually no she hadn't she would've seen it yeah probably I was like yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0255">but I like it when you're driving along and you sort of get a chain reaction so <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="165" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0255">you stop and let somebody in and then they're going along and then they stop and let somebody else in</u>
<u n="167" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0255">and then they're going along and then that person stops and you think it's like good karma isn't it?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0256" trans="overlap">it's like they say if you if you smile at somebody erm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0256">in the day</u>
<u n="172" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0256">then that normally make their day feel better or they'll then smile at someone else</u>
<u n="174" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0256">I I just think that er if I randomly smiled at a stranger on the street they'd probably think weirdo what's she doing?</u>
<u n="176" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0256">crazy and run the other direction</u>
<u n="179" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0256">so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0255">ah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0256">I'm never really sure about that</u>
<u n="183" who="S0255">er</u>
<u n="184" who="S0256"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0255">I might go and get some more fish tomorrow</u>
<u n="186" who="S0256">oh yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0255">did you want anything?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0256">er</u>
<u n="189" who="S0255">or you need to clean yours actually before you put anything in</u>
<u n="190" who="S0256">I need to clean mine</u>
<u n="191" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0256">I need to get some more sawtails because I've only I've got a male and a female I need to get another female</u>
<u n="193" who="S0255">did you lose one then?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0256">she got egg bound and died</u>
<u n="195" who="S0255">oh did she? was it the white one?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0256">the white one</u>
<u n="197" who="S0255">oh bless her that's a shame</u>
<u n="198" who="S0256"><unclear/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0256">she didn't have much of a fun life did she? bless her</u>
<u n="201" who="S0255">no no no</u>
<u n="202" who="S0256">then she got egg bound</u>
<u n="203" who="S0255">that's why you say you need er probably a couple more females</u>
<u n="204" who="S0256">I need yeah I need I need at least another one</u>
<u n="205" who="S0255">well are you going to do your fish tonight?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0256">mm I need to do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s watering tonight</u>
<u n="207" who="S0255">pardon?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0256">need to water <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s flowers</u>
<u n="209" who="S0255">oh yeah I was just gonna say if you did if you cleaned them out tonight I'd get you some more but I'm not gonna get you more to put in in there cos that's not fair on them cos er when they've just been moved it needs to be cleaner</u>
<u n="210" who="S0256">yeah I need to clean em out but it's <trunc>g</trunc> by the time I've eaten tea done <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s watering</u>
<u n="211" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0256">it's gonna be late and I don't wanna be too late for tea tonight to bed tonight</u>
<u n="213" who="S0255">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0256">cos I'm tired I'll get up early</u>
<u n="215" who="S0255">yeah no that's fine I think I'm gonna get</u>
<u n="216" who="S0256">no I'm probably gonna do em tomorrow or Friday</u>
<u n="217" who="S0255">some more of those erm er the albino rainbow fish or the gold ones</u>
<u n="218" who="S0256" trans="overlap">yeah I <unclear/> from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0255">yeah you can call round there can't you? I think they're <trunc>o</trunc> are they open till six? I'm not sure</u>
<u n="220" who="S0256">mm I'll check but I can pop in there on the way back from work Monday</u>
<u n="221" who="S0255">yeah okay</u>
<u n="222" who="S0256"><vocal desc="cough"/> or Saturday erm I'm out for a meal on Saturday night</u>
<u n="223" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="224" who="S0256">for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <trunc>sto</trunc> she stopped doing the erm district commissioner role</u>
<u n="225" who="S0255">oh okay</u>
<u n="226" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0255">so what's she doing? just the local ones going out or is it every is it a big?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0256">no <unclear/> a district thing er like a er just our district</u>
<u n="229" who="S0255">okay where's that?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0256">erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0255">oh lovely they do real nice salmon at the back there you can go and</u>
<u n="232" who="S0256" trans="overlap">I don't know what though it depends er they don't always do the salmon</u>
<u n="233" who="S0255">don't they?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0256">no they do a mixture of stuff on that grill</u>
<u n="235" who="S0255">mm mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0256">they do a mix er it depends what's on on the day <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0256"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0255">are you coughing better?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0256">mm no</u>
<u n="241" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0256">I sort of I'm doing like cos they're really tickly ones but they hurt so then I'm doing like pitiful coughs <vocal desc="cough"/> and then</u>
<u n="243" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>piti</trunc>pitiful coughs</u>
<u n="244" who="S0256">yeah not proper ones like right down in the chest and then every now and again I'll get one and I'm like <vocal desc="misc"/> and it really hurts</u>
<u n="245" who="S0255">mm is oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not there so you don't know whether she's better or not?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0256">no I don't know she's back tomorrow</u>
<u n="247" who="S0255">is she? oh</u>
<u n="248" who="S0256">yeah she only had like three days off she's not been of a week she's just using her holiday up</u>
<u n="249" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0256">cos she's got a lot left she's got like eighteen days left to use by the end of the year and she can only take over like seven or nine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0256">so</u>
<u n="253" who="S0255">and how much have you got left?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0256">well one I'll have one and a half days once I've taken all my holiday in October</u>
<u n="255" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0256">cos I've got a week off in October and a day off in October haven't I?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0256">erm so I will have one and a half days but I will be banking some flex I've got like four <trunc>hou</trunc> four and a half hours now in flex</u>
<u n="259" who="S0255">okay did I tell you mum's coming to stay? the week after I have <trunc>m</trunc>my op on the Monday</u>
<u n="260" who="S0256">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0255">she's coming on the Sunday probably till Wednesday</u>
<u n="262" who="S0256"><unclear/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says er right that week er that I have the op he says he cos he's on day he says he can come and visit me in hospital on Wednesday afternoon erm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0256">okay</u>
<u n="265" who="S0255">or Wednesday night so he said <trunc>may</trunc> could you cos I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna come Monday so I didn't know if you could do Tuesday after Rainbows maybe?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0256">probably</u>
<u n="267" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0256">yeah should be fine <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0255">he was just he was organising it saying well er cos er he was saying cos he's <unclear/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0256" trans="overlap">visiting hour goes on till like eight doesn't it? so</u>
<u n="271" who="S0255">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0256"><unclear/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0255">yeah cos er he was just saying</u>
<u n="274" who="S0256">why's he organising? he doesn't organise</u>
<u n="275" who="S0255" trans="overlap">well er he was just saying</u>
<u n="276" who="S0256">he's never organised</u>
<u n="277" who="S0255">er he said it was funny really he said do you want</u>
<u n="278" who="S0256"><unclear/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0255">do you want people to come and see you in hospital? and I said well they can if they like he said no I mean do you want people to? he said cos if you if some people think no I don't want anyone to come I'd rather just curl up and whatever he said but if you'd like us to come er he said if you want people to come you have to tell me otherwise I'll just think you might not want me to come and</u>
<u n="280" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0255">and I'll be busy and then I won't <trunc>d</trunc> come and he said but if you'd like me to come I'll come</u>
<u n="282" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0255">so I said yes</u>
<u n="284" who="S0256">it's that week isn't it?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's fine thirteenth yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0256">cos I'm off for my birthday so nana'll be here on my birthday</u>
<u n="287" who="S0255">oh right yeah no I'm yeah the thirteenth I I'll have it on the thirteenth</u>
<u n="288" who="S0256">and then she's coming on the Sunday?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0255">yeah she's coming on the Sunday</u>
<u n="290" who="S0256">until the Wednesday?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0256">what's the Wednesday? my birthday</u>
<u n="293" who="S0255">yes I know I know I'd seen that when I put it on the calendar</u>
<u n="294" who="S0256" trans="overlap">and I'm off work on the Wednesday</u>
<u n="295" who="S0255">you're off work that week?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0256">I'm off work that day</u>
<u n="297" who="S0255">just the day? oh I thought you were off the whole week?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0256">no I'm off the week week after</u>
<u n="299" who="S0255">oh okay oh that'll work nicely as well actually then</u>
<u n="300" who="S0256" trans="overlap">because that's the half-term and that's when we're gonna have like hours a day skating rehearsals</u>
<u n="301" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0256">but I'll be around I'll only help <unclear/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah no that'll that'll work really well</u>
<u n="304" who="S0256">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0255">that'll work really well</u>
<u n="306" who="S0256">so <unclear>right</unclear> I'll be off that week</u>
<u n="307" who="S0255" trans="overlap">just <unclear>see what I can</unclear> do with this tuna</u>
<u n="308" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I pay <unclear>you</unclear> pay attention <vocal desc="laugh"/> well you take stuff in that we say</u>
<u n="309" who="S0255"><unclear/> well <unclear/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0256">have you sprayed anything on that?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0255">pardon?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0256">have you sprayed anything on that?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0255">why?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0256">cos it'll stick</u>
<u n="315" who="S0255">oh okay good point</u>
<u n="316" who="S0256">cos tuna sticks</u>
<u n="317" who="S0255">it almost smells like it's fermenting could be the wine</u>
<u n="318" who="S0256">oh trying to get me drunk?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0255">no <pause dur="short"/> oh god where's this? oh <unclear>who</unclear> finished the scraping?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0256">I dunno?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0255">maybe okay</u>
<u n="322" who="S0256">like I pay attention to what's on there</u>
<u n="323" who="S0255">right erm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0256">I never pay attention to what's on there I just yeah I just know tuna sticks really badly to everything</u>
<u n="325" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="326" who="S0256">it's a sticky fish</u>
<u n="327" who="S0255">thank you for that</u>
<u n="328" who="S0256">anytime</u>
<u n="329" who="S0255">oh so yes I marinated it with I did soy sauce honey and then some white wine cos there was some open in the fridge</u>
<u n="330" who="S0256"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0255">and I thought it's probably got past drinking but it'll I'm sure it'll be alright for cooking</u>
<u n="332" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0255">so</u>
<u n="334" who="S0256">so you're not trying to get me drunk you're trying to erm poison me</u>
<u n="335" who="S0255">it'll be fine cos the alcohol <unclear>steams</unclear> doesn't it?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0256">burns off?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0255">well it erm well the alcohol evaporates so actually it's <trunc>j</trunc> you have the flavour when you cook with it you just have the flavour not the actual full erm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0256">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0255">thing</u>
<u n="340" who="S0256">ah mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0255">oh that smells good <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
