<text id="SZT4">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:17:42</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0486 S0528</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The ticket office in Creeh-ST-Michael.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Strangers</relationships>
		<topics>Swedish massage, hospice, nursery education, wife, female equality, terminology, the ME event next year and the involvement of women.</topics>
		<activity> Taking a break from the track work, working party.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Enplaining, Inquiring, complaining, advising, requesting,anecdote telling, making arrangements,</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0486">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Well, Somerset</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/Wales</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>I may have a slight Somerset accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Taunton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>40 years on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>retired artist and antique dealer/gallery owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0528">
				<exactage>77</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>West Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Axminster</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year 3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>w_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired accomodation manager, nationwide building society</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0486">good morning <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thank you</u>
<u n="2" who="S0528" trans="overlap">good morning</u>
<u n="3" who="S0486" trans="overlap">for talking to me <vocal desc="laugh"/> so here we are erm in <anon type="place"/> in the field that belongs to the parish council and is erm you're out here with the model engineers on a working party this morning</u>
<u n="4" who="S0528">correct</u>
<u n="5" who="S0486">erm tell me why do you come?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0528">to try and support the engineering club with a little bit of manual labour I like to support them in in other ways rather than just attending to play trains</u>
<u n="7" who="S0486">yeah that's great because there are always jobs to be done out here aren't there?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0528">there are indeed yes</u>
<u n="9" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah so how long have you been coming?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0528">probably for the last er four months now I think it's</u>
<u n="11" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right so you're quite a new boy doing this then?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0528" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="13" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0486">so erm what are your what are <trunc>y</trunc> what are the jobs you like doing best?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0528">I don't mind really I I just like to be involved erm the I would say the other way the one thing I don't like very much is painting</u>
<u n="17" who="S0486">oh right is it is it is it any particular reason? or</u>
<u n="18" who="S0528">it's just something I don't enjoy I've always been involved with the building trade in one form or another since National Service</u>
<u n="19" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="20" who="S0528" trans="overlap">erm so I'm quite practically minded can</u>
<u n="21" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="22" who="S0528" trans="overlap">turn my hand to most things</u>
<u n="23" who="S0486">right okay</u>
<u n="24" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0486">and what what what was your role when you did your National Service?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0528">I was in Royal Airforce Signals</u>
<u n="27" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="28" who="S0528">erm which was <pause dur="short"/> particularly based in erm private or secret locations such as underground signal centres</u>
<u n="29" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0528">erm so that all of the RAF signal traffic was kept confidant</u>
<u n="31" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="32" who="S0528">and secret as necessary</u>
<u n="33" who="S0486">right is that still the case or is that all opened up now?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0528">I er think it with the new technology everything has changed</u>
<u n="35" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="36" who="S0528">erm in <trunc>d</trunc> the days I was doing National Service it was all GPO telephone equipment er so you had GPO engineers but I would imagine now it's all high technology internet all sorts</u>
<u n="37" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0528">I don't know now</u>
<u n="39" who="S0486">right well erm so much I mean so much has been brought to the fore with the easement of the erm the secrets act hasn't it?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0486" trans="overlap">recently</u>
<u n="42" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0486">and erm where they did er I can't remember the place erm where they did all the decoding erm machines erm Bickley? not Bickley something like that</u>
<u n="44" who="S0528" trans="overlap">Bletchley Park</u>
<u n="45" who="S0486"><trunc>B</trunc>Bletchley Park</u>
<u n="46" who="S0528">yes</u>
<u n="47" who="S0486">we went to Bletchley Park quite recently</u>
<u n="48" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0486"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to go and</u>
<u n="50" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0486">we went have you been there?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0528">ironically we only live forty miles away and I've never been there</u>
<u n="53" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0528">erm watched documentaries on the programme er very interesting to see what they did but I've never actually been to the site</u>
<u n="55" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no and did you see the film recently?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0528">yes</u>
<u n="57" who="S0486">did you? that was <trunc>rea</trunc></u>
<u n="58" who="S0528" trans="overlap">incredible</u>
<u n="59" who="S0486">yeah Alan Turing</u>
<u n="60" who="S0528" trans="overlap">absolutely amazing</u>
<u n="61" who="S0486">was it Alan Turing?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0528">yeah and what a tragic life</u>
<u n="65" who="S0486">what a tragic life</u>
<u n="66" who="S0528" trans="overlap">for what he contributed to this country's security</u>
<u n="67" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I know that wasn't that Cumberbatch didn't he play?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yes it was</u>
<u n="69" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah he did he was very good wasn't he?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0528" trans="overlap">he <trunc>wa</trunc> he was absolutely brilliant it's well worth anyone watching that film</u>
<u n="71" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0528">to get a better understanding of what was involved</u>
<u n="73" who="S0486">yeah I mean you can as you say you can learn so much and er conversely we saw the suffragettes recently have</u>
<u n="74" who="S0528" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="75" who="S0486" trans="overlap">you seen that?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0528">no I haven't seen that</u>
<u n="77" who="S0486">erm well we asked someone to come with us and she said she didn't want to come because it would horrible and they tortured them and all that sort of thing but actually it was a very good film and it was in the same vein</u>
<u n="78" who="S0528">yes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0486">it was an educational film</u>
<u n="80" who="S0528">yeah yes</u>
<u n="81" who="S0486">it was I reckon a drama documentary</u>
<u n="82" who="S0528">yeah <trunc>i</trunc>it does <trunc>i</trunc>it records history which will be forgotten if someone does not record it</u>
<u n="83" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0528" trans="overlap">as such</u>
<u n="85" who="S0486">and erm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0486">that's great I mean they can keep doing Downton Abbey until they're blue in the face by just making up plots it just turns</u>
<u n="88" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0486" trans="overlap">into Coronation Street really</u>
<u n="90" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0486">but erm with these sort of spot erm interests I was I I'm related to Lloyd George the prime minister erm very distantly but I am related to him I mean everybody laughs and says they're related to Lloyd George but I am and he was in the suffragette film or the actor playing Lloyd George</u>
<u n="92" who="S0528" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="93" who="S0486" trans="overlap">was in the suffragette film and that was very interesting</u>
<u n="94" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0486" trans="overlap">so I recommend it to you it's not erm a bit like the Turing film it it's not erm it <trunc>does</trunc> you don't come out feeling happy it's not a happy film</u>
<u n="96" who="S0528">no</u>
<u n="97" who="S0486" trans="overlap">but at the same it's <trunc>i</trunc>instructional and and you can</u>
<u n="98" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0486">get the gist of the ideas at the time</u>
<u n="100" who="S0528">well there is so much we don't know about for instance world war two</u>
<u n="101" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0528" trans="overlap">you know erm for example my father was a military policeman</u>
<u n="103" who="S0486">oh was he?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0528">erm and he served in north Africa and Italy Tunisia and he ended up in Romania and people say we we didn't have forces in Romania but we did</u>
<u n="105" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="106" who="S0528">we had a military police detachment there</u>
<u n="107" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="108" who="S0528">were basically doing what this country did in <pause dur="short"/> iraq I think when they sent out police first of all and there was a sad loss of seven policemen who were</u>
<u n="109" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0528" trans="overlap">mobbed and killed</u>
<u n="111" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0528">by a gang er that's what my father did it was a small group of policemen</u>
<u n="113" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0528" trans="overlap">in Romania erm he had collected a large number of photographs posing with Russian officers</u>
<u n="115" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="116" who="S0528">all sorts local people local events er when he died I asked my children erm these photographic albums are quite an unusual record</u>
<u n="117" who="S0486" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="118" who="S0528">erm if I give them to you will what will you do with them?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0486" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0528">and they said well we'll take care of them dad you know</u>
<u n="121" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and I so I chose then I asked their consent and I donated them all the military police museum</u>
<u n="123" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="124" who="S0528">and they were actually thrilled to bits because apparently they get loads of paperwork about servicemen</u>
<u n="125" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0528">rarely get any photographs</u>
<u n="127" who="S0486">right right</u>
<u n="128" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and there's my dad in his military police uniform</u>
<u n="129" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="130" who="S0528">with his Jeep</u>
<u n="131" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0528">posing with Russian officers it incredible record they were thrilled to bits so it they've got all his personal documentation his ID cards his medals he was mentioned in dispatches</u>
<u n="133" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0528">they've got a complete record of one sergeant in</u>
<u n="135" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0528" trans="overlap">military police</u>
<u n="137" who="S0486">a real family pride then on an <trunc>anc</trunc> er as of an ancestor really</u>
<u n="138" who="S0528">yes and I didn't want it to get lost in the future</u>
<u n="139" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="140" who="S0528" trans="overlap">I thought that</u>
<u n="141" who="S0486">speak up oh they've gone by</u>
<u n="142" who="S0528">if it goes if it goes into history like that</u>
<u n="143" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0528" trans="overlap">that's a good record of world war two</u>
<u n="145" who="S0486">right yes</u>
<u n="146" who="S0528">from an unusual aspect of it you know</u>
<u n="147" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes exactly yeah it is</u>
<u n="148" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and he did survive the war</u>
<u n="149" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="150" who="S0528">er it did torment him later in life</u>
<u n="151" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0528">but erm yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0486">how do you <trunc>fee</trunc> if you can speak up a little more because we've got some people outside erm how do you see then when you see Flog It and people are selling their medals and</u>
<u n="154" who="S0528">I I don't really like it but I <trunc>th</trunc> I don't think you can you you can't manage it can you? they they become erm valued items and people will sell them erm if the family don't take care of them and pass them on</u>
<u n="155" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="156" who="S0528">to different generations</u>
<u n="157" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="158" who="S0528">then they get lost anyway</u>
<u n="159" who="S0486">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0528" trans="overlap">it's sad that they've become an item for making money on</u>
<u n="161" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh it does it is yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0528" trans="overlap">but that's again why I decided that my father's record and his medals</u>
<u n="163" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0528">should all go to the military police</u>
<u n="165" who="S0486">yes exactly yeah and and you and and that's right and and it's assured now and you you can rest rest assured I mean I've got a collection of erm Lloyd George memorabilia not that I've they're just things that</u>
<u n="166" who="S0528" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0486" trans="overlap">the family had that for some reason people gave to me no one else wanted them</u>
<u n="168" who="S0528">no</u>
<u n="169" who="S0486">and erm I got a lot of books erm and <trunc>m</trunc>my idea one day was to go through them and maybe write something of my own but I'm actually more of a novel writer and a poetry I'm I'm in the middle of a novel at the moment I'm on page er on chapter fourteen? erm of my first novel and I've done a poetry book so far erm but erm that's what I'm doing but anyway erm back to you so do you do any writing at all?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0528">no I I I'm not a writer cum author of any sort I do enjoy putting letters together</u>
<u n="171" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="172" who="S0528">and there's plenty of opportunity with the problems that we have these days</u>
<u n="173" who="S0486">yes that's right</u>
<u n="174" who="S0528">and whether it be problems with power companies or whatever</u>
<u n="175" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and I quite enjoy putting letters together</u>
<u n="177" who="S0486">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and making my point</u>
<u n="179" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="180" who="S0528" trans="overlap">but without being too rude about it</u>
<u n="181" who="S0486">no exactly well you you know who was a past master at that was Charles Dickens</u>
<u n="182" who="S0528">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0486">if you ever get a chance to look up Charles Dickens his letters to his clock maker or clock mender erm he wrote some very witty letters erm and I won't I I can't repeat it in the same way as Charles Dickens wrote it so it's best that you look it up because it's very entertaining</u>
<u n="184" who="S0528">okay</u>
<u n="185" who="S0486">really very entertaining indeed erm so yeah but erm it is nice to bring if you're complaining about something it's nice to bring a bit of humour into it don't you find that?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0528">oh I think so er you need to make the point strongly that you are trying to get home</u>
<u n="187" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0528">on the other hand you don't demand</u>
<u n="189" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="190" who="S0528">you may expect but not demand</u>
<u n="191" who="S0486">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0528" trans="overlap">er and I always try to put a sensible letter together and I always try to keep it to one page</u>
<u n="193" who="S0486">yes that's right</u>
<u n="194" who="S0528">I think people don't like to go</u>
<u n="195" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="196" who="S0528" trans="overlap">onto a second page</u>
<u n="197" who="S0486">no it's the same if you're applying for a job it's always best to keep it on one page</u>
<u n="198" who="S0528" trans="overlap">on one page</u>
<u n="199" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0486" trans="overlap">one page erm and also in to my mind I always make the typeface slightly larger because it's easier to read erm er you know if if type if the type is very small people even younger people have got challenging eye problems haven't they? whoa it's getting a bit noisy outside isn't it?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0528"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0486">anyway we've got another five minutes to do so</u>
<u n="204" who="S0528">that's okay</u>
<u n="205" who="S0486" trans="overlap">we'll have to <trunc>sh</trunc> you'll have to shout you see erm so erm are you involved in this erm show that they're going to put on next year?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0528">I don't have any details at the moment</u>
<u n="207" who="S0486">you don't no</u>
<u n="208" who="S0528" trans="overlap">of the show and I don't know what's planned</u>
<u n="209" who="S0486">no no</u>
<u n="210" who="S0528" trans="overlap">but I would like to be involved anyway</u>
<u n="211" who="S0486">yeah yeah okay well I'm sure they I'm sure that we will be erm erm it'll be all hands on deck won't it?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0528">I would imagine so if there's some</u>
<u n="213" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0528">big function</u>
<u n="215" who="S0486">I was <trunc>hopi</trunc> I mean always when they've done shows before I I've always brought my art along <trunc>wh</trunc>when when they were in the schools like they had one in the school erm several years erm and I brought my art <trunc>arou</trunc> along and erm exhibited it but I didn't make any sales because it's not that sort of show I do think though <trunc>may</trunc>maybe you might like to press the point erm you didn't hear it here that there might be some things for women because if the men come if you do something for women as well then it'll mean you'll get more support all the way round and I think that'll be a good idea really</u>
<u n="216" who="S0528">I think it's important that you do try and involve the ladies these days you know otherwise erm they can become treated as <vocal desc="laugh"/> er tea makers and</u>
<u n="217" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="218" who="S0528">and that's <trunc>n</trunc> that's not on</u>
<u n="219" who="S0486" trans="overlap">that's not on</u>
<u n="220" who="S0528">you know <trunc>th</trunc> it's</u>
<u n="221" who="S0486">that's not on</u>
<u n="222" who="S0528" trans="overlap">it's better that they take a an interesting</u>
<u n="223" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0528" trans="overlap">er role in the organisation even if it's only from time to time</u>
<u n="225" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah somebody asked me er or a few years ago now if I'd like to make the teas for something that an organisation that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was part of and I <trunc>s</trunc> I said to my husband well if I was holding an art group would he come and make the teas for me?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0528"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0486" trans="overlap">he wouldn't so I said no I'm not doing it erm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0528" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="229" who="S0486">because erm you know women aren't just hangers on</u>
<u n="230" who="S0528">no</u>
<u n="231" who="S0486" trans="overlap">they're people in their own right and to be treated like that it's it's going back Victorian times</u>
<u n="232" who="S0528" trans="overlap">it is it is</u>
<u n="233" who="S0486" trans="overlap">erm and it's erm although I'm not terrifically women's lib I'm I believe in equality and that's not treating people equally at all</u>
<u n="234" who="S0528">at at times in my last employment with the building society er I had a rather problematical manager to deal with</u>
<u n="235" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0528">and his secretary started to follow his same attitude and she was quite rude to me one day</u>
<u n="237" who="S0486" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and I went to both him and the girl and I said I don't mind whether you call me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="240" who="S0528" trans="overlap">I don <trunc>m</trunc> you choose I said but I do expect you to respect my age and my experience in the way you speak to me</u>
<u n="241" who="S0486">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and I said and I don't mind whether I work for a lady manager</u>
<u n="243" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0528">or a male manager</u>
<u n="245" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0528">I'm quite happy</u>
<u n="247" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0528" trans="overlap">as long as they know what they are doing</u>
<u n="249" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0528" trans="overlap">as long as they know the job</u>
<u n="251" who="S0486">yes exactly exactly</u>
<u n="252" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and I've always felt that way and there is</u>
<u n="253" who="S0486" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="254" who="S0528">to that degree equality is most important that women should have the opportunity</u>
<u n="255" who="S0486">yeah yes <trunc>i</trunc>it is very important</u>
<u n="256" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I mean the erm use of the word lady is erm is great and I was brought up to use it because it was erm a term of respect</u>
<u n="258" who="S0528">yes</u>
<u n="259" who="S0486">but these days I mean you think if you go to the doctor you call you say well I'd like to see a male doctor you never say I would like to see a female doctor you say I'd like to see a lady doctor</u>
<u n="260" who="S0528" trans="overlap">doctor</u>
<u n="261" who="S0486">that should go it should be male or female</u>
<u n="262" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0486" trans="overlap">to be equal to the male</u>
<u n="264" who="S0528">yes</u>
<u n="265" who="S0486">erm because it's a stigma really erm the use of the word lady erm or woman a woman doctor my mother always tell me to use the <trunc>wor</trunc> if you say oh that woman over there has got a bright red jacket on my mother would say to me it's very rude to use the word woman you've always got to say lady</u>
<u n="266" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0486" trans="overlap">well that's not that's not so anymore and it can't be so in <trunc>th</trunc> in these days of equality</u>
<u n="268" who="S0528">no no</u>
<u n="269" who="S0486">because you'd say that man over there nobody would say well that's rude you can say gentleman</u>
<u n="270" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0486">that man over there but <trunc>i</trunc>it's very strange erm and these things are being erm are being weeded out over the years aren't they?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0528">yeah I I've got involved <trunc>wi</trunc>with a number of other activities as well and and one was working in the hospice movement</u>
<u n="273" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="274" who="S0528">and I've worked in the hospice movement for more than sixteen years now</u>
<u n="275" who="S0486" trans="overlap">really? yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0528">and I had to change as I used to be a minibus driver and then the NHS got rid of most of the minibuses</u>
<u n="277" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="278" who="S0528">and I had to either withdraw from the hospice or find something else to do</u>
<u n="279" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="280" who="S0528">and I I chose to go to college at the age of sixty-six I think</u>
<u n="281" who="S0486">did you?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0528">and I do er Swedish body massage</u>
<u n="283" who="S0486">oh really? oh right my goodness</u>
<u n="284" who="S0528" trans="overlap">erm that is the most extremely rewarding thing I have ever done with in particular terminally ill patients</u>
<u n="285" who="S0486">really? yeah yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and I think it's it's not so much the massage but it's the warmth of somebody's touch</u>
<u n="287" who="S0486">yes exactly</u>
<u n="288" who="S0528">but initially it was a little bit of a problem because I'm sure the hospice felt that oh we shouldn't have a man</u>
<u n="289" who="S0486">yeah er</u>
<u n="290" who="S0528" trans="overlap">handling these ladies</u>
<u n="291" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0528" trans="overlap">but in the end it went complete reversal and the ladies</u>
<u n="293" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="294" who="S0528" trans="overlap">would ask for me</u>
<u n="295" who="S0486">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0528">and it was a matter of building trust</u>
<u n="297" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0528">and take someone into a therapy room</u>
<u n="299" who="S0486" trans="overlap">what a wonderful thing to do</u>
<u n="300" who="S0528">it it is it is</u>
<u n="301" who="S0486" trans="overlap">what a <trunc>wo</trunc> you still do it do you?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0528" trans="overlap">I still do it but because we've moved into a different area</u>
<u n="303" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0528">erm it's still in its infancy</u>
<u n="305" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="306" who="S0528" trans="overlap">with the health and wellbeing centre in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right gosh oh right</u>
<u n="308" who="S0528" trans="overlap">so I I'm due to be there this afternoon</u>
<u n="309" who="S0486">oh are you? gosh</u>
<u n="310" who="S0528" trans="overlap">and er</u>
<u n="311" who="S0486" trans="overlap">you are you do get around don't you? that's wonderful</u>
<u n="312" who="S0528" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there may or may not be people who would like to try</u>
<u n="313" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no no exactly</u>
<u n="314" who="S0528" trans="overlap">they can have simple things</u>
<u n="315" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0528">in fact the club could even do it if they have a thing with ladies here</u>
<u n="317" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0528">they could have hand massage <unclear>for nothing</unclear></u>
<u n="319" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes exactly that would be lovely</u>
<u n="320" who="S0528" trans="overlap">or to hands or feet or</u>
<u n="321" who="S0486" trans="overlap">well that's a wonderful idea now you see I wonder how many of those people out there know that about you and I know in fifteen minutes today</u>
<u n="322" who="S0528">most of the men wouldn't know er</u>
<u n="323" who="S0486" trans="overlap">they wouldn't</u>
<u n="324" who="S0528">because you have to obey erm all the er the rules about er privacy</u>
<u n="325" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0528" trans="overlap">you don't</u>
<u n="327" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0528" trans="overlap">talk about people</u>
<u n="329" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="330" who="S0528" trans="overlap">I would talk about an individual but</u>
<u n="331" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0528" trans="overlap">no names or</u>
<u n="333" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no of course not</u>
<u n="334" who="S0528" trans="overlap">where or when</u>
<u n="335" who="S0486">no of course not</u>
<u n="336" who="S0528">erm and it would only be a hint of</u>
<u n="337" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0528" trans="overlap">the sort of things</u>
<u n="339" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0528">that people have to face</u>
<u n="341" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0528" trans="overlap"><unclear>with</unclear></u>
<u n="343" who="S0486">I mean so many</u>
<u n="344" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0486">you're you're right thing about not being touched so many people are <trunc>s</trunc> maybe live on their own or go into a hospice they they they're they're coming to the end of their life and you know they've got no one no one ever touches them</u>
<u n="346" who="S0528">that's right</u>
<u n="347" who="S0486">they've gone <trunc>c</trunc> they've got completely no human contact</u>
<u n="348" who="S0528" trans="overlap">no and I felt that was important in the hospice environment because so often it's perhaps elderly ladies</u>
<u n="349" who="S0486">mm mm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0528" trans="overlap">who have been living on their own as a widow for perhaps twenty</u>
<u n="351" who="S0486" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0528">thirty years</u>
<u n="353" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0528">and no one has touched them</u>
<u n="355" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="356" who="S0528">but in that safe environment</u>
<u n="357" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0528">in a ward</u>
<u n="359" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0528" trans="overlap">in the room er surrounded by nursing staff and other staff</u>
<u n="361" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0528">I I have found it extremely rewarding the reactions</u>
<u n="363" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="364" who="S0528">it's just quite amazing</u>
<u n="365" who="S0486">yes I'm sure</u>
<u n="366" who="S0528">er</u>
<u n="367" who="S0486">yeah the other thing too which I mean it's it's very different but it's the same sort of thing people who take their friendly dogs into places</u>
<u n="368" who="S0528">oh yes</u>
<u n="369" who="S0486">and they're allowed to stroke them</u>
<u n="370" who="S0528">that's right</u>
<u n="371" who="S0486">and the touching of that is so beneficial</u>
<u n="372" who="S0528" trans="overlap"><trunc>def</trunc> it's such a highlight that is</u>
<u n="373" who="S0486">it is yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0486">and I mean there's something about a dog that always <trunc>wa</trunc> you know wants you to smile you want to smile don't you? there's something about a dog or a pet</u>
<u n="376" who="S0528">and they have got a level of understanding that far outreaches</u>
<u n="377" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="378" who="S0528" trans="overlap">what we have they know</u>
<u n="379" who="S0486" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="380" who="S0528" trans="overlap">what's going on</u>
<u n="381" who="S0486">yeah they do</u>
<u n="382" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yeah they do</u>
<u n="383" who="S0486" trans="overlap">they're amazing and and they're being used so much now to diagnose different cancers aren't they?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0528">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0486">and all sorts of diseases and it's</u>
<u n="386" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0486" trans="overlap">not just cancers it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0528" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0486">erm diabetes no erm er er er a helping dog now can be a diabetic dog who can erm a diabetic erm diagnosing dog should I say</u>
<u n="390" who="S0528">yes</u>
<u n="391" who="S0486" trans="overlap">who can notice the acetone on the breath or the smell of the person that they're looking at</u>
<u n="392" who="S0528">yeah their senses are just</u>
<u n="393" who="S0486">the senses are</u>
<u n="394" who="S0528" trans="overlap">incredible</u>
<u n="395" who="S0486" trans="overlap">incredible aren't they?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0528" trans="overlap">they really are</u>
<u n="397" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0528" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="399" who="S0486">now what have we done? we've done seventeen minutes are you happy with that?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0528">yes</u>
<u n="401" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="402" who="S0528">that's fine</u>
<u n="403" who="S0486">okay so seventeen thirty-nine</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
